<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 16:48:36 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert in Cultural Heritage (Cat. II, 30w/d)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-cultural-heritage-cat-ii-30w-d</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 16:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-cultural-heritage-cat-ii-30w-d</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Provide a sound analysis of the needs, constraints and potential of the tourism sector in Jerusalem as well as recommendations on relevance and feasibility of possible and specific interventions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in Cultural Heritage (Cat. II, 30w/d)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of a Bachelor degree in Archaeology, History, Anthropology, Arab studies or equivalent;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in developing GAP analyses;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to support consultative sector discussion, interviewing and facilitation of policy review;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in conducting historic and cultural heritage research and data collection;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent facilitation, computer, communication and coordination skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;minimum of 6 years’ experience in the cultural heritage sector;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Palestine is required;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Palestinian tourism sector is an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English, with excellent writing skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Arabic is required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert in Business and Tourism (Cat. II, 30 w/d)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-business-and-tourism-cat-ii-30-w-d</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 16:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-business-and-tourism-cat-ii-30-w-d</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Provide a sound analysis of the needs, constraints and potential of the tourism sector in Jerusalem as well as recommendations on relevance and feasibility of possible and specific interventions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in Business and Tourism (Cat. II, 30 w/d)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of a Bachelor degree in Economics, Business, Tourism or equivalent;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in developing GAP analyses and benchmarking studies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to lead feasibility and diagnostic analyses;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in conducting economic research and data collection;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent facilitation, computer, communication and coordination skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 6 years’ experience in the tourism sector;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in tourism sector development in developing countries and or in the Mediterranean countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Palestine and knowledge of the Palestinian tourism sector are assets;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English, with excellent writing skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Arabic is an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Economic or Private Sector Development Programmes (TL)
</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-economic-or-private-sector-development-programmes-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-economic-or-private-sector-development-programmes-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Provide a sound analysis of the needs, constraints and potential of the tourism sector in Jerusalem as well as recommendations on relevance and feasibility of possible and specific interventions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Senior Expert in Economic or Private Sector Development Programmes (TL) *&lt;/em&gt;(Cat. I, 45w/d)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s Degree in Economics or Business Development or equivalent degree;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team leading experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in developing economic indicators and leading private sector analyses;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in leading economic research and data collection;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in developing cultural tourism strategy with its implementation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent facilitation, computer, communication and coordination skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 10 years’ experience in Economic or Private Sector Development Programmes and experience in tourism/business/economic development in comparable/relevant contexts;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English with excellent writing skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Fisheries Trade Specialist (Cat. I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-fisheries-trade-specialist-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 12:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-fisheries-trade-specialist-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the Mid-Term Evaluation of the SmartFish Programme is to provide the IOC, relevant external services of the EU, as well as the other organisations of the IRCC – COMESA, EAC, IGAD as well as SADC – and the wider public with necessary information on the performance of the project and to formulate Programme Estimate no. 3 (PE3) in the context of the programming exercise of the 11th EDF RIP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Fisheries Trade Specialist (Cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree related to trade development and management;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of value chain performances analysis for value addition in the fishery sector would be appreciated;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;12 years professional experience related to the improvement of trade flows of fisheries or food products and investment promotion;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience in the context of the Economic Partnership Agreements between the EU and third countries and a good knowledge of the applicable rules and principles guiding the trade of fisheries and food products would be relevant;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An experience in the fisheries and/or aquaculture private sector would be appreciated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_soria-garcia@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Fisheries Economist and Team Leader (Cat. I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-fisheries-economist-and-team-leader-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 12:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-fisheries-economist-and-team-leader-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the Mid-Term Evaluation of the SmartFish Programme is to provide the IOC, relevant external services of the EU, as well as the other organisations of the IRCC – COMESA, EAC, IGAD as well as SADC – and the wider public with necessary information on the performance of the project and to formulate Programme Estimate no. 3 (PE3) in the context of the programming exercise of the 11th EDF RIP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Fisheries Economist and Team Leader (Cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A university degree related to fisheries, rural development or natural resources management, including a specialisation in economics;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of the financial and economic analysis of development projects would be appreciated;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 15 years’ working experience in the field of fisheries development and management;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous and recent experience in fisheries project formulation and evaluation in developing countries in Africa is required;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience as a project manager in the fisheries sector, as well as a good knowledge of the EDF procedures;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of the Eastern and Southern Africa and Indian Ocean region is expected and possibly an expertise related to other major donor initiatives in the region;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent English and French.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team of 4 Category II Experts in Migration, Construction, Design, Supply Contracts/Tender Dossiers (PRAG)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-of-4-category-ii-experts-in-migration-construction-design-supply-contracts-tender-dossiers-prag</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 11:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-of-4-category-ii-experts-in-migration-construction-design-supply-contracts-tender-dossiers-prag</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this project is to strengthen the infrastructural capacity of the Directorate General of Migration Management in order to effectively implement the EU-Turkey Readmission Agreement and to advance the implementation of the Visa Liberalisation Roadmap by preparation of tender documents for the supply of furniture of 7 new removal centres which will be constructed from the National funds in Ankara, Ağrı, Çanakkale, Kocaeli, Konya, Malatya and Tekirdağ and for the refurbishment and maintenance of 13 removal centres in Adana, Antalya, Aydın, Bursa, Çanakkale, Edirne, Gaziantep, İstanbul, İzmir, Kırıkkale, Kırklareli, Tekirdağ and Van which will be taken over from TNP (Turkish National Police). The provinces provided above are indicative and the Beneficiary will provide final locations before the start of the assignment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project location&lt;/strong&gt;: Ankara, Turkey and 13 removal centres (Adana, Antalya, Aydın, Bursa, Çanakkale, Edirne, Gaziantep, İstanbul, İzmir, Kırıkkale, Kırklareli, Tekirdağ, and Van)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A team of 4 Category II Experts in Migration, Construction, Design, Supply Contracts/Tender Dossiers (PRAG)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each proposed expert should meet following requirements:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master’s degree in engineering or architecture or social sciences. In the absence of required degree, the experts will have an equivalent professional experience of minimum 11 years in the relevant fields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good command of both written and spoken English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of experience in the relevant fields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PhD in relevant fields is considered to be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The proposed experts shall cover the following specific experiences as a team:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 years of experience in construction or design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 years of experience in the field of migration. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in refurbishment and/or renovation design of at least 2 superstructure (Buildings) projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in preparation of technical specifications and market research for supply contract in line with the PRAG.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least one project concerning the preparation of works tender dossier using FIDIC. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least one project for the preparation of Terms of Reference for the supervision of works according to PRAG.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in preparation of cost estimation for works.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in preparation of feasibility studies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience on EU standards on removal centres will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the design or refurbishment or maintenance and/or planning of buildings related to migration such as reception centres, women shelters, dormitories, rest homes etc. will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience as a migration advisor/expert in the preparation of investment projects regarding illegal migration will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in operation of removal centres will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jefe de Equipo – Categoría II </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/jefe-de-equipo-categoria-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2015 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/jefe-de-equipo-categoria-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Apoyar al Gobierno de Guatemala para proponer resoluciones a los obstáculos legales y las deficiencias administrativas existentes, orientado al desarrollo de una eficiente y efectiva evaluación, control y seguimiento de los instrumentos ambientales, generando un efecto positivo para la inversión pública, social y privada del país, con impacto de manera específica en el desarrollo rural.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Project location: Ciudad de Guatemala y sedes de las oficinas del MARN (a confirmar)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jefe de Equipo – Categoría II (50  días de trabajo)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formación universitaria en ciencias ambientales, derecho ambiental, administración, ingeniería y similares;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excelente dominio del español y buen dominio del inglés;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Postgrado en las ciencias señalados o afines será una ventaja;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Amplia experiencia en organización corporativa/pública, eficiencia administrativa, implementación y re-estructura institucional, de preferencia en América Latina;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia en coordinación sectorial e inter sectorial en análisis, estudios y consultorías en organización corporativa, análisis del desempeño y otros similares en el ámbito público de Guatemala o Latinoamérica;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia en análisis y evaluación de normativas ambientales (incluyendo cambio climático), para su reforma e implementación institucional;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conocimiento del sistema público de preferencia en Guatemala o Centroamérica;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capacidad para trabajar en entornos complejos;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Se valorará positivamente el conocimiento de las normativas ambientales para las licencias ambientales vigentes en el ámbito internacional.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert on Legal and Intellectual Property Rights (IPR) (Category II</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-legal-and-intellectual-property-rights-ipr-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-legal-and-intellectual-property-rights-ipr-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project is to contribute to the integration of the beneficiary Country with the ERA in the field of R&amp;amp;I, through increasing its overall success rate in the Horizon 2020 Programme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 3 – Expert on Legal and Intellectual Property Rights (IPR) (Category II, 26 w/d)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master’s degree in Law or equivalent general professional experience of 5 years (besides the minimum general experience);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years’ experience with the EU framework programmes such as FP7, FP6 and/or Horizon 2020 Programme;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least 3 projects in consultancy services related to Legal and IPR in EU FP7 and/or Horizon 2020;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in written and spoken English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert on Financial Issues (Category II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-financial-issues</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 10:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-financial-issues</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project is to contribute to the integration of the beneficiary Country with the ERA in the field of R&amp;amp;I, through increasing its overall success rate in the Horizon 2020 Programme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2 – Expert on Financial Issues (Category II, 52 w/d)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master’s degree in economics or equivalent general professional experience of 5 years (besides the minimum general experience);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years’ experience with the EU framework programmes such as FP7, FP6 and/or Horizon 2020 Programme;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least 3 projects in financial management in EU FP7 and/or Horizon 2020;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least 3 projects conducting trainings in financial consultancy in the field of SMEs related to H2020 – EU R&amp;amp;I programmes shall be considered an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in written and spoken English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader – Expert in EU Framework Programmes and Capacity Building and Training (Category II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-expert-in-eu-framework-programmes-and-capacity-building-and-training-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 10:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-expert-in-eu-framework-programmes-and-capacity-building-and-training-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project is to contribute to the integration of the beneficiary Country with the ERA in the field of R&amp;amp;I, through increasing its overall success rate in the Horizon 2020 Programme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader – Expert in EU Framework Programmes and Capacity Building and Training (Category II, 74w/d)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master’s degree in social/technical/natural sciences or equivalent general professional experience of 5 years (besides the minimum general experience);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years’ experience with the EU framework programmes such as FP7, FP6 and/or Horizon 2020 Programme;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least 2 projects for preparation or management of EU FP7 and/or H2020 programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least 3 projects for capacity building and/or conducting training in the field of EU FP7 programme and/or Horizon 2020 – EU Research and Innovation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience as a Team Leader on EU Funded project shall be considered an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in written and spoken English &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deux Experts en gestion de programme de la coopération de l’Union européenne</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-gestion-de-programme-de-la-cooperation-de-lunion-europeenne</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 08:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-gestion-de-programme-de-la-cooperation-de-lunion-europeenne</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Améliorer les perspectives d’impact, de durabilité et de synergie des interventions mises en œuvre par les organisations de la société civile et les communes camerounaises bénéficiaires de contrats de subventions octroyés par la Délégation de l’UE au Cameroun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experts en gestion de programme de la coopération de l’Union européenne (Cat.III)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire de niveau Master ou expérience professionnelle équivalente;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonne maitrise du française ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience d’au moins 3 années en gestion de programme de la coopération de l’Union européenne et/ou gestion de projet UE au sein d’une Communie et/ou d’OSC (expérience en gestion et suivi de contrats de subvention serait un plus) ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience et capacité avérée en élaboration, mise en œuvre et évaluation de modules et ateliers de formation et en accompagnement/conseil dans les domaines de la gestion opérationnelle et financière de projet ainsi que dans l’organisation de processus consultatifs ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance du contexte camerounais, notamment des problématiques liées a la gouvernance locale, des organisations de la société civile et du processus de décentralisation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonne maitrise de l’anglais&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans l’élaboration et la mise en œuvre de stratégie et d’outils de communication (y compris en relation presse et utilisation des réseaux sociaux) ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en gestion financière et comptable de projet (une expérience de gestion financière d’un projet finance par l’UE, y compris en audit de projet, serait un atout)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef d’équipe </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-dequipe</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 08:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-dequipe</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Améliorer les perspectives d’impact, de durabilité et de synergie des interventions mises en œuvre par les organisations de la société civile et les communes camerounaises bénéficiaires de contrats de subventions octroyés par la Délégation de l’UE au Cameroun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chef d’équipe (Categorie III, 125h/j)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire de niveau Master ou expérience professionnelle équivalente;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonne maitrise du française ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience d’au moins 3 années en gestion de programme de la coopération de l’Union européenne et/ou gestion de projet UE au sein d’une Communie et/ou d’OSC (expérience en gestion et suivi de contrats de subvention serait un plus) ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience et capacité avérée en élaboration, mise en œuvre et évaluation de modules et ateliers de formation et en accompagnement/conseil dans les domaines de la gestion opérationnelle et financière de projet ainsi que dans l’organisation de processus consultatifs ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience avérée en gestion d’une équipe d’au moins 3 personées et expérience dans la mise en œuvre de missionnes similaires ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Forte capacité analytique ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance du contexte camerounais, notamment des problématiques liées a la gouvernance locale, des organisations de la société civile et du processus de décentralisation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spécialiste en Renforcement des Capacités Institutionnelles et Mécanismes d’aide Publique au Développement</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/specialiste-en-renforcement-des-capacites-institutionnelles-et-mecanismes-daide-publique-au-developpement</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2015 19:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/specialiste-en-renforcement-des-capacites-institutionnelles-et-mecanismes-daide-publique-au-developpement</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;L’objectif général&lt;/strong&gt; de cette mission est contribuer à la réduction de la pauvreté à Djibouti en mettant l’accent sur la croissance économique des régions de l’intérieur, la participation de la société civile au développement local et l&amp;#39;amélioration de la condition des femmes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;L’objectif particulier&lt;/strong&gt; est élaborer un document d&amp;#39;action pour un projet de développement régional axé sur le renforcement des capacités des autorités locales, la participation de la société civile et l&amp;#39;amélioration de la condition de la femme djiboutienne.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spécialiste en Renforcement des Capacités Institutionnelles et Mécanismes d’aide Publique au Développement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire supérieur approprié. Une maîtrise en sociologie rurale, économie, géographie ou sciences sociales/ou de l’environnement ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience générale d&amp;#39;au moins 15 ans dans les domaines liés à la mission, dont 10 ans minimum dans le secteur de la décentralisation, le développement local, la gouvernance locale et l&amp;#39;administration publique dans des pays en développement ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 10 ans en assistance technique en renforcement des capacités institutionnelles ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 10 ans d&amp;#39;expérience internationale (pour les Pays moins avancés, de petite taille et à économie vulnérable) en mécanismes d&amp;#39;Aide publique au développement et en Investissement direct étranger;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en montage et gestion des fonds d&amp;#39;appui aux collectivités territoriales ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne connaissance en aménagement territorial;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compétences en préparation de documents de fiches d&amp;#39;identification, d&amp;#39;opérationnalisation de projets et d&amp;#39;appel d&amp;#39;Offres;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance des procédures du FED;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne capacité d&amp;#39;organisation et de travail en équipe pluridisciplinaire et être apte à gérer une équipe;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Savoir parfaitement communiquer, tant à l&amp;#39;oral qu&amp;#39;à l&amp;#39;écrit, tant avec des techniciens qu&amp;#39;avec des non-techniciens, avec des agents de base comme avec de hauts dirigeants;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Excellentes capacités à assurer des médiations et du transfert de compétences avec les cadres nationaux impliqués dans ce projet;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonne pratique de Windows, Word. Excel et logiciels spécifiques ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Une parfaite maîtrise de la langue française (lu, écrit, parlé) est requise;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Connaissance du pays et des langues locales un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert with Good Knowledge of Argentinian and EU Energy Sector </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-with-good-knowledge-of-argentinian-and-eu-energy-sector</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2015 08:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-with-good-knowledge-of-argentinian-and-eu-energy-sector</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The objective is to provide appropriate technical assistance and logistic support for improving the energy efficiency in Argentina.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert with Good Knowledge of Argentinian and EU Energy Sector&lt;/strong&gt; (30w/d, Category I):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in a discipline relevant to the scope of the assignment or equivalent professional experience (5 years in addition to the general professional experience);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to liaise successfully with relevant stakeholders, both public and private;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent level of Spanish and English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of the Argentine context and the EU context;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 10 years of general professional experience in the relevant areas for the assignment;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound knowledge and understanding of the EU regulatory framework on energy and relevant EU policies, including their external dimension;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years’ experience in activities and/or projects that involved direct exposure to EU energy efficiency policies and regulations and their implementation in at least one EU Member State.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert - Knowledge of Argentinian Energy Sector and EU Policies (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-knowledge-of-argentinian-energy-sector-and-eu-policies-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2015 08:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-knowledge-of-argentinian-energy-sector-and-eu-policies-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The objective is to provide appropriate technical assistance and logistic support for improving the energy efficiency in Argentina.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert - Knowledge of Argentinian Energy Sector and EU Policies (TL)&lt;/strong&gt; (40 w/d, Category I):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in a discipline relevant to the scope of the assignment or equivalent professional experience (5 years in addition to the general professional experience);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong diplomatic skills to deal with politically sensitive issues;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of EU policies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent knowledge of the Argentinean energy sector;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent level of Spanish and English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 10 years of general professional experience in the relevant areas;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and understanding of the Argentine national regulatory framework on energy;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conversant with the needs and demands of business operating in Argentina in terms of energy efficiency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years’ experience in activities directly related to Argentine energy policies and regulations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Protected Areas Management/Conservation Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-protected-areas-management-conservation-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2015 21:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-protected-areas-management-conservation-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Global objective of the present assignment is to contribute to collection, generation and display of information on Protected Areas in order to support decision-making and strategic planning on biodiversity conservation at different levels (local, national, regional, ecosystems, KLC).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Specific objective is to contribute to the establishment of an operational Regional Reference Information System (RRIS) for the BIOPAMA Observatory for Central and Western Africa and to the good functioning of the Observatory of Protected Areas of Central and Western Africa, through the finalization of the Governance module of the BIOPAMA tool and through the conception/development of ad hoc Decision Support Systems (DSSs). The latter shall rely on the information generated at PA level through the BIOPAMA tool itself and through information available from the key data providers and shall provide concrete answers to the key conservation queries of the stakeholders at the different levels of intervention (main focus on the local and the national levels). This work entails ad hoc reflection and formulation of different options on possible scaling-up modalities for the information available at PA level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Protected Areas Management/Conservation Specialist&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of thematic experience, and at least 6 years of field experience in Central and/or Western Africa;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master Degree or equivalent in Ecology, Geography, Biology or equivalent University careers;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of PA management challenges, extensive experience of the conservation sector and stakeholders in Central Africa, recognized expertise in institutional governance and organizational reform, skills in public relations and networking;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent French and English (speaking, reading and writing).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experts in Construction, Refurbishment, PRAG and Migration (Removal Centres)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-in-construction-refurbishment-prag-and-migration-removal-centres</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2015 21:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-in-construction-refurbishment-prag-and-migration-removal-centres</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this project is to strengthen the infrastructural capacity of the Directorate General of Migration Management in order to effectively implement the EU-Turkey Readmission Agreement and to advance the implementation of the Visa Liberalisation Roadmap by preparation of tender documents for the supply of furniture of 7 new removal centres which will be constructed from the National funds in Ankara, Ağrı, Çanakkale, Kocaeli, Konya, Malatya and Tekirdağ and for the refurbishment and maintenance of 13 removal centres in Adana, Antalya, Aydın, Bursa, Çanakkale, Edirne, Gaziantep, İstanbul, İzmir, Kırıkkale, Kırklareli, Tekirdağ and Van which will be taken over from TNP (Turkish National Police). The provinces provided above are indicative and the Beneficiary will provide final locations before the start of the assignment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experts in Construction, Refurbishment, PRAG and Migration (Removal Centres) - A team of 4 Category II Experts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each proposed expert should meet following requirements:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master’s degree in engineering or architecture or social sciences. In the absence of required degree, the experts will have an equivalent professional experience of minimum 11 years in the relevant fields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good command of both written and spoken English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of experience in the relevant fields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PhD in relevant fields is considered to be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The proposed experts shall cover the following specific experiences as a team:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 years of experience in construction or design.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 years of experience in the field of migration. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in refurbishment and/or renovation design of at least 2 superstructure (Buildings) projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in preparation of technical specifications and market research for supply contract in line with the PRAG.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least one project concerning the preparation of works tender dossier using FIDIC. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least one project for the preparation of Terms of Reference for the supervision of works according to PRAG.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in preparation of cost estimation for works.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in preparation of feasibility studies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience on EU standards on removal centres will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the design or refurbishment or maintenance and/or planning of buildings related to migration such as reception centres, women shelters, dormitories, rest homes etc. will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience as a migration advisor/expert in the preparation of investment projects regarding illegal migration will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in operation of removal centres will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 3 – Local Coordinator with Indian Water Management Experience</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-3-local-coordinator-with-indian-water-management-experience</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2015 21:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-3-local-coordinator-with-indian-water-management-experience</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to facilitate a coherent involvement of the EU and its Member States, jointly with the Indian authorities, in the Clean Ganga initiative of the Government of India.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 3 – Local Coordinator with Indian Water Management Experience (Category II, 145 w/d)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master Degree or equivalent in a field relevant to the project (such as water, engineering, law, economics) or, in its absence, higher education degree and equivalent professional experience of 3 years in addition to the general experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Worked on at least one project as a project manager;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Worked in at least 1 project with public sector, academia, and private sector stakeholders;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years’ experience in the area of environment, sustainable development or closely related field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years in the Indian water management sector as a technical expert;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Indian context, in particular the water sector and related administration will be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent English and Hindi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 2 –Expert in European Water Policy and Legislation</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-expert-in-european-water-policy-and-legislation</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2015 21:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-expert-in-european-water-policy-and-legislation</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to facilitate a coherent involvement of the EU and its Member States, jointly with the Indian authorities, in the Clean Ganga initiative of the Government of India.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2 –Expert in European Water Policy and Legislation (Category I, 95 w/d)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in Environment, Water, Biology or related field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years as an expert in the field of European water policy and legislation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 projects as an expert providing guidance and technical assistance to counterparts, defining work plans and following up on their execution;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 1 project as an expert with non-EU countries’ water authorities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 4 years of experience as an expert of river basin management and WFD implementation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience on a project related to India regarding water sector and administration will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Water Management Expert with European Policy/Legislation Experience (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-water-management-expert-with-european-policy-legislation-experience-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2015 17:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-water-management-expert-with-european-policy-legislation-experience-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to facilitate a coherent involvement of the EU and its Member States, jointly with the Indian authorities, in the Clean Ganga initiative of the Government of India.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Water Management Expert with European Policy/Legislation Experience (TL) (Category I, 40 w/d)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s Degree or equivalent in a field relevant to this project (such as engineering natural sciences, economics) or, in its absence, bachelor degree and equivalent professional experience of at least 3 years of the general experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years as a water management expert in projects related to European Water policy and legislation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Worked in at least 3 projects as a team providing guidance to experts and counterparts, defining work plans and following up on them;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Worked in at least one project with the public sector, academia and private stakeholders;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years as a technical expert in Basin Management planning, and implementation of the Water Framework Directive;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one project related to water management as a facilitator for working groups, expert’s seminars and multi-disciplinary teams;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Indian context, in particular the water sector and related administrations will be a strong asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
