<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 20:35:18 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert in Customs policy/Business Advisor - Category III</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-customs-policy-business-advisor-category-iii</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-customs-policy-business-advisor-category-iii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to improve the quality of the services of the SCA and to support modernisation and improvement of the functioning of SCA through strengthening its administrative and operational capacity. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective of this assignment is to provide technical assistance to the Department for Contracting and Financing of EU Funded projects (CFCU - Central Finance and Contracting Unit) and the beneficiary (Customs Administration of the Republic of Serbia - SCA) by developing the Terms of Reference for the implementation of service contract „Technical Assistance for Establishing the Institutional Framework for the Implementation of AIS/AES” to be financed under IPA 2013.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in Customs policy/Business advisor - Category III&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills :&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;University degree in a relevant discipline (e.g. Law, Economics, Public administration, Business Administration or other areas relevant to the project).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellent knowledge of English &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Computer literacy &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Required: Minimum three (3) years of professional experience in IT systems implementation for a Customs Administration in a EU member State (only counting experience after accession of a country to the EU) or related European Commission Services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in at least one project in development of IT systems in the field of the AIS and AES in EU Member States (only counting experience after accession of a country to the EU), European Commission Services or candidate countries(only counting experience after a country received candidate status); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Customs business processes and complex system integration in at least one project of such type; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of providing Technical Assistance in IPA countries covered by article 19 of IPA regulation in at least one project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customs IT Systems Expert - Category II</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/customs-it-systems-expert-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 20:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/customs-it-systems-expert-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to improve the quality of the services of the SCA and to support modernisation and improvement of the functioning of SCA through strengthening its administrative and operational capacity. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective of this assignment is to provide technical assistance to the Department for Contracting and Financing of EU Funded projects (CFCU - Central Finance and Contracting Unit) and the beneficiary (Customs Administration of the Republic of Serbia - SCA) by developing the Terms of Reference for the implementation of service contract „Technical Assistance for Establishing the Institutional Framework for the Implementation of AIS/AES” to be financed under IPA 2013.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Customs IT Systems Expert - Category II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Qualifications and skills *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in a relevant discipline (e.g. electrical engineering, computing, mathematics, etc) 
OR &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post-secondary education attested by a diploma in information and communication technology, followed by at least 3 years’ professional experience in developing It system for public administration above the ones requested in general and specific professional experience. 
OR &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Secondary (general or technical) education attested by a diploma giving access to post-secondary education, followed by at least 6 years’ professional experience in developing IT system for public administration above the ones requested in general and specific professional experience. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellent knowledge of English &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum six (6) years of professional experience in the preparation and implementation of projects in field developing IT systems for the public administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum six (6) years of experience of working in a national customs organisation in IT development in an EU Member State (only counting experience after accession of a country to the EU) or the European Commission; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in EU regulations, acquis and priorities in the Customs sector in relation to IT development, preferably with the software development procedure and communication part of the AIS (ICS) and AES (ECS); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in IT strategic planning in international corporate and/or government sector in at least one such project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Legal Expert – experience in  Customs Administration/Capacity Building in EU Member State (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-customs-administration-capacity-building-in-eu-member-state-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 20:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-customs-administration-capacity-building-in-eu-member-state-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to improve the quality of the services of the SCA and to support modernisation and improvement of the functioning of SCA through strengthening its administrative and operational capacity. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective of this assignment is to provide technical assistance to the Department for Contracting and Financing of EU Funded projects (CFCU - Central Finance and Contracting Unit) and the beneficiary (Customs Administration of the Republic of Serbia - SCA) by developing the Terms of Reference for the implementation of service contract „Technical Assistance for Establishing the Institutional Framework for the Implementation of AIS/AES” to be financed under IPA 2013.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Customs Administration/Capacity Building in EU Member State (TL)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Project Leader will execute, coordinate and manage the activities. He/she will ensure the timely and effective implementation of the services and achievement of results, through the proposed tasks. S/he is responsible for liaison between the Ministry of Finance, SCA, the CFCU and the EUD, and must ensure that the experts inputs and the working days are distributed in the most efficient and effective manner. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;University degree in relevant discipline (e.g. Law, Economics, Public Administration, IT or other areas relevant to the project) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellent knowledge of English language &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Computer literacy &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Required: Minimum twelve (12) years of professional experience with Customs Administration in an EU member state (only counting experience after accession of a country to the EU). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Specific professional experience *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum six (6) years of experience in Capacity Building support to Customs Administration, aligning national legislation in the field of customs with the EU and/or design of implementation regulations (of which at least three (3) years are gained since 1st January 2007); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous relevant experience in providing technical assistance to Governments in countries covered by article 19 of IPA regulation in the area of customs administration would be an advantage; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in preparation of terms of reference for service contracts ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in leading teams in the public or private sector and/or donor funded projects in minimum one project of similar size, complexity and duration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Business Administration Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-business-administration-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 08:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-business-administration-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this assignment is to contribute to access for Basotho and productive sectors to safe, affordable, equitable, sustainable and reliable water and sanitation services. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this assignment is to facilitate formulation and development of the WASCO Strategic Plan for the period 2015 to 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Business Administration Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Senior expert with at least Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Business Administration or a related field; or in its absence an equivalent level acquired through professional experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least twelve (12) years of experience in the field of strategic planning, strategy formulation, corporate change and other relevant fields;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated cross-cultural sensitivity; interpersonal, communication and negotiation skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer  literacy,  excellent  report  writing  skills  and  ability  to  produce  quality documents;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possesses very good analytical skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A proven track record in the facilitation and the development of strategic plans in recent years;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in strategic planning notably for water and sanitation utility companies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possesses good training qualities for an optimal transfer of knowledge in workshops.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Experts in Migration with Research Experience</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-experts-in-migration-with-research-experience</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 07:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-experts-in-migration-with-research-experience</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Global Objective *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
The global aim of this project is to accelerate Turkey’s accession to the EU by supporting the country’s policy makers and practitioners in designing and implementing evidence based comprehensive and realistic policies regarding international migration in Turkey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Specific Objective(s) *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
The specific objective of this project is to propose a methodology and assessment tools for analyzing migratory trends and characteristics; migration governance framework, reviewing international cooperation initiatives and regional context as well as migration impacts which will serve as basis of annual migration reports to be published by the General Directorate of Migration Management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project location&lt;/strong&gt;: Ankara and field visits to three districts in the provinces out of Ankara.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Experts in Migration with Research Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maximum 3 Senior experts that cover the following requirements to successfully deal with the issues and to cover all the activities indicated in this Terms of Reference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Each proposed expert&lt;/strong&gt; should meet following requirements:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Masters’ degree on social sciences, law or related fields. In the absence of the required Masters degree, the expert will have an additional equivalent professional experience of minimum 17 years in the relevant fields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; At least 12 years of professional working experience in the sector(s) related to the lot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years’ experience in quantitative and qualitative research methodology &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least  3 years’ experience in international migration. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good command of written and spoken English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The proposed experts shall cover the following &lt;strong&gt;specific experiences as a team&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the preparation of a situation assessment and yearly reports.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in a project or research related to the labor policies and economics analyses.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in a project or research requiring techniques in data mining and/or handling collected data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in a project or research related to impact assessment methodologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in a project or research related to data collection and management on migration. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in a project or research utilizing SWOT analyses or equivalent management tool..&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The experts shall satisfy the criteria as a team but each expert shall at least cover one of the requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Rabies Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-rabies-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2014 13:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-rabies-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;G1obal objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;То improve protection of public and animal health and environment through strengthening of mechanisms for control and eradication of the animal diseases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;То conduct evaluation of the rabies eradication  programme (specifically implementation of national policies/strategies for eradication of rabies, and the programme of aerial ora1 vaccination of foxes against rabies) in Serbia and provide recommendations for its eventual continuation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Rabies Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;at least up to Masters’ degree academic level or equivalent professional experience of at least 15 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good command of English,  including report writing skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 10 years of post-graduate  professional experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ideally, at  least 5 years  of experience  in veterinary sector,  preferably in the national veterinary administration in an EU Member State or one of the countries covered bу IPA regulation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participation in implementation and/or surveillance/monitoring and/or evaluation of programmes of national or regional aerial campaign(s) of oral vaccination of foxes or other wild carnivores against rabies in an EU Member State or one of the countries covered bу IPА regulation will bе considered as an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience (at least 1 year, postgraduate) in working in EU or OIE reference laboratory for rabies or national reference laboratories for rabies in an EU Member State will bе considered as an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@htspe.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Evaluation  Expert (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-evaluation-expert-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2014 13:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-evaluation-expert-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;G1obal objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;То improve protection of public and animal health and environment through strengthening of mechanisms for control and eradication of the animal diseases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;То conduct evaluation of the rabies eradication  programme (specifically implementation of national policies/strategies for eradication of rabies, and the programme of aerial ora1 vaccination of foxes against rabies) in Serbia and provide recommendations for its eventual continuation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Evaluation  Expert (TL)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;:at least up to Masters’ degree academic level or equivalent professional experience of at least 15 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good command of English, including report writing skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 10 years of post-graduate professional experience. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participation (as an evaluation expert or equivalent) in evaluation of least 2 EU funded projects in current or former Candidate or Potential Candidate Countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in  leading expert teams on  at  least one,  preferably more, evaluations of  EU  funded projects;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in evaluation or monitoring of  projects  whose main objectives include  protection of animal health or other veterinary (or food safety) matters will bе considered as an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@htspe.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Public Finance Management</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-public-finance-management</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 08:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-public-finance-management</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Objective:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of this consultancy is to support the Government of Botswana / National Authorising Officer (NAO) and EU Delegation to Botswana and SADC in the identification and formulation of support actions in Public Sector Reform (PSR), including PSR coordination and Public Finance Management (PFM) to be financed under the 11th EDF (2016– 2020).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Objectives:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To identify options and formulate potential actions for PSR/PFM to be financed under the 11th EDF in alignment with the Government of Botswana needs and priorities, as outlined in the &amp;lsquo;Vision 2016&amp;rsquo;, the &amp;lsquo;National Development Plan 10&amp;rsquo;, the emerging Public Sector Reform Coordination Programme (PSRCP), the Public Finance Management Reform Programme (PFMRP), complementary to support provided by other development partners and building on lessons learned under the 10th EDF. The actions also have to be aligned with and feed into the evolving NDP 11.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To assist the EU Delegation to Botswana and SADC in the development of the corresponding documents for the approval of specific actions in PSR/PFM at the identification and formulation stage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To work in close collaboration with the ongoing technical assistance to the PSRCO and the Public Finance Management Reform Programme Coordination Unit (PFM RP CU) at the MFDP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To collaborate and align with the team of experts working in parallel on a similar assignment (identification and formulation) with regards to Human Resources Development with a view to ensure complementarity between the two program components.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Public Finance Management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Public Finance or equivalent. In the absence of this, the equivalent professional experience of at least eight (8) years is required in addition to the experience required below;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years&amp;#39; experience in the various disciplines of Public Finance Management, PFM reform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven professional experience in various strands of Public Finance Management reforms: planning, implementing and/or coordinating PFM reform programmes);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in the identification and formulation of projects/programs for donor institutions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in the development of Identification and Action Fiches and TAPs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience with EU procedures (in particular EDF procedures) and knowledge of EU aid modalities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in public sector strategic planning and budgeting;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in formulating of budget support programs and related indicators;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of different aid modalities and their strengths and weaknesses in different program contexts;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience from doing PFM work in middle income countries is an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working with a Ministry of Finance and/or Planning in Sub-Saharan Africa is an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Soft skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in organising stakeholder meetings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and facilitation skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent report writing skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assignment Duration:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;63 working days per expert, split into 3 missions: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;October 2014- Phase 1, 33 days (3 Home-Based, 30 Botswana)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;January/Febuary 2015- Phase 2, 25 days (Botswana)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;April 2015- Phase 3, 5 days (Home-Based)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Public Sector Reform (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-public-sector-reform-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 08:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-public-sector-reform-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Objective:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of this consultancy is to support the Government of Botswana / National Authorising Officer (NAO) and EU Delegation to Botswana and SADC in the identification and formulation of support actions in Public Sector Reform (PSR), including PSR coordination and Public Finance Management (PFM) to be financed under the 11th EDF (2016– 2020).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Objectives:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To identify options and formulate potential actions for PSR/PFM to be financed under the 11th EDF in alignment with the Government of Botswana needs and priorities, as outlined in the &amp;lsquo;Vision 2016&amp;rsquo;, the &amp;lsquo;National Development Plan 10&amp;rsquo;, the emerging Public Sector Reform Coordination Programme (PSRCP), the Public Finance Management Reform Programme (PFMRP), complementary to support provided by other development partners and building on lessons learned under the 10th EDF. The actions also have to be aligned with and feed into the evolving NDP 11.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To assist the EU Delegation to Botswana and SADC in the development of the corresponding documents for the approval of specific actions in PSR/PFM at the identification and formulation stage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To work in close collaboration with the ongoing technical assistance to the PSRCO and the Public Finance Management Reform Programme Coordination Unit (PFM RP CU) at the MFDP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To collaborate and align with the team of experts working in parallel on a similar assignment (identification and formulation) with regards to Human Resources Development with a view to ensure complementarity between the two program components.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Public Sector Reform (TL)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Public Administration or Political Science or another field relevant to the assignment. In the absence of this, the equivalent professional experience of at least eight (8) years is required in addition to the experience required below;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years&amp;#39; experience in the sector related to the Lot Governance and Home Affairs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven professional experience in various strands of Public Sector Reform: sector/ministry restructuring and modernization; and/or - management of parastatals; and/or - public administration reforms (decentralization, right-sizing etc).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven professional experience in public sector strategic planning and budgeting;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven professional experience in coordination of public sector reforms;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in the identification and formulation of projects/programs for donor institutions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in the development of Identification and Action Fiches and TAPs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience with EU procedures (in particular EDF procedures) and knowledge of EU aid modalities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in formulating of budget support programs and related indicators;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of different aid modalities (project and budget support) and their strengths and weaknesses in different program contexts;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience from doing PSR work in middle income countries is an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Soft skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in organising stakeholder meetings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and facilitation skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent report writing skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assignment Duration:&lt;/strong&gt;
63 working days per expert, split into 3 missions: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;October 2014 - Phase 1, 33 days (3 Home-Based, 30 Botswana)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;January/Febuary 2015 - Phase 2, 25 days (Botswana)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;April 2015 - Phase 3, 5 days (Home-Based)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in PSD/Finance/Trade with expertise in Adult Training and EU Policies</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-psd-finance-trade-with-expertise-in-adult-training-and-eu-policies-1</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2014 15:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-psd-finance-trade-with-expertise-in-adult-training-and-eu-policies-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The specific objective of the assignment is to assist DEVCO.C4 in the organisation, preparation and delivery of the training programme on Trade and Private Sector Development (TPSD) for EU staff, both at Headquarters and in Delegations in third countries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In particular, the expert will &lt;strong&gt;assist DEVCO.C4 with&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the design and delivery of the TPSD training, presenting different modules, to be agreed before each training session, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the maintenance and updating of training material, including e.g. the regular updating of the electronic training repository (containing the different presentations, technical notes, handouts and exercises), the creation of new training modules, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the logistical organisation of the training sessions in Delegations, including, among others, the preparation of course handouts (printed material, USB sticks), assisting trainees in the preparation of case studies to be presented during the training, the reservation of training rooms and equipment when abroad &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the course evaluation with a view to improving the overall quality training and &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the administrative management of hiring additional experts with specific expertise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in PSD/Finance/Trade with expertise in Adult Training and EU Policies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Expert will comply with the following requirements, as regards to education, skills and type of experience:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in a field related to one or more of the areas to be addressed during the training, or equivalent experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years&amp;#39; documented work experience in the identification, design and implementation of PSD, access to finance and Trade Related Assistance programmes in developing countries ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and presentation skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent facilitation skills, with a focus on hands-on practical training;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience in design and delivery of adult training; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in English, and a working knowledge of French and/or Spanish is a plus;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good reporting skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Well-informed about EU trade policy and EU external aid policies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conversant with the principles and methodologies of project cycle management and aid delivery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assignment location&lt;/strong&gt;: Training in Brussels and in regional location (Mozambique indicatively envisaged at this stage, TBC)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:francesca_giordano@dai.com&quot;&gt;Francesca_Giordano@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key Experts, External Results Oriented Monitoring (ROM)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-experts-</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 15:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-experts-</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Results Oriented Monitoring (ROM)&lt;/strong&gt; reviews aim to assist the European Commission’s (EC) services and EU Delegations (EUD) in monitoring of and reporting on EU financed development and cooperation projects and programmes (hereafter “projects”) in third countries through independent reviews of the progress of their implementation and the achievement of project results. Compared to the ROM reviews conducted over the past decade, ROM reviews will proceed on a number of reforms that aim to improve the quality and the focus in coverage of the ROM reviews and take into account the high level of devolution reached over the past decade for project preparation and monitoring tasks to EUDs at field level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This lot covers the EU funded national and regional projects and programmes whether single or multi-country and also Cross-Border-Cooperation (CBC) projects and programmes. These projects are implemented in the countries covered by the European Neighbourhood and Partnership Instrument (ENPI) and the European Neighbourhood Instrument (ENI)  in Algeria, Egypt, Israel, Jordan, Lebanon, Libya, Morocco, Syria, Tunisia and Palestine (Neighbourhood South); Armenia, Azerbaijan, Belarus, Georgia, Moldova and Ukraine (Neighbourhood East); Russia. If relevant, including partner countries other than ENI Southern Partner Countries (ENISPCs) :Bosnia and Herzegovina, Albania, Mauritania, Montenegro, Turkey, Bahrain, Comoros, Djibouti, Iraq, Kuwait, Oman, Qatar, Saudi Arabia, Somalia, Sudan, United Arab Emirates and Yemen, when associated to the activities foreseen in regional programmes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Team Leader will head a team of key experts, comprised of a Deputy Team Leader and four &lt;strong&gt;key experts&lt;/strong&gt; who will organise and supervise the implementation of the contract, carry out ROM reviews, be in charge of the internal QC and will draft the annual as well as the end of contract consolidated ROM analysis. They shall cover, as much as possible, the following areas of expertise: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employment and social protection&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Energy &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good Governance including: Democracy, rule of law, human rights; Public administration, including decentralisation; PFM and macroeconomics stability (related to Budget Support)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Natural resources, environment, climate change&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trade and Private sector development including: Regional integration; Business environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sustainable agriculture, food and nutrition security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transport&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development and security nexus, including drugs and migration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Civil society&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Statistics and performance measurement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Experts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for &lt;strong&gt;8 experts&lt;/strong&gt; (4 covering &lt;strong&gt;ACP&lt;/strong&gt; countries and 4 covering &lt;strong&gt;ENPI&lt;/strong&gt; countries). These positions are &lt;strong&gt;full time (220 man days/ year&lt;/strong&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These key experts implement the internal QC system preferably in their area of expertise and will be assigned ROM reviews/support missions according to their area of expertise, including: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PFM &amp;amp; Macroeconomics stability expertise,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Statistics and performance measurement expertise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They ensure timely delivery of ROM reports by ROM experts and QC checklists to EC services. They provide their inputs in their area of expertise in order to draft the annual as well as the end of contract consolidated ROM analysis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has a university master degree (or equivalent).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she must be fluent both in French and English.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They have a minimum of 12 years of experience in development cooperation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They have a minimum of 5 years of experience as project manager.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They have a minimum of 10 years of experience in one of the abovementioned areas of expertise. Experience in other of the above mentioned areas of expertise is an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They have a minimum of 5 years of experience in results based approaches, monitoring, and/or evaluation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They have a minimum of 3 years of experience on Neighbourhood countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They have preferably a good knowledge of EU and other donors implementing modalities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They have preferably experience in gender mainstreaming related to his/her area of expertise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in EC format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting (reference no. &lt;strong&gt;ROM/KE&lt;/strong&gt;) in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note that this is a long-term EU-funded project not a EC COM Lot 1 Framework project.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deputy Team Leader, External Results Oriented Monitoring (ROM)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/deputy-team-leader-external-results-oriented-monitoring-rom</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 15:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/deputy-team-leader-external-results-oriented-monitoring-rom</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Results Oriented Monitoring (ROM)&lt;/strong&gt; reviews aim to assist the European Commission’s (EC) services and EU Delegations (EUD) in monitoring of and reporting on EU financed development and cooperation projects and programmes (hereafter “projects”) in third countries through independent reviews of the progress of their implementation and the achievement of project results. Compared to the ROM reviews conducted over the past decade, ROM reviews will proceed on a number of reforms that aim to improve the quality and the focus in coverage of the ROM reviews and take into account the high level of devolution reached over the past decade for project preparation and monitoring tasks to EUDs at field level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This lot covers the EU funded national and regional projects and programmes whether single or multi-country and also Cross-Border-Cooperation (CBC) projects and programmes. These projects are implemented in the countries covered by the European Neighbourhood and Partnership Instrument (ENPI) and the European Neighbourhood Instrument (ENI)  in Algeria, Egypt, Israel, Jordan, Lebanon, Libya, Morocco, Syria, Tunisia and Palestine (Neighbourhood South); Armenia, Azerbaijan, Belarus, Georgia, Moldova and Ukraine (Neighbourhood East); Russia. If relevant, including partner countries other than ENI Southern Partner Countries (ENISPCs) :Bosnia and Herzegovina, Albania, Mauritania, Montenegro, Turkey, Bahrain, Comoros, Djibouti, Iraq, Kuwait, Oman, Qatar, Saudi Arabia, Somalia, Sudan, United Arab Emirates and Yemen, when associated to the activities foreseen in regional programmes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Team Leader will head a team of key experts, comprised of the &lt;strong&gt;Deputy Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; and four other key experts who will organise and supervise the implementation of the contract, carry out ROM reviews, be in charge of the internal QC and will draft the annual as well as the end of contract consolidated ROM analysis. They shall cover, as much as possible, the following areas of expertise: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employment and social protection&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Energy &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good Governance - Democracy, rule of law, human rights; Public administration, including decentralisation; PFM and macroeconomics stability (related to Budget Support)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Natural resources, environment, climate change&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trade and Private sector development including: Regional integration; Business environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sustainable agriculture, food and nutrition security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transport&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development and security nexus, including drugs and migration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Civil society&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Statistics and performance measurement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for &lt;strong&gt;2 Deputy Team Leaders&lt;/strong&gt; - once covering &lt;strong&gt;ACP countries&lt;/strong&gt; and the other covering &lt;strong&gt;ENPI countries&lt;/strong&gt;.  This position is a &lt;strong&gt;full time position (220 man days/ year)&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Deputy Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; (DTL) supports the Team Leader (TL) in fulfilling his/her tasks and responsibilities. He/she is in charge in particular of the application of the internal QC system by ROM QC experts and all ROM experts. He/she drafts the quarterly QC reports and follows-up the recommendations of the QA reports. Like the TL, he/she implements ROM reviews as a sector expert for projects and programmes and plays the role of a ROM QC expert.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has a university master degree (or equivalent).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she must be fluent both in French and English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He/she has a minimum of 15 years of experience in development cooperation, notably in project management with a minimum of 5 years of experience as Deputy TL or TL preferably of a mixed team of long and short term experts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has a minimum of 10 years of experience in one of the abovementioned areas of expertise. Experience in other of the above mentioned areas of expertise is an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has a minimum of 5 years of experience in results based approaches, monitoring, and/or evaluation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has a minimum of 3 years and preferably 5 years of experience in quality systems in services sectors: improving work processes and efficiency, defining quality policies and objectives, implementing quality procedures. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she or the TL has a minimum of 5 years of experience on Neighbourhood countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has preferably a good knowledge of EU and other donors implementing modalities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has preferably experience in gender mainstreaming related to his/her area of expertise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in EC format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting (&lt;strong&gt;ROM/DTL&lt;/strong&gt;) in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note that this is a long-term EU-funded project not a EC COM Lot 1 Framework project.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader, External Results Oriented Monitoring (ROM)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 14:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Results Oriented Monitoring (ROM)&lt;/strong&gt; reviews aim to assist the European Commission’s (EC) services and EU Delegations (EUD) in monitoring of and reporting on EU financed development and cooperation projects and programmes (hereafter “projects”) in third countries through independent reviews of the progress of their implementation and the achievement of project results. Compared to the ROM reviews conducted over the past decade, ROM reviews will proceed on a number of reforms that aim to improve the quality and the focus in coverage of the ROM reviews and take into account the high level of devolution reached over the past decade for project preparation and monitoring tasks to EUDs at field level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This lot covers the EU funded national and regional projects and programmes whether single or multi-country and also Cross-Border-Cooperation (CBC) projects and programmes. These projects are implemented in the countries covered by the European Neighbourhood and Partnership Instrument (ENPI) and the European Neighbourhood Instrument (ENI)  in Algeria, Egypt, Israel, Jordan, Lebanon, Libya, Morocco, Syria, Tunisia and Palestine (Neighbourhood South); Armenia, Azerbaijan, Belarus, Georgia, Moldova and Ukraine (Neighbourhood East); Russia. If relevant, including partner countries other than ENI Southern Partner Countries (ENISPCs) :Bosnia and Herzegovina, Albania, Mauritania, Montenegro, Turkey, Bahrain, Comoros, Djibouti, Iraq, Kuwait, Oman, Qatar, Saudi Arabia, Somalia, Sudan, United Arab Emirates and Yemen, when associated to the activities foreseen in regional programmes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; will head a team of key experts, comprised of a &lt;strong&gt;Deputy Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; and four other &lt;strong&gt;key experts&lt;/strong&gt; who will organise and supervise the implementation of the contract, carry out ROM reviews, be in charge of the internal QC and will draft the annual as well as the end of contract consolidated ROM analysis. They shall cover, as much as possible, the following areas of expertise: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employment and social protection&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Energy &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good Governance - Democracy; rule of law; human rights; Public administration, including decentralisation; PFM and macroeconomics stability (related to Budget Support)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Natural resources, environment, climate change&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trade and Private sector development including - Regional integration; Business environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sustainable agriculture, food and nutrition security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transport&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development and security nexus, including drugs and migration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Civil society&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Statistics and performance measurement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt;
DAI is looking for &lt;strong&gt;2 Team Leaders&lt;/strong&gt;; one to cover ACP countries and the other to cover ENPI countries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has a university master degree (or equivalent).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she must be fluent both in French and English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;
He/she has a minimum of 15 years of experience in development cooperation with a minimum of 8 years of experience as Team Leader, preferably of a mixed team of long and short term experts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has a minimum of 10 years of experience in one of the above mentioned areas of expertise. Experience in other of the above mentioned areas of expertise is an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has a minimum of 5 years of experience in results based approaches, monitoring and/or evaluation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she or the Deputy TL has a minimum of 5 years of experience on from Neighbourhood countries, preferably on Southern and/or Eastern Neighbourhood countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has preferably a good knowledge of EU and other donors implementing modalities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has preferably experience in gender mainstreaming related to his/her area of expertise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in EC format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:%20sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting (reference no.ROM/TL) in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note that this is a long-term EU-funded project and does not come under EC COM Lot 1.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Operations Lead</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/corporate-operations-lead-1</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 12:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/corporate-operations-lead-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overarching purpose of this work will be to support the Government of Indonesia (GoI) to strengthen the capacity of all levels of Indonesian government and communities for improved services and economic growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Three substantive pillars will support the long-term goal of a prosperous and stable Indonesia, by contributing to the development of active, inclusive communities and of a capable, responsive state as summarized below, interacting as necessary with sectoral investments under the frontline framework:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work under Pillar 1 will foster active, inclusive communities to support community development in Indonesia;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If implemented under Pillar 2, AIPD2 (Australia-Indonesia Partnership for Decentralisation) would foster a capable, responsive Indonesian state by supporting central and subnational governments for improved service delivery; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If implemented under Pillar 3, NGO support and strengthening would support efforts to foster active, inclusive communities and a capable, responsive Indonesian state.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Corporate Operations Lead&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in a relevant field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5-7 years of experience with substantial international project management and field office management experience. Management consulting experience a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experience in any of the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Human resources and adviser management, especially in recruitment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Logistics and procurement;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capacity building and training;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Office management, including interpreting and translation, administration, office systems, reporting; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Financial management, budgeting and reporting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to work independently and to handle confidential information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent organizational skills and ability to prioritize and multitask.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong decision making ability and attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated leadership skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactive, results-oriented, creative problem solver.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent writing, communication, analytical and negotiation skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work with a diverse set of staff in various technical areas and at different levels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written English skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Bahasa Indonesian an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in DFAT format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:%20sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;strong&gt;DFAT/AOP/006&lt;/strong&gt; in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted. Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M&amp;E Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/me-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 11:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/me-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overarching purpose of this work will be to support the Government of Indonesia (GoI) to strengthen the capacity of all levels of Indonesian government and communities for improved services and economic growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Three substantive pillars will support the long-term goal of a prosperous and stable Indonesia, by contributing to the development of active, inclusive communities and of a capable, responsive state as summarized below, interacting as necessary with sectoral investments under the frontline framework:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work under Pillar 1 will foster active, inclusive communities to support community development in Indonesia;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If implemented under Pillar 2, AIPD2 (Australia-Indonesia Partnership for Decentralisation) would foster a capable, responsive Indonesian state by supporting central and subnational governments for improved service delivery; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If implemented under Pillar 3, NGO support and strengthening would support efforts to foster active, inclusive communities and a capable, responsive Indonesian state.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;M&amp;amp;E Specialist&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of a Bachelor’s degree in Social Sciences (International Development), Business Administration, Economics or other related fields; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5-7 years of relevant professional experience, including 3 years in an M&amp;amp;E position with an international donor-funded development project/organization; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated knowledge and experience in application of the logical framework approach, Performance Monitoring Plan development, and environmental assessment and impact monitoring; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience of donor performance management schemes; knowledge of DFAT M&amp;amp;E processes desirable. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with tracking the impacts of public-private partnerships (attribution of results, cost-sharing, etc); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in participatory design (outcome mapping, after action review, structured interviews, focus groups, case studies, surveys, and secondary data analysis techniques); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of survey design, data collection and data management, and data analysis using rigorous statistics and appropriate software; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with innovative handheld and online data collection systems; and &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with economic development programs and gender mainstreaming. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to explain M&amp;amp;E processes to staff and partners and ensure that they adhere to the highest standards of quality, relevance and timeliness in their M&amp;amp;E efforts; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical skills and ability to write clear reports; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to explain highly technical results to non-technical audiences; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Bahasa Indonesian an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in DFAT format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:%20sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; with the reference &lt;strong&gt;DFAT/AOP/006&lt;/strong&gt; in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Operations Lead</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/corporate-operations-lead</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 11:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/corporate-operations-lead</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overarching purpose of this work will be to support the Government of Indonesia (GoI) to strengthen the capacity of all levels of Indonesian government and communities for improved services and economic growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Three substantive pillars will support the long-term goal of a prosperous and stable Indonesia, by contributing to the development of active, inclusive communities and of a capable, responsive state as summarized below, interacting as necessary with sectoral investments under the frontline framework:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work under Pillar 1 will foster active, inclusive communities to support community development in Indonesia;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If implemented under Pillar 2, AIPD2 (Australia-Indonesia Partnership for Decentralisation) would foster a capable, responsive Indonesian state by supporting central and subnational governments for improved service delivery; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If implemented under Pillar 3, NGO support and strengthening would support efforts to foster active, inclusive communities and a capable, responsive Indonesian state.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Corporate Operations Lead&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in a relevant field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5-7 years of experience with substantial international project management and field office management experience. Management consulting experience a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in any of the following:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Human resources and adviser management, especially in recruitment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Logistics and procurement;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capacity building and training;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Office management, including interpreting and translation, administration, office systems, reporting; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Financial management, budgeting and reporting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to work independently and to handle confidential information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent organizational skills and ability to prioritize and multitask.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong decision making ability and attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated leadership skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactive, results-oriented, creative problem solver.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent writing, communication, analytical and negotiation skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work with a diverse set of staff in various technical areas and at different levels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written English skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Bahasa Indonesian an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in DFAT format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:%20sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;strong&gt;DFAT/AOP/006&lt;/strong&gt; in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted. Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contractor Representative / Program Director</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/contractor-representative-program-director</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 11:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/contractor-representative-program-director</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overarching purpose of this work will be to support the Government of Indonesia (GoI) to strengthen the capacity of all levels of Indonesian government and communities for improved services and economic growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Three substantive pillars will support the long-term goal of a prosperous and stable Indonesia, by contributing to the development of active, inclusive communities and of a capable, responsive state as summarized below, interacting as necessary with sectoral investments under the frontline framework:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work under Pillar 1 will foster active, inclusive communities to support community development in Indonesia;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If implemented under Pillar 2, AIPD2 (Australia-Indonesia Partnership for Decentralisation) would foster a capable, responsive Indonesian state by supporting central and subnational governments for improved service delivery; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If implemented under Pillar 3, NGO support and strengthening would support efforts to foster active, inclusive communities and a capable, responsive Indonesian state.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contractor Representative / Program Director&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Bachelor’s degree required in development studies, management, or other relevant topic. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least ten years of relevant and progressively responsible field-based experience in international development, including experience at management level. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to generate options that consider an appropriate range of capacity development supports and to translate agreed support into action. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in creating and implementing systems for logistics and procurement, contract management, human resources and adviser management, and financial and office management. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to contribute to strategic thinking and planning as part of multidisciplinary teams; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Awareness of social inclusivity and gender equality issues for implementation; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with M4P market development approach; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience leading and managing staff in a complex cross-cultural environment. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to adhere to the requirements of working in an Australian Aid Program, including compliance with DFAT procedures and policies and the DFAT Code of Conduct.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong verbal and written communication skills and excellent spoken and written English. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent reader/speaker of Bahasa Indonesian (desirable)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in DFAT format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:%20sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;strong&gt;DFAT/AOP/006&lt;/strong&gt; in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert on Public Financial Management</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-public-financial-management</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-public-financial-management</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to assess the implementation performance of the Support to the Implementation of the VLAP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s):&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of this assignment are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To evaluate the Government of Moldova compliance with the General Conditions defined in Section 3 of Appendix 2 and the relevant Specific Conditions defined in Section 4 of Appendix 2 of the Financing Agreement on Support to the Implementation of the VLAP, for the disbursement of the 1st instalment (see the Financing Agreement attached).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To advise the European Commission on payment (total, partial, or non-payment) of the 1st instalment of the Support to the Implementation of the VLAP. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert on Public Financial Management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master Degree in finance or economics, or a university degree in the above areas with equivalent professional experience of at least 10 years in the relevant field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the EU procurement rules and excellent reporting and drafting skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in written and spoken English. Knowledge of Romanian or Russian would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Moldovan context would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General and specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 12 years of professional experience in Public Finance Management;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 5 years of professional experience in public finance management agencies, preferably in CIS or/and a country covered by the European Neighbourhood Policy;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of the latest developments and best practices in public financial management;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working with various levels of Government;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of EU external aid procedures, project cycle management principles and budget support methodology and evaluation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in performance assessment and review of EU budget support programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project management and preparation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
