<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2015 08:46:27 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader / Public Management and Planning (Category II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-public-management-and-planning-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2015 08:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-public-management-and-planning-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inception Technical Assistance to support Bangladesh Small and Cottage Industries Corporation (BSCIC)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technical Assistance to BSCIC during the programme Inception Phase in order to support and to facilitate the operational start-up of the PRISM project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader / Public Management and Planning (Category II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master degree in public administration and/or management, public financial management, social sciences or/and professional experience in related field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least 6 years of professional experience in development cooperation planning, management and implementation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;managerial and leadership skills including the ability to work effectively with officials from government in third countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience as team leader in at least 2 assignments of similar nature and scope;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;be fully familiar with the EU financial and contractual procurement rules; experience in preparation and management of Programme Estimate (PE) in line with EU rules and procedures is mandatory;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience as Imprest Administrator or Imprest Accounting Officer in the context of private indirect decentralised operations is considered an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience in the preparation of ToR, global and annual work plans and budgets for public sector in third countries in the context of donor funded development programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience of training/ coaching officials from government on EU financial and contractual procurement rules: especially preparation and management of PE as well as preparation of global and annual work plans and budgets; ,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;having country specific experience in Bangladesh, previous work experience with officials from government of Bangladesh is considered an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;have good drafting and communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent working knowledge of written and spoken English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:francesca_giordano@dai.com&quot;&gt;Francesca_Giordano@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader – SEED Pacific</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-seed-pacific</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 20:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-seed-pacific</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objective of the Programme&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Australian Government recently established the &lt;strong&gt;innovationXchange&lt;/strong&gt; to drive innovation throughout Australia’s aid program so that it becomes an intrinsic way of thinking and acting. The &lt;strong&gt;innovationXchange&lt;/strong&gt; will create and test development innovations, source new ideas for the wider aid program, and work with the private sector to find more creative and clever ways to achieve better results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Australian Department of Foreign Affairs and Trade (DFAT) works constructively with the private sector in the Pacific in many ways, seeing both successes and opportunities for learning. DFAT has therefore developed &lt;strong&gt;SEED Pacific&lt;/strong&gt;, an innovative initiative that seeks to harness the collective power of business and society to solve development challenges in the Pacific. &lt;strong&gt;SEED Pacific&lt;/strong&gt; will target businesses that are prepared to show leadership and innovation in the Pacific and will broker and support the most promising partnerships between global businesses and local organisations to develop new business solutions that have a development impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organisations&lt;/strong&gt; will receive:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support to tailor their business solutions to the Pacific&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Networking opportunities and links to strategic partners&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunities to develop business solutions in collaboration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Match funding for the best business solutions identified through a competitive process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;objectives&lt;/strong&gt; of SEED Pacific are to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Source, test and scale new business ideas that solve development challenges in the Pacific&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work in an innovative way with partners to create and implement the Initiative and the business solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Forge new multi-sector partnerships with Pacific-based organisations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leverage private sector finance for development outcomes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn from failures as much as successes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scope of Work&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; will be responsible for the technical leadership and overall management of the project.  S/he will oversee the long-term expatriate, short term experts and local staff in achieving project results. S/he will undertake regular assessments of the broader political environment within which the project operates to ensure flexibility and rapid reprioritization of activities when necessary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duties and Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serve as principal liaison with DFAT, government counterparts across the Pacific and community stakeholders on programme communications and technical implementation activities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and manage relationships with key actors including government, the private sector, and CSOs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage and provide oversight of project finances.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage staff and recruitment practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with DAI Head Office on programme planning, implementation, personnel, and budget. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversee contractual and financial matters with donors and key partners, and play a key role in the preparation of budget.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regularly draft and compile monthly, quarterly and annual reports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide timely and accurate reporting to DFAT on all programme areas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversee all technical aspects of the project and participate, as required, in assessment, analysis, and training.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage, lead and oversee long and short term staff and subcontractors in achieving project results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversee the participatory planning process and produce a strategic plan for project deliverables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversee the development and implementation of the M&amp;amp;E framework.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Present programme findings to stakeholders and clients; both written and oral.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate programme activities with other donors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure good relations with donor agencies and local implementing partners.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure good, frequent, and direct communications with the Head Office.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;More than 10 years of experience in managing multi-cultural teams and complex projects in developing countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;More than 5 years of experience in the design and implementation of challenge or enterprise funds, or innovation initiatives.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated programme implementation capability, particularly in building capacity of counterparts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An advanced Degree in Political Science, International Development, Public/ Business Administration or related area is required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent networking experience and relationship management skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferable experience of working in Australia or the Pacific region.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated knowledge of latest good governance practices in international development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience working with senior host-country counterparts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous management experience of DFAT-funded programmes, ideally in a TL role, or other donor projects including familiarity with donor management tools, mechanisms and procedures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English is required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to Apply&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;br&gt;
If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in DFAT format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting DFAT/SEEDS in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please note that all profiles are indicative only and therefore subject to change.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior EU Joint Programming Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-eu-joint-programming-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2015 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-eu-joint-programming-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior EU Joint Programming Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master degree academic level in social sciences, political sciences, development management, governance or any other relevant filed or equivalent professional experience of 13 years &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 10 years of professional experience in international development cooperation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5 years in the field of donor coordination, development effectiveness&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 1 year working with the EU Development Partners (either the European Commission and/or EU Member states)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in EU Joint Programming or EU coordination will be considered an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Laos and/or other South East Asian countries will be considered a strong advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Public Finance Management Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-public-finance-management-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 11:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-public-finance-management-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the FWC is to assist the EUD to prepare documentation necessary for the efficient programming of a Sector budget support intervention in the IPA 2015
Programming year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support preparation of the Annexes to the Sector Reform Contract/Action document, in line with the Sector budget support Guidelines from DG ELARG 2014 (the Guidelines will be provided to the contractor at the inception meeting);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support the elaboration of the first and second draft version of the Sector Reform Contract / Action Document (including the identification and negotiation of the relevant targets and tranche disbursement indicators).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organise training sessions on SBS preparation and implementation with local stakeholders (line ministries, oversight bodies, NGOs, academia, etc.);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide assessment on the quality of the SBS selected sector policy and the performance management systems at the national and selected sector levels (PAR and PFM sector).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Public Finance Management Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in Economy/Finance, Management or related area (in the absence of diploma, minimum eight (8) years of relevant professional experience in addition to the minimum number of years of general experience specified below)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum 10 (ten) preferably 12 (twelve) years of experience of working on PFM issues, such as budget planning, preparation and execution; public investment programme and revenue management including taxation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least two (2), preferably three (3) projects during the last six years in design, development or implementation of PFM reform programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in implementation, monitoring, evaluation or assessment of sector budget support projects would be an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:adeline_vanhoutte@dai.com&quot;&gt;Adeline_VanHoutte@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Public administration Reform Expert (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-public-administration-reform-expert-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-public-administration-reform-expert-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the FWC is to assist the EUD to prepare documentation necessary for the efficient programming of a Sector budget support intervention in the IPA 2015
Programming year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support preparation of the Annexes to the Sector Reform Contract/Action document, in line with the Sector budget support Guidelines from DG ELARG 2014 (the Guidelines will be provided to the contractor at the inception meeting);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support the elaboration of the first and second draft version of the Sector Reform Contract / Action Document (including the identification and negotiation of the relevant targets and tranche disbursement indicators).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organise training sessions on SBS preparation and implementation with local stakeholders (line ministries, oversight bodies, NGOs, academia, etc.);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide assessment on the quality of the SBS selected sector policy and the performance management systems at the national and selected sector levels (PAR and PFM sector).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Public Administration Reform Expert (TL)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in Economy, Law, Political science or other relevant field (in the absence of diploma, minimum eight (8) years of relevant professional experience in addition to the minimum number of years of general experience specified below).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum 10 (ten) preferably 12 (twelve) years of postgraduate experience in the area of programming, management or monitoring in the field of public administration reform processes at national or local level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the implementation of at least two (2), preferably three (3) projects during the last six years in the field of implementation of service delivery improvement, decentralization or governance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the preparing at least one (1), preferably two (2) sector budget support projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the EU accession process would be an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:adeline_vanhoutte@dai.com&quot;&gt;Adeline_VanHoutte@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Voter Registration Expert (Cat. I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-voter-registration-expert-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2015 17:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-voter-registration-expert-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The European Union intends to send an expert mission to assess the upcoming Constitutional Referendum in Tanzania, currently foreseen to take place on 30 April 2015, although delay cannot be excluded, with a possible re-run within either thirty or sixty days since the publication of final results depending whether these tie or cast a &amp;ldquo;YES&amp;rdquo; vote in one constituent part and &amp;ldquo;NO&amp;rdquo; in the other. The mission will also assess to the extent possible the efficiency and credibility of the Voter Registration operations managed by NEC. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The purpose of the Expert Mission is to collect factual information concerning this electoral process, in line with the criteria contained in the Commission Communication on Electoral Assistance and Observation [COM(2000)191] Moreover the experts will produce strategic analysis and reporting on the ongoing electoral processes and will provide essential analysis for the possible EU EOM to be deployed for the General elections tentatively foreseen for 25 October 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Voter Registration Expert (Cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Advanced University degree in law, political science, international relations, public administration, statistics, computer science or any other discipline relevant to the assignment, or equivalent professional experience of approximately 12 years in the area related to Lot 7. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience:&lt;/strong&gt;
At least 12 years in the field of voter registration or related to Lot 7. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years in the specific field of voter registration and elections, preferably as part of an EU Election Observation Mission or an EU Election Technical Assistance project; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of electoral issues in developing countries, possibly in Africa, in regards to voter registration. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of electronic registration issues, including in regards to data capture and consolidation, data management, card distribution, the challenge of maintaining a list in a difficult environment, transparency and stakeholder confidence. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in the country and/or the region, and good networks within the different sectors of society in order to be immediately operational is an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adaptability to a multicultural working environment. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to clearly summarize findings and present them in a manner compatible with requested EEM reports. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and spoken skills in English. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Electoral/Legal Expert / Team Leader (Cat. I) </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-electoral-legal-expert-team-leader-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2015 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-electoral-legal-expert-team-leader-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The European Union intends to send an expert mission to assess the upcoming Constitutional Referendum in Tanzania, currently foreseen to take place on 30 April 2015, although delay cannot be excluded, with a possible re-run within either thirty or sixty days since the publication of final results depending whether these tie or cast a &amp;ldquo;YES&amp;rdquo; vote in one constituent part and &amp;ldquo;NO&amp;rdquo; in the other. The mission will also assess to the extent possible the efficiency and credibility of the Voter Registration operations managed by NEC. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The purpose of the Expert Mission is to collect factual information concerning this electoral process, in line with the criteria contained in the Commission Communication on Electoral Assistance and Observation [COM(2000)191]1. Moreover the experts will produce strategic analysis and reporting on the ongoing electoral processes and will provide essential analysis for the possible EU EOM to be deployed for the General elections tentatively foreseen for 25 October 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Electoral/Legal Expert / Team Leader (Cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced University degree in Law, Political Science, International Relations or any other discipline relevant to the assignment, or equivalent professional experience of at least 12 years in the area related to Lot 7. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in Law will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least 12 years of experience in the area related to Lot 7. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years’ work experience in the field of electoral assistance and electoral observation and analysis, preferably as part of an EU Election Observation Mission or an Election Technical Assistance project of the EU or of other international organisations, possibly including managing an electoral observation mission, drafting statements and reports; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with the legal and regulatory framework for the elections as well as international and regional standards for elections. In this context the “Compendium of International Standards for Elections” is an important background document; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent understanding of the functioning of election management bodies; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in political analysis. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in representing and providing briefings. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven work experience with analysis of legal framework for elections will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in assessing the media landscape and media framework, according to international and regional standards, particularly as regards to elections, will be an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in the country and/or the region and good networks within the different sectors of society in order to be immediately operational will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and spoken English. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Knowledge of Kiswahili (even if only passive)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In addition&lt;/strong&gt;, the Electoral/Legal Expert / Team Leader will present the following profile: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and inter-personal skills; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent report drafting skills; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coordination and management skills and past experience of management in a similar assignment; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proven knowledge and field experience of EU policies and programmes in the area of human rights, democratization and good governance; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proven work experience in project implementation and budget management of international civilian missions, preferably as part of an EU Election Observation Mission or an EU Election Technical Assistance project; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proven work experience of managing mission budgets and contracts of local staff is an asset. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adaptability to a multicultural working environment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert in M&amp;E and Education (Category II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-me-and-education-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2015 14:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-me-and-education-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overall objectives of the mid-term review (MTR) are to offer an overview of the activities carried out in the first phase of the implementation of the two Programmes : &amp;ldquo;Support to the
Community Courts of Eritrea&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Capacity Building for the Public Administration of Eritrea&amp;rdquo; and to provide recommendations for the successful implementation during the remainder of the implementation periods. The MTR shall provide recommendations for the way forward and confirm one of the two scenarios:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Scenario: no major changes in the programme’s orientation and objectives but with suggestions for revisions that may be necessary to adapt the programme to emerging needs.
• Scenario: major changes in the programme’s orientation, objectives and implementation modalities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in M&amp;amp;E and Education (Category II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in social sciences or a related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven communication and reporting skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum of six years&amp;#39; experience of the LFA and PCM&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Proven experience in Monitoring and Evaluation of donor funded programmes
• Experience in programme in the higher education sector
• Knowledge of the &lt;strong&gt;Eritrean context&lt;/strong&gt; will be an advantage
• Knowledge of the &lt;strong&gt;Eritrean education system&lt;/strong&gt; will be an advantage&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fluency in English is required. &lt;strong&gt;Knowledge of other languages used in Eritrea&lt;/strong&gt; will be an advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring and Evaluation Expert (Category II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/monitoring-and-evaluation-expert-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2015 14:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/monitoring-and-evaluation-expert-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overall objectives of the mid-term review (MTR) are to offer an overview of the activities carried out in the first phase of the implementation of the two Programmes : &amp;ldquo;Support to the
Community Courts of Eritrea&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Capacity Building for the Public Administration of Eritrea&amp;rdquo; and to provide recommendations for the successful implementation during the remainder of the implementation periods. The MTR shall provide recommendations for the way forward and confirm one of the two scenarios:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Scenario: no major changes in the programme’s orientation and objectives but with suggestions for revisions that may be necessary to adapt the programme to emerging needs.
• Scenario: major changes in the programme’s orientation, objectives and implementation modalities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring and Evaluation Expert (Category II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in social sciences or a related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven communication and reporting skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum of six years&amp;#39; experience of the LFA and PCM&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in Monitoring and Evaluation of donor funded programmes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in programme in the justice sector&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Eritrean context will be an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Eritrean legal context will be an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fluency in English is required. Knowledge of other languages used in Eritrea will be an advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Evaluation Expert (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-evaluation-expert-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2015 14:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-evaluation-expert-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overall objectives of the mid-term review (MTR) are to offer an overview of the activities carried out in the first phase of the implementation of the two Programmes : &amp;ldquo;Support to the Community Courts of Eritrea&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Capacity Building for the Public Administration of Eritrea&amp;rdquo; and to provide recommendations for the successful implementation during the remainder of the implementation periods. The MTR shall provide recommendations for the way forward and confirm one of the two scenarios:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Scenario: no major changes in the programme’s orientation and objectives but with suggestions for revisions that may be necessary to adapt the programme to emerging needs.
• Scenario: major changes in the programme’s orientation, objectives and implementation modalities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Evaluation Expert (TL)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in social sciences or a related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven communication, coordination and reporting skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of twelve years&amp;#39; experience in the development sector, particularly in terms of providing services to donors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience on leading an evaluation team for Governance programmes or other similar programmes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Functional knowledge of EDF procedures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience in Eritrea will be an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;
Fluency and impeccable report writing ability in English are required&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert in Agricultural Programming/M&amp;E (Category II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-agricultural-programming-me-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2015 11:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-agricultural-programming-me-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To enhance MoA capacity in planning, implementation, monitoring and management of EU funded programmes particularly AAWB and PSRG-A programmes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To advice and support the MoA-assigned General Coordinator of the AAWB &amp;amp; PSRG-A programmes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in Agricultural Programming/M&amp;amp;E (Category II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master Degree in Business Administration or Master Degree in Agro-economic from a recognised University or equivalent. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years’ experience in agricultural programme&amp;rsquo;s formulation, implementation, management, coordination and monitoring and evaluation in developing countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven expertise in strategic planning, with a wealth of practical experience in developing world agricultural communities and support to public sector institutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years’ experience as project manager in relevant discipline;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of computer skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command in English language (speaking, reading and writing);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Arabic language (speaking and reading) will be an advantage. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert in Local Development/Local Governance – Category II</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-local-development-local-governance-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-local-development-local-governance-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With the aim to provide the Lebanese Authorities, beneficiaries of the EU funded programmes with an overall, independent and accountable result-oriented Ex-post Evaluation of :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo; Appui au développement local dans le nord du Liban&amp;rdquo; – ENPI/2008/19-623 – Component Community Development : a selection of 5 projects implemented by the European Social Development Fund (ESFD);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo; Support for economic recovery I : Local development, reconstruction, infrastructure rehabilitation&amp;rdquo; – ENPI/2007/18-882 – Component Local Development Projects : the 12 projects implemented by the Unions of Municipalities (UoM);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo; Local Authorities in Development&amp;rdquo; : a selection of 6 projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this assignment is threefold:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To assess the implementation of the interventions, paying a particular attention to the results of the project against its objectives;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To assess the impact of the programmes compared to the initial objectives;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To propose key lessons and recommendations for the Lebanese Authorities to prepare a strategy and design orientation interms of support to local development and for the future EU interventions in order to improve current and upcoming actions in the field of local development/local governance in Lebanon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in Local Development/Local Governance – Category II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least Masters Degree in economics, social science, or equivalent; in its absence equivalent professional experience of 10 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in implementing programmes aiming at improving local governance is compulsory;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least six (6) years of experience in sectors related to lot 7 (i.e. technical description), in addition to the minimum expertise common to all lots, is compulsory.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience as evaluator in the local development field in at least 1 project/programme;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience as evaluator in the local development field of an EU funded project/programme is an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Mediterranean countries and knowledge of Middle East political context;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of EU project cycle management, EU procedures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Soft skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Excellent writing and editing skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Excellent command of Arabic and English is compulsory;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:adeline_vanhoutte@dai.com&quot;&gt;Adeline_VanHoutte@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader, Law &amp; Justice Sector, Papua New Guinea</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-law-justice-sector-papua-new-guinea</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 08:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-law-justice-sector-papua-new-guinea</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectives of the role:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; will manage and support a team of technical and operational staff to deliver a highly complex and important DFAT investment to &lt;strong&gt;support law and justice in Papua New Guinea&lt;/strong&gt;.  The program will build on Australian support to the sector from the &lt;strong&gt;Papua New Guinea-Australia Law and Justice Partnership&lt;/strong&gt;, which was completed in June 2014 and its ensuing &lt;strong&gt;Transition Program&lt;/strong&gt;, which runs from July 2014 to December 2015. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The program will target agencies along with sub-national institutions and stakeholders in Hela, Southern Highlands, Gulf, Western, Oro and Morobe provinces, plus the Autonomous Region of Bougainville (ARB).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; will establish and manage relationships with both potential and identified stakeholders, and will facilitate and coordinate collaboration with other development programs being implemented by DFAT and other donors. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Length of the project&lt;/strong&gt;: 2016 - 2019
&lt;strong&gt;Start Date&lt;/strong&gt;:  August 2015 (to support the mobilisation and transition phase)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Criteria:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A tertiary degree in a relevant field (e.g. international development, international law);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in capacity development techniques (related to technical skills) and the ability to use a variety of approaches to increase the skills and service delivery standards of partner agencies, counterparts and team members. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High level interpersonal skills including verbal and written communication skills and an ability to produce high quality technical reports, guidance notes and templates. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to lead teams of professionals and to coach and mentor junior staff members, and work effectively with others to build strong partnerships and contribute to sustainable outcomes. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to work sensitively in a complex multi-cultural environment and high levels of personal resilience to work successfully in remote and challenging locations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in implementing governance programs in decentralised service delivery contexts and familiarity and understanding of working with law and justice agencies and community justice initiatives;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in leading organisational development and change management processes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to mainstream gender-sensitive programming and anti-corruption initiatives within program design and implementation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated capacity to manage a transitional mobilisation phase in which the managing contractor changes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An outstanding history of working with the Australian Aid program and the Department for Foreign Affairs and Trade (DFAT);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience in Papua New Guinea and the Pacific region.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How to apply: Please send your CV by email to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;Sarah_Owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;.  Please note that due to high volumes of applications, we cannot guarantee to respond to each applicant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Please note that all profiles are indicative only and therefore subject to change once the ToR is made available.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWP 2 Projects Review</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Beyond WTO Program (B-WTO) was developed in response to a request from the Government of Vietnam (GoV) for donor support to help with managing economic integration and the transition to a market economy following WTO accession. The B-WTO goal is “to strengthen government’s capacity to manage the integration of Vietnam into the global economy and the transition of Vietnam to a socialist market economy”. The immediate objective is “implementation of priority policy actions from the GoV’s Action Plan to enhance Vietnam’s capacity to sustain pro-poor growth (GAP)”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The remit of this project was a review of the 2nd annual work plan’s implementation (AWP2) of Phase 2 of the B-WTO in May 2013. The objectives of the review were to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the project implementation performance and project results relative to the logical framework targets and evaluation criteria. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the results achieved at the Component and Program’s level according to the Monitoring and Evaluation (M&amp;amp;E) framework of the Program.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify lessons learned from implementation, make recommendations for the remaining duration of the program and the Independent Completion Report process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program 2013 Performance and Quality Mapping Exercise</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID’s PNG Program is looking to improve its performance and quality (P&amp;amp;Q) standards and systems. The purpose of this project was to map the PNG Program’s current P&amp;amp;Q capacity and systems, to address the risk of AusAID being unable to demonstrate results for its increased investments in PNG over the next four years. Over the last several years, the PNG Program has undertaken a number of M&amp;amp;E assessments and reviews which have identified key strengths and challenges within the program. This project was intended to pick up where these assessments left off. Through a desk review and consultations with sector teams, the Review Team were to distil key P&amp;amp;Q risks and issues for the PNG Program. The Review Team’s brief included the provision of recommendations on priority activities to support sector approaches to M&amp;amp;E, strengthen the Program’s ability to collect evidence, provide critical analysis and report on results.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID required a consultant to assist with the development and finalisation of its Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework. Development of a humanitarian monitoring and evaluation framework is a key commitment outlined in AusAID’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy (HAP) and its associated Implementation Plan. In line with the agency focus on results reporting, the HAP and HAP Implementation Plan commit AusAID to develop a monitoring and evaluation framework to support the initial performance assessment framework contained within the HAP and AusAID annual reporting under the Comprehensive Aid Policy Framework.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key objective of this assignment was to build the Humanitarian program’s capacity for monitoring and reporting results by:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In consultation with AusAID’s Humanitarian team, redraft and finalise the Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework, to ensure it provides a platform to:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track implementation of key commitments in Australia’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy; and,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish a set of measurable humanitarian performance indicators (in addition to the two CAPF indicators) to enable AusAID to track achievements, lessons learned and to report on the results achieved from AusAID’s humanitarian work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of Pacific Forum Compact Reporting</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The purpose of the assignment was to examine country views of aid effectiveness and regional organisations expressed through Forum Compact reporting, particularly peer review of Forum Island Countries’ national development plan processes. The services provided included the preparation of a think piece which outlines key aid effectiveness issues arising from country reporting under the Compact reporting and discusses options for addressing these issues.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study on Community-based Social Protection</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/study-on-community-based-social-protection</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/study-on-community-based-social-protection</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Poverty and Social Analysis is the process of using and generating evidence on poverty throughout the aid management cycle. Most poverty and social analysis focuses on economic and human capital, but there are two oft neglected elements: voice and influence, and social capital. Yet more and more development practitioners are recognizing the importance of social capital, particularly informal social capital, in preventing and addressing poverty and vulnerability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This project supported AusAID to explore:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the role of informal social capital in the Fijian context and whether it lends itself to fair redistribution of resources and, if so, the ways in which AusAID can engage with local communities to strengthen existing social capital structures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;how such structures can enable the disempowered and poor to claim their entitlements in the three domains discussed in the PSA framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the potential challenges that can arise from such efforts. For instance, the poorest are often included on less favorable terms within social networks, and have access to fewer and lower-quality networks. Further, we need to better understand how poverty and disempowerment intersect with an absence of informal social capital, the repercussions this has, and the options available for tackling this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
