<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 14:48:39 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Electoral/Political Expert (Team Leader)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/electoral-political-expert-team-leader</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 14:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/electoral-political-expert-team-leader</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Electoral Follow-up Mission to Pakistan 2016&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the assignment is to contribute to the consolidation of democracy and to support institution building and transparency in Pakistan of the implementation of the EU EOM recommendations of 2013.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Electoral/Political Expert (Team Leader) – Cat. I, 18 wd&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree Academic level in Political Science, International Relations, Law or any other discipline relevant to the assignment OR, in absence of the Master&amp;rsquo;s degree, equivalent professional experience of approximately 15 years in the area related to Lot 7. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in the area related to Lot 7. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 8 years of relevant experience in election systems, legislation and administration, including: voter/candidate registration, election-related legislation and international standards in the election field, designing and drafting election-related projects and planning and implementing election observations missions and election-related technical assistance projects, drafting statements and reports. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;S/he must have previously been directly involved in election observation by the EU or other organisations with the participation in at least 5 election observation missions with international or domestic organisations. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent understanding of political party functioning. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in electoral issues in developing countries, particularly in South Asia. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven work experience on political context legislation and good understanding of political context of the elections in different countries. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in assessing the media landscape and media framework according to international and regional standards. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent understanding of the functioning of election management bodies. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent knowledge of all issues related to the evaluation of electoral assistance projects; 
*Excellent communication and inter-personal skills and report drafting skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordination and management skills and past experience of management in a similar assignment, preferably as Deputy Chief Observer in an Election observation mission or as Chief Technical Adviser in a technical assistance project; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven knowledge and field experience of EU policies and programmes in the area of human rights, democratisation and good governance; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven work experience in project implementation and budget management of international civilian missions, preferably as part of an EU Election Observation Mission or an EU Election Technical Assistance project is an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legal Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/legal-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 14:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/legal-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Election Follow-up Mission to Kenya&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of this assignment is to contribute to the consolidation of democracy and to support institution building and transparency in Kenya in the context of the implementation of the EU EOM recommendations of 2013. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of the Mission are: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;to assess and report to the European External Action Service (EEAS) and the European Commission (EC FPI) on the progress made in electoral reforms since the delivery of the final report of the 2013 EU EOM. The findings of the mission will be shared with the European Parliament and Member States. The mission will focus its assessment on the implementation of the recommendations of the 2013 EU EOM and on the aligning of all elements of the electoral process to international standards and relevant national legislation of Kenya;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;in view of future elections, in particular the 2017 elections, advise on potential EU action(s) that could contribute strengthening the implementation of the recommendations and/or to the overall improvement of the electoral framework.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Legal Expert&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced University degree in Law or equivalent professional experience of over 12 years in the area related to Lot 7. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 12 years in the field of electoral assistance and in the sector(s) directly related to the Lot 7. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Familiarity with the legal and regulatory framework for the election as well as international and regional standards for elections. In this context the “Compendium of International Standards for Elections” is an important background document ; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellent understanding of human rights issues in the country and the region; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience in assessing the political landscape and human rights, according to international and regional standards, particularly as regards in the context of elections; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous experience in the country and/or the region is an asset; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adaptability to a multicultural working environment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellent written and spoken skills in English. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader /Political-Electoral Expert (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-political-electoral-expert-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 13:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-political-electoral-expert-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Election Follow-up Mission to Kenya&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of this assignment is to contribute to the consolidation of democracy and to support institution building and transparency in Kenya in the context of the implementation of the EU EOM recommendations of 2013. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of the Mission are: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;to assess and report to the European External Action Service (EEAS) and the European Commission (EC FPI) on the progress made in electoral reforms since the delivery of the final report of the 2013 EU EOM. The findings of the mission will be shared with the European Parliament and Member States. The mission will focus its assessment on the implementation of the recommendations of the 2013 EU EOM and on the aligning of all elements of the electoral process to international standards and relevant national legislation of Kenya;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;in view of future elections, in particular the 2017 elections, advise on potential EU action(s) that could contribute strengthening the implementation of the recommendations and/or to the overall improvement of the electoral framework.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Team Leader /Political-Electoral Expert (Category I) *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in Law, Political Science, International Relations or any other discipline relevant to the assignment, or equivalent professional experience of over 12 years in the area related to Lot 7. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in the area related to Lot 7. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Approximately 5 years work experience in the field of electoral assistance and electoral observation and analysis, preferably as part of an EU Election Observation Mission and/or an EU Election Technical Assistance project, possibly including managing an electoral observation mission, drafting statements and reports; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with the national legal and regulatory framework for elections, including the issue of voter registration, as well as international and regional standards for elections. In this context the &amp;ldquo;Compendium of International Standards for Elections&amp;rdquo; is an important background document; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven work experience in political assessment and analysis, and good understanding of electoral systems; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent understanding of political party functioning; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven work experience on and good understanding of the establishment of electoral lists and voter registration; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent understanding of the functioning of election management bodies; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in assessing the media landscape and media framework according to international and regional standards; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in electoral issues in developing countries, particularly in Africa; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent knowledge of all issues related to the evaluation of electoral assistance projects; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous working experience in the country and/or the region; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adaptability to a multicultural working environment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellent written and spoken skills in English. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, the Team Leader will present the following profile: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and inter-personal skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent report drafting skills; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordination and management skills and past experience of management in a similar assignment, preferably as Deputy Chief Observer in an Election observation mission or as Chief Technical Adviser in a technical assistance project; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven knowledge and minimum 5 years of field experience of EU policies and programmes in the area of human rights, democratisation and good governance; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven work experience in project implementation and budget management of international civilian missions, preferably as part of an EU Election Observation Mission or an EU Election Technical Assistance project is an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven familiarity with contractual and budgetary procedures of EU external action and related mechanisms is an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key Expert in EDF Financial and Procurement Procedures / PCM and Performance Assessment/Logical Framework (Category 2) </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-expert-in-edf-financial-and-procurement-procedures-pcm-and-performance-assessment-logical-framework-category-2</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-expert-in-edf-financial-and-procurement-procedures-pcm-and-performance-assessment-logical-framework-category-2</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to West Africa Gulf of Guinea Organisation in Maritime Security (SWAGOGOMS)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This assignment will provide a coherent proposal to  ECOWAS and EU for the fight against illicit maritime activities in the Gulf of Guinea. It will give sufficient background information and justifications to enable the ECOWAS and EU to make an informed decision on specific objectives and implementation modalities of  the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Expert in EDF Financial and Procurement Procedures / PCM and Performance Assessment/Logical Framework (Category 2)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a University Degree in Project Management, Business, Finance, Engineering, Development Cooperation,or relevant, directly related discipline, or equivalent; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with development of coherent concepts for EDF projects (including design of objectives, OVIs, results, contractual procedures, activities, planning, budgets Minimum of 8 years of professional experience as programme manager/expert &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 4 years&amp;#39; experience with EDF programming procedures will be an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in contributing to the design, identification, formulation of EU development Projects (at least 5 identifications of formulations) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred skills&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project management EU Funded projects in developing countries (at least 3 years); would be an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of maritime security issues an asset &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent in English both in spoken and written language; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of spoken and written French; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Portuguese is considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key Expert in Information Systems and Data-gathering, Management and Exchange (Category 2)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-expert-in-information-systems-and-data-gathering-management-and-exchange-category-2</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-expert-in-information-systems-and-data-gathering-management-and-exchange-category-2</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to West Africa Gulf of Guinea Organisation in Maritime Security (SWAGOGOMS)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This assignment will provide a coherent proposal to  ECOWAS and EU for the fight against illicit maritime activities in the Gulf of Guinea. It will give sufficient background information and justifications to enable the ECOWAS and EU to make an informed decision on specific objectives and implementation modalities of  the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Expert in Information Systems and Data-gathering, Management and Exchange (Category 2)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Minimum required skills: *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Candidate should have&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a University Degree in Information technology, engineering, or relevant, directly related discipline, or equivalent; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 5 years of professional experience as IT/network programme manager/expert in inter-systems information exchange. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project management in developing countries; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred skills:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with EDF programming procedures will be an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience (min 2 years of the the maritime) sector an asset &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in contributing to the design, the identification, the formulation of EU development Projects an asset &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work experience in GoG countries an asset &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent in English both in spoken and written language; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of spoken and written French; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Portuguese is considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key Expert in Rule of Law and Maritime Law Enforcement (Traffics, other Illicit Activities) (category 1)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-expert-in-rule-of-law-and-maritime-law-enforcement-traffics-other-illicit-activities-category-1</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 13:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-expert-in-rule-of-law-and-maritime-law-enforcement-traffics-other-illicit-activities-category-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to West Africa Gulf of Guinea Organisation in Maritime Security (SWAGOGOMS)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This assignment will provide a coherent proposal to  ECOWAS and EU for the fight against illicit maritime activities in the Gulf of Guinea. It will give sufficient background information and justifications to enable the ECOWAS and EU to make an informed decision on specific objectives and implementation modalities of  the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Expert in Rule of Law and Maritime Law Enforcement (Traffics, other Illicit Activities) (category 1)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master Degree (University Level) in Law, Political Science, Development Cooperation, Humanitarian Aid or relevant, directly related discipline, or equivalent; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in international standards and methods regarding maritime law reforms; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 8 years of professional experience as programme manager/expert in maritime legislation (ZEE and territorial waters), law enforcement and operational implementation of activities at international level encompassing trafficking (humans, arms, drugs etc) and IUU fishing &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in contributing to the design, the identification, the formulation of EU development Projects (at least 2 identifications of formulations) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Experience in communication, negotiation and dialogue at high level; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred skills&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of West Africa Peace and security dynamics &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 3 years&amp;#39; experience with EDF programming procedures will be an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience of the workings of the maritime law sector in GoG an asset &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in design of capacity building projects on maritime law reform and law enforcement will be an asset &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent in English both in spoken and written language;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Knowledge of spoken and written French required; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Portuguese is considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader and Key Expert in Maritime Security and Identification/Formulation</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-and-key-expert-in-maritime-security-and-identification-formulation</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-and-key-expert-in-maritime-security-and-identification-formulation</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to West Africa Gulf of Guinea Organisation in Maritime Security (SWAGOGOMS)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This assignment will provide a coherent proposal to ECOWAS and EU for the fight against illicit maritime activities in the Gulf of Guinea. It will give sufficient background information and justifications to enable the ECOWAS and EU to make an informed decision on specific objectives and implementation modalities of  the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader and Key Expert in Maritime Security and Identification/Formulation responsible of the mission and final AD&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master Degree (Academic level) in Defence or Security Affairs, Project and Programme Management, , Public Administration, Political Science, Law or relevant, directly related discipline, or equivalent; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 8 years professional experience in maritime security sector &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in monitoring the identification/formulation of large development projects in complex political environments (at least3 significant identifications/formulations) with particular reference to EU-funded projects/programmes, and familiarity with the methodological approach set by the European Commission; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of EDF programming procedures &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound and proven experience in identification and formulation methods and techniques, preferably in developing countries, including at the programme and policy level plus relevant field experience. Ability to assess and communicate best practices; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in problem analysis, stakeholders&amp;#39; analysis and construction of logical framework; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full working knowledge of English and French, as well as excellent report writing and communication skills in both languages; additional knowledge of Portuguese will be an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative ability to identify practical solutions to overcome challenges to time-critical projects; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Experience in communication, negotiation and dialogue at high level; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred skills&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 12 years of professional experience &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 5 years&amp;#39; experience with EDF programming procedures will be an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in EC programmes design and identification in developing countries &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; In-depth knowledge of maritime security related issues and systems &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of West Africa peace and security architecture and dynamics. Work experience at least in two Gulf of Guinea Countries &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in contributing to ECOWAS programmes &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific expertise in maritime security systems and infrastructure issues (technical assistance, capacity development, training, awareness campaigns) especially in countries with common law legal system 
• Experience in Nigeria&amp;rsquo;s governance issues an asset &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category II Information Management and Agriculture/FNS Policy Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-information-management-and-agriculture-fns-policy-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2015 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-information-management-and-agriculture-fns-policy-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To contribute to the socio-economic development and poverty reduction in Zimbabwe through supporting agricultural related information collection, data quality control and analysis as well as outreach, capacity development , management and information dissemination. These should be attended in a way that can effectively and efficiently contribute to creating a sustainable, diversified, competitive and efficient agricultural sector that supports inclusive economic growth and revenue generation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category I Agricultural Statistics and Monitoring Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in the fields of agriculture, Statistics, Information management, Geographic information systems, Agricultural monitoring, Agro meteorology or equivalent. OR 12 years&amp;#39; professional experience in consultancy and management of programs/projects in the field of data systems analysis and management, policy and programming.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience in agricultural statistics, information management systems, Geographic Information systems and mapping;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong background in agriculture and food security issues. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Southern Africa region and Zimbabwe in the above sectors would be an added value.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:%20chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category I Information Management Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-information-management-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2015 13:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-information-management-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To contribute to the socio-economic development and poverty reduction in Zimbabwe through supporting agricultural related information collection, data quality control and analysis as well as outreach, capacity development, management and information dissemination. These should be attended in a way that can effectively and efficiently contribute to creating a sustainable, diversified, competitive and efficient agricultural sector that supports inclusive economic growth and revenue generation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category I Information Management Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in the fields of agriculture, Information management, international cooperation or equivalent. OR 12 years&amp;#39; professional experience in consultancy and management of programs/projects in the field of data systems analysis and management, policy and programming.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience in information management systems, policy formulation and programming;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong background in agriculture and food security issues. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Southern Africa region and Zimbabwe in the above sectors wold be an added value. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the European Union instruments for ACP countries and of EDF procedures is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category I Agricultural Statistics and Monitoring Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in the fields of agriculture, Statistics, Information management, Geographic information systems, Agricultural monitoring, Agro meteorology or equivalent. OR 12 years&amp;#39; professional experience in consultancy and management of programs/projects in the field of data systems analysis and management, policy and programming.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience in agricultural statistics, information management systems, Geographic Information systems and mapping;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong background in agriculture and food security issues. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Southern Africa region and Zimbabwe in the above sectors would be an added value.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWP 2 Projects Review</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Beyond WTO Program (B-WTO) was developed in response to a request from the Government of Vietnam (GoV) for donor support to help with managing economic integration and the transition to a market economy following WTO accession. The B-WTO goal is “to strengthen government’s capacity to manage the integration of Vietnam into the global economy and the transition of Vietnam to a socialist market economy”. The immediate objective is “implementation of priority policy actions from the GoV’s Action Plan to enhance Vietnam’s capacity to sustain pro-poor growth (GAP)”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The remit of this project was a review of the 2nd annual work plan’s implementation (AWP2) of Phase 2 of the B-WTO in May 2013. The objectives of the review were to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the project implementation performance and project results relative to the logical framework targets and evaluation criteria. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the results achieved at the Component and Program’s level according to the Monitoring and Evaluation (M&amp;amp;E) framework of the Program.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify lessons learned from implementation, make recommendations for the remaining duration of the program and the Independent Completion Report process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program 2013 Performance and Quality Mapping Exercise</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID’s PNG Program is looking to improve its performance and quality (P&amp;amp;Q) standards and systems. The purpose of this project was to map the PNG Program’s current P&amp;amp;Q capacity and systems, to address the risk of AusAID being unable to demonstrate results for its increased investments in PNG over the next four years. Over the last several years, the PNG Program has undertaken a number of M&amp;amp;E assessments and reviews which have identified key strengths and challenges within the program. This project was intended to pick up where these assessments left off. Through a desk review and consultations with sector teams, the Review Team were to distil key P&amp;amp;Q risks and issues for the PNG Program. The Review Team’s brief included the provision of recommendations on priority activities to support sector approaches to M&amp;amp;E, strengthen the Program’s ability to collect evidence, provide critical analysis and report on results.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID required a consultant to assist with the development and finalisation of its Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework. Development of a humanitarian monitoring and evaluation framework is a key commitment outlined in AusAID’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy (HAP) and its associated Implementation Plan. In line with the agency focus on results reporting, the HAP and HAP Implementation Plan commit AusAID to develop a monitoring and evaluation framework to support the initial performance assessment framework contained within the HAP and AusAID annual reporting under the Comprehensive Aid Policy Framework.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key objective of this assignment was to build the Humanitarian program’s capacity for monitoring and reporting results by:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In consultation with AusAID’s Humanitarian team, redraft and finalise the Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework, to ensure it provides a platform to:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track implementation of key commitments in Australia’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy; and,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish a set of measurable humanitarian performance indicators (in addition to the two CAPF indicators) to enable AusAID to track achievements, lessons learned and to report on the results achieved from AusAID’s humanitarian work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of Pacific Forum Compact Reporting</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The purpose of the assignment was to examine country views of aid effectiveness and regional organisations expressed through Forum Compact reporting, particularly peer review of Forum Island Countries’ national development plan processes. The services provided included the preparation of a think piece which outlines key aid effectiveness issues arising from country reporting under the Compact reporting and discusses options for addressing these issues.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study on Community-based Social Protection</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/study-on-community-based-social-protection</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/study-on-community-based-social-protection</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Poverty and Social Analysis is the process of using and generating evidence on poverty throughout the aid management cycle. Most poverty and social analysis focuses on economic and human capital, but there are two oft neglected elements: voice and influence, and social capital. Yet more and more development practitioners are recognizing the importance of social capital, particularly informal social capital, in preventing and addressing poverty and vulnerability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This project supported AusAID to explore:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the role of informal social capital in the Fijian context and whether it lends itself to fair redistribution of resources and, if so, the ways in which AusAID can engage with local communities to strengthen existing social capital structures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;how such structures can enable the disempowered and poor to claim their entitlements in the three domains discussed in the PSA framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the potential challenges that can arise from such efforts. For instance, the poorest are often included on less favorable terms within social networks, and have access to fewer and lower-quality networks. Further, we need to better understand how poverty and disempowerment intersect with an absence of informal social capital, the repercussions this has, and the options available for tackling this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Provision of a Child Protection Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/provision-of-a-child-protection-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/provision-of-a-child-protection-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For this project HTSPE was contracted to provide a child protection specialist and handle all the associated management and administrative work. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The child protection specialist provided by HTSPE was required to work on an assignment designed to assist the Pacific Division (PACD) to improve its approach to child protection and managing risks to children. AusAID has a number of partners in the Pacific who work with children or come into contact with children through their activities. The AusAID-wide child protection stocktake, conducted in May 2013 found that there are a number of organisations funded by AusAID in the Pacific with a high or very high inherent child protection risk. Consistent with the stocktake report PACD proposes to escalate efforts to ensure partner organisations policies, procedures and practices are in accordance with AusAID’s Child Protection Policy 2013 and to make child protection a more explicit focus of PACD’s risk management system.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Environment and Biology Expert (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/opportunities/senior-environment-and-biology-expert-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 20:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/opportunities/senior-environment-and-biology-expert-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Expert 2 is expected to contribute the implementation of all of the related modules and the preparation of both training materials and Training Evaluation Report in the context of related chapter/s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in Biology, Ecology, Chemistry or other Natural Sciences related to assignment. In the absence of the degree required, at least 17 years of professional experience in the related areas is requested.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good command of both written and spoken English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General professional experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in the sector(s) related to the Lot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience in technical and/or scientific fields required for the implementation of the Water Framework Directive and/or Habitat Directive and/or other related Directives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 river basin management plans experience in terms of setting of environmental objectives and/or setting, design and upgrade of biological monitoring programme and/or execution and assessment of biological monitoring.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in development of measures for water pollution reduction and/or improving ecological status, and/or river basin characterisation/analysis will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in projects related to Integrated Water Resources Management will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
