<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 20:55:32 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agricultural Experts with Experience of Working with MFAT</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/agricultural-experts-mfat-experience</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2014 13:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/agricultural-experts-mfat-experience</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2&gt;Project Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;New Zealand Aid Programme&lt;/strong&gt;, acting for and on behalf of the Ministry of Foreign Affairs and Trade &lt;strong&gt;(MFAT)&lt;/strong&gt;, has appointed a Panel of specialist advisers and organisations with a wide range of skills, capabilities and areas of expertise across the &lt;strong&gt;Agriculture&lt;/strong&gt; sector. This range reflects the diverse and international nature of New Zealand Aid Programme work that is often conducted in niche areas of specific regions and countries. MFAT will use the Panel as its preferred sourcing method for &lt;strong&gt;agriculture sector specialists&lt;/strong&gt; to support the delivery of international development activities, and will open for a two year term with the option to extend for an additional two years at MFAT’s discretion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HTSPE&lt;/strong&gt;, with their partner &lt;strong&gt;AgFirst New Zealand&lt;/strong&gt;, is one of the contractors on a pre-approved list of suppliers who are available to provide MFAT with the specified services outlined in the Deed of Standing Offer. Over time, MFAT may expand the panel to meet evolving business needs or if they require additional specialisms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 16 agriculture specialisms provided across the Panel are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agribusiness&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. attracting investors to the agricultural industry; preparing a range of policy options for agribusiness development; designing and implementing livelihood projects;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agricultural economics&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. monitoring and evaluation of agricultural programs; carrying out financial and cost-benefit analyses; leading financial surveys;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agricultural extension services and technology transfer&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. carrying out training; agricultural extension; rural advisory services; technology transfer programs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Applied agricultural research&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. design and implementation of applied research trials;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Market access&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. development of efficient and effective rural markets; value chain approaches; conducting reviews and surveys to identify new market opportunities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tropical cash crop and food production&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. knowledge of tropical cultivation, including annual and perennial crops; agro-production and marketing;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Temperate cash crop and food production&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. advising on production methods for temperate crops;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food safety&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. phytosanitary standards; animal welfare and health; food safety regulations;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tropical and/or Dryland Livestock production&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. research on the challenges facing livestock production in these areas; livestock production evaluations;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Temperate Livestock production&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. identifying and reviewing animal health issues, designing and implementing methods for improved production;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organic production and/or ethical certification systems&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. providing knowledge and advice on farm management, productivity and best practice around organic production; conducting a review on the applicability of ethical certification systems, such as Fair Trade;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Post-harvest operations&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. advising on the storage of crops post-harvest; methods of crop mechanisation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agro-processing&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. assess and review food processing techniques; advise on the potential to expand into new markets;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food security&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. knowledge of food security information systems and early warning systems; familiarity with the availability of various subsidies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agriculture education and curriculum development&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. understanding of agriculture issues in New Zealand; experience in delivering training courses and workshops;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trade and market analysis&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. capable of undertaking evidence-based analyses; establishing contact with key partners and stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**Duration of overall Panel contract: March 2014 - May 2016 (may be extended)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Experience &amp;amp; Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agricultural Experts with experience of working with MFAT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to enhance our Consultants&amp;#39; Database, HTSPE would like to hear from consultants with expertise in the above agriculture specialisms, and with experience of working with MFAT, who would be interested in assignments within this Panel Agreement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**Experience and Qualifications required&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum bachelor level degree;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly skilled agricultural professionals with experience in any of the aforementioned 16 specialisms;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A good understanding of agricultural practices in New Zealand;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong stakeholder management skills, with proven ability to identify stakeholder needs and achieve desired results;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working on donor-funded development programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of project management and the project life cycle;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working in the Asia-Pacific region;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in spoken and written English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Application Procedure&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for Panel assignments please email your CV to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:hr@htspe.com&quot;&gt;hr@htspe.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting &lt;strong&gt;2013127/AA/MFAT&lt;/strong&gt; in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We are only able to respond to candidates who meet the specifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
