<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 07:27:46 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tourism Spatial/ Physical Planning Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/tourism-spatial-physical-planning-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 07:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/tourism-spatial-physical-planning-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zambia National Tourism Master Plan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of this project is to develop a National Tourism Master Plan (NTMP) and subsidiary destination development and actions plans. The specific objective of this assignment is to analyse the current needs and challenges of the tourism sector in Zambia and, on this basis, develop a NTMP. The NTMP will define strategies and activities and provide distinct mapping that will catalyse the further development of the country’s tourism sector to promote local participation and development based on sustainable tourism principles and practices. Destination-Specific Development Plans have to be foreseen for the following areas:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Samfya Beach destination plan covering tourism assets in Samfya, Mansa and Kawambwa in Luapula Province. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kasaba Bay destination plan covering tourism assets in Kaputa, Kasama, Nsumbu National Park, Lake Tanganyika, Mbala areas. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;South and North Luangwa destination plan covering tourism assets in Mpika, Chama, Mfuwe, Lavushi Manda, South Luangwa, North Luangwa national parks and surrounding areas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lower Zambezi destination plan covering Lower Zambezi National Park, Chirundu, Luangwa Zambezi national park, Churundu, Siavonga, Lake Kariba and the surrounding areas. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Destination Lusaka development plan covering tourism assets related to Meetings, Incentives Conferences and Exhibition (MICE) wildlife, heritage museums, cultural centres/villages and art gallery. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zambezi source destination plan covering tourism assets on natural and cultural heritage, mining and sport in West-Lunga national park and the rest of North-Western and Copperbelt provinces (ie, Ikelegi, Solwezi, Zambezi, Kasempa, Chingola, Mufulila, Kitwe, Ndola). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key expert 2: Tourism Spatial/ Physical Planning Expert – 110 working days&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification and skills&lt;/strong&gt;: at least Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in tourism policy, tourism development planning and marketing or equivalent. In the absence of a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree, the expert must have an equivalent extra professional experience (two years) in the below mentioned sectors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;: at least 6 years of international experience in one or more of the following fields: physical planning for tourism; infrastructure planning and development; zoning, urban planning and economic development; land use analysis and experience working with national and local governments to formulate tourism development action plans in both urban and rural environments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;: Native English speaker or equivalent level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Desirable skills&lt;/strong&gt; among the following: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;tourism sector analysis;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;workshop planning and coordination, report writing, field activity coordination;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;product analysis and development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;marketing and creation of tourism zones;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;development of national sustainable tourism strategy, including natural and cultural tourism aspects and their particular sustainable development challenges, needs, and quality standards;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Environmental Impact Assessment processes and natural disaster risk management;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the assessment of revenue generation mechanisms; taxation and the creation of investment structures to enhance participation of local investors; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Streamlining both national and international interest in supporting additional investment to support enabling infrastructure developments already underway.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader/Sustainable Tourism Development Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-sustainable-tourism-development-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-sustainable-tourism-development-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zambia National Tourism Master Plan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of this project is to develop a National Tourism Master Plan (NTMP) and subsidiary destination development and actions plans. The specific objective of this assignment is to analyse the current needs and challenges of the tourism sector in Zambia and, on this basis, develop a NTMP. The NTMP will define strategies and activities and provide distinct mapping that will catalyse the further development of the country’s tourism sector to promote local participation and development based on sustainable tourism principles and practices. Destination-Specific Development Plans have to be foreseen for the following areas:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Samfya Beach destination plan covering tourism assets in Samfya, Mansa and Kawambwa in Luapula Province. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kasaba Bay destination plan covering tourism assets in Kaputa, Kasama, Nsumbu National Park, Lake Tanganyika, Mbala areas. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;South and North Luangwa destination plan covering tourism assets in Mpika, Chama, Mfuwe, Lavushi Manda, South Luangwa, North Luangwa national parks and surrounding areas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ower Zambezi destination plan covering Lower Zambezi National Park, Chirundu, Luangwa Zambezi national park, Churundu, Siavonga, Lake Kariba and the surrounding areas. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;estination Lusaka development plan covering tourism assets related to Meetings, Incentives Conferences and Exhibition (MICE) wildlife, heritage museums, cultural centres/villages and art gallery. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zambezi source destination plan covering tourism assets on natural and cultural heritage, mining and sport in West-Lunga national park and the rest of North-Western and Copperbelt provinces (ie, Ikelegi, Solwezi, Zambezi, Kasempa, Chingola, Mufulila, Kitwe, Ndola). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/technical-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2016 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/technical-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Paper for EPEC on the use of PPP’s for developing Port Infrastructure in Europe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EPEC seeks to undertake a critical review of the PPP models used in the publicly-owned port sector globally and their enabling (or impeding) conditions and to make an assessment as to whether the same or different structures (e.g. possible availability-based structures) could be used successfully in the EU. As part of the work, EPEC wishes to explore the potential opportunity to include the use of the blending of EU (mainly CEF1) grants with PPPs2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aim of this assignment is to deliver a Technical Paper than analyses and concludes on the aspects of PPP for port infrastructure, in such a way that EPEC will be in a position to provide relevant information and practical advice to its Members. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 3: Technical Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technical specialist, with at least 10 years of professional experience in planning and implementation of maritime transport infrastructure projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with European ports will be an additional merit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good English communication and writing skills, especially in report writing, are essential.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legal Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/legal-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2016 21:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/legal-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Paper for EPEC on the use of PPP’s for developing Port Infrastructure in Europe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EPEC seeks to undertake a critical review of the PPP models used in the publicly-owned port sector globally and their enabling (or impeding) conditions and to make an assessment as to whether the same or different structures (e.g. possible availability-based structures) could be used successfully in the EU. As part of the work, EPEC wishes to explore the potential opportunity to include the use of the blending of EU (mainly CEF1) grants with PPPs2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aim of this assignment is to deliver a Technical Paper than analyses and concludes on the aspects of PPP for port infrastructure, in such a way that EPEC will be in a position to provide relevant information and practical advice to its Members. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2: Legal Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Legal expert, with specific understanding of the international and local PPP laws, EU Directives and Regulations (also including Regulation on State Aid), as well as demonstrated experience (at least 10 years) with international infrastructure PPP and concession contracts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience and/or demonstrated understanding of the ownership and regulation regime of ports in Europe.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good English communication and writing skills, especially in report writing, are essential.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior PPP Expert (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-ppp-expert-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2016 20:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-ppp-expert-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Paper for EPEC on the use of PPP’s for developing Port Infrastructure in Europe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EPEC seeks to undertake a critical review of the PPP models used in the publicly-owned port sector globally and their enabling (or impeding) conditions and to make an assessment as to whether the same or different structures (e.g. possible availability-based structures) could be used successfully in the EU. As part of the work, EPEC wishes to explore the potential opportunity to include the use of the blending of EU (mainly CEF1) grants with PPPs2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aim of this assignment is to deliver a Technical Paper than analyses and concludes on the aspects of PPP for port infrastructure, in such a way that EPEC will be in a position to provide relevant information and practical advice to its Members. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 1: PPP Expert – Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in Finance, Management, Economics, Engineering or any other relevant field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 15 years’ demonstrated experience in providing advisory services to public authorities on the strategic development of large infrastructure projects on PPP basis including experience in project structuring and risk analysis, risk allocation and management; project financing and commercial appraisal; PPP structures; project agreements and related project documents. Successful preparation of PPP projects with at least three financially closed projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the European PPP sector will be an additional merit. Relevant qualifications and experience in the transport sector and experience in the ports sector will be additional merits, especially if associated to container terminals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent English communication and writing skills, especially in report writing, are essential.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Communications Expert (Cat. II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/communications-expert-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 12:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/communications-expert-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring and Visibility of Civil Society Facility Programme&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to promote the visibility and ensure effective implementation of the overall Civil Society Facility programme, as well as provide the overall guidance on key messages and coordinate the communication of all contracts of the programme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Promote public awareness on the role and importance of civil society and the actions implemented in the framework of this assistance through elaboration and assistance m implementation of Communication and Visibility Plan for the whole programme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ensure regular monitoring of the Programme performance and results, including monitoring of sub-granted projects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Communications Expert (Cat. II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MA degree or equivalent academic qualifications in public relations/communication
Or&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of professional experience (as defined below)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in spoken and written English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of the Armenian language is an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience in organising and managing communication activities, developing communication strategies and public infonnation campaigns;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience with and understanding of audio-visual production processes and social media communication  tools;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven   experience  in  drafting  information   material   in  a  journalistic   and   accessible language that demonstrates results;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good understanding of the Armenian  media landscape and communication channels used by professionals as well as by youth, male/female and urban/rural  audiences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring Expert (Cat. II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/monitoring-expert-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 12:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/monitoring-expert-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring and Visibility of Civil Society Facility Programme&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to promote the visibility and ensure effective implementation of the overall Civil Society Facility programme, as well as provide the overall guidance on key messages and coordinate the communication of all contracts of the programme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Promote public awareness on the role and importance of civil society and the actions implemented in the framework of this assistance through elaboration and assistance m implementation of Communication and Visibility Plan for the whole programme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ensure regular monitoring of the Programme performance and results, including monitoring of sub-granted projects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring Expert (Cat. II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree or equivalent  academic qualifications  in human  rights, democracy, good governance or related fields
Or&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years ofrelevant professional experience (as defined below)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability  to  analyze  data  and  recommend  appropriate  actions  and  to  prepare  reporting documents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and facilitation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of English, Armenian will be considered an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience  in monitoring/consultancy in capacity-development  programmes  in the areas of civil society, community development, policy monitoring/advocacy;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Project Cycle Management and Logical Framework approach&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A working knowledge of EU results-based monitoring methodology;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with financial management and accountability issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Civil Society Expert (Cat. II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/civil-society-expert-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 12:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/civil-society-expert-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring and Visibility of Civil Society Facility Programme&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to promote the visibility and ensure effective implementation of the overall Civil Society Facility programme, as well as provide the overall guidance on key messages and coordinate the communication of all contracts of the programme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Promote public awareness on the role and importance of civil society and the actions implemented in the framework of this assistance through elaboration and assistance m implementation of Communication and Visibility Plan for the whole programme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ensure regular monitoring of the Programme performance and results, including monitoring of sub-granted projects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Civil Society Expert (Cat. II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s  degree  or  equivalent   academic  qualifications   in  human   rights,  democratic governance and development, Political Science and other social sciences
Or&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of relevant professional experience (as defined below)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and facilitation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of English, Armenian will be considered an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional  Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous  experience  in  planning  and  implementing  CSO  capacity  building  activities  ts required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven  knowledge  of regulatory  framework  governing operation  of civil  society in Armenia
• Proven knowledge of current Armenian political and socio-economic environment, in particular relevant to civil society operation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LT-Capacity Building Expert (Cat. II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/lt-capacity-building-expert-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/lt-capacity-building-expert-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring and Visibility of Civil Society Facility Programme&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to promote the visibility and ensure effective implementation of the overall Civil Society Facility programme, as well as provide the overall guidance on key messages and coordinate the communication of all contracts of the programme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Promote public awareness on the role and importance of civil society and the actions implemented in the framework of this assistance through elaboration and assistance m implementation of Communication and Visibility Plan for the whole programme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ensure regular monitoring of the Programme performance and results, including monitoring of sub-granted projects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LT-Capacity Building Expert (Cat. II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s  degree  or  equivalent  academic  qualifications  m  management,  international relations or social sciences or related fields
Or&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of relevant professional experience (as defined below)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication  and facilitation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of written and spoken English and report writing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven knowledge of Project Cycle Management (PCM)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven  experience  in  designing  and  implementation   of  capacity  building  projects  m particular in areas related to civil society development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in setting up and managing expert teams;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Armenia will be considered an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of EU-Armenia relations and reforms will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 3 –  Financial planning expert  (Category III)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-3-financial-planning-expert-category-iii</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 10:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-3-financial-planning-expert-category-iii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective is to improve policy implementation at the centre of government, by establishing a strong link between the macroeconomic and fiscal scenario and structural reform agenda and establishing monitoring and reporting framework of the National Development Strategy 2016-2021 and Economic Reform Programme. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support to the OPM/SPO, MoF and line ministries in the process of outlining implementation arrangements of the National Development Strategy, and ensuring that they are presented into the annual work plan of the government and the Economic Reform Programme. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support the National ERP Coordinator and its coordination structures towards improving the link between the macroeconomic and fiscal scenario and the structural reform agenda, which includes costing of reform measures, and their integration in the fiscal framework as well as elaborating in detail their expected outcome or impact. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least Master degree in financial or economic sciences; or&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Bachelor degree in financial or economic sciences with 5 year of experience (in addition to the minimum number of years required under general professional experience below); or in absence of a degree &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• 7 years of experience in financial or economic sciences (in addition to the minimum number of years required under general professional experience below).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 3 years preferable 5 years of professional experience in the field of financial or economic sciences. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 2 projects preferable 4 projects  in addressing links between national policies and budget planning &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 1 year preferable 3 years of experience in implementing programs in the area of  public finance management or economic programs &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expert must be proficient in report drafting in English.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail:%20Veronica_Hernandez-Castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;Veronica_Hernandez-Castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 2 – Policy planning and Monitoring and Evaluation expert (Category III)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-policy-planning-and-monitoring-and-evaluation-expert-category-iii</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 10:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-policy-planning-and-monitoring-and-evaluation-expert-category-iii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective is to improve policy implementation at the centre of government, by establishing a strong link between the macroeconomic and fiscal scenario and structural reform agenda and establishing monitoring and reporting framework of the National Development Strategy 2016-2021 and Economic Reform Programme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support to the OPM/SPO, MoF and line ministries in the process of outlining implementation arrangements of the National Development Strategy, and ensuring that they are presented into the annual work plan of the government and the Economic Reform Programme. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support the National ERP Coordinator and its coordination structures towards improving the link between the macroeconomic and fiscal scenario and the structural reform agenda, which includes costing of reform measures, and their integration in the fiscal framework as well as elaborating in detail their expected outcome or impact.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Qualification and skills *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least Master degree in social, political, or economic sciences; or&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Bachelor degree in social, political, or economic sciences with 5 year of experience (in addition to the minimum number of years required under general professional experience below); or in absence of a degree &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• 7 years of experience in social, political, or economic sciences (in addition to the minimum number of years required under general professional experience below).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 3 years preferable 5 years of professional experience in the field of social, or economic sciences. 
Specific professional experience&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 2 years preferable 3 years of professional experience in the monitoring and evaluation, research and policy formulation and dialogue. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 1 year preferable 3 years of experience in implementing programs in the area of economic reforms. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expert must be proficient in report drafting in English.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail:%20Veronica_Hernandez-Castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;Veronica_Hernandez-Castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader – Strategic planning and Policy Development at central level (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-strategic-planning-and-policy-development-at-central-level-category-i-1</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-strategic-planning-and-policy-development-at-central-level-category-i-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective is to improve policy implementation at the centre of government, by establishing a strong link between the macroeconomic and fiscal scenario and structural reform agenda and establishing monitoring and reporting framework of the National Development Strategy 2016-2021 and Economic Reform Programme. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support to the OPM/SPO, MoF and line ministries in the process of outlining implementation arrangements of the National Development Strategy, and ensuring that they are presented into the annual work plan of the government and the Economic Reform Programme. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support the National ERP Coordinator and its coordination structures towards improving the link between the macroeconomic and fiscal scenario and the structural reform agenda, which includes costing of reform measures, and their integration in the fiscal framework as well as elaborating in detail their expected outcome or impact.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Qualification and skills *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least Master degree in social, political, or economic sciences; or&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Bachelor degree in social, political, or economic sciences with 3 year of experience (in addition to the minimum number of years required under general professional experience below); or in absence of a degree &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• 7 years of experience in social, political, or economic sciences (in addition to the minimum number of years required under general professional experience below)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 12 years preferable 15 years of professional experience in the field of social, political, or economic sciences. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 3 years preferable 6 years of professional experience in the management position or team leader position. 
• At least 2 years preferable 4 years of experience in policy planning and coordination, policy formulation, including budgetary impact assessment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 1 project preferably 3 projects related to building monitoring and evaluation systems. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expert must be proficient in report drafting in English.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail:%20Veronica_Hernandez-Castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;Veronica_Hernandez-Castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert No. 2 (Category I expert) - Expert in the field of PPP and delivery of trainings</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-no-2-category-i-expert-expert-in-the-field-of-ppp-and-delivery-of-trainings</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 08:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-no-2-category-i-expert-expert-in-the-field-of-ppp-and-delivery-of-trainings</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the contract is to improve the general conditions in the Beneficiary country for more successful implementation of the Law on Public-Private Partnership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The specific objective of this assignment is Harmonization of the Law on Public-Private Partnership with the latest available EU Directive;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strengthen the administrative capacities of the Ministry of Economy as the final beneficiary of the project, as well as the other National and Local Authorities and the private sector for implementation of the legal framework for Public-Private Partnership.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Expert No. 2 will be in charge of preparing the materials, organizing and delivering trainings in the field of PPP, mainly for the tasks envisaged in Activity 1.2 and Activity 2, as he/she will also assist the Expert No.1 (Team Leader) in preparation of the Guide for implementation of the PPP. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least Master Degree  Academic level in Business Administration, law, economic or engineering, or in its absence, 3 years of general professional experience above the minimum general professional experience requested below. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Minimum 12 years of general professional experience in the area of PPP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience in at least 3 years of delivering trainings in the fields of PPP;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience in at least one (1) International/EU funded project in the area of PPP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail:%20CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert No. 1 (Category I expert /Team Leader) Legal approximation Expert in the field of PPP</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-no-1-category-i-expert-team-leader-legal-approximation-expert-in-the-field-of-ppp</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 08:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-no-1-category-i-expert-team-leader-legal-approximation-expert-in-the-field-of-ppp</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the contract is to improve the general conditions in the Beneficiary country for more successful implementation of the Law on Public-Private Partnership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The specific objective of this assignment is Harmonization of the Law on Public-Private Partnership with the latest available EU Directive;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strengthen the administrative capacities of the Ministry of Economy as the final beneficiary of the project, as well as the other National and Local Authorities and the private sector for implementation of the legal framework for Public-Private Partnership.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Legal approximation expert in the field of public private partnership will act as a Team leader, thus he/she will be responsible for day to day exercises, making sure that the objectives and outputs of the Project are being met and Project activities delivered. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Team Leader also has to play a key role with respect to outreach, information sharing, public visibility, and liaising with other technical assistance initiatives. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an expert in the field of public - private partnership he/she has to be working on the activities 1 – Assessment and harmonization of the legislation on concessions and public private partnership compatible with EU legislation and activity - Sub-activity 1.1: Analysis of the current situation regarding PPP and Activity - 2- Preparation of Guide for implementation of the public private partnership compatible with EU legislation and to coordinate the other activity regarding the development of the Institutional capacity of the Legal Department - Unit for normative and legal affairs in area of Public-Private partnership and Concession and ensure that the functions and the legal provisions are commensurate with the requirements detailed in the public - private partnership system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least Master Degree  Academic level in law, or in its absence, 3 years of general professional experience above the minimum general professional experience requested below. 
General professional experience &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Minimum 12 years of experience in commercial Law;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 5 years of experience in the area of PPP legislation; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience in at least two (2) EU funded projects in the area of PPP;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience in at least one (1) project aimed on drafting or preparation of legislative documents (Law/Bylaw/Guidelines/Manuals etc.) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language and computer literacy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Fluent in oral and written English;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Computer literacy&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail:%20CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Profil de l&#39;expert 2,  – catégorie 1 (12 ans d&#39;expérience au moins)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/profil-de-lexpert-2-categorie-1-12-ans-dexperience-au-moins</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 08:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/profil-de-lexpert-2-categorie-1-12-ans-dexperience-au-moins</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif global est de contribuer à la conservation de la biodiversité et des services écosystémiques pour un développement durable en Afrique de l’Ouest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif spécifique est de renforcer durablement la conservation des écosystèmes du complexe WAP (W, Pendjari, Arly) dans une perspective régionale et avec optimisation des bénéfices pour la population riveraine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deux experts de catégorie 1 pour 47 jours prestés chacun dont 10 jours prestés chacun dans leur pays. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;expert 2 aura un diplôme d&amp;#39;enseignement supérieur dans un des domaines suivants : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sciences agronomiques, forestières, biologiques ou socio-économiques (ou équivalent), 
L&amp;#39;expert devra posséder au moins 12 ans  d&amp;#39;expérience en coopération au développement. 
Il devra posséder une excellente connaissance et pratique en gestion du cycle de projet / approche cadre logique. 
Il devra posséder une bonne connaissance des cadres institutionnels des pays africains en matière de gestion de l&amp;#39;environnement. 
L&amp;#39;expert devra maîtriser le français à l&amp;#39;écrit et à l&amp;#39;oral. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;expert devra avoir les expériences spécifiques minimales suivantes : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir travaillé au moins cinq ans sur un ou des projets liés à la conservation de la nature / biodiversité ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir réalisé au moins 2 études de formulation ou identification dans le domaine de la protection de l&amp;#39;environnement. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir réalisé au moins 3 évaluations externes (ex-ante, à mi-parcours ou finale)

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir travaillé au moins deux ans le contexte Ouest Africain ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Une expérience spécifique dans les domaines suivants est un plus : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;au moins trois ans sur un ou des projets de développement de capacités institutionnelles, en lien avec le développement local ou le développement rural (environnement, agriculture, élevage, agroforesterie), et &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir travaillé avec les organismes régionaux du type de l&amp;#39;UEMOA ou de la CEDEAO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail:%20CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Profil de l&#39;expert 1, Chef de mission  – catégorie 1 (12 ans d&#39;expérience au moins)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/profil-de-lexpert-1-chef-de-mission-categorie-1-12-ans-dexperience-au-moins</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 08:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/profil-de-lexpert-1-chef-de-mission-categorie-1-12-ans-dexperience-au-moins</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif global est de contribuer à la conservation de la biodiversité et des services écosystémiques pour un développement durable en Afrique de l’Ouest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif spécifique est de renforcer durablement la conservation des écosystèmes du complexe WAP (W, Pendjari, Arly) dans une perspective régionale et avec optimisation des bénéfices pour la population riveraine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deux experts de catégorie 1 pour 47 jours prestés chacun dont 10 jours prestés chacun dans leur pays. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Profil de l&amp;#39;expert 1, Chef de mission  – catégorie 1 (12 ans d&amp;#39;expérience au moins)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;expert doit posséder au moins un diplôme d&amp;#39;enseignement supérieur dans un des domaines suivants : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agronomie, foresterie, environnement / ressources naturelles (ou équivalent)
L&amp;#39;expert devra posséder au moins 12 ans d&amp;#39;expérience dans l&amp;#39;appui aux politiques, programmes ou de projets de développement. 
Il devra posséder une excellente connaissance et pratique en gestion du cycle de projet / approche cadre logique. 
Il devra posséder une très bonne connaissance théorique et pratique des procédures du FED. 
L&amp;#39;expert devra maîtriser le français à l&amp;#39;écrit et à l&amp;#39;oral, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;expert devra avoir les expériences spécifiques minimales suivantes : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir travaillé au moins cinq ans sur un ou des projets liés à la conservation de la nature / biodiversité;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir réalisé au moins 2 études de formulation ou identification dans le domaine de la protection de l&amp;#39;environnement. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir réalisé au moins 5 évaluations externes (ex-ante, à mi-parcours ou finale), dont au moins 3 financées par la Commission Européenne (FED ou BUDGET), dont au moins une évaluation sur un projet régional. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir travaillé au moins deux ans dans le contexte Ouest Africain ou d&amp;#39;une autre région africaine;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Une expérience spécifique dans les domaines suivants est un plus : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;au moins trois ans sur un ou des projets de développement, en lien avec le développement local ou le développement rural (environnement, agriculture, élevage, agroforesterie), et &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir une expérience plus large en &amp;ldquo;approche cadre logique / gestion du cycle de projet / intégration de l&amp;#39;environnement&amp;rdquo;. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir travaillé avec une ou des Communautés Economiques Régionales africaine du type de l&amp;#39;UEMOA ou de la CEDEAO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir une expérience avec le Programme des Nations Unies pour le Développement (PNUD/UNDP)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail:%20CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMarina_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert III (Communication Expert, Cat.II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-iii-communication-expert-catii</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-iii-communication-expert-catii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to strengthen the role and coordination of the Ministry for EU Affairs (MEU) in capacity building of local grassroots NGOs and strengthening public-Civil Society Organizations (CSO) cooperation at local level in accordance with EU accession process. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specifically the objective are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To increase awareness in local actors such as civil society organizations (particularly grassroots) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To implement pilot schemes for the strategies developed by the Ministry for EU Affairs at local level,&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To develop the capacity of local actors especially the civil society organizations in Antalya and İzmir concerning the EU process and the access to EU funds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responsible for the implementation of all communication activities as well as the preparation of all visibility materials. He/she will support the Team Leader as necessary in the promotional and networking aspects of the activities. Each activity will include a communication aspect thus the communication expert shall be available for all contracting period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Qualifications and Skills:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least Master’s degree or equivalent in Communication or Public Relations or Social Sciences or equivalent. In the absence of the required degree, minimum 11 years of working experience in the field of communication is requested.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Good command of spoken and written English.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 6 years of experience in the field of communication.
Specific Professional Experience &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 2 work experiences in EU projects as a Communication or Public Relations (PR) expert.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 5 experiences in designing or preparation of PR publications (such as poster, brochure, flyer, newsletter, compendium etc.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Work experience involving local administrations and other local actors in Turkey will be an asset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail:%20veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert II (Civil Society Expert, Cat.II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-ii-civil-society-expert-catii</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 08:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-ii-civil-society-expert-catii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to strengthen the role and coordination of the Ministry for EU Affairs (MEU) in capacity building of local grassroots NGOs and strengthening public-Civil Society Organizations (CSO) cooperation at local level in accordance with EU accession process. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specifically the objective are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To increase awareness in local actors such as civil society organizations (particularly grassroots) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To implement pilot schemes for the strategies developed by the Ministry for EU Affairs at local level,&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To develop the capacity of local actors especially the civil society organizations in Antalya and İzmir concerning the EU process and the access to EU funds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responsible for the implementation of “Activity B.1.2. Capacity Building Training for Civil Society Organizations”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Qualifications and Skills:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least Master’s degree. In the absence of the required degree at least 11 years of professional experience the area relevant to the assignment is requested,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Good command of spoken and written English,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 6 years of experience in the sector(s) related to the lot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*Specific Professional Experience *&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 3 work experiences in the fields of civil society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 5 experiences as a trainer in the field of civil society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience in preparation of a training module in the field of civil society will be an asset. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Consulting experience working with Civil Society Organizations will be an asset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail:%20veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert I (Team Leader, Cat. II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-i-team-leader-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 08:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-i-team-leader-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to strengthen the role and coordination of the Ministry for EU Affairs (MEU) in capacity building of local grassroots NGOs and strengthening public-Civil Society Organizations (CSO) cooperation at local level in accordance with EU accession process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specifically the objective are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To increase awareness in local actors such as civil society organizations (particularly grassroots) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To implement pilot schemes for the strategies developed by the Ministry for EU Affairs at local level,&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To develop the capacity of local actors especially the civil society organizations in Antalya and İzmir concerning the EU process and the access to EU funds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responsible for general coordination of project activities, project management and implementation, thus he/she will ensure coordination among other experts and backstopping team. Team Leader will mainly be responsible for each activity and preparation of the reports (inception and final reports). Team Leader will specifically deal with Training for Project Cycle Management. Team Leader will also responsible for checking the outputs and indicators are in accordance with the ToR and the work schedule. He/she shall act as the main counterpart to the MEU in relation to the performance of project activities. He/she will be responsible for the efficient and effective financing management monitoring and the project implementation in line with EU procedures and this ToR.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Qualifications and Skills:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least Master’s degree. In the absence of the required degree, at least 11 years of work experience in the area relevant to assignment is requested.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Good command of spoken and written English.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Turkish language will be an asset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 6 years of experience in the sector(s) related to the lot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*Specific Professional Experience *&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 3 experiences as team leader or project manager or other managerial positions in   EU projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Work experience as a trainer on PCM in at least 3 trainings for EU-funded programmes or projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail:%20veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ASiST Programme</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/asist-programme-1</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 14:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/asist-programme-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Purpose of role&lt;/strong&gt;
DAI’s ASiST programme is an advisory service for the European Commission rural development, food security and nutrition directorate (unit C1) within the Directorate General for Development and Cooperation (DEVCO). ASiST aims at providing support to identify and fine-tune tools to achieve the strategic objectives of food and nutrition security and sustainable agriculture in developing countries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ASiST Coordinator will provide direct hands-on support to the Team Leader and C1 Programme Manager to coordinate efficient delivery across the repertoire of ASiST technical and operational tasks. The role will add further value to ASiST by supporting a number of new or expanded functions, including: (i) coordinating a new technical help desk service; (ii) servicing ASiST’s knowledge management systems; and (iii) strengthening coordination and communications with internal and external stakeholders. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key tasks and responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;General operational support&lt;/em&gt;
• Routine support to the full complement of programme activities under the supervision of the Team Leader and DEVCO C1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Regular liaison with the DEVCO C1 Programme Manager and core team to ensure efficient and effective activity coordination, including through attending in-person meetings at DEVCO headquarters on a flexible basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Service and participate in ASiST’s frequent meetings and events, including organising venues, attendance lists, agendas, minute taking, circulating and monitoring agreed follow-up actions. These events include regular strategy meetings with DEVCO and the ASiST team as well as a range of conferences, presentations, roundtables, etc involving other DEVCO units, services and partners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Direct support to delivery of ASiST technical services. These include quality assurance of reports, research, studies, etc relating to ASiST’s core technical themes as well as an often significant volume of demand-driven requests from DEVCO and EU Delegations. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Play an active role in programme process planning and improvement initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Communication and collaboration&lt;/strong&gt;
• Serve as the coordination point to facilitate ongoing technical and thematic collaboration with other relevant DEVCO units and services (such as NAS and FANSSA) around key topics and activities of mutual relevance;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Support the team to continually promote ASiST, EU and thematic visibility, including through developing and disseminating communications materials, maintaining newsletters, etc;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Manage ASiST’s knowledge management systems, including: coordinating and disseminating regular knowledge products; helping DEVCO C1 in organising EU InfoPoint debriefings; taking the lead role in managing ASiST content on the Capacity4Dev portal. With the latter, the junior expert will be in charge of collecting contributions from ASiST experts after each mission and updating Capacity4Dev by writing blog posts on specific insights and writing briefs to illustrate social transfer instruments and issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Responsible for helping the Team Leader to explore and develop innovative ways of exchanging information and learning with C1 and EUDs around key themes and services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ASiST Helpdesk coordination&lt;/strong&gt;
• Work with the team to set up and manage the ASiST helpdesk, including receiving, fielding and coordinating enquiries and responses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications, knowledge, skills and experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/em&gt;
• Minimum Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in a relevant field or equivalent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience in coordinating projects and activities operating across multiple locations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience with project communications and knowledge management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience in providing quality assurance to reports and proofing reports or written products for development agencies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Excellent written and verbal communication skills in both English and French.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Strong organisational skills with excellent attention to detail.
• Proactive, resourceful, team player and able to independently manage complex tasks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Excellent interpersonal skills – able to establish and maintain positive working relationships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• A strong client-service delivery approach to delivering tasks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Ability to work under pressure and to tight deadlines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• MS Office expertise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;
• Minimum 5 years of professional experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Previous experience working with European Union Delegations and DEVCO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;
• Minimum 5 years of professional experience in one of the following thematic areas: food security, nutrition, resilience, sustainable agriculture, rural development, social transfers. Field experience would be an advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Demonstrable understanding of DEVCO, EUD processes and PRAG rules.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience working with EU-funded projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience working in international development cooperation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV to &lt;a href=&quot;mail:%20penny_buckle@dai.com&quot;&gt;penny_buckle@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
