<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2014 11:47:40 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poverty Reduction Specialist — Cat. II</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/poverty-reduction-specialist-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2014 11:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/poverty-reduction-specialist-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The objectives of the Final evaluation of the AMSP 2010 Social Mitigation Programme are to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make an independent assessment of the performance of the AMSP 2010 contribution &amp;ldquo;to mitigate the adverse effects of the EU sugar price reform and the overall decline of the sugar industry for the most disadvantaged groups&amp;rdquo;.and &amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;to identify socioeconomic needs and validate alternative local development strategies for the most affected populations&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Draw key lessons and recommendation for possible follow up actions by the EU, the Government of Fiji and other partners involved in the programme.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Poverty Reduction Specialist — Cat. II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree (MSc or more) in Socio-Economics for Rural Development or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NGO&amp;rsquo;s implemented development programmes, vocational training, housing and micro-projects and microfinance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gender and Youth in Development issues, participatory approach and consultation with NGOs/CSOs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 5 years in socio-economics studies and experience of social dimension of industry restructuring&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience in Small Islands Developing State&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience in Pacific/Figi context an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Agro-Economist (TL) – Cat. I </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-agro-economist-tl-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2014 11:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-agro-economist-tl-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The objectives of the Final evaluation of the AMSP 2010 Social Mitigation Programme are to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make an independent assessment of the performance of the AMSP 2010 contribution &amp;ldquo;to mitigate the adverse effects of the EU sugar price reform and the overall decline of the sugar industry for the most disadvantaged groups&amp;rdquo;.and &amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;to identify socioeconomic needs and validate alternative local development strategies for the most affected populations&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Draw key lessons and recommendation for possible follow up actions by the EU, the Government of Fiji and other partners involved in the programme.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Agro-Economist (TL) – Cat. I&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A university degree (MSc or more) in Agricultural economics, Economics for rural development or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10 years of relevant international experience in developing countries in the context of rural development/agriculture/management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The expert must have experience in participatory programme/project evaluation and must be familiar with the concept and implementation of EU funded projects. The expert is expected to have professional experience in the evaluation of development projects for international aid donors and to be fully familiar with the Commission&amp;rsquo;s Project Cycle Management and Logical Framework Approach as well as EU evaluation methodology. Project Management at senior level on similar programmes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent computer and communication skills (both oral and written English).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following experience would be an asset:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience as Team Leader&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience in small island developing states.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluation of other AMSP would be an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expertise&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agriculture and rural development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SME development and Civil Society Organisations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;EU Evaluation methodology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junior Resettlement Expert  with experience of Cambodia land projects (Category II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-resettlement-expert-with-experience-of-cambodia-land-projects-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2014 10:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-resettlement-expert-with-experience-of-cambodia-land-projects-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The objective of this contract is to develop an inception report for the assessment that will identify and reconcile disputed claims in relation to the sugarcane plantations in Cambodia, and the monitoring of potential remedial action measures. The Inception Report will include the prioritization of the locations, the methodology, clear timelines for the remainder of the process, as well as, a communication strategy and a set of performance indicators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Junior Resettlement Expert  with experience of Cambodia land projects (Category II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Masters Degree, as attested by a recognised diploma in a relevant field (such as law, land planning, socio-economics, development economics, political science or international relations etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific experience in resettlement projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven related expertise with complex multi stakeholder land disputes, in developing country contexts;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in community facilitation, conflict resolution, and communications, in South East Asia;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven familiarity with relevant international standards, including IFC Performance Standard 5;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent interpersonal relationship skills and be able to collaborate in a neutral and diplomatic manner with public bodies, civil society, and the communities in a sensitive environment;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in carrying out assignments for the EU or other equivalent international development partners will be considered an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific experience in and knowledge of Cambodia in land related projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Resettlement Expert with experience in SE Asia (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-resettlement-expert-with-experience-in-se-asia-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2014 10:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-resettlement-expert-with-experience-in-se-asia-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this contract is to develop an inception report for the assessment that will identify and reconcile disputed claims in relation to the sugarcane plantations in Cambodia, and the monitoring of potential remedial action measures. The Inception Report will include the prioritization of the locations, the methodology, clear timelines for the remainder of the process, as well as, a communication strategy and a set of performance indicators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Resettlement Expert with experience in SE Asia (TL)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Masters’ Degree, as attested by a recognised diploma in a relevant field (such as law, land planning, socio-economics, development economics, political science or international relations, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Internationally renowned resettlement expert with extensive experience in the design, implementation, and/or monitoring and evaluation of resettlement projects in developing countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven related expertise with complex multi stakeholder land disputes at high seniority level;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven familiarity with relevant international standards, including IFC Performance Standard 5;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent interpersonal relationship skills and be able to collaborate in a neutral and diplomatic manner with public bodies, civil society, and the communities in a sensitive environment;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in carrying out assignments for the EU or other equivalent international development partners, will be considered an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific experience in, and knowledge of, Southeast Asia and in particular Cambodia will be considered an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Expert should have a high level of proficiency in spoken and written English. Proficiency in Khmer will be considered an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experts in Design of Agriculture (particularly vegetable production) Initiatives – SE Asia context</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-in-design-of-agriculture-particularly-vegetable-production-initiatives-se-asia-context</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2014 12:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-in-design-of-agriculture-particularly-vegetable-production-initiatives-se-asia-context</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;New Zealand is currently implementing an activity in &lt;strong&gt;Binh Dinh Province, Viet Nam&lt;/strong&gt;, aimed at linking poor rural households to markets.  One objective of this current activity is to increase the volume of certified safe vegetables supplied to local markets and to markets outside Binh Dinh in order to improve economic returns to farmers and to safeguard human and environmental health in the Province.  It has become evident that the ability of farmers to comply with the current certification process (VietGAP) presents challenges and a new approach to vegetable production, post-harvest handling and marketing could be useful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This assignment will be completed in two phases: &lt;strong&gt;Phase One&lt;/strong&gt; is to undertake field work and in-country consultation to design the Activity, based on the terms of reference and produce an &lt;strong&gt;Activity Design Document&lt;/strong&gt; (ADD).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proceeding to &lt;strong&gt;Phase Two&lt;/strong&gt; will be at the sole discretion of MFAT.  Should it proceed, implementation of the activity will begin in the second quarter of 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experts in Design of Agriculture (particularly vegetable production) Initiatives – SE Asia context&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Applicants must be able to demonstrate the following minimum knowledge, skills and experience which are required to deliver this assignment:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An understanding of Viet Nam and the political context and agriculture systems;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the design and implementation of agriculture (particularly vegetable production) initiatives in a development context and preferably in South East Asia;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to deliver high quality outputs to time;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to lead others and to confidently engage, and gain the respect of, senior officials and a range of stakeholders in a cross-cultural setting;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong commitment to participation of key stakeholders;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong proven organizational and logistical skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent English, written and cross-cultural communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, the following attributes will be considered an advantage:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience of working with &lt;strong&gt;MFAT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tertiary qualification in a relevant discipline&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting the job title in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Due to high volumes of applications, only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert(e) Electoral(e) (Catégorie II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-electorale-categorie-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2014 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-electorale-categorie-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Contribuer à la mise en place d’un système efficient de gestion financière du processus électoral en vue de la maîtrise des coûts de la préparation et de l’organisation des élections au Bénin et de la pérennisation de ses instruments dans le cadre législatif existant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert(e) Electoral(e) (Catégorie II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formation et connaissances linguistiques :&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formation supérieure en sciences humaines et/ou politiques ou équivalent sanctionnée par un diplôme de niveau universitaire bac + 5 ou équivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Toute formation complémentaire dans le domaine de la planification et suivi des élections sera appréciée comme un atout complémentaire.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise parfaite des logiciels informatiques les plus courants (traitement de texte et tableur).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise parfaite du français.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle :&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle d&amp;#39;au moins 6 ans dans le domaine de la planification, suivi et analyse de processus électoraux ou équivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle dans le domaine dans les pays en voie de développement d&amp;#39;au moins 6 missions ou 2 ans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Toute expérience professionnelle le domaine de missions d&amp;#39;observation électorale élections ou équivalent sera appréciée.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicolas_fichers@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicolas_fichers@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert(e) Planificateur – Economiste (chef d'équipe) (Catégorie II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-planificateur-economiste-chef-dequipe-categorie-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2014 10:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-planificateur-economiste-chef-dequipe-categorie-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Contribuer à la mise en place d’un système efficient de gestion financière du processus électoral en vue de la maîtrise des coûts de la préparation et de l’organisation des élections au Bénin et de la pérennisation de ses instruments dans le cadre législatif existant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert(e) Planificateur – Economiste (chef d&amp;#39;équipe) (Catégorie II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formation et connaissances linguistiques :&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formation supérieure d’économiste ou équivalent sanctionnée par un diplôme de niveau universitaire bac + 5 ou équivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Toute formation complémentaire dans le domaine de la planification institutionnelle et budgétaire sera appréciée comme un atout complémentaire.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise parfaite des logiciels informatiques les plus courants (traitement de texte et tableur).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise parfaite du français.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle :&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle d&amp;#39;au moins 6 ans dans le domaine de l’analyse et planification institutionnelle et budgétaire ou équivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle dans le domaine dans les pays en voie de développement d&amp;#39;au moins 6 missions ou 2 ans.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Toute expérience professionnelle dans le domaine de planification, suivi et analyse électoraux ou équivalent sera appréciée.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicolas_fichers@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicolas_fichers@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWP 2 Projects Review</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Beyond WTO Program (B-WTO) was developed in response to a request from the Government of Vietnam (GoV) for donor support to help with managing economic integration and the transition to a market economy following WTO accession. The B-WTO goal is “to strengthen government’s capacity to manage the integration of Vietnam into the global economy and the transition of Vietnam to a socialist market economy”. The immediate objective is “implementation of priority policy actions from the GoV’s Action Plan to enhance Vietnam’s capacity to sustain pro-poor growth (GAP)”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The remit of this project was a review of the 2nd annual work plan’s implementation (AWP2) of Phase 2 of the B-WTO in May 2013. The objectives of the review were to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the project implementation performance and project results relative to the logical framework targets and evaluation criteria. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the results achieved at the Component and Program’s level according to the Monitoring and Evaluation (M&amp;amp;E) framework of the Program.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify lessons learned from implementation, make recommendations for the remaining duration of the program and the Independent Completion Report process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program 2013 Performance and Quality Mapping Exercise</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID’s PNG Program is looking to improve its performance and quality (P&amp;amp;Q) standards and systems. The purpose of this project was to map the PNG Program’s current P&amp;amp;Q capacity and systems, to address the risk of AusAID being unable to demonstrate results for its increased investments in PNG over the next four years. Over the last several years, the PNG Program has undertaken a number of M&amp;amp;E assessments and reviews which have identified key strengths and challenges within the program. This project was intended to pick up where these assessments left off. Through a desk review and consultations with sector teams, the Review Team were to distil key P&amp;amp;Q risks and issues for the PNG Program. The Review Team’s brief included the provision of recommendations on priority activities to support sector approaches to M&amp;amp;E, strengthen the Program’s ability to collect evidence, provide critical analysis and report on results.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID required a consultant to assist with the development and finalisation of its Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework. Development of a humanitarian monitoring and evaluation framework is a key commitment outlined in AusAID’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy (HAP) and its associated Implementation Plan. In line with the agency focus on results reporting, the HAP and HAP Implementation Plan commit AusAID to develop a monitoring and evaluation framework to support the initial performance assessment framework contained within the HAP and AusAID annual reporting under the Comprehensive Aid Policy Framework.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key objective of this assignment was to build the Humanitarian program’s capacity for monitoring and reporting results by:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In consultation with AusAID’s Humanitarian team, redraft and finalise the Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework, to ensure it provides a platform to:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track implementation of key commitments in Australia’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy; and,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish a set of measurable humanitarian performance indicators (in addition to the two CAPF indicators) to enable AusAID to track achievements, lessons learned and to report on the results achieved from AusAID’s humanitarian work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of Pacific Forum Compact Reporting</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The purpose of the assignment was to examine country views of aid effectiveness and regional organisations expressed through Forum Compact reporting, particularly peer review of Forum Island Countries’ national development plan processes. The services provided included the preparation of a think piece which outlines key aid effectiveness issues arising from country reporting under the Compact reporting and discusses options for addressing these issues.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study on Community-based Social Protection</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/study-on-community-based-social-protection</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/study-on-community-based-social-protection</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Poverty and Social Analysis is the process of using and generating evidence on poverty throughout the aid management cycle. Most poverty and social analysis focuses on economic and human capital, but there are two oft neglected elements: voice and influence, and social capital. Yet more and more development practitioners are recognizing the importance of social capital, particularly informal social capital, in preventing and addressing poverty and vulnerability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This project supported AusAID to explore:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the role of informal social capital in the Fijian context and whether it lends itself to fair redistribution of resources and, if so, the ways in which AusAID can engage with local communities to strengthen existing social capital structures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;how such structures can enable the disempowered and poor to claim their entitlements in the three domains discussed in the PSA framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the potential challenges that can arise from such efforts. For instance, the poorest are often included on less favorable terms within social networks, and have access to fewer and lower-quality networks. Further, we need to better understand how poverty and disempowerment intersect with an absence of informal social capital, the repercussions this has, and the options available for tackling this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Provision of a Child Protection Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/provision-of-a-child-protection-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/provision-of-a-child-protection-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For this project HTSPE was contracted to provide a child protection specialist and handle all the associated management and administrative work. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The child protection specialist provided by HTSPE was required to work on an assignment designed to assist the Pacific Division (PACD) to improve its approach to child protection and managing risks to children. AusAID has a number of partners in the Pacific who work with children or come into contact with children through their activities. The AusAID-wide child protection stocktake, conducted in May 2013 found that there are a number of organisations funded by AusAID in the Pacific with a high or very high inherent child protection risk. Consistent with the stocktake report PACD proposes to escalate efforts to ensure partner organisations policies, procedures and practices are in accordance with AusAID’s Child Protection Policy 2013 and to make child protection a more explicit focus of PACD’s risk management system.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extractives for Growth Program (E4G) – M&amp;E Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/extractives-for-growth-program-e4g-me-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 06:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/extractives-for-growth-program-e4g-me-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As part of the Department of Foreign Affairs and Trade’s (DFAT) consolidated Sub-Saharan African Aid program, Extractives for Growth (E4G) will be one of three key components. Through E4G, Australia will focus its assistance in three areas where the greatest potential for generating shared value between governments, communities and industry exists: skills development; extractives and communities; and the enabling environment. These are areas that: represent major risks for the private sector; are key to governments leveraging maximum development value from their extractives resources; will determine the employment and livelihood benefits that flow to communities; and require (and provide opportunities for) partnerships between governments, industry and communities to find solutions. The new program will harness Australia’s extractives-related expertise (private sector, government, non-government organisation, research and training). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;E4G will focus on &lt;strong&gt;three target countries (Tanzania, Zambia and Mozambique)&lt;/strong&gt; where Australia can maximise development benefits, and where there is a commitment by the government and private sector to improve the social benefits and economic growth opportunities from a well-managed and transparent extractives sector. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, ‘enabling environment’ activities will be conducted in 8-10 countries in Sub-Saharan Africa. These countries are likely to include Madagascar, South Africa, Ethiopia, Ghana and Nigeria, with the remainder yet to be determined.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Extractives for Growth Program (E4G) – M&amp;amp;E Specialist&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in associated discipline will provide a considerable advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven communication and negotiation skills and an ability to work in a variety of cultural settings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English. Proficiency in French and Portuguese will be considered an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills and an ability to work with a wide range of stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to deliver long-term development programs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 5 years in Monitoring and Evaluation, preferably in the field of extractives and natural resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of experience working in Sub-Saharan Africa&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in the extractives and natural resources fields is desirable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous work with the Department of Foreign Affairs and Trade’s (DFAT) is also desirable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please send your CV to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:brian_green@dai.com&quot;&gt;brian_green@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;. Due to the high number of applicants, if you have not been contacted by the application closing date then please assume your application has been unsuccessful. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;&lt;strong&gt;Please note that all profiles are indicative only and therefore subject to change once the ToR is made available&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extractives for Growth Program (E4G) – Operations Manager</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/extractives-for-growth-program-e4g-operations-manager</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 06:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/extractives-for-growth-program-e4g-operations-manager</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As part of the Department of Foreign Affairs and Trade’s (DFAT) consolidated Sub-Saharan African Aid program, Extractives for Growth (E4G) will be one of three key components. Through E4G, Australia will focus its assistance in three areas where the greatest potential for generating shared value between governments, communities and industry exists: skills development; extractives and communities; and the enabling environment. These are areas that: represent major risks for the private sector; are key to governments leveraging maximum development value from their extractives resources; will determine the employment and livelihood benefits that flow to communities; and require (and provide opportunities for) partnerships between governments, industry and communities to find solutions. The new program will harness Australia’s extractives-related expertise (private sector, government, non-government organisation, research and training). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;E4G will focus on &lt;strong&gt;three target countries (Tanzania, Zambia and Mozambique)&lt;/strong&gt; where Australia can maximise development benefits, and where there is a commitment by the government and private sector to improve the social benefits and economic growth opportunities from a well-managed and transparent extractives sector. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, ‘enabling environment’ activities will be conducted in 8-10 countries in Sub-Saharan Africa. These countries are likely to include Madagascar, South Africa, Ethiopia, Ghana and Nigeria, with the remainder yet to be determined.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Extractives for Growth Program (E4G) – Operations Manager&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven communication and negotiation skills and an ability to work in a variety of cultural settings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English. Proficiency in French and Portuguese will be considered an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills and an ability to work with a wide range of stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent project management skills &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to deliver long-term development programs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in the extractives and natural resources fields&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous work with the Department of Foreign Affairs and Trade’s (DFAT) is desirable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Significant experience working in Sub-Saharan Africa&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please send your CV to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:brian_green@dai.com&quot;&gt;brian_green@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;. Due to the high number of applicants, if you have not been contacted by the application closing date then please assume your application has been unsuccessful. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Please note that all profiles are indicative only and therefore subject to change once the ToR is made available.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extractives for Growth Program (E4G) – Senior Technical Adviser</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/extractives-for-growth-program-e4g-senior-technical-adviser</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 06:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/extractives-for-growth-program-e4g-senior-technical-adviser</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As part of the Department of Foreign Affairs and Trade’s (DFAT) consolidated Sub-Saharan African Aid program, Extractives for Growth (E4G) will be one of three key components. Through E4G, Australia will focus its assistance in three areas where the greatest potential for generating shared value between governments, communities and industry exists: skills development; extractives and communities; and the enabling environment. These are areas that: represent major risks for the private sector; are key to governments leveraging maximum development value from their extractives resources; will determine the employment and livelihood benefits that flow to communities; and require (and provide opportunities for) partnerships between governments, industry and communities to find solutions. The new program will harness Australia’s extractives-related expertise (private sector, government, non-government organisation, research and training). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;E4G will focus on &lt;strong&gt;three target countries (Tanzania, Zambia and Mozambique&lt;/strong&gt;) where Australia can maximise development benefits, and where there is a commitment by the government and private sector to improve the social benefits and economic growth opportunities from a well-managed and transparent extractives sector. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, ‘enabling environment’ activities will be conducted in 8-10 countries in Sub-Saharan Africa. These countries are likely to include Madagascar, South Africa, Ethiopia, Ghana and Nigeria, with the remainder yet to be determined.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Extractives for Growth Program (E4G) – Senior Technical Adviser&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in natural resources or an associated discipline &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven communication and negotiation skills and an ability to work in a variety of cultural settings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English. Proficiency in French and Portuguese will be considered an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills and an ability to work with a wide range of stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to deliver long-term development programs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years of experience working in the extractives and natural resources fields&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous work with the Department of Foreign Affairs and Trade’s (DFAT) is desirable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Significant experience working in Sub-Saharan Africa&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please send your CV to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:brian_green@dai.com&quot;&gt;brian_green@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;. Due to the high number of applicants, if you have not been contacted by the application closing date then please assume your application has been unsuccessful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please note that all profiles are indicative only and therefore subject to change once the ToR is made available.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extractives for Growth Program (E4G) – Team Leader</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/extractives-for-growth-program-e4g-team-leader</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 06:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/extractives-for-growth-program-e4g-team-leader</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As part of the Department of Foreign Affairs and Trade’s (DFAT) consolidated Sub-Saharan African Aid program, Extractives for Growth (E4G) will be one of three key components. Through E4G, Australia will focus its assistance in three areas where the greatest potential for generating shared value between governments, communities and industry exists: skills development; extractives and communities; and the enabling environment. These are areas that: represent major risks for the private sector; are key to governments leveraging maximum development value from their extractives resources; will determine the employment and livelihood benefits that flow to communities; and require (and provide opportunities for) partnerships between governments, industry and communities to find solutions. The new program will harness Australia’s extractives-related expertise (private sector, government, non-government organisation, research and training). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;E4G will focus on &lt;strong&gt;three target countries (Tanzania, Zambia and Mozambique)&lt;/strong&gt; where Australia can maximise development benefits, and where there is a commitment by the government and private sector to improve the social benefits and economic growth opportunities from a well-managed and transparent extractives sector. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, ‘enabling environment’ activities will be conducted in 8-10 countries in Sub-Saharan Africa. These countries are likely to include Madagascar, South Africa, Ethiopia, Ghana and Nigeria, with the remainder yet to be determined.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Extractives for Growth Program (E4G) – Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in natural resources or an associated discipline&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven communication and negotiation skills and an ability to work in a variety of cultural settings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English. Proficiency in French and Portuguese will be considered an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills and an ability to work with a wide range of stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to deliver long-term development programs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some experience working in the field of extractives and natural resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 8 years of previous experience as a Team Leader &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous work with the Department of Foreign Affairs and Trade’s (DFAT) is desirable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in Sub-Saharan Africa&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please send your CV to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:brian_green@dai.com&quot;&gt;brian_green@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;. Due to the high number of applicants, if you have not been contacted by the application closing date then please assume your application has been unsuccessful. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;&lt;strong&gt;Please note that all profiles are indicative only and therefore subject to change once the ToR is made available&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australia Awards – Alumni Engagement Manager</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/australia-awards-alumni-engagement-manager</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 21:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/australia-awards-alumni-engagement-manager</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As part of the Department of Foreign Affairs and Trade’s (DFAT) consolidated Sub-Saharan African Aid program, Australia Awards will be one of three key components.  Australia Awards are prestigious international scholarships offered by the Australian Government to the next generation of global leaders. Australia Awards provide opportunities for long-term (Masters) and short course study and professional development, aiming to develop capacity and leadership skills so that individuals can contribute to development in their home country. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scholarships have been a key part of Australia’s aid program to Africa since the 1960s, providing over 5,000 scholarships across the continent and are an important development and public diplomacy tool in Sub-Saharan Africa. In addition to building critical skills and knowledge, they foster an engaged and influential network of leaders, reformers and advocates driving development across the continent, contributing to Australian economic diplomacy objectives and promoting valuable links between Australia and African countries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Australia Awards will be comprised of:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Australia Awards Scholarships: demand-driven Masters undertaken at Australian universities, to be offered to approximately 11 Sub-Saharan African countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Australia Awards Africa Short Courses: tailored short (two-three months) post-graduate courses in sectors where Australia has recognised expertise and which are areas of priority to partner governments (agriculture, extractives and public policy). Offered to approximately 22 Sub-Saharan African countries, short course awards will be delivered through Australian registered training organisations, in partnership with African institutions to promote relevance. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Australia Award Fellowships: short-term opportunities for study, research and professional attachment in Australia, delivered by Australian organisations. Currently available across Africa to nominated fellows from eligible countries (this will be delivered through a global program external to the AADP).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Australia Awards – Alumni Engagement Manager&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tertiary degree in a relevant discipline&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven communication and negotiation skills and an ability to work in a variety of cultural settings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English. Proficiency in French and Portuguese will be considered an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills and an ability to work with a wide range of stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent project management skills &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to deliver long-term development programs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working on previous scholarships/exchange programs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience of working in Sub-Saharan Africa&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous work with the Department of Foreign Affairs and Trade’s (DFAT) is desirable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please send your CV to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:brian_green@dai.com&quot;&gt;brian_green@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;. Due to the high number of applicants, if you have not been contacted by the closing date, please assume your application has been unsuccessful. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;&lt;strong&gt;Please note that all profiles are indicative only and therefore subject to change once the ToR is made available&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
