<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2014 20:08:37 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert en Développement Rural ou de l’environnement - Chef d’équipe (Cat.I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-developpement-rural-ou-de-lenvironnement-chef-dequipe-cati</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2014 20:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-developpement-rural-ou-de-lenvironnement-chef-dequipe-cati</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Quatre contrats de subvention ont été signées entre l’Union Européenne et chacun des quatre bénéficiaires. Les bénéficiaires directs sont les populations vulnérables vivant autour de ces zones de conservations. Les actions sont menées avec la collaboration de Madagascar National Parks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif global de la mission d’évaluation à mi-parcours est ainsi d’émettre des constats portant sur :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Le bilan des réalisations achevées ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;L’opérationnalité des partenaires du projet sur le terrain ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;L’analyse des premiers résultats directs et impacts obtenus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;En vue de fournir aux instances décisionnelles, toutes les informations nécessaires et suffisantes permettant de rendre compte des résultats obtenus, d’améliorer la qualité de l’intervention pour la période de mise en œuvre restante et de veiller à une utilisation efficiente des ressources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert en Développement Rural ou de l’environnement - Chef d’équipe (Cat.I):&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;niveau Master au minimum dans le domaine des sciences humaines et sociales : anthropologie, sociologie ou domaine équivalent, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;justifiant d’une expérience d’au moins 12 années dans le domaine du développement rural ou de l’environnement, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;implique en qualité d’expert en évaluation dans au moins 3 prestations similaires sur les 5 dernières années dont au moins 1 en tant que Chef d’Equipe, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;de préférence dans des contrats avec l’Union européenne, &lt;strong&gt;parlant couramment le français.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:francesca_giordano@dai.com&quot;&gt;Francesca_Giordano@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Administrative Experts</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/two-administrative-experts</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2014 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/two-administrative-experts</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective :&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this contract is to perform an impact evaluation of the reorganisation and personnel movements in selected Albanian public administration institutions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of this contract concern an evaluation of the following elements: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the justification for organisational changes; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the justification for personnel movements; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the impact of the organisational and personnel changes on the sustainability of EU funded capacity building undertakings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Two Administrative Experts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree (of at least 3 years)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fluent in English – defined as minimum Level 2 in the standard CV format. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven knowledge of legal terminology will further be considered a strong asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Senior Public Administration Experts</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/two-senior-public-administration-experts</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2014 14:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/two-senior-public-administration-experts</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective :&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this contract is to perform an impact evaluation of the reorganisation and personnel movements in selected Albanian public administration institutions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of this contract concern an evaluation of the following elements: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the justification for organisational changes; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the justification for personnel movements; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the impact of the organisational and personnel changes on the sustainability of EU funded capacity building undertakings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Two Senior Public Administration Experts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;University degree of at least 3 years in political science, law, public administration, organisational theory or related areas. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The senior experts must have demonstrated experience in theoretical and operational management practices in public administration institutions. Knowledge of the Albanian context in terms of legislative framework of the Public Administration (public law and labour relations, administrative law and state organisation, administrative justice) will be a strong asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The senior experts must cover as a minimum the following areas of expertise: management of human resources, management of public institutions, organisational theory and statistics, administrative and public law. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The senior experts must have as a minimum of ten years of experience gained in the sector of public administration management and reform such as in the preparation and/or implementation of public administration reform programmes, of programmes regarding the management of human resources, and/or of programmes regarding organisational structuring/re-structuring of public institutions. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Each of the senior experts must have at least 2 years of experience with evaluation of programmes/projects/policies in the sector and at least one specific experience from the evaluation of programmes/projects/policies regarding the management of human resources and the organisational restructuring of public bodies, management of human resources and assignment, movements of public employees etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Horticultural Value Chain Specialists with Africa Experience</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/horticultural-value-chain-specialists-with-africa-experience</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 12:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/horticultural-value-chain-specialists-with-africa-experience</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Commencing in &lt;strong&gt;October 2013&lt;/strong&gt;, the Kenya Avocado Industry Support Programme aims to assist avocado farmers in Kenya through the provision of an improved avocado variety for tree replacement, sustainable production and postharvest systems, enhanced horticultural research and extension capability, and a secure pathway to market for produce.  The duration of the activity is five years between October 2013 and October 2018.  Plant and Food Research, through its subcontract with Olivado Kenya, work in territory with local farmers, and horticultural research/extension organisations to achieve these goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;primary purposes&lt;/strong&gt; of the evaluation are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Decision-making: to inform the future shape, direction and support for the Kenya avocado industry support programme.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning: to identify what is working and what is not, and apply these lessons learnt to continuously improve the delivery of the Kenya avocado industry support programme.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accountability: to account to MFAT and other stakeholders for the resources committed and the difference they are likely to make.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Horticultural Value Chain Specialists with Africa Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The attributes (knowledge, skills, experience) required of the evaluation team are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in horticultural value chain in developing countries, preferably Kenya or East Africa&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in analyzing and projecting potential economic benefits from agricultural interventions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of best practice for private sector participation in development programming would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluation expertise and experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research, report writing and presentation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of best practice for cross-cutting issues including Gender, Human Rights and Environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting Kenya Value Chains in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert on National Environment Policies</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-national-environment-policies</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 09:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-national-environment-policies</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project of which this contract will be a part is to support the Government of Georgia in its efforts to strengthen the approximation process towards the EU in the fields of environment and climate action, as foreseen in the relevant provisions of the Association Agreement signed on 27th June 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective of this contract is to support the MENRP of Georgia for developing a realistic and action-oriented Roadmap establishing key priorities and benchmarks to ensure compliance and enhance cooperation between Georgia and the EU on issues related to environment and climate action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The principal beneficiary is the Ministry of Environment and Natural Resources Protection of Georgia (MENPR). In addition, the assignment will target all relevant stakeholders involved in the support to environment and climate actions in Georgia, including other government bodies, the civil society, donors, financial institutions and implementing agencies in these domains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2 (Category III): Expert on National Environment Policies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Education at least Higher or Secondary education Degree in environmental sciences or other related fields or, in its absence, a minimum of 3 years equivalent professional experience related&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;at least 3 years of proven experience in support to national institution building actions related to environment, including the elaboration of policies, strategic documents and action plans.
Specific professional experience:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;proven  knowledge  of  environment  policies  and  related  strategic  planning  processes  in Georgia;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;proven experience in the elaboration of  strategic documents, action plans or other technical documents in the fields of environment or other related fields in Georgia;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;desirable knowledge of the EU acquis and policies in the environment and other related fields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Soft skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;strong planning, communication and analytical skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;proven practical-oriented approach and excellent report writing skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;desirable participation and good team interaction as part of short-term technical assignments in the country;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;computer literacy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proven fluency in written and spoken English and Georgian.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Environment Institutions &amp; Policy Expert with EU/Regional Experience (Category II) (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/environment-institutions-policy-expert-with-eu-regional-experience-category-ii-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/environment-institutions-policy-expert-with-eu-regional-experience-category-ii-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project of which this contract will be a part is to support the Government of Georgia in its efforts to strengthen the approximation process towards the EU in the fields of environment and climate action, as foreseen in the relevant provisions of the Association Agreement signed on 27th June 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective of this contract is to support the MENRP of Georgia for developing a realistic and action-oriented Roadmap establishing key priorities and benchmarks to ensure compliance and enhance cooperation between Georgia and the EU on issues related to environment and climate action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The principal beneficiary is the Ministry of Environment and Natural Resources Protection of Georgia (MENPR). In addition, the assignment will target all relevant stakeholders involved in the support to environment and climate actions in Georgia, including other government bodies, the civil society, donors, financial institutions and implementing agencies in these domains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Environment Institutions &amp;amp; Policy Expert with EU/Regional Experience (Category II): Team leader&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Education at least Masters Degree in environmental sciences or other related fields or, in its absence, a minimum of 6 years equivalent professional experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least 6 years of proven experience in support to institution building actions related to environment or other related fields.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;proven experience in support to environment and other related policies and strategic planning processes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;proven knowledge of the EU acquis and policies in the environment and other related fields; desirable experience in countries with a similar context i.e. South Caucasus, CIS and other Eastern European countries with comparable experiences in EU approximation processes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Soft skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;strong planning, communication and analytical skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;proven practical-oriented approach and excellent report writing skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;proven leadership  and coordination skills, experience and efficient use of time and resources within intensive short-time assignments;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;computer literacy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;proven fluency in written and spoken English.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Capacity Development Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/capacity-development-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/capacity-development-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The global objective of the assignment is to provide the relevant external co-operation services of the European Union, the partner government and, as appropriate, the wider sector stakeholders with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an overall independent assessment of the performance of the LVC-PPD project paying particularly attention to the results of the project against its objectives, and providing policy relevant, actionable and evidence-based lessons and recommendations that inform the design of the follow-on project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an advanced project draft for a 5 year animal health sector follow-on project based on most recent GoE policies and livestock sector strategies (GTP II, CRGE, VSD Animal Health Strategy, Livestock Master Plan, Veterinary Privatisation Roadmap with simultaneous strengthening of public sector core public good functions), lessons and recommendations drawn from LVC-PPD, SHARE and other ongoing initiatives in the sector, and needs and gaps articulated by GoE, livestock producers and traders, public and private animal health service providers, and OIE PVS analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Capacity Development Expert – Category 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree (university or equivalent institution or in its absence equivalent professional experience of at least 15 years) in Economics, Business Management of Agriculture, Agricultural Economics or equivalent; Post graduate studies in animal health economics/ design of national animal disease control strategies would be considered an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent analytical and reporting skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in both written and spoken English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Initiative, tact and ability to maintain harmonious working relationships in a multicultural setting;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of professional experience with the identification, assessment, formulation,monitoring and evaluation of donor-funded projects and programmes on livestock sector development, in particular in the areas of institutional development and human capacity building, curricula development, knowledge management and ICT;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of and experience with EDF rules and procedures is an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific and relevant experience of working in developing countries, preferably in Sub-Saharan Africa; working experience in the Horn of Africa Region would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience with design, implementation and/or evaluation of donor-funded projects addressing training, capacity building, education and curricula development in the livestock disease surveillance, meat inspection, export certification and livestock identification movement control and traceability sectors and related ICT;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid professional experience with project formulation and evaluation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid knowledge of institutional and capacity development and change management in public sector agriculture institutions in Sub-Saharan African countries, preferably Ethiopia.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:roxanne_garrana@dai.com&quot;&gt;Roxanne_Garrana@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Livestock Value Chain and Trade Expert/ Team Leader -Identification and Formulation</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/livestock-value-chain-and-trade-expert-team-leader-identification-and-formulation</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 09:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/livestock-value-chain-and-trade-expert-team-leader-identification-and-formulation</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The global objective of the assignment is to provide the relevant external co-operation services of the European Union, the partner government and, as appropriate, the wider sector stakeholders with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an overall independent assessment of the performance of the LVC-PPD project paying particularly attention to the results of the project against its objectives, and providing policy relevant, actionable and evidence-based lessons and recommendations that inform the design of the follow-on project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an advanced project draft for a 5 year animal health sector follow-on project based on most recent GoE policies and livestock sector strategies (GTP II, CRGE, VSD Animal Health Strategy, Livestock Master Plan, Veterinary Privatisation Roadmap with simultaneous strengthening of public sector core public good functions), lessons and recommendations drawn from LVC-PPD, SHARE and other ongoing initiatives in the sector, and needs and gaps articulated by GoE, livestock producers and traders, public and private animal health service providers, and OIE PVS analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Livestock Value Chain and Trade Expert/ Team Leader -Identification and Formulation – Category 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree (university or equivalent institution or in its absence equivalent professional experience of at least 18 years) in agriculture/ agricultural economics, veterinary medicine or equivalent. Post graduate studies in veterinary epidemiology/ animal health economics would be considered an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent analytical, communication and reporting skills including solid experience in field assessments and participatory data collection;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in both written and spoken English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Initiative, tact and proven ability to maintain harmonious working relationships in a multicultural setting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of relevant professional experience in developing countries, at least 7 of which have been in Africa and at least 5 years as team leader in large projects, dealing with livestock value chain development and rationalization of livestock services in public private partnership;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid proven professional experience with developing policies, strategies, approaches, and tools for improving the livestock value chain system and increasing livestock production and productivity;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Profound knowledge of and experience with EC aid modalities, project cycle management, and EDF rules and procedures;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific and relevant experience of working in developing countries, preferably in Sub-Saharan Africa and in particular in the Horn of Africa Region;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in the design, implementation and evaluation of donor funded veterinary services restructuring programmes encompassing regulated and effective quality private sector services;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience with establishing managing and assessing robust performance monitoring frameworks with clear-cut goals, outcomes, outputs, inputs, processes, indicators, data needs and sources, and reporting formats and frequency, for effective monitoring, reporting and updating progress of donor-funded programs and projects in particular in the agricultural sector;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid knowledge of capacity development challenges in public and private sector agricultural institutions in Sub-Saharan African countries, preferably Ethiopia;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid experience with the conduct of desk literature reviews, analyses and syntheses for monitoring/evaluation and planning purposes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven working experience with mainstreaming gender/ environment/ nutrition security assessments in program design, implementation, monitoring, and evaluation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with leading a multi-sectoral team of experts with diverse academic and social backgrounds conducting evaluations or project formulations;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the policy environment of Ethiopia&amp;rsquo;s livestock production, export and health sector would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:roxanne_garrana@dai.com&quot;&gt;Roxanne_Garrana@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Private Animal Health Services Expert (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/public-private-animal-health-services-expert-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 08:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/public-private-animal-health-services-expert-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The global objective of the assignment is to provide the relevant external co-operation services of the European Union, the partner government and, as appropriate, the wider sector stakeholders with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an overall independent assessment of the performance of the LVC-PPD project paying particularly attention to the results of the project against its objectives, and providing policy relevant, actionable and evidence-based lessons and recommendations that inform the design of the follow-on project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an advanced project draft for a 5 year animal health sector follow-on project based on most recent GoE policies and livestock sector strategies (GTP II, CRGE, VSD Animal Health Strategy, Livestock Master Plan, Veterinary Privatisation Roadmap with simultaneous strengthening of public sector core public good functions), lessons and recommendations drawn from LVC-PPD, SHARE and other ongoing initiatives in the sector, and needs and gaps articulated by GoE, livestock producers and traders, public and private animal health service providers, and OIE PVS analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Private Animal Health Services Expert/ Team Leader-Evaluation – Category 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree (university or equivalent institution or in its absence equivalent professional experience of at least 18 years) in veterinary medicine or equivalent. Post graduate studies in veterinary epidemiology/ animal health economics/ design of national animal disease control strategies would be considered an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent analytical, communication and reporting skills including solid experience in field assessments and participatory data collection;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in both written and spoken English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Initiative, tact and proven ability to maintain harmonious working relationships in a multicultural setting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of relevant professional experience in developing countries, at least 7 of which have been in Africa and at least 5 years as team leader in large projects, working within National Veterinary services;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid proven professional experience with developing policies, strategies, approaches, and tools for effective delivery of livestock services;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of and experience with EU project cycle management, implementation of Programme Estimates and EDF rules and procedures is an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific and relevant experience of working in developing countries, preferably in Sub-Saharan Africa and in particular in the Horn of Africa Region;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in the design, implementation and evaluation of institutional support projects addressing public service reforms, institutional and capacity development and change management in particular in the livestock and/or animal health sector;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven working experience with conducting gender/ environment/ nutrition security assessments in policy analysis, research, program design, implementation, monitoring, and evaluation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to develop gender, environment and nutrition security indicators for performance monitoring and evaluation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid experience with the conduct of desk literature reviews, analyses and syntheses for monitoring/evaluation and planning purposes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with leading a multi-sectoral team of experts with diverse academic and social backgrounds conducting evaluations or project formulations;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid knowledge of capacity development challenges in public sector agriculture institutions in Sub-Saharan African countries, preferably Ethiopia;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the policy environment of Ethiopia&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Agriculture and Livestock State-Ministry would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:roxanne_garrana@dai.com&quot;&gt;Roxanne_Garrana@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agriculture Expert with Experience in Africa and EC Procedures</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/agriculture-expert-with-experience-in-africa-and-ec-procedures</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 13:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/agriculture-expert-with-experience-in-africa-and-ec-procedures</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The objective of the assignment is to support the Contracting Authority (National Authorising Officer for EDF) and the Ministry of Agriculture Food Security and Cooperatives to design the guidelines for applicants (Restricted Call for Proposals) and evaluate the concept notes as well as the full proposals. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agriculture Expert with Experience in Africa and EC Procedures (Category III)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master degree in, Agriculture, Agronomy, Rural Development or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years’ experience in the below mentioned fields&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of agriculture sector in Africa and or East Africa region.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in Project Management and EC procedures for external actions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with EC Calls for Proposals, design of Guidelines and project evaluations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in project cycle management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in Grain Post-harvest activities in Africa is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Language: English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post-Harvest Management Expert with M&amp;E Experience</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/post-harvest-management-expert-with-me-experience</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 13:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/post-harvest-management-expert-with-me-experience</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The objective of the assignment is to support the Contracting Authority (National Authorising Officer for EDF) and the Ministry of Agriculture Food Security and Cooperatives to design the guidelines for applicants (Restricted Call for Proposals) and evaluate the concept notes as well as the full proposals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Post-Harvest Management Expert with M&amp;amp;E Experience (Category II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master degree in, Agriculture, Agronomy, Agriculture Engineering or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in Grain Post-harvest Management activities in Sub Saharan Africa&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with the Tanzanian socio-economic context and strong knowledge of Tanzanian institutions in the field of agriculture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated knowledge and ability in Monitoring and Evaluation of development programs and projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated knowledge in gender mainstreaming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years work experience in the field of Post-harvest Management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Language: English; Kiswahili is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experto en Fortalecimiento Institucional  (Sector Gobernación) (Categoria II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-en-fortalecimiento-institucional-sector-gobernacion-categoria-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2014 14:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-en-fortalecimiento-institucional-sector-gobernacion-categoria-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Diseñar y ejecutar un Plan de Capacitación enfocado a mejorar las capacidades y destrezas profesionales de los y las trabajadores y empleados en las áreas de incidencia del POFI (planificación, presupuestación y seguimiento dentro del enfoque de la gestión por resultado de desarrollo, presupuestación de mediano plazo, fortaleciendo la inclusión de los enfoques de sostenibilidad ambiental y de género).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;El Plan de Capacitación está basado en un análisis de la demanda existente en las instituciones beneficiarias y consiste de 2 bloques:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Para el sector rural: talleres en Planificación basada en la gestión por resultado.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Para el sector gobernación: talleres en Alta Gerencia Publica&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experto en Fortalecimiento Institucional  (Sector Gobernación) (Categoria II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cualificaciones&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Un Experto/a con título universitario en las áreas de ciencias sociales, económicas, o similares.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experiencia general:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia profesional por un mínimo de 6 años en el análisis de políticas públicas con especial énfasis en planificación y presupuestación dentro del enfoque de una gestión orientada a resultados de desarrollo.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia de trabajo en el sector relacionado a gobernación (Migración y Extranjería, Sistemas Penitenciarios, prevención y combate de incendios, etc.) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia en el diseño y facilitación de talleres y otras acciones de capacitación.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia sólida y diversificada en el ámbito del conocimiento específico necesario, en particular, experiencia en materia de planificación estratégica en países en desarrollo.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excelente capacidad de comunicación verbal y por escrito en español y con capacidad de transmisión de conocimientos y “saber hacer”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Al menos uno de los/las expertos propuestos deberá poseer un buen conocimiento en temas relacionados con igualdad de género, aspectos ambientales, socioculturales y consideraciones de derechos humanos y análisis de la integración de estos temas en la planificación&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Número de días laborables&lt;/strong&gt;: 42&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicolas_fichers@dai.com&quot;&gt;Nicolas_fichers@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experto en Fortalecimiento Institucional  (Sector Rural) (Categoria II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-en-fortalecimiento-institucional-sector-rural-categoria-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2014 13:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-en-fortalecimiento-institucional-sector-rural-categoria-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Diseñar y ejecutar un Plan de Capacitación enfocado a mejorar las capacidades y destrezas profesionales de los y las trabajadores y empleados en las áreas de incidencia del POFI (planificación, presupuestación y seguimiento dentro del enfoque de la gestión por resultado de desarrollo, presupuestación de mediano plazo, fortaleciendo la inclusión de los enfoques de sostenibilidad ambiental y de género).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;El Plan de Capacitación está basado en un análisis de la demanda existente en las instituciones beneficiarias y consiste de 2 bloques:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Para el sector rural: talleres en Planificación basada en la gestión por resultado.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Para el sector gobernación: talleres en Alta Gerencia Publica&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experto en Fortalecimiento Institucional  (Sector Rural) (Categoria II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cualificaciones:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Un Experto/a con título universitario en las áreas de ciencias sociales, económicas, o similares.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Experiencia general: *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia profesional por un mínimo de 6 años en el análisis de políticas públicas con especial énfasis en planificación y presupuestación dentro del enfoque de una gestión orientada a resultados de desarrollo.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia de trabajo en el sector productivo rural para el caso del experto que trabajará en el sector rural&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia en el diseño y facilitación de talleres y otras acciones de capacitación.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia sólida y diversificada en el ámbito del conocimiento específico necesario, en particular, experiencia en materia de planificación estratégica en países en desarrollo.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excelente capacidad de comunicación verbal y por escrito en español y con capacidad de transmisión de conocimientos y “saber hacer”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Al menos uno de los/las expertos propuestos deberá poseer un buen conocimiento en temas relacionados con igualdad de género, aspectos ambientales, socioculturales y consideraciones de derechos humanos y análisis de la integración de estos temas en la planificación.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Número de días laborables&lt;/strong&gt;: 42&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicolas_fichers@dai.com&quot;&gt;Nicolas_fichers@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert in Monitoring and Evaluation of Sugar Programmes, Irrigation Development Schemes and Smallholder Development of Sugar Projects (Cat. II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-monitoring-and-evaluation-of-sugar-programmes-irrigation-development-schemes-and-smallholder-development-of-sugar-projects-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2014 13:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-monitoring-and-evaluation-of-sugar-programmes-irrigation-development-schemes-and-smallholder-development-of-sugar-projects-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overall independent assignment will provide the GoM and the EU with an overall independent and reliable assessment about the overall performance of the 2008 Accompanying Measures for Sugar Protocol in Malawi Protocol.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in Monitoring and Evaluation of Sugar Programmes, Irrigation Development Schemes and Smallholder Development of Sugar Projects (Cat. II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree (or degree with 10 years relevant work experience) in a sugar sector related qualification such as: agriculture economics, agronomy, agribusiness, irrigation, rural development, community development, social science;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific and relevant experience of working in SADC and/or other developing countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one previous experience in the formulation and/or evaluation of Agriculture and/or Food Security and/or Rural development programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one working experience with the principles and working methods of project cycle management and EU aid delivery methods;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency and excellent knowledge of English as a working language.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additional requirements, which would be considered as an advantage:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous relevant experience in the last 10 years of monitoring and evaluating projects with a focus on the sugar industry in Sub-Saharan Africa;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant experience in irrigation development schemes in Sub-Saharan Africa during the last 10 years;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated comparative country experience and knowledge;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant experience in irrigation development schemes in Sub-Saharan Africa during the last 10 years;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated comparative country experience and knowledge of the sugar sector and management information systems;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years relevant field experience in smallholder development of sugar projects, including capacity building, participatory approaches and experience in cross cutting issues such as HIV/AIDS, gender awareness, environmental and social impact, climate change ect;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate comparative country field experience in capacity building of community based organisations, institutions at local level including district assemblies and traditional authorities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound monitoring and evaluation expertise of smallholder farmer/out-grower schemes with focus on the sugar sector will be favoured;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spoken Chichewa would be seen as an advantage (alternatively a translator will be procured)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:francesca_giordano@dai.com&quot;&gt;Francesca_Giordano@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Environment and Biology Expert (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/opportunities/senior-environment-and-biology-expert-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 20:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/opportunities/senior-environment-and-biology-expert-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Expert 2 is expected to contribute the implementation of all of the related modules and the preparation of both training materials and Training Evaluation Report in the context of related chapter/s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in Biology, Ecology, Chemistry or other Natural Sciences related to assignment. In the absence of the degree required, at least 17 years of professional experience in the related areas is requested.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good command of both written and spoken English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General professional experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in the sector(s) related to the Lot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience in technical and/or scientific fields required for the implementation of the Water Framework Directive and/or Habitat Directive and/or other related Directives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 river basin management plans experience in terms of setting of environmental objectives and/or setting, design and upgrade of biological monitoring programme and/or execution and assessment of biological monitoring.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in development of measures for water pollution reduction and/or improving ecological status, and/or river basin characterisation/analysis will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in projects related to Integrated Water Resources Management will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader – NGO Support and Strengthening</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-ngo-support-and-strengthening</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 15:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-ngo-support-and-strengthening</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overarching purpose of this work will be to support the Government of Indonesia (GoI) to strengthen the capacity of all levels of Indonesian government and communities for improved services and economic growth.
Three substantive pillars will support the long-term goal of a prosperous and stable Indonesia, by contributing to the development of active, inclusive communities and of a capable, responsive state as summarized below, interacting as necessary with sectoral investments under the frontline framework:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work under Pillar 1 will foster active, inclusive communities to support community development in Indonesia;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If implemented under Pillar 2, AIPD2 (Australia-Indonesia Partnership for Decentralisation) would foster a capable, responsive Indonesian state by supporting central and subnational governments for improved service delivery; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If implemented under Pillar 3, NGO support and strengthening would support efforts to foster active, inclusive communities and a capable, responsive Indonesian state.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader – NGO Support and Strengthening&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of a Bachelor’s degree in management, organizational development, international development, community development, a social science or similar field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 10 years of technical and project management experience in civil society development and NGO/CSO capacity building in democratic transition countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5 years’ experience as a Team Leader on donor-funded projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of incorporating gender equality into project delivery. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work with a diverse set of staff in various technical areas and at different levels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written English skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous working experience in Indonesia (desirable)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Bahasa Indonesian (desirable)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in DFAT format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;sendto:sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah.owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting DFAT/AOP/006 in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader – Decentralisation Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-decentralisation-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-decentralisation-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overarching purpose of this work will be to support the Government of Indonesia (GoI) to strengthen the capacity of all levels of Indonesian government and communities for improved services and economic growth.
Three substantive pillars will support the long-term goal of a prosperous and stable Indonesia, by contributing to the development of active, inclusive communities and of a capable, responsive state as summarized below, interacting as necessary with sectoral investments under the frontline framework:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work under Pillar 1 will foster active, inclusive communities to support community development in Indonesia;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If implemented under Pillar 2, AIPD2 (Australia-Indonesia Partnership for Decentralisation) would foster a capable, responsive Indonesian state by supporting central and subnational governments for improved service delivery; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If implemented under Pillar 3, NGO support and strengthening would support efforts to foster active, inclusive communities and a capable, responsive Indonesian state.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader – Decentralisation Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in a relevant field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 10 years of experience on national and local governments policy review and formulation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Substantial international project management and field office management experience. Management consulting experience a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5 years’ experience as a Team Leader on donor-funded projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in supporting central and subnational governments for improved public service delivery including: Human resources and adviser management, especially in recruitment; Logistics and procurement; Capacity building and training;Office management, including interpreting and translation, administration, office systems, reporting; Financial management, budgeting and reporting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work with a diverse set of staff in various technical areas and at different levels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in advising at senior decision levels of relevant Ministries and Institutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of incorporating gender equality into project delivery. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written English skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous working experience in Indonesia (desirable)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Bahasa Indonesian (desirable)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in DFAT format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;sendto:sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting DFAT/AOP/006 in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key Experts, External Results Oriented Monitoring (ROM)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-experts-</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 15:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-experts-</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Results Oriented Monitoring (ROM)&lt;/strong&gt; reviews aim to assist the European Commission’s (EC) services and EU Delegations (EUD) in monitoring of and reporting on EU financed development and cooperation projects and programmes (hereafter “projects”) in third countries through independent reviews of the progress of their implementation and the achievement of project results. Compared to the ROM reviews conducted over the past decade, ROM reviews will proceed on a number of reforms that aim to improve the quality and the focus in coverage of the ROM reviews and take into account the high level of devolution reached over the past decade for project preparation and monitoring tasks to EUDs at field level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This lot covers the EU funded national and regional projects and programmes whether single or multi-country and also Cross-Border-Cooperation (CBC) projects and programmes. These projects are implemented in the countries covered by the European Neighbourhood and Partnership Instrument (ENPI) and the European Neighbourhood Instrument (ENI)  in Algeria, Egypt, Israel, Jordan, Lebanon, Libya, Morocco, Syria, Tunisia and Palestine (Neighbourhood South); Armenia, Azerbaijan, Belarus, Georgia, Moldova and Ukraine (Neighbourhood East); Russia. If relevant, including partner countries other than ENI Southern Partner Countries (ENISPCs) :Bosnia and Herzegovina, Albania, Mauritania, Montenegro, Turkey, Bahrain, Comoros, Djibouti, Iraq, Kuwait, Oman, Qatar, Saudi Arabia, Somalia, Sudan, United Arab Emirates and Yemen, when associated to the activities foreseen in regional programmes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Team Leader will head a team of key experts, comprised of a Deputy Team Leader and four &lt;strong&gt;key experts&lt;/strong&gt; who will organise and supervise the implementation of the contract, carry out ROM reviews, be in charge of the internal QC and will draft the annual as well as the end of contract consolidated ROM analysis. They shall cover, as much as possible, the following areas of expertise: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employment and social protection&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Energy &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good Governance including: Democracy, rule of law, human rights; Public administration, including decentralisation; PFM and macroeconomics stability (related to Budget Support)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Natural resources, environment, climate change&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trade and Private sector development including: Regional integration; Business environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sustainable agriculture, food and nutrition security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transport&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development and security nexus, including drugs and migration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Civil society&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Statistics and performance measurement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Experts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for &lt;strong&gt;8 experts&lt;/strong&gt; (4 covering &lt;strong&gt;ACP&lt;/strong&gt; countries and 4 covering &lt;strong&gt;ENPI&lt;/strong&gt; countries). These positions are &lt;strong&gt;full time (220 man days/ year&lt;/strong&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These key experts implement the internal QC system preferably in their area of expertise and will be assigned ROM reviews/support missions according to their area of expertise, including: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PFM &amp;amp; Macroeconomics stability expertise,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Statistics and performance measurement expertise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They ensure timely delivery of ROM reports by ROM experts and QC checklists to EC services. They provide their inputs in their area of expertise in order to draft the annual as well as the end of contract consolidated ROM analysis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has a university master degree (or equivalent).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she must be fluent both in French and English.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They have a minimum of 12 years of experience in development cooperation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They have a minimum of 5 years of experience as project manager.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They have a minimum of 10 years of experience in one of the abovementioned areas of expertise. Experience in other of the above mentioned areas of expertise is an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They have a minimum of 5 years of experience in results based approaches, monitoring, and/or evaluation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They have a minimum of 3 years of experience on Neighbourhood countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They have preferably a good knowledge of EU and other donors implementing modalities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They have preferably experience in gender mainstreaming related to his/her area of expertise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in EC format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting (reference no. &lt;strong&gt;ROM/KE&lt;/strong&gt;) in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note that this is a long-term EU-funded project not a EC COM Lot 1 Framework project.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deputy Team Leader, External Results Oriented Monitoring (ROM)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/deputy-team-leader-external-results-oriented-monitoring-rom</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 15:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/deputy-team-leader-external-results-oriented-monitoring-rom</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Results Oriented Monitoring (ROM)&lt;/strong&gt; reviews aim to assist the European Commission’s (EC) services and EU Delegations (EUD) in monitoring of and reporting on EU financed development and cooperation projects and programmes (hereafter “projects”) in third countries through independent reviews of the progress of their implementation and the achievement of project results. Compared to the ROM reviews conducted over the past decade, ROM reviews will proceed on a number of reforms that aim to improve the quality and the focus in coverage of the ROM reviews and take into account the high level of devolution reached over the past decade for project preparation and monitoring tasks to EUDs at field level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This lot covers the EU funded national and regional projects and programmes whether single or multi-country and also Cross-Border-Cooperation (CBC) projects and programmes. These projects are implemented in the countries covered by the European Neighbourhood and Partnership Instrument (ENPI) and the European Neighbourhood Instrument (ENI)  in Algeria, Egypt, Israel, Jordan, Lebanon, Libya, Morocco, Syria, Tunisia and Palestine (Neighbourhood South); Armenia, Azerbaijan, Belarus, Georgia, Moldova and Ukraine (Neighbourhood East); Russia. If relevant, including partner countries other than ENI Southern Partner Countries (ENISPCs) :Bosnia and Herzegovina, Albania, Mauritania, Montenegro, Turkey, Bahrain, Comoros, Djibouti, Iraq, Kuwait, Oman, Qatar, Saudi Arabia, Somalia, Sudan, United Arab Emirates and Yemen, when associated to the activities foreseen in regional programmes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Team Leader will head a team of key experts, comprised of the &lt;strong&gt;Deputy Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; and four other key experts who will organise and supervise the implementation of the contract, carry out ROM reviews, be in charge of the internal QC and will draft the annual as well as the end of contract consolidated ROM analysis. They shall cover, as much as possible, the following areas of expertise: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employment and social protection&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Energy &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good Governance - Democracy, rule of law, human rights; Public administration, including decentralisation; PFM and macroeconomics stability (related to Budget Support)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Natural resources, environment, climate change&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trade and Private sector development including: Regional integration; Business environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sustainable agriculture, food and nutrition security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transport&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development and security nexus, including drugs and migration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Civil society&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Statistics and performance measurement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking for &lt;strong&gt;2 Deputy Team Leaders&lt;/strong&gt; - once covering &lt;strong&gt;ACP countries&lt;/strong&gt; and the other covering &lt;strong&gt;ENPI countries&lt;/strong&gt;.  This position is a &lt;strong&gt;full time position (220 man days/ year)&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Deputy Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; (DTL) supports the Team Leader (TL) in fulfilling his/her tasks and responsibilities. He/she is in charge in particular of the application of the internal QC system by ROM QC experts and all ROM experts. He/she drafts the quarterly QC reports and follows-up the recommendations of the QA reports. Like the TL, he/she implements ROM reviews as a sector expert for projects and programmes and plays the role of a ROM QC expert.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has a university master degree (or equivalent).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she must be fluent both in French and English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He/she has a minimum of 15 years of experience in development cooperation, notably in project management with a minimum of 5 years of experience as Deputy TL or TL preferably of a mixed team of long and short term experts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has a minimum of 10 years of experience in one of the abovementioned areas of expertise. Experience in other of the above mentioned areas of expertise is an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has a minimum of 5 years of experience in results based approaches, monitoring, and/or evaluation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has a minimum of 3 years and preferably 5 years of experience in quality systems in services sectors: improving work processes and efficiency, defining quality policies and objectives, implementing quality procedures. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she or the TL has a minimum of 5 years of experience on Neighbourhood countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has preferably a good knowledge of EU and other donors implementing modalities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has preferably experience in gender mainstreaming related to his/her area of expertise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in EC format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting (&lt;strong&gt;ROM/DTL&lt;/strong&gt;) in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note that this is a long-term EU-funded project not a EC COM Lot 1 Framework project.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader, External Results Oriented Monitoring (ROM)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 14:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Results Oriented Monitoring (ROM)&lt;/strong&gt; reviews aim to assist the European Commission’s (EC) services and EU Delegations (EUD) in monitoring of and reporting on EU financed development and cooperation projects and programmes (hereafter “projects”) in third countries through independent reviews of the progress of their implementation and the achievement of project results. Compared to the ROM reviews conducted over the past decade, ROM reviews will proceed on a number of reforms that aim to improve the quality and the focus in coverage of the ROM reviews and take into account the high level of devolution reached over the past decade for project preparation and monitoring tasks to EUDs at field level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This lot covers the EU funded national and regional projects and programmes whether single or multi-country and also Cross-Border-Cooperation (CBC) projects and programmes. These projects are implemented in the countries covered by the European Neighbourhood and Partnership Instrument (ENPI) and the European Neighbourhood Instrument (ENI)  in Algeria, Egypt, Israel, Jordan, Lebanon, Libya, Morocco, Syria, Tunisia and Palestine (Neighbourhood South); Armenia, Azerbaijan, Belarus, Georgia, Moldova and Ukraine (Neighbourhood East); Russia. If relevant, including partner countries other than ENI Southern Partner Countries (ENISPCs) :Bosnia and Herzegovina, Albania, Mauritania, Montenegro, Turkey, Bahrain, Comoros, Djibouti, Iraq, Kuwait, Oman, Qatar, Saudi Arabia, Somalia, Sudan, United Arab Emirates and Yemen, when associated to the activities foreseen in regional programmes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; will head a team of key experts, comprised of a &lt;strong&gt;Deputy Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; and four other &lt;strong&gt;key experts&lt;/strong&gt; who will organise and supervise the implementation of the contract, carry out ROM reviews, be in charge of the internal QC and will draft the annual as well as the end of contract consolidated ROM analysis. They shall cover, as much as possible, the following areas of expertise: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employment and social protection&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Energy &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good Governance - Democracy; rule of law; human rights; Public administration, including decentralisation; PFM and macroeconomics stability (related to Budget Support)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Natural resources, environment, climate change&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trade and Private sector development including - Regional integration; Business environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sustainable agriculture, food and nutrition security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transport&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development and security nexus, including drugs and migration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Civil society&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Statistics and performance measurement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt;
DAI is looking for &lt;strong&gt;2 Team Leaders&lt;/strong&gt;; one to cover ACP countries and the other to cover ENPI countries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has a university master degree (or equivalent).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she must be fluent both in French and English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;
He/she has a minimum of 15 years of experience in development cooperation with a minimum of 8 years of experience as Team Leader, preferably of a mixed team of long and short term experts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has a minimum of 10 years of experience in one of the above mentioned areas of expertise. Experience in other of the above mentioned areas of expertise is an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has a minimum of 5 years of experience in results based approaches, monitoring and/or evaluation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she or the Deputy TL has a minimum of 5 years of experience on from Neighbourhood countries, preferably on Southern and/or Eastern Neighbourhood countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has preferably a good knowledge of EU and other donors implementing modalities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she has preferably experience in gender mainstreaming related to his/her area of expertise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in EC format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:%20sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting (reference no.ROM/TL) in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note that this is a long-term EU-funded project and does not come under EC COM Lot 1.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
