<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 19:51:58 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sénior, catégorie I, en gestion du capital humain </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-categorie-i-en-gestion-du-capital-humain</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 19:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-categorie-i-en-gestion-du-capital-humain</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Refonte du système d’information de l’Institution du Médiateur du Royaume&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contribuer au processus de convergence règlementaire dans le domaine de la protection des droits de l’Homme, tout en favorisant le rapprochement règlementaire avec l’Acquis de l’Union européenne et l’adoption des bonnes pratiques internationales. Contribuer à la conception et au développement d’un système d’information performant en vue de permettre à l’Institut du Médiateur d’assurer son rôle constitutionnel de protection des droits des usagers face à l’administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expertise 4 : Sénior, catégorie I, en gestion du capital humain&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire supérieur, de niveau Master en gestion des ressources humaines, en communication ou diplôme équivalent et pertinent par rapport aux objectifs du contrat;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience professionnelle de 5 ans en gestion des ressources humaines auprès d’une institution publique ou privée, en plus de celle indiquée comme expérience professionnelle générale, pourra compenser l’absence de Master ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 12 ans d’expérience en organisation et gestion des ressources humaines auprès d’une institution publique ou privée en UE/EEE ou PEV ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience spécifique d’au moins 5 ans, dans la conception ou la mise en œuvre de la politique des RH dans le cadre de la réorganisation d’au moins une institution publique ou privée en UE/EEE ou PEV ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience spécifique dans la conception ou mise en œuvre de la stratégie de communication dans le cadre de la réorganisation d’au moins une institution publique ou privée en UE/EEE ou PEV serait un atout;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissance linguistique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonne maîtrise de la langue française parlée et écrite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;La connaissance de la langue arabe serait un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junior, de catégorie II, Développeur – para métreur</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-de-categorie-ii-developpeur-para-metreur</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 17:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-de-categorie-ii-developpeur-para-metreur</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Refonte du système d’information de l’Institution du Médiateur du Royaume&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contribuer au processus de convergence règlementaire dans le domaine de la protection des droits de l’Homme, tout en favorisant le rapprochement règlementaire avec l’Acquis de l’Union européenne et l’adoption des bonnes pratiques internationales. Contribuer à la conception et au développement d’un système d’information performant en vue de permettre à l’Institut du Médiateur d’assurer son rôle constitutionnel de protection des droits des usagers face à l’administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expertise 3 : Junior, de catégorie II, Développeur – para métreur&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire supérieur, de niveau Master en programmation ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience professionnelle de 5 ans en plus de celle indiquée comme expérience professionnelle générale, pourra compenser l’absence de Master ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 5 ans d’expérience en matière de langages de programmation utilisés pour les applications web avec bases de données (PHP, SQL, (X) HTML, Javascript)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 3 ans d’expérience en analyse de contraintes et développement d&amp;#39;application orienté web sont demandées .&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissance linguistique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne maîtrise de la langue française parlée et écrite,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;La connaissance de la langue arabe serait un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior, de catégorie I, analyste en système d’information et procédures </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-de-categorie-i-analyste-en-systeme-dinformation-et-procedures</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 17:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-de-categorie-i-analyste-en-systeme-dinformation-et-procedures</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Refonte du système d’information de l’Institution du Médiateur du Royaume
*&lt;/em&gt;
Contribuer au processus de convergence règlementaire dans le domaine de la protection des droits de l’Homme, tout en favorisant le rapprochement règlementaire avec l’Acquis de l’Union européenne et l’adoption des bonnes pratiques internationales. Contribuer à la conception et au développement d’un système d’information performant en vue de permettre à l’Institut du Médiateur d’assurer son rôle constitutionnel de protection des droits des usagers face à l’administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expertise 2 : Senior, de catégorie I, analyste en système d’information et procédures&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire supérieur, de niveau Master en informatique et systèmes d’information&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience professionnelle de 5 ans en plus de celle indiquée comme expérience professionnelle générale, pourra compenser l’absence de Master ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 12 ans d’expérience dans le conseil informatique et l’analyse des process pour des services publics, des administrations publiques &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 5 ans d’expérience en informatique décisionnelle avec une expérience avérée de proposition de nouveaux outils d’assistance aux échanges d’information&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissance linguistique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne maîtrise de la langue française parlée et écrite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;La connaissance de la langue arabe serait un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior, de catégorie I, 1 expert métier de la médiation, Chef de mission</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-de-categorie-i-1-expert-metier-de-la-mediation-chef-de-mission</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-de-categorie-i-1-expert-metier-de-la-mediation-chef-de-mission</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Refonte du système d’information de l’Institution du Médiateur du Royaume&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contribuer au processus de convergence règlementaire dans le domaine de la protection des droits de l’Homme, tout en favorisant le rapprochement règlementaire avec l’Acquis de l’Union européenne et l’adoption des bonnes pratiques internationales. Contribuer à la conception et au développement d’un système d’information performant en vue de permettre à l’Institut du Médiateur d’assurer son rôle constitutionnel de protection des droits des usagers face à l’administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expertise 1 : Senior, de catégorie I, 1 expert métier de la médiation, Chef de mission (51 jours)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire supérieur, niveau Master en droit/sociologie ou diplôme équivalent et pertinent par rapport aux objectifs du contrat;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience professionnelle de 5 ans, en plus de celle indiquée comme expérience professionnelle générale, pourra compenser l’absence de master ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 12 ans d’expérience en tant que conseiller en médiation/médiateur auprès d’une institution homologue au sein de l’UE/EEE ou PEV ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience spécifique de 5 ans dans une institution similaire à l’IMR utilisant les Nouvelles Techniques d’Information et de Communication &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissance linguistique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne maîtrise de la langue française parlée et écrite;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;La connaissance de la langue arabe serait un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert  CAT  II, en gestion financière et administrative (120  jours  à  prester)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-cat-ii-en-gestion-financiere-et-administrative-120-jours-a-prester</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 05:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-cat-ii-en-gestion-financiere-et-administrative-120-jours-a-prester</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assistance Technique d&amp;#39;appui transversal au demarrage des activites du programme SAN&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général de la mission est de contribuer à l&amp;#39;opérationnalisation de la convention de financement du projet SAN 11ème FED.
L’objectif particulier est d’assurer une mise en œuvre rapide, effective et efficace des activités de démarrage du programme SAN (pré- et post- signature de la convention de financement), à travers des appuis à la coordination nationale et aux composantes sectorielles en matière de renforcement des capacités et de gestion- administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visits to the regions of&lt;/strong&gt;:  Ouaddaï, Wadi Fira, Guéra, Tandjilé, Logone occidental.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert  CAT  II, en gestion financière et administrative (120  jours  à  prester,  dont  115 au Tchad)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Formation *&lt;/em&gt;:
Une formation d&amp;#39;études supérieures sanctionnée par un diplôme d&amp;#39;au moins niveau Master (bac+5) en comptabilité, finance, business &amp;amp; administration, logistique ou autre diplôme équivalent / similaire&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 6 ans d&amp;#39;expérience professionnelle en appui à la gestion financière/administrative de projets et programmes dans les secteurs liés à la mission (développement rural au sens large, sécurité alimentaire, santé communautaire et nutrition, infrastructures rurales, développement local etc.).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience avérée (justifiée par au moins trois missions) en analyse des besoins en ressources humaines, définition des postes et profils, ainsi que formation, appui-conseil, renforcement des capacités.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans la mise en place d&amp;#39;un système efficace de gestion comptable et financière, y compris système de contrôle et reporting financier.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne connaissance des instruments UE pour le financement des actions extérieures et une parfaite maîtrise des règles et procédures FED, justifiée par au moins 4 missions d&amp;#39;expertise dans le cadre de projets et programme FED, préférablement en Afrique sub-saharienne, comprenant l&amp;#39;élaboration/gestion de devis-programmes, l&amp;#39;élaboration de DAO (y compris niveau international) et dossiers d&amp;#39;appels à propositions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans l&amp;#39;élaboration de procurement plans.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  La connaissance et/ou la familiarité avec le contexte national/régional, les institutions, les politiques nationales et stratégies sectorielles sera un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellente capacité analytique, de synthèse, de conception et de rédaction; bonne capacité de communication et de concertation avec des acteurs divers. Maîtrise des outils et des moyens de communication et visibilité.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Efficacité dans l&amp;#39;organisation du travail en fonction des objectifs à atteindre et des échéances, initiative, résilience au travail sous pression.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parfaite maîtrise du Français, écrit et oral.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;lina_forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWP 2 Projects Review</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Beyond WTO Program (B-WTO) was developed in response to a request from the Government of Vietnam (GoV) for donor support to help with managing economic integration and the transition to a market economy following WTO accession. The B-WTO goal is “to strengthen government’s capacity to manage the integration of Vietnam into the global economy and the transition of Vietnam to a socialist market economy”. The immediate objective is “implementation of priority policy actions from the GoV’s Action Plan to enhance Vietnam’s capacity to sustain pro-poor growth (GAP)”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The remit of this project was a review of the 2nd annual work plan’s implementation (AWP2) of Phase 2 of the B-WTO in May 2013. The objectives of the review were to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the project implementation performance and project results relative to the logical framework targets and evaluation criteria. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the results achieved at the Component and Program’s level according to the Monitoring and Evaluation (M&amp;amp;E) framework of the Program.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify lessons learned from implementation, make recommendations for the remaining duration of the program and the Independent Completion Report process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program 2013 Performance and Quality Mapping Exercise</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID’s PNG Program is looking to improve its performance and quality (P&amp;amp;Q) standards and systems. The purpose of this project was to map the PNG Program’s current P&amp;amp;Q capacity and systems, to address the risk of AusAID being unable to demonstrate results for its increased investments in PNG over the next four years. Over the last several years, the PNG Program has undertaken a number of M&amp;amp;E assessments and reviews which have identified key strengths and challenges within the program. This project was intended to pick up where these assessments left off. Through a desk review and consultations with sector teams, the Review Team were to distil key P&amp;amp;Q risks and issues for the PNG Program. The Review Team’s brief included the provision of recommendations on priority activities to support sector approaches to M&amp;amp;E, strengthen the Program’s ability to collect evidence, provide critical analysis and report on results.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID required a consultant to assist with the development and finalisation of its Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework. Development of a humanitarian monitoring and evaluation framework is a key commitment outlined in AusAID’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy (HAP) and its associated Implementation Plan. In line with the agency focus on results reporting, the HAP and HAP Implementation Plan commit AusAID to develop a monitoring and evaluation framework to support the initial performance assessment framework contained within the HAP and AusAID annual reporting under the Comprehensive Aid Policy Framework.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key objective of this assignment was to build the Humanitarian program’s capacity for monitoring and reporting results by:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In consultation with AusAID’s Humanitarian team, redraft and finalise the Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework, to ensure it provides a platform to:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track implementation of key commitments in Australia’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy; and,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish a set of measurable humanitarian performance indicators (in addition to the two CAPF indicators) to enable AusAID to track achievements, lessons learned and to report on the results achieved from AusAID’s humanitarian work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of Pacific Forum Compact Reporting</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The purpose of the assignment was to examine country views of aid effectiveness and regional organisations expressed through Forum Compact reporting, particularly peer review of Forum Island Countries’ national development plan processes. The services provided included the preparation of a think piece which outlines key aid effectiveness issues arising from country reporting under the Compact reporting and discusses options for addressing these issues.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study on Community-based Social Protection</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/study-on-community-based-social-protection</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/study-on-community-based-social-protection</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Poverty and Social Analysis is the process of using and generating evidence on poverty throughout the aid management cycle. Most poverty and social analysis focuses on economic and human capital, but there are two oft neglected elements: voice and influence, and social capital. Yet more and more development practitioners are recognizing the importance of social capital, particularly informal social capital, in preventing and addressing poverty and vulnerability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This project supported AusAID to explore:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the role of informal social capital in the Fijian context and whether it lends itself to fair redistribution of resources and, if so, the ways in which AusAID can engage with local communities to strengthen existing social capital structures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;how such structures can enable the disempowered and poor to claim their entitlements in the three domains discussed in the PSA framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the potential challenges that can arise from such efforts. For instance, the poorest are often included on less favorable terms within social networks, and have access to fewer and lower-quality networks. Further, we need to better understand how poverty and disempowerment intersect with an absence of informal social capital, the repercussions this has, and the options available for tackling this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Provision of a Child Protection Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/provision-of-a-child-protection-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/provision-of-a-child-protection-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For this project HTSPE was contracted to provide a child protection specialist and handle all the associated management and administrative work. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The child protection specialist provided by HTSPE was required to work on an assignment designed to assist the Pacific Division (PACD) to improve its approach to child protection and managing risks to children. AusAID has a number of partners in the Pacific who work with children or come into contact with children through their activities. The AusAID-wide child protection stocktake, conducted in May 2013 found that there are a number of organisations funded by AusAID in the Pacific with a high or very high inherent child protection risk. Consistent with the stocktake report PACD proposes to escalate efforts to ensure partner organisations policies, procedures and practices are in accordance with AusAID’s Child Protection Policy 2013 and to make child protection a more explicit focus of PACD’s risk management system.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Environment and Biology Expert (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/opportunities/senior-environment-and-biology-expert-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 20:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/opportunities/senior-environment-and-biology-expert-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Expert 2 is expected to contribute the implementation of all of the related modules and the preparation of both training materials and Training Evaluation Report in the context of related chapter/s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in Biology, Ecology, Chemistry or other Natural Sciences related to assignment. In the absence of the degree required, at least 17 years of professional experience in the related areas is requested.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good command of both written and spoken English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General professional experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in the sector(s) related to the Lot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience in technical and/or scientific fields required for the implementation of the Water Framework Directive and/or Habitat Directive and/or other related Directives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 river basin management plans experience in terms of setting of environmental objectives and/or setting, design and upgrade of biological monitoring programme and/or execution and assessment of biological monitoring.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in development of measures for water pollution reduction and/or improving ecological status, and/or river basin characterisation/analysis will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in projects related to Integrated Water Resources Management will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
