<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 21:04:46 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>TL/Senior Expert in Gender Equality and Women&#39;s Empowerment or Sexual and Reproductive Health/Rights (or similar field) </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/tl-senior-expert-in-gender-equality-and-womens-empowerment-or-sexual-and-reproductive-health-rights-or-similar-field</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 21:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/tl-senior-expert-in-gender-equality-and-womens-empowerment-or-sexual-and-reproductive-health-rights-or-similar-field</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preventing Sexual and Gender Based Violence against Women and Girls in Developing Countries&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To provide technical support to the European Commission services in order to reach the global objective, as regards both the technical and the financial assessment of the received proposals. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TL/Senior Expert in Gender Equality and Women&amp;rsquo;s Empowerment or Sexual and Reproductive Health/Rights (or similar field)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The team leader must have university degree of relevant discipline and at least 12 years of professional experience in Gender Equality and women&amp;rsquo;s&amp;#39; empowerment and sexual and reproductive health and rights or in human rights or any other related relevant sector. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of professional experience from developing countries, 5 years of working with civil society organisations or other non-state actors as well as have demonstrated knowledge on EC policies and programmes is required. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience as team leader is preferable. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have good command of English or French with ability to read proposals and review the quality of proposal assessments in both languages. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category II:  Economic/Business expert </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-economic-business-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 20:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-economic-business-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drafting a Feasibility Study for Establishment of Science and Technology Park&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project is to improve the current innovation ecosystem in the country by strengthening the cooperation among academia, industry and government. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project shall develop a comprehensive Feasibility study and Action plan for the establishment and operation of a Science and Technology Park (STP) aiming to strengthen the country’s innovation capacities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert category II:  Economic/business expert (40 working days)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education of at least Master Degree Academic level, in Economic or Business Administration, or general professional experience of 3 (three) years above the minimum general professional experience requested below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of general professional experience in economics or business administration in preparation of business models/plans and/or cost-benefit analysis. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least two (2) project for preparation of cost-benefit analysis for construction of science or technology parks, or economic and industrial zones. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language Skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English, both written and spoken. Knowledge of the Macedonian language is an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&quot;&gt;gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category II: Architect/Civil Engineer </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-architect-civil-engineer</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-architect-civil-engineer</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drafting a Feasibility Study for Establishment of Science and Technology Park&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project is to improve the current innovation ecosystem in the country by strengthening the cooperation among academia, industry and government. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project shall develop a comprehensive Feasibility study and Action plan for the establishment and operation of a Science and Technology Park (STP) aiming to strengthen the country’s innovation capacities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert Category II: Architect/Civil Engineer (40 working days)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education at least Master Degree Academic level, in Architecture or Engineering, or general professional experience of 3 (three) years above the minimum general professional experience requested below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of general professional experience in architecture or civil engineering in preparations of architectural/construction project designs. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least two (2) projects in preparation of architectural and urban design for construction of science and technology parks or economic and industrial zones;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English, both written and spoken. Knowledge of the Macedonian language is an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&quot;&gt;gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category I: Science Technology Park Expert (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-science-technology-park-expert-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 20:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-science-technology-park-expert-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drafting a Feasibility Study for Establishment of Science and Technology Park&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project is to improve the current innovation ecosystem in the country by strengthening the cooperation among academia, industry and government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project shall develop a comprehensive Feasibility study and Action plan for the establishment and operation of a Science and Technology Park (STP) aiming to strengthen the country’s innovation capacities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert Category I: STP Expert (70 working days)/ to act also as a Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further to his/her overall project management and coordination, project representation, as well as reporting. He/she should ensure that the project outputs and reporting requirements are timely fulfilled. He/she shall will coordinate, supervise, manage, monitor and appraise all aspects of the project experts’ output.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education of at least Master Degree Academic level , in engineering, economics or business administration, or general professional experience of 3 (three) years above the minimum general professional experience requested below. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of general professional experience in engineering, economy or business administration or similar, in business modelling, preparations of business plans/studies. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least two (2) projects related to preparation of Feasibility Study for Science and/or Technology Park, or preparation of STP model analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt; 
Fluency in English, both written and spoken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&quot;&gt;gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legal/Judicial/Security Reform Expert with Police/Judiciary or Justice Ministry Experience</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/legal-judicial-security-reform-expert-with-police-judiciary-or-justice-ministry-experience</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/legal-judicial-security-reform-expert-with-police-judiciary-or-justice-ministry-experience</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identification and Formulation Mission - Rule of Law - Fata, KP and Balochistan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; is to assist the EU Delegation in the design of a programme under the AAP 2018 to reinforce the rule of law in KP, FATA and Balochistan. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Legal/Judicial/Security Reform Expert with Police/Judiciary or Justice Ministry Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s Degree in law, political science, international relations or any relevant disciplines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Experience *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 6 years of relevant professional experience in programs related to rule of Law, judicial or security reform, particularly direct experience working with the Police, Judiciary, Line Ministries for justice or related fields.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proven knowledge of the socio-political situation in Pakistan and particularly in KP and FATA is required&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proven working experience in rule of law and justice or security sector in Pakistan and particularly in KP and FATA would be a distinct advantage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strong communication skills and proven record of multi-stakeholder consultations and cooperation with donors, international organisations, public administrations and civil society in the sector;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strong inter-personal and presentation skills, awareness of cultural sensitivities;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ability to independently solve complex and challenging problems;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strong report writing skills, using a clear and concise language, structuring written presentations;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Urdu/Pashtun would be an asset&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader, Senior Expert in Rule of Law, Justice or Security Sector and/or Police Reform</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-expert-in-rule-of-law-justice-or-security-sector-and-or-police-reform</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 17:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-expert-in-rule-of-law-justice-or-security-sector-and-or-police-reform</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identification and Formulation Mission Rule of Law - Fata, KP and Balochistan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; is to assist the EU Delegation in the design of a programme under the AAP 2018 to reinforce the rule of law in KP, FATA and Balochistan. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader, Senior Expert in Rule of Law, Justice or Security Sector and/or Police Reform&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s Degree in law, political science, international relations or any relevant disciplines &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specialisation course in security sector reform, rule of law or justice reform would be an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Experience *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 12 years of relevant professional experience, including at least five years in a senior positions in an international development role in Rule of Law, justice or security sector and/or police reform;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Professional experience in countries with holistic approaches to security sector reform and rule of law, including experience working with the major stakeholders is required;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proven track record of developing rule of law programme in fragile situations in Europe or South Asia is desirable and knowledge of the political context of KP an FATA in Pakistan will be a distinct advantage;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowledge of the International and EU policy documents relevant to Rule of law and security sector reform programming in situations of fragility &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous experience in EU programming documents such as identification fiches, action documents and all the related annexes is required&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strong communication skills and proven record of multi-stakeholder consultations and cooperation with donors, international organisations, public administrations and civil society in the sector;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strong inter-personal and presentation skills, awareness of cultural sensitivities;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ability to independently solve complex and challenging problems;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strong report writing skills, using a clear and concise language, structuring written presentations;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation Expert specialised in Local Development and Local Governance</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/evaluation-expert-specialised-in-local-development-and-local-governance</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 16:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/evaluation-expert-specialised-in-local-development-and-local-governance</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation - Support to Public Administration Reform and Local Development&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Systematic and timely evaluation of its programmes and activities is an established priority of the European Commission. The focus of evaluations is on the assessment of achievements, the quality and the results of Actions in the context of an evolving cooperation policy with an increasing emphasis on result-oriented approaches. From this perspective, evaluations should look for evidence of why, whether or how these results are linked to the EU intervention and seek to identify the factors driving or hindering progress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evaluations should provide an understanding of the cause and effects links between inputs and activities, and outputs, outcomes and impacts. Evaluations should serve accountability, decision making, and learning and management purposes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main objectives of this evaluation are to provide the relevant services of the European Union, the interested stakeholders with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an overall independent assessment of the past performance of the &amp;lsquo;Support to Public Administration Reform and Local Development&amp;rsquo; Programme, paying particular attention to its [in case of a mid-term evaluation you may add ‘intermediate’] results measured against its objectives;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Key lessons and recommendations in order to improve current performance of the programme and to provide an insight into future cooperation with Egypt in the sectors of interventions. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In particular, this evaluation will serve in assessing key elements of relevance, effectiveness, efficiency, sustainability, and early signs of impact among other important criteria.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main users of this evaluation will be the European Union and the Government of Egypt (GoE) represented by key beneficiaries and stakeholders of the programme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 6 months&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 3 – Evaluation Expert specialised in Local Development and Local Governance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The expert should have at least a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in a domain relevant to the assignment (e.g. local governance, Public Administration, public management, or other relevant field of Social Sciences) or, in its absence, a Bachelor Degree and an additional equivalent professional experience of at least three years working on development projects in areas related to the programme to be evaluated. The equivalent experience must be above the general experience duration fixed below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional experience and competencies:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of proven professional experience in fields of Development Cooperation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record of specific professional experience in local development and decentralisation reforms. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in evaluating cooperation programmes, especially EU funded interventions, with focus on local development / local governance / decentralisation. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least one assignment in capacity building, particularly in the field of local development and training capacities in fields of local governance and decentralisation. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analytical and methodological skills, excellent interpersonal and communications skills, as well as the ability to function in sensitive contexts. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working in ENP countries, especially those of the ENP South, will be considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English (speaking and writing skills).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of the Arabic language (speaking and writing skills) will be considered an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category I: Evaluation Expert specialised in PFM Reform </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-evaluation-expert-specialised-in-pfm-reform</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 16:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-evaluation-expert-specialised-in-pfm-reform</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation - Support to Public Administration Reform and Local Development&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Systematic and timely evaluation of its programmes and activities is an established priority of the European Commission. The focus of evaluations is on the assessment of achievements, the quality and the results of Actions in the context of an evolving cooperation policy with an increasing emphasis on result-oriented approaches. From this perspective, evaluations should look for evidence of why, whether or how these results are linked to the EU intervention and seek to identify the factors driving or hindering progress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evaluations should provide an understanding of the cause and effects links between inputs and activities, and outputs, outcomes and impacts. Evaluations should serve accountability, decision making, and learning and management purposes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main objectives of this evaluation are to provide the relevant services of the European Union, the interested stakeholders with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an overall independent assessment of the past performance of the &amp;lsquo;Support to Public Administration Reform and Local Development&amp;rsquo; Programme, paying particular attention to its [in case of a mid-term evaluation you may add ‘intermediate’] results measured against its objectives;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Key lessons and recommendations in order to improve current performance of the programme and to provide an insight into future cooperation with Egypt in the sectors of interventions. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In particular, this evaluation will serve in assessing key elements of relevance, effectiveness, efficiency, sustainability, and early signs of impact among other important criteria.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main users of this evaluation will be the European Union and the Government of Egypt (GoE) represented by key beneficiaries and stakeholders of the programme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 6 months&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2 - Category I: Evaluation Expert specialised in PFM Reform&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The expert should have at least a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in a domain relevant to the assignment (e.g. public finance management, development Economics, Public Administration, public management, or other relevant field of Social Sciences) or, in its absence, a Bachelor Degree and an additional equivalent professional experience of at least three years working on development projects in areas related to the programme to be evaluated. The equivalent experience must be above the general experience duration fixed below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional experience and competencies:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of proven professional experience in fields of Development Cooperation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record of specific professional experience in public finance management. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in evaluating cooperation programmes, especially EU funded interventions, with focus on public finance management / economic development. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least one assignment in capacity building, particularly in the field of strengthening public finance management.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analytical and methodological skills, excellent interpersonal and communications skills, as well as the ability to function in sensitive contexts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working in ENP countries, especially those of the ENP South, will be considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English (speaking and writing skills).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of the Arabic language (speaking and writing skills) will be considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation Expert (Team Leader) and Expert in Governance Reform</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/evaluation-expert-team-leader-and-expert-in-governance-reform</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/evaluation-expert-team-leader-and-expert-in-governance-reform</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation - Support to Public Administration Reform and Local Development&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Systematic and timely evaluation of its programmes and activities is an established priority of the European Commission. The focus of evaluations is on the assessment of achievements, the quality and the results of Actions in the context of an evolving cooperation policy with an increasing emphasis on result-oriented approaches. From this perspective, evaluations should look for evidence of why, whether or how these results are linked to the EU intervention and seek to identify the factors driving or hindering progress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evaluations should provide an understanding of the cause and effects links between inputs and activities, and outputs, outcomes and impacts. Evaluations should serve accountability, decision making, and learning and management purposes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main objectives of this evaluation are to provide the relevant services of the European Union, the interested stakeholders with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an overall independent assessment of the past performance of the &amp;lsquo;Support to Public Administration Reform and Local Development&amp;rsquo; Programme, paying particular attention to its [in case of a mid-term evaluation you may add ‘intermediate’] results measured against its objectives;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Key lessons and recommendations in order to improve current performance of the programme and to provide an insight into future cooperation with Egypt in the sectors of interventions. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In particular, this evaluation will serve in assessing key elements of relevance, effectiveness, efficiency, sustainability, and early signs of impact among other important criteria.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main users of this evaluation will be the European Union and the Government of Egypt (GoE) represented by key beneficiaries and stakeholders of the programme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 6 months&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 1 - Category 1: Evaluation Expert (Team Leader) and Expert in Governance Reform&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The expert should have at least a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in a domain relevant to the assignment (e.g. Public Administration, public management, development Economics, or other relevant field of Social Sciences) or, in its absence, a Bachelor Degree and an additional equivalent professional experience of at least three years working on development projects in areas related to the programme to be evaluated. The equivalent experience must be above the general experience duration fixed below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional experience and competencies&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of proven professional experience in fields of Development Cooperation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record of specific professional experience at least in governance, including in public administration / administrative reform. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in evaluating cooperation programmes, especially EU funded interventions. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record of assignments as Team Leader of development cooperation funded assignments. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least one assignment in capacity building, particularly in the field of strengthening public services. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analytical and methodological skills, excellent interpersonal and communications skills, as well as the ability to function in sensitive contexts. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working in ENP countries, especially those of the ENP South, will be considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English (speaking and writing skills).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of the Arabic language (speaking and writing skills) will be considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Systems Analysis Expert </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/systems-analysis-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/systems-analysis-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation for Assistance to Agriculture in the West Bank (AAWB) and Private Sector Reconstruction Gaza Agriculture (PSRG-A) Programmes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The AAWB programme entered into full scale implementation aiming to serve about 400 final beneficiaries as well as the PSRG-A programme may serve about 400 final beneficiaries too. In total the estimated number of final beneficiaries is estimated at 800.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DESCRIPTION OF THE EVALUATION ASSIGNMENT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Type of evaluation&lt;/strong&gt; Mid-term Evaluation
&lt;strong&gt;Coverage *&lt;em&gt;AAWB and PSRG-A Programmes under three decisions
*&lt;/em&gt;Geographic scope&lt;/strong&gt; West Bank and Gaza Strip
&lt;strong&gt;Period to be evaluated&lt;/strong&gt; The entire period&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 120 days&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Systems Analysis Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:
*&lt;em&gt;Education *&lt;/em&gt;: at least a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Management Information Systems (MIS), Business Administration, Economics or other cognate discipline; OR equivalent professional experience of 6 years (above the general professional experience duration fixed below) in an area of systems analysis and assessment related to public sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years professional experience in the management and/or evaluation of projects in the fields of development aid.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years&amp;#39; experience in MIS systems analysis of the public sector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience of working in a development policy environment in fragile or conflict affected regions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agriculture Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/agriculture-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 11:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/agriculture-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation for Assistance to Agriculture in the West Bank (AAWB) and Private Sector Reconstruction Gaza Agriculture (PSRG-A) Programmes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The AAWB programme entered into full scale implementation aiming to serve about 400 final beneficiaries as well as the PSRG-A programme may serve about 400 final beneficiaries too. In total the estimated number of final beneficiaries is estimated at 800.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DESCRIPTION OF THE EVALUATION ASSIGNMENT&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Type of evaluation&lt;/strong&gt; Mid-term Evaluation
&lt;strong&gt;Coverage AAWB and PSRG&lt;/strong&gt; - A Programmes under three decisions
&lt;strong&gt;Geographic scope&lt;/strong&gt; West Bank and Gaza Strip
&lt;strong&gt;Period to be evaluated&lt;/strong&gt; The entire period&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 120 days&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agriculture Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:
&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt; at least a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree Agriculture or other cognate discipline; *&lt;em&gt;OR *&lt;/em&gt;equivalent professional experience of 6 years (above the general professional experience duration fixed below) in an area of
related to agribusinesses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years professional experience in the management and / or evaluation of projects in the fields of development aid.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 year experience in agribusinesses implementation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience of working in a development policy environment in fragile or conflict affected regions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Private Sector Development (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-private-sector-development-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 11:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-private-sector-development-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation for Assistance to Agriculture in the West Bank (AAWB) and Private Sector Reconstruction Gaza Agriculture (PSRG-A) Programmes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The AAWB programme entered into full scale implementation aiming to serve about 400 final beneficiaries as well as the PSRG-A programme may serve about 400 final beneficiaries too. In total the estimated number of final beneficiaries is estimated at 800.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DESCRIPTION OF THE EVALUATION ASSIGNMENT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;nd PSRG-A Programmes under three decisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Geographic scope West Bank and Gaza Strip&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Period to be evaluated The entire period&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 120 days&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in Private Sector Development – Team leader&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education at least a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Business Administration, Economics or Agricultural Engineering or&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;other cognate discipline; OR equivalent professional experience of 6 years (above the general professional experience duration fixed below) in an area of private sector development related to &lt;strong&gt;microfinance&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years professional experience in the management and/or evaluation of projects in the fields of development aid.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years&amp;#39; experience in managing and/or delivering micro-finance similar projects/programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years&amp;#39; experience of evaluation similar programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the EC&amp;rsquo;s implementing rules and guidelines (including DEVCO evaluation approach and methodology: &lt;a href=&quot;https://ec.europa.eu/europeaid/evaluation/methodology_en&quot;&gt;https://ec.europa.eu/europeaid/evaluation/methodology_en&lt;/a&gt;);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience leading evaluation teams;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent coordination and team management skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience of working in a development policy environment in fragile or conflict affected regions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category I Expert – Water Resources Engineer </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-expert-water-resources-engineer</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 12:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-expert-water-resources-engineer</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identification and Formulation Mission for the Revival of Balochistan Water Resources Programme&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this assignment is to assist the EU Delegation in identifying and formulating a realistic demand driven programme for the Revival of Balochistan Water Resources Programme. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; is to assist the EU Delegation in drafting an Identification Fiche, Action Document for the Revival of Baluchistan Water Resources Programme of €65 million, (€50 million from the EU and €15 million from blending facility) to be approved by the headquarters within the year 2018. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category I Expert – Water Resources Engineer&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A University degree in Civil, Agriculture or Water Resources Engineering or a relevant, directly related discipline. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post graduate studies and/or trainings in the areas related to water sector development will be considered an advantage. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full working knowledge of English and excellent report writing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of professional experience is required in water sector development programme, on-farm water management and high irrigation efficiency system, water conservation and rain water harvesting, canal water including control of surface water, mini dams and recharge of ground water techniques. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 8 years of professional experience is required in the developing countries on water sector programmes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of experience as a team member for conducting identification and formulation of water sector projects with the government authorities, coordinating with donors and civil society organizations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferably required professional experience in Pakistan or South Asian countries, Afghanistan, Bangladesh, Bhutan, India, Maldives and Sri Lanka.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven capacity to adapt to hard working conditions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of undertaking a minimum of 8 identification and/or formulation of programmes in support of water sector and/or agriculture development in at least 3 different countries. Such experience will be considered more relevant if referring to a minimum of 3 EU-funded interventions and if specifically applied to water conservation, water saving techniques for irrigated agriculture and recharge of ground water and/or to South Asia or water stressed countries. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in policy setting/drafting preferably in a field related to water related programmes or poverty reduction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working with government planning and development, finance and other relevant line departments is preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good understanding of EU external cooperation policies and instruments and in particular of the above mentioned relevant sectors EU policy and procedure is necessary. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound knowledge of Project Cycle Management (PCM). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in identifying and formulation missions of EU.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Water Sector Development Expert (Economist - Team Leader) </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/water-sector-development-expert-economist-team-leader</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/water-sector-development-expert-economist-team-leader</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identification and Formulation Mission for the Revival of Balochistan Water Resources Programme&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this assignment is to assist the EU Delegation in identifying and formulating a realistic demand driven programme for the Revival of Balochistan Water Resources Programme. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; is to assist the EU Delegation in drafting an Identification Fiche, Action Document for the Revival of Baluchistan Water Resources Programme of €65 million, (€50 million from the EU and €15 million from blending facility) to be approved by the headquarters within the year 2018. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Expert I – Water Sector Development Expert (Economist - Team Leader)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; will be responsible for overall assignment, coordination with the relevant partners along with the other team member.  The Team Leader will be the focal point of contact for the EU Delegation. The Team Leader will also present the Aide Memoire and lead the meetings with the line agencies and relevant organizations involved in the water sector of Baluchistan. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A University degree in Development Economics, Public Policy and Administration, Public Finance Management, Development Studies, or a relevant, directly related discipline. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post graduate studies and/or specific training in related areas will be considered an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full working knowledge of English and excellent report writing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of professional experience is required in one or more of the following fields: water development programme, water resource management, agriculture and on-farm water management, planning and administration. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 8 years of professional experience is required in the developing countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of experience as Team Leader for conducting identification and formulation of water sector projects with the government authorities, coordinating with donors and civil society organizations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferably required professional experience in Pakistan or South Asian countries, Afghanistan, Bangladesh, Bhutan, India, Maldives and Sri Lanka.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven capacity to adapt to hard working conditions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven 5 years managerial skills as far as orienting a mission, analyzing complex situations, relating professionally and efficiently with multiple stakeholders over a limited duration of time, drafting possible and feasible scenarios. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of undertaking a minimum of 8 identification and/or formulation of programmes in support of water sector and/or agriculture development in at least 3 different countries. Such experience will be considered more relevant if referring to a minimum of 3 EU-funded interventions and if specifically applied to water and agriculture and/or to South Asia or water stressed countries. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in policy setting/drafting preferably in a field related to water or poverty reduction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working with government planning and development, finance and other relevant line departments is preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good understanding of EU external cooperation policies and instruments and in particular of the above mentioned relevant sectors EU policy and procedure is necessary. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound knowledge of Project Cycle Management (PCM).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in identification and formulation missions of EU&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pool of Experts, IDDF Advisory Services</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/pool-of-experts-iddf-advisory-services</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 13:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/pool-of-experts-iddf-advisory-services</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IDDF Advisory Services&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;overall objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the project is to further develop and apply the Integrated Decentralisation Diagnostic Framework (IDDF).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: December 2017 to October 2018&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A &lt;strong&gt;Pool of Experts&lt;/strong&gt; with the same profile will be required in the application of the IDDF in &lt;strong&gt;6 selected countries&lt;/strong&gt; (to be confirmed).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;professional experience in development cooperation / international relations;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience in the design and implementation of programs aiming at supporting decentralisation reforms, local development and Local Governance in developing countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience as a coordinator of teams implementing support programs in the field of decentralisation, local Governance and/or Local development in partner countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in designing and conducting studies and analysis in fields related the assignment, and in drafting related terms of references;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in mainstreaming of local authorities in overall EU development cooperation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound knowledge of EC aid modalities (budget support, project approach) as well as aid delivery mechanism;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;professional experience in organising and delivering seminars and workshop related to decentralisation reforms, local and territorial development, territorial approaches and the mainstreaming of LAs in EU supported programs and projects with excellent facilitation and presentation skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent drafting and oral presentation skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in the context of the Thematic Programme CSO-LA and/or its predecessor will be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English, French and Spanish. Portuguese will be an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&quot;&gt;Gabriela_Georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader, Senior Expert in Decentralisation/Local Development/Governance </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-expert-in-decentralisation-local-development-governance</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 13:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-expert-in-decentralisation-local-development-governance</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IDDF Advisory Services&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;overall objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the project is to further develop and apply the Integrated Decentralisation Diagnostic Framework (IDDF).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: December 2017 to October 2018&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader, Senior Expert in Decentralisation/Local Development/Governance (Category I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;37 days of input (tasked with managing the team of pool experts and updating the IDDF)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 12 year’s professional experience in development cooperation / international relations;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years’ experience in the design and implementation of programs aiming at supporting decentralisation reforms, local development and Local Governance in developing countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of experience as a coordinator of teams implementing support programs in the field of decentralisation, local Governance and/or Local development in partner countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in designing and conducting studies and analysis in fields related the assignment, and in drafting related terms of references;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in mainstreaming of local authorities in overall EU development cooperation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound knowledge of EC aid modalities (budget support, project approach) as well as aid delivery mechanism;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5 years’ professional experience in organising and delivering seminars and workshop related to decentralisation reforms, local and territorial development, territorial approaches and the mainstreaming of LAs in EU supported programs and projects with excellent facilitation and presentation skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent drafting and oral presentation skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in the context of the Thematic Programme CSO-LA and/or its predecessor will be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English, French and Spanish. Portuguese will be an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&quot;&gt;Gabriela_Georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PFM Expert (Cat.I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/pfm-expert-cati</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/pfm-expert-cati</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Evaluation - Governance Programme in the Gambia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Final Evaluation of the Governance Programme using the DAC Criteria to examine the following components:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Access to Justice and Legal Education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Journalists and Media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Public Financial Management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mission&lt;/strong&gt;: Start 08/01/2018 – 26/01/2018 end 
&lt;strong&gt;Assignment&lt;/strong&gt;: Start 08/01/2018 - 09/03/2018 ends&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PFM Expert - category I&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;: At least Master Degree in Economics, or PFM, or Public Administration, or another relevant field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: A minimum of 12 years&amp;#39; experience, in the various disciplines of PFM, PFM reform, research and PFM/fiscal policy formulation and dialogue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: Experience in evaluation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;: Fluent in English (spoken and written).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&quot;&gt;Gabriela_Georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader - Governance Expert (Cat.I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-governance-expert-cati</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 17:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-governance-expert-cati</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Evaluation - Governance Programme in the Gambia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Final Evaluation of the Governance Programme using the DAC Criteria to examine the following components:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Access to Justice and Legal Education&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Journalists and Media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Public Financial Management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mission&lt;/strong&gt;: Start 08/01/2018 – 26/01/2018 end 
&lt;strong&gt;Assignment&lt;/strong&gt;: Start 08/01/2018 - 09/03/2018 ends&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader - Governance Expert - category I&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;: At least Master Degree in Public Administration, or Law, or Promotion and protection of human rights, or another field relevant to Governance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: A minimum of 12 years&amp;#39; experience in at least one of the various disciplines of Governance, Promotion and protection of fundamental human rights,Democratisation processes (incl. civic education), Reinforcement of the rule of law, Reform of judiciary, Free independent and economically viable media and freedom of expression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: Experience in evaluation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;: Fluent in English (spoken and written).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&quot;&gt;Gabriela_Georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security Expert (CAT I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/security-expert-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 16:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/security-expert-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Study to identify areas of beneficial cooperation between CARIFORM and Latin America in the area of Crime and Security&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To undertake a study to identify possible areas of beneficial cooperation between CARIFORUM and Latin America, including concrete entry points for Caribbean participation in existing EU continental cooperation programmes with Latin America in the area of Crime and Security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KE1: Security Expert (CAT I)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post graduate qualifications (at least a Master’s degree) or equivalent (or, in its absence,equivalent professional experience – see also below) in Security Studies, Law, Political Sciences, or related fields;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid analytical skills, particularly the ability to conduct research and prepare appropriate findings and conclusions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent interpersonal and communication skills (both oral and written), including demonstrated tact in intercultural communication;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to build trust across cultural lines;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent report writing skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong planning and organisation skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency/mastery in oral and written English and at least effective operational proficiency in Spanish;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer literacy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least twelve (12) years’ experience in the security sector, but in the absence of postgraduate qualifications at least four more years of relevant professional experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience at a senior or advisory level in either Government, a relevant international or regional organisation would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the security sector reform in an international environment;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct experience in statistical analysis and research in a developing country context;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Up-to-date and comprehensive knowledge and experience of EU development policies and instruments;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of EU practices in development programmes related to the sector would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous consulting and relevant experience of working in Latin America and/or the Caribbean.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&quot;&gt;Gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>International Relations Specialist or Economic Development Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/international-relations-specialist-or-economic-development-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 12:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/international-relations-specialist-or-economic-development-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Consultancy to develop a framework for an effective platform for structured and continuous FCORs/OCTS/CARIFORUM dialogue at the political and technical level&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the Programme is to deepen and strengthen cooperation and contribute to the sustainable social and economic development of the Wider Caribbean Region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; is to design a framework for structured and continuous dialogue to strengthen political, economic and technical cooperation between the Caribbean Forum of the African, Caribbean and Pacific States (CARIFORUM), the FCORs and OCTs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key expert 2: International Relations Specialist or Economic Development Specialist&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master’s Degree in International Relations, International Development Policy, Development Economics, Business/Public Administration or related discipline;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OR in its absence not less than three (3) years&amp;#39; relevant experience in addition to the 12 years professional experience required below&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the economic, social and political development realities in the CARIFORUM/FCOR/OCT context would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English (written and spoken) and good articulation in French is required. Articulation in Spanish and/or Dutch would be a further asset but is not necessary. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 12-years relevant development cooperation and regional integration experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in formulation, organization, planning, and/or implementation of regional economic and political cooperation and collaboration policy and related activities, including knowledge and experience of related EDF procedures and processes; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated professional experience in the fostering of inter-agency and inter-governmental relations, including the formulation of policy for the promotion of regional cooperation, collaboration and integration, at both the technical and political levels;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in relevant institutional strengthening and reform processes; such experience in a general Caribbean regional cooperation context would be a plus. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience as a Team Leader in relevant regional cooperation processes; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Caribbean Regional Integration processes and the EU/CARIFORUM EPA process will be an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
