<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 14:30:10 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experts on Peace Building in Post Conflict Scenarios</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-on-peace-building-in-post-conflict-scenarios</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-on-peace-building-in-post-conflict-scenarios</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation of IcSP actions supporting the Colombian Peace Process&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In particular, this evaluation will serve to assess the contribution made by the IcSP (financial and political) to the EU&amp;rsquo;s support to the Colombian Peace Process from 2015 until now, i.e. nearly two years after the signature of the final Peace Agreement, being the first two years critical for advancing in the implementation and contributing to sealing and protecting the gains achieved. The period of the evaluation therefore covers both the negotiation phase at its most difficult point in time, and includes the delicate period from the signature of the first Peace Agreement (26th September 2016), until the signature and ratification of the Final Agreement (24th November 2016) and its implementation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation will serve to measure the impact, timeliness and pertinence of the IcSP interventions and their results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;duration of the longest assignment&lt;/strong&gt; is 52 working days (most likely performed by the team leader), the total duration is 134 working days, including time for finalising the final report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experts on Peace Building in post conflict scenarios&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Security studies, Development, International Relations, Diplomacy, Political or Social sciences, Law, Public Administration or other relevant field related to this assignment; or, in its absence, equivalent professional experience of 5 years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years professional experience in the management and/or evaluation of projects in the fields of peace building in post conflict scenarios.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of professional experience in work/evaluation on peace building in post conflict scenarios. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience on the peace building in Colombia.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience of project cycle management (PCM) application, monitoring and evaluation of projects preferably in the field of crisis, post-crisis assistance or development, notably in fragile states and/or countries prone to political instability, man-made disasters, and in particular those funded by the EU;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the evaluation of complex and politically sensitive projects in a conflict or conflict prone contexts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;   Excellent command of Spanish (written and spoken)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following knowledge and experience constitute additional assets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience with evaluation of IfS or IcSP funded interventions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience with the political and socio-economic context in Colombia.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good command of English (written and spoken)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3861&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3861&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader, Expert on Crisis and/ or Post-Conflict Related Interventions</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-expert-on-crisis-and-or-post-conflict-related-interventions</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-expert-on-crisis-and-or-post-conflict-related-interventions</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation of IcSP actions supporting the Colombian Peace Process&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In particular, this evaluation will serve to assess the contribution made by the IcSP (financial and political) to the EU&amp;rsquo;s support to the Colombian Peace Process from 2015 until now, i.e. nearly two years after the signature of the final Peace Agreement, being the first two years critical for advancing in the implementation and contributing to sealing and protecting the gains achieved. The period of the evaluation therefore covers both the negotiation phase at its most difficult point in time, and includes the delicate period from the signature of the first Peace Agreement (26th September 2016), until the signature and ratification of the Final Agreement (24th November 2016) and its implementation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation will serve to measure the impact, timeliness and pertinence of the IcSP interventions and their results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category I expert: Team Leader, Expert on Crisis and/ or Post-Conflict Related Interventions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Development, International Relations, Diplomacy, Political or Social sciences, Law, Public Administration or other relevant field related to this assignment; or, in its absence, equivalent professional experience of 5 years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years professional experience in the management and/or evaluation of projects in the fields of crisis management/post-conflict related intervention, humanitarian aid and/or development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of professional experience in work/evaluation on crisis management, peace building in Colombia.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience of project cycle management (PCM) application, monitoring and evaluation of projects preferably in the field of crisis, post-crisis assistance or development, notably in fragile states and/or countries prone to political instability, man-made disasters, and in particular those funded by the EU;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in conducting evaluation / reviews / assessment of large-scale donor funded projects or programmes in a conflict or conflict prone context, in Colombia.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Soft skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent coordination and team management skills as evidenced by previous assignments;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communicating skills, in particular, liaising with different stakeholders (including diplomatic corps, Governmental officials, security agencies and civil society) as evidenced by previous assignments;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong capacity to quickly understand complex and changing circumstances as evidenced by previous assignments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of Spanish and English (written and spoken).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following knowledge and experience will constitute additional assets&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience with evaluation of IfS or IcSP funded interventions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the political and socio-economic context in Colombia;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Devco evaluation approach and methodology:
&lt;a href=&quot;https://ec.europa.eu/europeaid/evaluation/methodology_en&quot;&gt;https://ec.europa.eu/europeaid/evaluation/methodology_en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;duration of the longest assignment&lt;/strong&gt; is 52 working days (most likely performed by the team leader),the total duration is 134 working days, including time for finalising the final report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3861&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3861&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert in Development Cooperation/Project Evaluation</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-development-cooperation-project-evaluation</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 11:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-development-cooperation-project-evaluation</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final (ex post) Evaluation of Technical Assistance to OCTA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EVALUATION OBJECTIVES&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This final evaluation, which has been foreseen in the Technical and Administrative Provisions of the project’s Financing Agreement (see point 4.2 of Annex II to the Financing Agreement PTOREG/FED/21998), will provide the decision-makers of the beneficiary countries (OCTs), the relevant external co-operation services of the European Commission and the wider public with sufficient information to: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make an overall independent assessment about the performance of the project/programme (i.e. the technical assistance to OCTA), paying particularly attention to the impact of the project actions against its objectives; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify key lessons learned and propose practical recommendations/corrections for follow-up actions for future projects of similar nature including recommendations for potential adjustments; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the adequacy/weaknesses of the management structure and the methodology chosen for the implementation of the project. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the sustainability of the activities undertaken and/or initiated especially concerning the identified results of the project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2: (Category II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At minimum a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree Academic level in the field of social sciences, economic sciences, or engineering.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A post-degree specialisation in thematic issues related to development cooperation, institutional relations and, capacity building. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full command (excellent working knowledge and report writing) of English or French. Full command in both languages would be an added advantage. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General and specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of experience in the field of development cooperation projects including sound experience in evaluation of projects. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience working in OCTs would be an added advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid and proved practical work experience with principles and working methods of EC aid delivery methods and cycle of operations, in particular evaluation methodology.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3854&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3854&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert (TL) in Development Cooperation/Capacity Building </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-tl-in-development-cooperation-capacity-building</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-tl-in-development-cooperation-capacity-building</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final (ex post) Evaluation of Technical Assistance to OCTA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EVALUATION OBJECTIVES&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This final evaluation, which has been foreseen in the Technical and Administrative Provisions of the project’s Financing Agreement (see point 4.2 of Annex II to the Financing Agreement PTOREG/FED/21998), will provide the decision-makers of the beneficiary countries (OCTs), the relevant external co-operation services of the European Commission and the wider public with sufficient information to: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make an overall independent assessment about the performance of the project/programme (i.e. the technical assistance to OCTA), paying particularly attention to the impact of the project actions against its objectives; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify key lessons learned and propose practical recommendations/corrections for follow-up actions for future projects of similar nature including recommendations for potential adjustments; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the adequacy/weaknesses of the management structure and the methodology chosen for the implementation of the project. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the sustainability of the activities undertaken and/or initiated especially concerning the identified results of the project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team leader (Category I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At minimum a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree Academic level in the field of social sciences, economic sciences, or engineering.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A post-degree specialisation in thematic issues related to development cooperation, institutional relations and capacity building. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full command (excellent working knowledge and report writing) of English and French. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General and specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in the field of development cooperation projects in particular sound experience in preparation, management and evaluation of projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proved experience in institutional relations and capacity building.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of experience as team leader / project manager in OCTs would be an added advantage. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid and proved practical work experience with principles and working methods of EC aid delivery methods and cycle of operations, in particular evaluation methodology.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3854&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3854&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Public Finance Management Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-public-finance-management-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 11:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-public-finance-management-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to Public Finance Policy Reforms&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Systematic and timely evaluation of its programmes and activities is an established priority of the European Commission. The focus of evaluations is on the assessment of achievements, the quality and the results of Programme in the context of an evolving cooperation policy with an increasing emphasis on result-oriented approaches. From this perspective, evaluations should look for evidence of why, whether or how these results are linked to the EU intervention and seek to
identify the factors driving or hindering progress. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this evaluation is to provide the relevant services of the European Union, the interested stakeholders and the wider public with: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an overall independent assessment of the past performance of the &amp;ldquo;Support to Public Finance Policy Reforms in Moldova&amp;rdquo;, paying particular attention to its results measured against its objectives; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;key lessons and recommendations in order to improve future Programmes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In particular, this evaluation will serve the following specific objectives: to understand the performance of the Programme, its enabling factors and those hampering a proper delivery of results as to inform the planning of the future EU interventions and Programme(s) in the same sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation aims at assessing:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;to what extent PFPR programme has achieved its expected results, notably through contributing to the implementation of the partner government&amp;rsquo;s Public Finance Management Reform Strategy 2013-2020 sector strategies by providing opportunities for the improvement of national policy processes and policy implementation. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The evaluation should also specifically analyse how the budget support programme has contributed (or not) to strengthen PFM systems, including improved transparency within government systems, improved Domestic Revenues Mobilisation and stronger accountability. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The evaluation will also pay attention to other aid modalities (basket/common funds, projects), in order to assess the complementarity and synergy (or discrepancy) of these modalities with budget support.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It should also assess the impact of the budget support operation(s) on the M&amp;amp;E systems in the sectors supported by budget support. Budget support should aim to strengthen the monitoring systems in the sectors it supports, in alignment with the existing national level monitoring and evaluation systems, and contribute to the improved availability and credibility of data. Availability of the robust progress reports by the government, providing results information against targets set under the strategy, and the use of these reports to facilitate informed policy dialogue between the different stakeholders (CSOs, SAI,Parliament, donors) and evidence based decision making is one indicator of the capacity of the government in the area of M/E.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert II Public Finance Management Specialist, Category I&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in the field of economy, public finance management, public administration or other field relevant to the assignment or, in its absence, 5 years of equivalent professional experience in the fields mentioned above on top of the general professional experience specified below,;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: 
At least 12 years&amp;#39; experience in public finance management;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of experience in managing and/or implementing and/or monitoring and/or evaluating budget support in public finance management; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in projects implemented in the current IPA or ENI countries will be an advantage. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of written and spoken English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Romanian or Russian will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3855&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3855&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Public Administration Reform/Finance Management (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-public-administration-reform-finance-management-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 11:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-public-administration-reform-finance-management-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to Public Finance Policy Reforms&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Systematic and timely evaluation of its programmes and activities is an established priority of the European Commission. The focus of evaluations is on the assessment of achievements, the quality and the results of Programme in the context of an evolving cooperation policy with an increasing emphasis on result-oriented approaches. From this perspective, evaluations should look for evidence of why, whether or how these results are linked to the EU intervention and seek to
identify the factors driving or hindering progress. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this evaluation is to provide the relevant services of the European Union, the interested stakeholders and the wider public with: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an overall independent assessment of the past performance of the &amp;ldquo;Support to Public Finance Policy Reforms in Moldova&amp;rdquo;, paying particular attention to its results measured against its objectives; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;key lessons and recommendations in order to improve future Programmes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In particular, this evaluation will serve the following specific objectives: to understand the performance of the Programme, its enabling factors and those hampering a proper delivery of results as to inform the planning of the future EU interventions and Programme(s) in the same sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation aims at assessing:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;to what extent PFPR programme has achieved its expected results, notably through contributing to the implementation of the partner government&amp;rsquo;s Public Finance Management Reform Strategy 2013-2020 sector strategies by providing opportunities for the improvement of national policy processes and policy implementation. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The evaluation should also specifically analyse how the budget support programme has contributed (or not) to strengthen PFM systems, including improved transparency within government systems, improved Domestic Revenues Mobilisation and stronger accountability. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The evaluation will also pay attention to other aid modalities (basket/common funds, projects), in order to assess the complementarity and synergy (or discrepancy) of these modalities with budget support.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It should also assess the impact of the budget support operation(s) on the M&amp;amp;E systems in the sectors supported by budget support. Budget support should aim to strengthen the monitoring systems in the sectors it supports, in alignment with the existing national level monitoring and evaluation systems, and contribute to the improved availability and credibility of data. Availability of the robust progress reports by the government, providing results information against targets set under the strategy, and the use of these reports to facilitate informed policy dialogue between the different stakeholders (CSOs, SAI,Parliament, donors) and evidence based decision making is one indicator of the capacity of the government in the area of M/E.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert I, Team Leader, Category I&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in the field of economy, public finance management, public administration or other field relevant to the assignment or, in its absence, 5 years of equivalent professional experience in the fields mentioned above on top of the general professional experience specified below,;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least 12 years&amp;#39; experience in design and/or, implementation and/ or evaluation of public administration reforms or public finance management reforms&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of experience in evaluation of budget support programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in managing and/or implementing and/or monitoring and/or evaluating budget support in public finance management will constitute an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in evaluating projects implemented in the current Instrument for pre-accession (IPA) or European Neighbourhood Instrument (ENI) countries will be an advantage. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of written and spoken English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Romanian or Russian will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3855&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3855&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert Senior en dans le Domaine de la Gouvernance Locale et de Développement Local/Rural</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-senior-en-dans-le-domaine-de-la-gouvernance-locale-et-de-developpement-local-rural</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-senior-en-dans-le-domaine-de-la-gouvernance-locale-et-de-developpement-local-rural</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assistance technique pour les autorites locales relative aux actions sous la ligne thematique DCI/ANE/OSCAL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectifs généraux&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général de ce marché est d&amp;#39;améliorer l&amp;#39;efficacité du suivi et de la gestion de la Délégation de l&amp;#39;Union européenne à Madagascar des contrats de subventions en cours  sur le programme thématique Autorités Locales  ainsi que ceux issus de l&amp;#39;appel à proposition (EuropeAid/159874) sur cette même ligne Lot 2 AL en cours (date limite pour la remise des propositions complètes le 31/08/2018)  « Promouvoir la bonne gouvernance locale pour l&amp;#39;amélioration des services de base de qualité par une contribution accrue de la société civile et des autorités locales priorisant la promotion de l&amp;#39;égalité et de l&amp;#39;équité sociales et entre les femmes et les hommes ». &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif(s) particulier(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif particulier de la mission est d&amp;#39;assurer le suivi et l&amp;#39;accompagnement sur le terrain de l&amp;#39;avancement des projets en cours et ceux  issus de l&amp;#39;appel à proposition 159874  lot 2 AL don’t l&amp;#39;objectif est de &amp;ldquo;contribuer à l&amp;#39;amélioration de la gouvernance locale et au bon fonctionnement des services communaux pour un exercice impliquant la concertation des citoyen(ne)s, réel et efficient des prérogatives des Autorités Locales au bénéfice de leur population.&amp;rdquo;. Ceci tout en offrant un appui technique pour renforcer les capacités des bénéficiaires des subventions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 1 – Cat I&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formation, compétences, qualification&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme d’études supérieures en : ingénieur, doctorat ou équivalent en sciences administratives, sciences économiques, sciences politiques, sciences sociales ou autres domaines pertinents tels que développement rural, sciences agronomique (bac + 5 minimum); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise parfaite du français écrit et oral;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise parfaite des outils informatiques courants;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonnes capacités de rédaction, de synthèse, de modération et de présentation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonne capacité d&amp;#39;écoute et de dialogue&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience générale professionnelle&lt;/strong&gt;:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;au moins 10 ans d&amp;#39;expérience dans les projets de coopération au développement sur le terrain, de préférence en Afrique et dans l&amp;#39;Océan Indien.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 10 ans d&amp;#39;expérience dans le domaine de la gouvernance locale et de développement local/rural, dont au moins 5 ans à l&amp;#39;international &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 5 expériences dans l&amp;#39;appui technique, la formation / coaching au profit des ONG/OSC et autorités locales dans le montage, la mise en oeuvre et la gestion de projets &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience dans l&amp;#39;évaluation de propositions de projets de développement local dans le cadre d&amp;#39;un appel à propositions de l&amp;#39;Union européenne &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans le suivi ou l&amp;#39;évaluation de projets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne connaissance des procédures de l&amp;#39;UE (FED ou Budget) et du cycle de gestion de projet (notamment du cadre logique)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une bonne connaissance d&amp;#39;au moins deux des thématiques suivantes sera considérée un atout : planification locale participative, genre et développement local, environnement,  droits de l&amp;#39;Homme et approche basée sur les droits, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience d’appui aux AL à Madagascar sera considérée comme un atout majeur&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3851&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3851&lt;/a&gt;    &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert in Integrated Water Resource Management</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-integrated-water-resource-management</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-integrated-water-resource-management</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identification and Formulation Action Document - Integrated Water Resource Management in the Kyrgz Republic&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;
Support the identification and formulation of the EU&amp;rsquo;s future Integrated Water resource management sector under the Integrated Rural Development priority area in the Kyrgyz Republic for the next phase of support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;
Conduct an evaluation/study of the Integrated Water resource management sector (including Irrigation and Drinking water supply and sanitation) in the Kyrgyz Republic and identify/formulate a program for the future integrated rural development interventions of the EU (total amount of 21 million euros for 3 years) in relation with Government needs and priorities of the Multi-Annual Indicative Programme (MIP) for 2014-2020 and targeting the Budget Support modality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category II Expert 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Masters or Doctorate Degree (or equivalent) in a field relevant to rural development and/or water management from both a policy and field perspective;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least 6 years of experience in Integrated Rural Development project formulation and management in developing countries, with preference for projects in Kyrgyzstan and Central Asia or in a similar context;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience in integrated water resource management like Irrigation and/or Drinking water supply and sanitation in developing countries, with preference for project in Kyrgyzstan and Central Asia or similar context;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the social, political and economic Kyrgyz or Central Asian context will be considered an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in integrating environment and climate change issues in rural/agricultural sector development, in managing or supporting the implementation of environmentally sustainable, climate-resilient farming practices, and/or in managing natural resources in the context of rural development will be considered as an important advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one assignment for identification, formulation or  implementation of an EU funded project will be considered an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Soft skills&lt;/strong&gt;: 
Excellent  communication skills (both oral and written communication skills);&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English both oral and written&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in Russian both oral and written&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of Kyrgyz will be considered as an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3844&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3844&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Water Management/Rural Development Expert with Budget Support Experience</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/water-management-rural-development-expert-with-budget-support-experience</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 07:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/water-management-rural-development-expert-with-budget-support-experience</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identification and Formulation Action Document - Integrated Water Resource Management in the Kyrgz Republic&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;
Support the identification and formulation of the EU&amp;rsquo;s future Integrated Water resource management sector under the Integrated Rural Development priority area in the Kyrgyz Republic for the next phase of support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;
Conduct an evaluation/study of the Integrated Water resource management sector (including Irrigation and Drinking water supply and sanitation) in the Kyrgyz Republic and identify/formulate a program for the future integrated rural development interventions of the EU (total amount of 21 million euros for 3 years) in relation with Government needs and priorities of the Multi-Annual Indicative Programme (MIP) for 2014-2020 and targeting the Budget Support modality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category II Expert 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications  and skills&lt;/strong&gt;: 
At  least Masters  Degree Academic  level  (or equivalent)  in a field relevant to rural development and/or water management from both a policy and field perspective; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional  experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;br&gt;
At  least  6 years  of experience  in  Budget  Support  project formulation   and/or   management   in  developing   countries,   with   preference   for  projects   in Kyrgyzstan and Central Asia or similar context;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional  experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience in Integrated Rural Development  projects  formulation and/or management in developing countries, with preference for project in Kyrgyzstan and Central Asia or similar context;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in integrated water resource management formulation and/or management will be considered an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in integrating environment  and  climate  change  issues  in  rural/agricultural sector development, in managing or supporting the implementation of environmentally sustainable, climate-resilient fanning practices, and/or in managing natural resources  in the context of rural development will be considered as an important advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the social, political and economic Kyrgyz or Central Asian context will be considered an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one assignment for identification, formulation or  implementation of an EU funded project will be considered an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Soft skills&lt;/strong&gt;: 
Excellent  communication skills (both oral and written communication skills);&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English both oral and written&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of Russian will be considered as an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3844&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3844&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert en Communication (Cat II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-communication-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-communication-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Préparation et expérimentation de la mise en œuvre de la Budgétisation Sensible au Genre en Tunisie&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif général&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général de la prestation est de fournir une assistance technique pour la préparation d&amp;#39;une stratégie et l’expérimentation de la mise en œuvre de la Budgétisation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sensible au Genre en Tunisie et ainsi de créer au terme de cet accompagnement les conditions nécessaires à une généralisation de la mise en œuvre de la BSG en Tunisie.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectifs spécifique&lt;/strong&gt;s
Les objectifs spécifiques sont les suivants : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OS 1 : Appuyer le Ministère des Finances dans la prise en compte de la Budgétisation Sensible au Genre dans le processus de réforme de la Gestion Budgétaire par Objectifs engagé en Tunisie; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OS 2 : Appuyer le Ministère des Finances dans la mise en œuvre de la Budgétisation Sensible au Genre, en adoptant une démarche progressive et expérimentale pour deux ou trois ministères; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OS 3 : Appuyer les ministères sectoriels pilotes dans la mise en œuvre de la BSG au niveau central et au niveau déconcentré; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OS 4 : Poursuivre la sensibilisation à la BSG pour les autres ministères.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert en communication (Cat II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Diplôme universitaire de niveau Master en communication (ou
domaine équivalent), ou expérience équivalente (minimum 2 ans en plus des 6 ans demandés ci-dessous).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt;
Expérience d’au  moins 6 ans  dans le domaine de la 
Communication&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience d&amp;#39;au moins 2 expériences en communication institutionnelle. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle (au moins 2 missions) dans le domaine de la conception, la rédaction et l’édition de supports de communication et de l’organisation d’évènements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Atouts supplémentaires&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;La connaissance des questions liées au genre ou/ et aux réformes budgétaires/ politiques publiques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissances linguistiques&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parfaite connaissance des langues française et arabe.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;KE3 &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3842&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3842&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert en Formation (Cat I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-formation-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 14:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-formation-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Préparation et expérimentation de la mise en œuvre de la Budgétisation Sensible au Genre en Tunisie&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif général&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général de la prestation est de fournir une assistance technique pour la préparation d&amp;#39;une stratégie et l’expérimentation de la mise en œuvre de la Budgétisation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sensible au Genre en Tunisie et ainsi de créer au terme de cet accompagnement les conditions nécessaires à une généralisation de la mise en œuvre de la BSG en Tunisie.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectifs spécifiques&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les objectifs spécifiques sont les suivants : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OS 1 : Appuyer le Ministère des Finances dans la prise en compte de la Budgétisation Sensible au Genre dans le processus de réforme de la Gestion Budgétaire par Objectifs engagé en Tunisie; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OS 2 : Appuyer le Ministère des Finances dans la mise en œuvre de la Budgétisation Sensible au Genre, en adoptant une démarche progressive et expérimentale pour deux ou trois ministères; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OS 3 : Appuyer les ministères sectoriels pilotes dans la mise en œuvre de la BSG au niveau central et au niveau déconcentré; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OS 4 : Poursuivre la sensibilisation à la BSG pour les autres ministères.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert en Formation (Cat I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire de niveau Master dans le domaine de la formation, le développement, l’économie ou des Finances Publiques, ou expérience équivalente (minimum 2 ans en plus des 12 ans demandés ci-dessous);&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Formations complémentaires obligatoires dans les domaines de:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;la définition et la mise en œuvre de plan de formation,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;l’organisation de formations,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;l&amp;#39;approche genre, l&amp;#39;égalité entre les femmes et les hommes,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle Générale&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expérience d’au moins 12 ans dans la définition, la mise
en œuvre, le suivi de plans de formation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience d’au moins 10 ans (pouvant être comprise dans l&amp;#39;expérience générale)  dans le cadre de l’aide au développement de projet relevant de la réforme de la Gestion des Finances Publiques, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Au moins 3 expériences de formateur dans des projets de formation, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Au moins une expérience dans le cadre d’appui à l&amp;#39;approche genre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Atouts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formations complémentaires sans être obligatoires dans les domaines suivants : &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;la Gestion des Finances publiques notamment gestion budgétaire&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;la Réforme budgétaire de type LOLF, les Budgets - programme,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;la définition, la mise en œuvre et le suivi des politiques publiques,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience de formation à la BSG;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise de l&amp;#39;arabe.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissances linguistiques&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise parfaite des logiciels de bureautiques;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise du français.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;KE2 &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3841&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3841&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef de Mission et expert en finances publiques (Cat I)

</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-et-expert-en-finances-publiques-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 13:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-et-expert-en-finances-publiques-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Préparation et expérimentation de la mise en œuvre de la Budgétisation Sensible au Genre en Tunisie&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif général&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général de la prestation est de fournir une assistance technique pour la préparation d&amp;#39;une stratégie et l’expérimentation de la mise en œuvre de la Budgétisation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sensible au Genre en Tunisie et ainsi de créer au terme de cet accompagnement les conditions nécessaires à une généralisation de la mise en œuvre de la BSG en Tunisie.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectifs spécifiques&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les objectifs spécifiques sont les suivants : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OS 1 : Appuyer le Ministère des Finances dans la prise en compte de la Budgétisation Sensible au Genre dans le processus de réforme de la Gestion Budgétaire par Objectifs engagé en Tunisie; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OS 2 : Appuyer le Ministère des Finances dans la mise en œuvre de la Budgétisation Sensible au Genre, en adoptant une démarche progressive et expérimentale pour deux ou trois ministères; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OS 3 : Appuyer les ministères sectoriels pilotes dans la mise en œuvre de la BSG au niveau central et au niveau déconcentré; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OS 4 : Poursuivre la sensibilisation à la BSG pour les autres ministères.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team leader et expert en finances publiques (Cat I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Diplôme universitaire de niveau Master dans le domaine de 
l&amp;#39;économie ou des finances, ou expérience équivalente (minimum 2 ans en plus des 12 ans demandés ci-dessous).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle Générale&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expérience d’au moins 12 ans dans la définition, la mise en
œuvre, le suivi des réformes budgétaire et comptable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience d’au moins 10 ans (pouvant être comprise dans l&amp;#39;expérience générale) dans le cadre de l’aide au développement de projet relevant de la réforme de la Gestion des Finances Publiques; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins deux missions de réforme des finances publiques don’t au moins 1 comme chef d’équipe;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins une expérience dans la définition, la mise en œuvre ou le suivi de politique publique; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins deux expériences confirmées dans des projets d’appui à la prise en compte du Genre dans les budgets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Atouts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Formations complémentaires dans les domaines suivants:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;la gestion des Finances publiques notamment gestion budgétaire (préparation, exécution, reddition des comptes),&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;la Réforme budgétaire de type LOLF, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;les Budgets - programme,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;l&amp;#39;informatisation de la gestion budgétaire et comptable, la définition, la mise en œuvre et le suivi des politiques publiques,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;l&amp;#39;approche genre, l&amp;#39;égalité entre les femmes et les hommes,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;la conduite de diagnostics,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;la réalisation de feuilles de route.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissances linguistiques&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maitrise du français.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maitrise parfaite des logiciels de bureautiques.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;KE1 &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3840&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3840&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Management Expert (II) Technical Assistant to SADC Secretariat</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/project-management-expert-ii-technical-assistant-to-sadc-secretariat</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 14:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/project-management-expert-ii-technical-assistant-to-sadc-secretariat</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance to support SADC Secretariat on strengthening the SADC Secretariat&amp;rsquo;s ex-ante Procurement Compliance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The objective of this assignment is to improve the relevance, effectiveness and efficiency of procurement systems in supporting SADC Secretariat&amp;rsquo;s operational requirements and
achievement of planned activities.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt; 
The specific objectives of the assignment include the following: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analysis and revision process of the SADC procurement ex-ante policy and guidelines; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strengthening ICT systems to implement a fully functional ex-ante system;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate the automation of the SADC procurement system, including the proposed ex-ante procurement compliance system; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strengthening the performance management system to introduce sanctions for staff that demonstrate non-compliance with Secretariat requirements and ex-ante procurement procedures. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The assignment will provide the SADC Secretariat management with necessary tools and procedures for addressing non-compliance issues. It should be noted that existing sanctions
for non-compliance are weak and undermine efforts to improve compliance and accountability in procurement.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Management Expert (II) Technical Assistant to SADC Secretariat&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum requirements&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferably a Master’s degree in project and/or logistics management, planning or other related fields or equivalent; OR in the absence of a formal Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in the required field: relevant work experience of at least 10 years; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years proven previous working experience in design, appraisal and strengthening of procurement systems in the public sector; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable skills in conducting due diligence of government procurement systems for international financial institutions and multi-lateral lending agencies;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years proven previous working experience in procurement, associated with ICP programs, preferably with regional agencies in sub-Saharan Africa.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific requirements&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to synthesize issues and effective report writing skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven working experience in dealing with regional integration and/or Regional Economic Communities (RECs), preferably in the African context; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience of working in large regional/international organisations; specific experience working closely with senior management of regional/international organisations would be an advantage; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in drafting documents; specific experience in drafting documents related to procurement systems will be an advantage; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work independently, as well as part of a team;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong problem-solving skills and a “can do” attitude;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced coordination and prioritisation skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in institutional capacity building programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous working experience of drafting of training materials and conducting trainings; specific experience with trainings on procurement systems will constitute an advantage;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven previous experience in managing contracts;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in setting up corporate systems and processes; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other requirements&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of written and spoken English; ability to communicate in French or Portuguese will be an advantage; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and analytical skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven working experience in the SADC region will constitute an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven working experience in African context, preferably sub-Saharan Africa;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience working with International Cooperation Partners (ICPs);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in using MS Project or other similar project management systems;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of SADC priorities and challenges towards regional integration. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3836&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3836&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Advisor - EDF/Expert in EU Development Assistance</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-eu-development-assistance</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-eu-development-assistance</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance to support SADC Secretariat on EU Development Cooperation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objective of this assignment is to strengthen the SADC-EU cooperation relationship and to effectively contribute to SADC&amp;rsquo;s engagement with the European Union to enhance implementation of the revised Regional Indicative Strategic Development Plan (RISDP).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of the assignment include the following:- &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engage with SADC Secretariat to provide speedy, effective and efficient quality policy reactions and strategic guidance concerning the preparation and implementation of EU financed programmes; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engage with SADC Secretariat to enhance the policy dialogue with the EU, especially in relation to programming and implementation of co-operation programmes; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engage with SADC Secretariat to enhance resource mobilization through effective use of EU instruments, regional funding initiatives and development bank financing modalities;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engage with SADC Secretariat to oversee the implementation of EU-funded and supported programmes;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engage with SADC Secretariat to strengthen SADC visibility and corporate image with the EU, through improved corporate and thematic visibility and communication strategic interventions at regional and international platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Advisor – EDF&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum requirements&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferably a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in the field of Political Science, Law, Economics,Development Studies or other related studies. 
OR in the absence of a formal Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in the required field: relevant work experience of at least 10 years; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of professional experience in the area of EU development assistance and/or any other relevant field.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific requirements&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have proven working experience in drafting strategy documents, preferably in an EU or regional integration context; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have proven working experience in establishing and conducting multi-stakeholder coordination and/or policy dialogues.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have proven work experience in the area of management of the EU development financial resources. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have proven previous experience in dealing with EDF rules and procedures, as well as EU financial instruments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in dealing with Regional Economic Communities (RECs) within the African Context constitutes an advantage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other requirements&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in written and spoken English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and analytical skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound knowledge of regional integration policies and strategies; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven working experience in the SADC region is an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate in French or Portuguese is an asset.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3835&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3835&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef de Mission, Expert dans le domaine du Génie Civil </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-expert-dans-le-domaine-du-genie-civil</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 14:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-expert-dans-le-domaine-du-genie-civil</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Audit technique de projet d&amp;#39;assainissement et de restructuration urbaine de Hann et Petit Mbao&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectifs généraux&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général du projet dont ce marché fait partie est de contribuer à l&amp;#39;amélioration du cadre et des conditions de vie des populations des quartiers de Hann Village et de Petit Mbao par la rationalisation du tissu urbain, la réduction de l&amp;#39;insalubrité, la facilitation de l&amp;#39;accès par toutes les catégories de population aux services publics de base et la stimulation de l&amp;#39;économie locale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif(s) particulier(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La mission qui sera confiée à l&amp;#39;auditeur consiste à assurer le Maître d&amp;#39;Ouvrage et l&amp;#39;Union européenne:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;du bon déroulement des travaux exécutés dans le cadre du projet d&amp;#39;Assainissement et de Restructuration Urbaine de Hann et Petit Mbao et de leur surveillance,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;de la conformité des prestations avec les dispositions de la convention de financement et des contrats signés,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;de la bonne organisation du chantier, du respect des règles contractuelles et des règles de l&amp;#39;art dans la construction routière,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;de la qualité technique des réalisations et des dépenses effectuées,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;de la bonne gestion contractuelle des marchés en vérifiant si chaque intervenant souscrit correctement à ses obligations, et ceci afin de diminuer à caractère préventif le risque de réclamation, litige et/ou contentieux.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Le titulaire a l&amp;#39;obligation de signaler toute anomalie qui affecterait ou pourrait affecter ces objectifs et de faire les recommandations correspondantes pour les prévenir ou pour y remédier. Il doit être totalement indépendant des attributaires des contrats de travaux et de surveillance ainsi que de tout intérêt particulier dans l&amp;#39;Etat du Maître d&amp;#39;Ouvrage qui pourrait compromettre son indépendance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert catégorie l, Chef de Mission&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chef de mission catégorie et durée de l&amp;#39;expérience équivalente Expert de catégorie I &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Formation *&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;expert aura un diplôme d&amp;#39;ingénieur dans le domaine du génie civil ou équivalent, ou ayant exercé des fonctions similaires pendant 15 ans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;expert devra avoir une expérience minimale de 12 ans dans la réalisation, le contrôle de projets de construction routière, et/ou d&amp;#39;adduction dteau et d&amp;#39;assainissement, et/ou d&amp;#39;aménagement urbain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;expert devra avoir réalisé au moins un projet en qualité de chef de mission de contrôle d&amp;#39;un projet équivalent (construction routière, ou adduction d&amp;#39;eau et assainissement, ou aménagement urbain), et réalisé au moins un audit technique sur un projet équivalent (construction routière, ou adduction d&amp;#39;eau et assainissement, ou aménagement urbain).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;expert devra avoir une bonne connaissance des procédures relatives aux marchés de travaux financés par le Fonds Européen de Développement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience constituant un avantage&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expérience sur des projets d&amp;#39;aménagement et/ou de restructuration urbaine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expérience gestion de contentieux dans le cadre de marchés de travaux routiers, génie civile et/ou aménagement urbain (analyse de réclamations)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expérience dans le cadre d&amp;#39;activités d&amp;#39;Informations, d&amp;#39;Education et de Communication de projet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expérience en Afrique subsaharienne&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissances linguistiques&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;expert aura une excellente maitrise orale et écrite de la langue &lt;strong&gt;française&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3834&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3834&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Sector Evaluation Research Expert - Category II</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/public-sector-evaluation-research-expert-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/public-sector-evaluation-research-expert-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Global objective&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project of which this contract will be a part is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To contribute towards building a capable state, responsive to the needs of all its citizens and the  promotion of national interest, accountability and transparency in service delivery, and utilising public resources in an effective and efficient way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specific objectives&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The service provider shall achieve the following specific objectives (SOs) for this assignment:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SO 1 - Undertake an evaluation of the current cost-recovery, revenue generation and funding model in order to determine its effectiveness, cost-efficiency, cost-recovery, competitiveness and growth potential as well as other key considerations outlined in Section 2.3, within the public sector environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SO 2 - Review and capture the NSG business model and consider the alignment between the business model and the funding model of the NSG&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SO 3 Provide recommendations for modification and improvement of the NSG business and funding model in order to promote sustainability and financial viability of the organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SO 4 - Provide for recommendations on the potential for collaboration, partnerships and other forms of revenue generation to contribute to the NSG funding model&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Compulsory: A Masters&amp;#39; degree or equivalent qualification in the disciplines related to the Lot 6 (Innovative Financing for Development, preferably in public administration, public service or evaluation and research). In the absence of a Masters&amp;#39; degree, a Bachelors&amp;#39; degree or equivalent qualification with at least 3 additional years&amp;#39; experience over and above the 6 years&amp;#39; experience stipulated in the fields listed above will be considered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compulsory - At least 6 years&amp;#39; experience in providing advice and support on public sector monitoring and evaluation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compulsory - At least 2 experiences in providing public sector advice to Government Institutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compulsory : At least 2 experiences in conducting research and evaluations within the public sector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferred : At least 2 experiences providing advice and support in the education and training sector on issues related to cost recovery models.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferred  - Experience  within  the  South African  public  sector  providing  technical advice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferred – Experience in supporting schools of governance or schools of administration in South Africa or in other countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Soft skills&lt;/strong&gt;
Compulsory: Good communication and facilitation skills
Language
Compulsory: Excellent writing skills in English&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3832&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3832&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business analyst (Team Leader) - Category 1</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/business-analyst-team-leader-category-1</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 14:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/business-analyst-team-leader-category-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Global objective&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project of which this contract will be a part is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To contribute towards building a capable state, responsive to the needs of all its citizens and the  promotion of national interest, accountability and transparency in service delivery, and utilising public resources in an effective and efficient way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specific objectives&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The service provider shall achieve the following specific objectives (SOs) for this assignment:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SO 1 - Undertake an evaluation of the current cost-recovery, revenue generation and funding model in order to determine its effectiveness, cost-efficiency, cost-recovery, competitiveness and growth potential as well as other key considerations outlined in Section 2.3, within the public sector environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SO 2 - Review and capture the NSG business model and consider the alignment between the business model and the funding model of the NSG&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SO 3 Provide recommendations for modification and improvement of the NSG business and funding model in order to promote sustainability and financial viability of the organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SO 4 - Provide for recommendations on the potential for collaboration, partnerships and other forms of revenue generation to contribute to the NSG funding model&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Compulsory: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Masters&amp;#39; degree or equivalent qualification in the disciplines related to the Lot 6 (Innovative Financing for Development, preferably in Business, Commerce, Management and Leadership). In the absence of a Masters&amp;#39; degree, a Bachelors&amp;#39; degree or equivalent qualification with at least 3 additional years&amp;#39; experience over and above the 12 years&amp;#39; experience stipulated in the fields listed above will be considered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compulsory: At least 12 years&amp;#39; experience in Business analysis, advice and support to organisations in the public or private sector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compulsory: At least 2 experiences providing advice and support within the education and training sector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compulsory:  At least 2 experiences providing  advice and support within the public sector including on cost-recovery modelling.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferred: Experience in providing support to the South African public service sector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferred – Experience in  supporting  schools  of  governance or  schools  of administration in South Africa or in other countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Soft skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Compulsory: Excellent communication and facilitation skills
Language
Compulsory: Excellent writing skills (English)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3831&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3831&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key expert 5: Expert for Tourism; Category I</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-expert-5-expert-for-tourism-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 13:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-expert-5-expert-for-tourism-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GLOBAL OBJECTIVE&lt;/strong&gt;
To contribute to the Government of Uganda&amp;rsquo;s successful completion of the Mid-Term Review (MTR) of the 2nd National Development Plan (NDP2) and the end evaluation of the 1st National Development Plan (NDP-1).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPECIFIC OBJECTIVES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To assess progress made against the NDP-1 and NDP-2 objectives in the thematic areas of Infrastructure (1), Employment (2) Industrialization and Value Addition (3), Minerals, Oil and Gas (4) and Tourism (5).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To identify evidence-based, justified and detailed short-term (NDP-2), medium-term (NDP-3) and long-term (10 years NDP) adjustments and actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REQUESTED SERVICES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Consultants’ services will indicatively include but not necessarily be limited to the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GENERAL SERVICES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Validate or update the specific organization &amp;amp; methodology, including work-plan, during the inception phase.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify, review and analyse reference documents that are relevant to the NDP2 MTR and the NDP1 end evaluation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Undertake  fieldwork  to  collect  data  and  carry  out  data  analysis  to  inform  the  respective assessment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct meetings with key stakeholders at various levels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct consultation and validation workshops to inform the outputs of the assignment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare an inception report&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare for each (5) thematic area a main report and a synthesis report.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate and take a leading role in the Government of Uganda&amp;rsquo;s dissemination conference(s) of the final reports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish  a  web-based  repository  of  working  documents  to  allow  NPA  to  monitor  timely progress made against the assignment&amp;rsquo;s outputs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPECIFIC SERVICES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyse for each of the 4 thematic areas outlined in chapter 2.2 the (a) current situation, (b) progress made against the NDP targets and &amp;copy; public and private financing against NDP projections.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct   for   each   thematic   area   an  inventory  (status)  of   public   investment   projects implemented during NDP.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess community-level experiences and perceptions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyse for each thematic area main drivers and opportunities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify for each thematic area the factors that have proved critical or hindered progress under both NDP-1 and NDP-2.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess for each thematic area the extent to which NDP-1 and NDP-2 have guided policies, strategic planning, budgeting and actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess for each thematic area the impacts (positive and negative) of policy, planning and budget actions under the NDP-1 and NDP-2 periods.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the institutional functions linked with each thematic area under a programme-based planning and budgeting approach and provide the necessary adjustments to facilitate and enhance compliance between the NDP and the programme-based approaches.
Apply for each thematic area the applicable OECD DAC Evaluation Criteria to NDP-1 and NDP-2.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the efficiency, effectiveness and sustainability of the implementation and mechanisms for each thematic area under both the NDP-1 and the NDP-2 and outline the necessary improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyse for each thematic area lessons learned during the NDP implementation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify for each thematic area international best practices relevant to Uganda.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify and justify for each thematic area priority lessons learned and recommendations for the medium- (NDP-3) and long-term (10-year) NDP.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide  for  each  thematic  area  evidence-/best  practices-based  guidance  on  alternative policies, strategic priorities and actions to achieve better results within Uganda’s setting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide for each thematic area medium-term (2020/21-2024/25) and long-term (2020/21- 2029/30) estimates of required results and indicative budget requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum requirements&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced University degree (Master&amp;rsquo;s degree or equivalent) in tourism, business administration, economics, private sector development or any other closely related subject.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent English communication and writing skills (C-2 level proficiency). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PhD degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum requirements&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of successful international working experience with the sustainable development of the tourism sector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum requirements&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Profound  international  working  experience  with  evaluating  national  or  sector-level strategies and investment plans for tourism development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Profound knowledge of the state of the tourism sector in Uganda.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3830&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3830&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key expert 4: Expert for Minerals, Oil and Gas; Category I</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-expert-4-expert-for-minerals-oil-and-gas-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 13:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-expert-4-expert-for-minerals-oil-and-gas-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GLOBAL OBJECTIVE&lt;/strong&gt;
To contribute to the Government of Uganda&amp;rsquo;s successful completion of the Mid-Term Review (MTR) of the 2nd National Development Plan (NDP2) and the end evaluation of the 1st National Development Plan (NDP-1).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPECIFIC OBJECTIVES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To assess progress made against the NDP-1 and NDP-2 objectives in the thematic areas of Infrastructure (1), Employment (2) Industrialization and Value Addition (3), Minerals, Oil and Gas (4) and Tourism (5).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To identify evidence-based, justified and detailed short-term (NDP-2), medium-term (NDP-3) and long-term (10 years NDP) adjustments and actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REQUESTED SERVICES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Consultants’ services will indicatively include but not necessarily be limited to the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GENERAL SERVICES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Validate or update the specific organization &amp;amp; methodology, including work-plan, during the inception phase.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify, review and analyse reference documents that are relevant to the NDP2 MTR and the NDP1 end evaluation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Undertake  fieldwork  to  collect  data  and  carry  out  data  analysis  to  inform  the  respective assessment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct meetings with key stakeholders at various levels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct consultation and validation workshops to inform the outputs of the assignment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare an inception report&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare for each (5) thematic area a main report and a synthesis report.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate and take a leading role in the Government of Uganda&amp;rsquo;s dissemination conference(s) of the final reports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish  a  web-based  repository  of  working  documents  to  allow  NPA  to  monitor  timely progress made against the assignment&amp;rsquo;s outputs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPECIFIC SERVICES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyse for each of the 4 thematic areas outlined in chapter 2.2 the (a) current situation, (b) progress made against the NDP targets and &amp;copy; public and private financing against NDP projections.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct   for   each   thematic   area   an  inventory  (status)  of   public   investment   projects implemented during NDP.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess community-level experiences and perceptions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyse for each thematic area main drivers and opportunities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify for each thematic area the factors that have proved critical or hindered progress under both NDP-1 and NDP-2.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess for each thematic area the extent to which NDP-1 and NDP-2 have guided policies, strategic planning, budgeting and actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess for each thematic area the impacts (positive and negative) of policy, planning and budget actions under the NDP-1 and NDP-2 periods.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the institutional functions linked with each thematic area under a programme-based planning and budgeting approach and provide the necessary adjustments to facilitate and enhance compliance between the NDP and the programme-based approaches.
Apply for each thematic area the applicable OECD DAC Evaluation Criteria to NDP-1 and NDP-2.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the efficiency, effectiveness and sustainability of the implementation and mechanisms for each thematic area under both the NDP-1 and the NDP-2 and outline the necessary improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyse for each thematic area lessons learned during the NDP implementation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify for each thematic area international best practices relevant to Uganda.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify and justify for each thematic area priority lessons learned and recommendations for the medium- (NDP-3) and long-term (10-year) NDP.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide  for  each  thematic  area  evidence-/best  practices-based  guidance  on  alternative policies, strategic priorities and actions to achieve better results within Uganda’s setting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide for each thematic area medium-term (2020/21-2024/25) and long-term (2020/21- 2029/30) estimates of required results and indicative budget requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum requirements&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced University degree (Master&amp;rsquo;s degree or equivalent) in economics, geology or any other closely related subject.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent English communication and writing skills (C-2 level proficiency). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PhD degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum requirements&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At  least  12  years  of  successful  international  working  experience  in  the  sustainable development of mineral-, oil- or gas sectors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum requirements&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Profound international working experience with evaluating national or sector-level strategies and investment plans for the sustainable development of the mineral-, oil or gas sectors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Profound knowledge of the state of the mineral-, oil and gas sectors in Uganda.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3829&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3829&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key expert 3: Expert for Industrialization and Value Addition; Category I</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-expert-3-expert-for-industrialization-and-value-addition-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 13:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-expert-3-expert-for-industrialization-and-value-addition-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GLOBAL OBJECTIVE&lt;/strong&gt;
To contribute to the Government of Uganda&amp;rsquo;s successful completion of the Mid-Term Review (MTR) of the 2nd National Development Plan (NDP2) and the end evaluation of the 1st National Development Plan (NDP-1).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPECIFIC OBJECTIVES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To assess progress made against the NDP-1 and NDP-2 objectives in the thematic areas of Infrastructure (1), Employment (2) Industrialization and Value Addition (3), Minerals, Oil and Gas (4) and Tourism (5).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To identify evidence-based, justified and detailed short-term (NDP-2), medium-term (NDP-3) and long-term (10 years NDP) adjustments and actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REQUESTED SERVICES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Consultants’ services will indicatively include but not necessarily be limited to the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GENERAL SERVICES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Validate or update the specific organization &amp;amp; methodology, including work-plan, during the inception phase.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify, review and analyse reference documents that are relevant to the NDP2 MTR and the NDP1 end evaluation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Undertake  fieldwork  to  collect  data  and  carry  out  data  analysis  to  inform  the  respective assessment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct meetings with key stakeholders at various levels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct consultation and validation workshops to inform the outputs of the assignment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare an inception report&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare for each (5) thematic area a main report and a synthesis report.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate and take a leading role in the Government of Uganda&amp;rsquo;s dissemination conference(s) of the final reports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish  a  web-based  repository  of  working  documents  to  allow  NPA  to  monitor  timely progress made against the assignment&amp;rsquo;s outputs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPECIFIC SERVICES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyse for each of the 4 thematic areas outlined in chapter 2.2 the (a) current situation, (b) progress made against the NDP targets and &amp;copy; public and private financing against NDP projections.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct   for   each   thematic   area   an  inventory  (status)  of   public   investment   projects implemented during NDP.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess community-level experiences and perceptions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyse for each thematic area main drivers and opportunities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify for each thematic area the factors that have proved critical or hindered progress under both NDP-1 and NDP-2.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess for each thematic area the extent to which NDP-1 and NDP-2 have guided policies, strategic planning, budgeting and actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess for each thematic area the impacts (positive and negative) of policy, planning and budget actions under the NDP-1 and NDP-2 periods.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the institutional functions linked with each thematic area under a programme-based planning and budgeting approach and provide the necessary adjustments to facilitate and enhance compliance between the NDP and the programme-based approaches.
Apply for each thematic area the applicable OECD DAC Evaluation Criteria to NDP-1 and NDP-2.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the efficiency, effectiveness and sustainability of the implementation and mechanisms for each thematic area under both the NDP-1 and the NDP-2 and outline the necessary improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyse for each thematic area lessons learned during the NDP implementation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify for each thematic area international best practices relevant to Uganda.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify and justify for each thematic area priority lessons learned and recommendations for the medium- (NDP-3) and long-term (10-year) NDP.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide  for  each  thematic  area  evidence-/best  practices-based  guidance  on  alternative policies, strategic priorities and actions to achieve better results within Uganda’s setting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide for each thematic area medium-term (2020/21-2024/25) and long-term (2020/21- 2029/30) estimates of required results and indicative budget requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum requirements&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced University degree (Master&amp;rsquo;s degree or equivalent) in business administration, economics, private sector development, trade, economic policy, or any other closely related subject.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent English communication and writing skills (C-2 level proficiency). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PhD degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum requirements&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of successful international working experience in the area of national industrialization and value addition strategies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum requirements&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Profound working experience with evaluating national or sector-level strategies and investment plans for industrial development and value addition.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Profound knowledge of the state of industrialization and value addition in the Ugandan economy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format 
External CWS using Project-Proposal UK Application Form 
Link to job posting: &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3828&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3828&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
