<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 08:20:28 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Administrative Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/administrative-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/administrative-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to the evaluation of IPA II CSF &amp;lsquo;Regional Thematic Networks of CSOs&amp;rsquo; Call for Proposals&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;
To ensure adequate conditions to assess the call for proposals by providing the necessary technical assistance to the European Commission in the evaluation process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;
To assist the Evaluation Committee in assessing the proposals received under this call for proposals for 84 man - days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Administrative Expert&lt;/strong&gt;
• At least secondary education degree level and at least 3 years professional experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;Aurelie_Durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Assessors with Sector Experience and knowledge of EU External Aid Programmes</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-assessors-with-sector-experience-and-knowledge-of-eu-external-aid-programmes</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 08:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-assessors-with-sector-experience-and-knowledge-of-eu-external-aid-programmes</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to the evaluation of IPA II CSF &amp;lsquo;Regional Thematic Networks of CSOs&amp;rsquo; Call for Proposals&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;
To ensure adequate conditions to assess the call for proposals by providing the necessary technical assistance to the European Commission in the evaluation process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;
To assist the Evaluation Committee in assessing the proposals received under this call for proposals for 84 man - days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Assessors with Sector Experience and knowledge of EU External Aid Programmes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;senior experts&lt;/strong&gt; should have:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years of experience and a Master’s Degree Academic level or, in the absence of the Master’s Degree Academic level, in total at least 15 years professional experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of the issues covered by the grant programme concerned in the specific domain (e.g. Education, Culture, Good Governance, Human Rights, Minorities and Vulnerable groups, Gender issues, Reconciliation, Philanthropy, Media Freedom, Environment and climate action, Social inclusion, etc.), notably as concerns support to Civil Society Organisations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;team as a whole&lt;/strong&gt; should have the following expertise:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the rules and procedures of EU external aid programmes and ideally supporting evidence of a recent practical experience in the evaluation of proposals submitted under EU external aid programmes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of EU and enlargement-related matters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent oral and writing skills in English (level 1 in a scale from 1 to 5, where 1 is &amp;ldquo;excellent&amp;rdquo; and 5 is &amp;ldquo;basic&amp;rdquo; (Senior Experts)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced understanding of democratization and civil society related issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one amongst the senior experts should have at least 5 years of experience in evaluation and/ or management of programmes and/or projects financed by the Instrument for Pre-accession Assistance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one amongst the senior experts should have at least 5 years of experience in evaluation and/or management of programmes and/or projects to support civil society&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience with PROSPECT and PADOR is an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The working language is English. Knowledge of Albanian, Serbian, Bosnian, Montenegrin, Macedonian and/or Turkish would be an advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the &lt;strong&gt;Assessors (Senior Experts)&lt;/strong&gt; will assume also the role of Team Leader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;Aurelie_Durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Development Socio-Economist </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-development-socio-economist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 07:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-development-socio-economist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Promoting responsible supply chain in the area of conflict minerals (3TG), All Countries&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The proposed consultancy shall contribute to the EU&amp;rsquo;s effort towards supporting good governance and responsible mineral sourcing in developing partner-countries, with emphasis on conflict affected and high-risk areas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Development Socio-Economist – Cat. I&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least  Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree  from an  accredited academic institution or  equivalent  professional experience in the areas of socio-economic planning, in conformity with the scope and requirements of the present Terms of Reference.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven  track  record  of  at  least  ten  (10)  years  hands-on  professional  experience  in  the design/implementation/evaluation of socio-economic capacity building in developing countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with consultancy work for international organisations with specific regional or country focus; specific experience with European Union funded programmes and Delegations would be an additional asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proof of analytical capabilities, research and technical writing skills in similar assignments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and oral communication and presentation skills in English language.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer literate, specifically proficient in the use of standard desktop editing, spreadsheets, databases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record of at least six (6) years’ with the design/programming, planning / implementation  / evaluation of regional or country donor or industry funded programmes related to socio-economic development of local institutions and communities in countries with major extractive industries or conflict minerals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with the implementation of corporate social responsibility schemes shall be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Team Leader: Mining Engineer / Geologist (or equivalent)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-team-leader-mining-engineer-geologist-or-equivalent</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 07:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-team-leader-mining-engineer-geologist-or-equivalent</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Promoting responsible supply chain in the area of conflict minerals (3TG)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The proposed consultancy shall contribute to the EU&amp;rsquo;s effort towards supporting good governance and responsible mineral sourcing in developing partner-countries, with emphasis on conflict affected and high-risk areas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader: Mining Engineer / Geologist (or equivalent). (Cat I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree from an accredited academic institution or equivalent professional experience in the areas of industrial / artisanal mining in conformity with the scope and requirements of the present Terms of Reference&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record of at least ten (10) years hands-on professional experience in various areas of extractive industries and mineral supply chains in developing countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with consultancy work for international organisations with specific regional or country focus; specific experience with European Union funded programmes and Delegations would be an additional asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proof of analytical capabilities, research and technical writing skills in similar assignments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and oral communication and presentation skills in English language.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer literate, specifically proficient in the use of standard desktop editing, spreadsheets, databases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record of at least six (6) years’ with the design/programming, planning / implementation/ evaluation of regional or country donor or industry funded programmes including in the legal/voluntary conformity requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working with private sector managed supply chains, possibly in conflict-affected and high-risk countries; knowledge of due diligence and exposure to programmes in the area of responsible sourcing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with public private partnerships, due diligence and certification schemes, corporate social responsibility related to the industrial / artisanal mining sector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Experts in National Water and Sanitation Management and Planning</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-experts-in-national-water-and-sanitation-management-and-planning</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-experts-in-national-water-and-sanitation-management-and-planning</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Short-term Expert - Identification and Formulation of the 11th EDF WASH for Solomon Islands&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;overall objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the assignment is to assist the Solomon Islands Government (SIG) and EU to timely programme and implement the 11th EDF National Indicative Programme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this assignment is to assist the EU and SIG, in consultation with stake holders, in designing the interventions (identification and formulation) to be financed from the 11th EDF under the WASH sector in updating existing Urban WASH Action Document and make possible the next steps to take place, proposing implementation modalities in accordance to EU available instruments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project location&lt;/strong&gt;: Honiara. Necessary specific provincial travels to Gizo, Auki, Munda or Noro must be considered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Experts in National Water and Sanitation Management and Planning&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in civil or water engineering, Water supply and Sanitation Management or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in spoken and written English, with good reporting, interpersonal and communication skills.
General Professional experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 12 years working experience in Water and Sanitation management and planning at national level or in Water Systems for more than 200,000 users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;7 years working experience in WASH in developing countries or Pacific Islands States;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years working experience in EU funded projects with direct and indirect management, implementing EU budget support (general or sector reform contract) and is familiar with the EU budget support procedures and guidelines;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in WASH or urban development projects and programs implemented with International Financial Institutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient knowledge of standard computer software (MS word, Excel and project management software);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven working experience in facilitating Public-Private Partnership Programmes or similar programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in capacity building activities for government and NGOs/CSOs in the WASH sector (especially in engineering) and/or in strategic and policy support.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;Aurelie_Durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Dairy Sector Specialist (Cat I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-dairy-sector-specialist-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 11:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-dairy-sector-specialist-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance Support to the Ministry of Agriculture in the Area of Livestock Development&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;overall objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the project is to contribute to the reduction of poverty by creating pro-poor growth, securing livelihoods of small holder farmers and providing locally produced diversified food on the market.
The purpose of the contract is to support the Ministry of Agriculture in developing a sound intervention in the livestock sector as part of the 11th EDF, focussing on rangeland based smallholder livestock development. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidates with experience working in the &lt;strong&gt;SADC region&lt;/strong&gt; are preferable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Dairy Sector Specialist (Cat I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Masters Degree in agriculture, agricultural economics, livestock science or closely related field; alternatively, a basic degree in a relevant area with at least 5 years additional experience above the professional experience indicated below; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimally twelve years proven experience in the field of expertise, agriculture and livestock development of which minimally five years in the development of smallholder dairy development in a developing country context; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound understanding of dairy processing and marketing; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent analytical skills and strategic planning skills; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in both written and spoken English is essential. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Animal Production/Health Specialist (Cat I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-animal-production-health-specialist-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-animal-production-health-specialist-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance Support to the Ministry of Agriculture in the Area of Livestock Development&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;overall objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the project is to contribute to the reduction of poverty by creating pro-poor growth, securing livelihoods of small holder farmers and providing locally produced diversified food on the market.
The purpose of the contract is to support the Ministry of Agriculture in developing a sound intervention in the livestock sector as part of the 11th EDF, focussing on rangeland based smallholder livestock development. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidates with experience working in the &lt;strong&gt;SADC region&lt;/strong&gt; are preferable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Animal Production/Health Specialist (Cat I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Masters Degree in livestock science, animal science, agriculture, animal production and health or closely related field; alternatively, a basic degree in a relevant area with at least 5 years additional experience above the professional experience indicated below; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimally twelve years proven experience in the field of expertise, of which minimally five years’ experience in cattle/livestock production systems, with emphasis on animal nutrition. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong, proven experience in development of smallholder production; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound knowledge of animal health aspects of livestock development; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in both written and spoken English is essential. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rangeland Management Specialist (Cat I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/rangeland-management-specialist-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/rangeland-management-specialist-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance Support to the Ministry of Agriculture in the Area of Livestock Development&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project is to contribute to the reduction of poverty by creating pro-poor growth, securing livelihoods of small holder farmers and providing locally produced diversified food on the market.
The purpose of the contract is to support the Ministry of Agriculture in developing a sound intervention in the livestock sector as part of the 11th EDF, focussing on rangeland based smallholder livestock development. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidates with experience working in the SADC region are preferable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rangeland Management Specialist (Cat I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Masters Degree in natural resource management, agriculture, environmental science or closely related field; alternatively, a basic degree in a relevant area with at least 5 years additional experience above the professional experience indicated below; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimally twelve years proven experience in the field of expertise, of which minimally five years’ experience in rangeland management &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong, proven networks in international markets; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent negotiation skills are required; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven training skills and a proven track record in imparting knowledge and skills; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in international trade environment including tariff and non-tariff barriers to trade, accreditation schemes, and international logistics arrangements for fresh produce; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in both written and spoken English is essential; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team leader – International Livestock Development Expert (Cat I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-international-livestock-development-expert-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-international-livestock-development-expert-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance Support to the Ministry of Agriculture in the Area of Livestock Development&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;overall objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the project is to contribute to the reduction of poverty by creating pro-poor growth, securing livelihoods of small holder farmers and providing locally produced diversified food on the market.
The purpose of the contract is to support the Ministry of Agriculture in developing a sound intervention in the livestock sector as part of the 11th EDF, focussing on rangeland based smallholder livestock development. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidates with experience working in the SADC region are preferable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team leader – International Livestock Development Expert (Cat I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Masters Degree in agriculture, agricultural economics, livestock science or closely related field; alternatively, a basic degree in a relevant area with at least 5 years additional experience above the professional experience indicated below; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimally twelve years proven experience in the field of expertise, agriculture and livestock development of which minimally seven years in the development of smallholder livestock development preferably in sub-Sahara Africa; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound understanding of and experience in livestock marketing; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in international trade environment including tariff and non-tariff barriers to trade,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent analytical skills and strategic planning skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong, proven team leadership/management skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in both written and spoken English is essential;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Social Development and Gender Expert  (Team Leader)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-social-development-and-gender-expert-team-leader</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-social-development-and-gender-expert-team-leader</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gender Analysis for Thailand and Malaysia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;
The gender analysis will provide an understanding whether gender inequalities persist in Thailand and Malaysia and its causes, how it intersects with other inequalities, how it impacts on human rights enjoyment and/or benefits produced by and access to development efforts as well as an understanding of partner governments’ commitment and capacity to work on GEWE issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requested services&lt;/strong&gt;
The gender analyse should provide qualitative information, sex-age disaggregated data and analysis on the gender situation in the country/sector in order to contribute to the political/policy dialogue and facilitate the development of gender-sensitive country strategies as well as programmes and projects throughout the whole PPCM cycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Social Development and Gender Expert  (Team Leader) 33 working days&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced university degree (Minimum Master) in in development studies, social development, gender studies certified by a Diploma (or equivalent professional experience of at least 15 years if candidate does not possess an advance university degree.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated writing and communication skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer literacy (minimum MS Word, Excel).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of twelve years’ experience in social development and gender analysis;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific experience and expertise on gender analysis, gender mainstreaming and women’s participation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience working on national gender policies in developing countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience  of  working  in  South  East  Asia  and  preferably  in  Thailand  and  Malaysia  is essential,;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organisational development and capacity building experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of international/regional agreements and initiatives on gender (UN, CEDAW, Beijing, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in managing a team of experts;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Up-to-date and comprehensive knowledge and experience of EU development, policies, instruments and facilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Cat.III Gender Experts</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/two-catiii-gender-experts</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/two-catiii-gender-experts</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gender Analysis for Thailand and Malaysia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;
The gender analysis will provide an understanding whether gender inequalities persist in Thailand and Malaysia and its causes, how it intersects with other inequalities, how it impacts on human rights enjoyment and/or benefits produced by and access to development efforts as well as an understanding of partner governments’ commitment and capacity to work on GEWE issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requested services&lt;/strong&gt;
The gender analyse should provide qualitative information, sex-age disaggregated data and analysis on the gender situation in the country/sector in order to contribute to the political/policy dialogue and facilitate the development of gender-sensitive country strategies as well as programmes and projects throughout the whole PPCM cycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Two Gender Experts Cat III (2*15 or 30 working days)&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Category III experts can either be a single person or two different people each responsible for a country. Please note that the Evaluation Committee will evaluate the expert(s) Cat III CV(s) as well as the Expert Cat I CV(s) in its evaluation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree certified by a Diploma (or equivalent professional experience of at least 5 years if candidate(s) do not possess a university diploma)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good communication skills, both oral and written;
** Computer literacy (minimum MS Word, Excel, MIS). General professional experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 years’ experience in the context of gender and development (this can include consultancy on gender development programmes as well as more academic works such as gender related studies etc.);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowledge of the development and gender context of Thailand and Malaysia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowledge of development and gender context in South East Asia would be an asset.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Agriculture/Rural Development Experts with Food Safety or Veterinary/Animal Health Experience</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/two-agriculture-rural-development-experts-with-food-safety-or-veterinary-animal-health-experience</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 07:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/two-agriculture-rural-development-experts-with-food-safety-or-veterinary-animal-health-experience</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation of the EU-funded Support to Agriculture and Rural Development under IPA I&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The primary objective of this project is to evaluate to which extent the EU assistance provided under the IPA programmes 2007-2013 (IPA I) in the areas of agriculture, rural development, food safety and animal health/veterinary has reached its objectives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective of this assignment is to evaluate the achievements under the IPA programmes 2007-2013 (IPA I) in the areas of agriculture, rural development, food safety and animal health/veterinary and inform on the factors behind success or failure of this assistance and their geographical (urban/rural) and gender distribution. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Two Agriculture/Rural Development Experts with Food Safety or Veterinary/Animal Health Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Master degree in agriculture/economic/veterinary/health/business administration/ biology/ geography/ statistics; or a bachelor degree in agriculture/ economic/ veterinary/ health/ business administration/ biology/ geography/ statistics and 5 years professional experience (in addition to the minimum number of years of general professional experience required below). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 6 years, preferably 10 years of experience in the field of agriculture and/or rural development and/or food safety and/or veterinary/animal health.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience as evaluation expert in minimum one project, preferably three projects aimed at evaluating EU programmes financed under EU pre-accession assistance in the field of agriculture and/or rural development and/or food safety and/or veterinary/animal health.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The minimum number of working days for the two experts altogether is 100 working days.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both experts should be proficient in English language and have very good reporting and communication skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experto Categoría III – Informático</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-categoria-iii-informatico</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 08:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-categoria-iii-informatico</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ATI MMAyA 2016-17&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;El contrato tiene como objetivo general apoyar al MMAYA en la implementación de los programas actuales así como en la fase de preparación de un Nuevo Convenio de Financiación (CF) Sectorial y el Programas de Asistencia Técnica al MMAyA. El asesoramiento se producirá a través de la provisión de estudios, metodologías, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project location&lt;/strong&gt;: La Paz, misiones a las potenciales zonas de intervención: Santa Cruz, Tarija, Cochabamba, Beni, Pando y Oruro&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experto Categoría III – Informático&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preparación y calificaciones&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formación académica en los rubros de informática, ingeniería, geografía o cualquier otro tipo de diploma científico;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competencia en manejo de bases de datos Postgres/PostGIS, relacional y sistemas de información distribuidos: manejo de los usuarios, configuración y adaptación de la base de datos, desarrollo de funciones y de consultas, carga y exportación de datos, back-ups;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competencia en operaciones básicas de redes informáticas (TCP / IP , VPN, FTP &amp;hellip;);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competencia en manejo y mantenimiento del servidor, versionamiento Git, SO LINUX, Windows;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competencia en programación/desarrollo de interfaces web para bases de datos (digitalización de datos y consultas);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competencia deseable en lenguajes de programación y herramientas informáticas (SQL y PHP, HTML. Manejo de Drupal, Javascript, Python)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conocimiento en SIG y datos geoespaciales deseable;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debe hablar y escribir fluidamente en español. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experiencia profesional&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mínimo 3 años de experiencia en programación y /o gestión de sistemas, con la aplicación de las competencias arriba mencionadas;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mínimo 3 años de experiencia laboral en Bolivia, que permita un conocimiento de las condiciones de sistemas informáticos en el país;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia en apoyo a sistemas gubernamentales, y del Ministerio de Medioambiente y Agua en particular, deseable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experto Categoría III - Coordinador</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-categoria-iii-coordinador</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-categoria-iii-coordinador</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ATI MMAyA 2016-17&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;El contrato tiene como objetivo general apoyar al MMAYA en la implementación de los programas actuales así como en la fase de preparación de un Nuevo Convenio de Financiación (CF) Sectorial y el Programas de Asistencia Técnica al MMAyA. El asesoramiento se producirá a través de la provisión de estudios, metodologías, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project location&lt;/strong&gt;: La Paz, misiones a las potenciales zonas de intervención: Santa Cruz, Tarija, Cochabamba, Beni, Pando y Oruro&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experto Categoría III - Coordinador:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preparación y calificaciones&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formación académica en los rubros de economía, ciencias sociales o biología. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formación complementaria (postgrado o maestría) es deseable, particularmente en temáticas de desarrollo y/o relacionadas al sector de agua y medioambiente.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debe hablar y escribir fluidamente en español. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debe tener facilidad de comunicación y negociación para relacionarse con autoridades nacionales, subnacionales y organizaciones sociales, competencia intercultural y la predisposición de adaptarse a cambios del entorno institucional con creatividad. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experiencia profesional general&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mínimo de 5 años de experiencia en el sector de agua y medioambiente. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mínimo de 5 años de experiencia laboral en países en vías de desarrollo.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mínimo de 3 años de experiencia laboral con organismos de cooperación (donantes, agencias técnicas, ONGs) en Bolivia.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia demostrada en el desarrollo y/o implementaciones de programas sectoriales, en coordinación con instancias gubernamentales y/o sociales.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experiencia profesional específica deseable&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia en el diseño y/o la implementación de programas de apoyo sectorial, idealmente con la modalidad de apoyo presupuestario de la Unión Europea.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia específica relacionada con políticas de agua, manejo de cuencas, biodiversidad y/o sector forestal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia en el diseño y/o implementación de programas de fortalecimiento de capacidades. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia en trabajo dentro de o en apoyo a instituciones gubernamentales a nivel central o sub-nacional. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert I - Technical Adviser with Experience in a NAO Office</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-i-technical-adviser-with-experience-in-a-nao-office</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 19:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-i-technical-adviser-with-experience-in-a-nao-office</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Short Term Technical Assistance to Support the NAO Office&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of this assignment is to improve the efficiency and effectiveness with which the EU Assistance to Kenya is implemented &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective is to provide technical assistance to the National Treasury primarily to support coordination of the financial management of EU Grants to County Governments, but also to ensure that the National Treasury performs its role with regards to the administration of Grants as outlined in the PFM Act and PFM Regulations and the Cotonou Partnership Agreement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert I - Technical Adviser with Experience in a NAO Office&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Master’s degree in either of the following disciplines: Economics, Finance, Business Administration, Social Sciences or Public Administration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of spoken and written English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 12 years professional experience in an advisory role either in the public or private sector and/or development financing of which at least 5 years must be in an NAO office &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive and demonstrated understanding of funding modalities of the European Union&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent understanding of the current aid architecture (trends in aid policy management, coordination and modes of aid delivery)  such as budget support and use of country systems &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of development cooperation and the various instruments of the EU&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated understanding of project cycle management, developing and implementing monitoring framework for donor funded programmes and the respective challenges for Aid Management
Specific professional experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years work experience in ACP region preferably relevant work experience in a developing country&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with public financial programming and decentralised budgeting/financing system&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated Knowledge of EDF procedures particularly financial and procurement procedures , reporting requirements and programming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;Aurelie_Durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category II Expertise in Sociology</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-expertise-in-sociology</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 19:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-expertise-in-sociology</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation of the Sector Policy Support Programme &amp;lsquo;Promoting mutual trade by removing technical barriers to trade between Ukraine and the European Union&amp;rsquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific purpose for undertaking this evaluation is to evaluate the Technical Barriers to Trade in Sector Budget Support according to the standard OECD criteria and finally study the effects of EU-funded cooperation in the area of technical barriers to trade on the business climate in Ukraine and of the perceptions by the business community of the reforms supported by the TBT SBS and other EU-funded programmes on the subject.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a matter of fact, systematic and timely evaluation of its programmes, activities, instruments, legislation and non-spending activities is a priority of the European Commission in order to demonstrate accountability and to promote lesson learning to improve policy and practice. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The generic purpose of the evaluation is to identify key lessons and to produce recommendations to improve current and inform future choices on the sector reform contracts in Ukraine and on the cooperation between the EU in Ukraine in the sphere of the removal of technical barriers in the trade in industrial goods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 130 days (until May 2017)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category II Expertise in Sociology – 45 working days&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in a field related to the assignment – economic, social or legal sciences - or at least extra 5 years of experience additional to that described below under the general professional experience; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent English communication skills, both spoken and written. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Ukrainian (or Russian) would be a very strong asset;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least 6 years of relevant professional experience in sociology;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;professional experience in development cooperation will be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years of practical experience in designing, implementation and analysis of sociological polls;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical experience in application of the focus groups tool.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category I Expertise  in Technical Barriers to Trade </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-expertise-in-technical-barriers-to-trade</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 19:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-expertise-in-technical-barriers-to-trade</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation of the Sector Policy Support Programme &amp;lsquo;Promoting mutual trade by removing technical barriers to trade between Ukraine and the European Union&amp;rsquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific purpose for undertaking this evaluation is to evaluate the Technical Barriers to Trade in Sector Budget Support according to the standard OECD criteria and finally study the effects of EU-funded cooperation in the area of technical barriers to trade on the business climate in Ukraine and of the perceptions by the business community of the reforms supported by the TBT SBS and other EU-funded programmes on the subject.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a matter of fact, systematic and timely evaluation of its programmes, activities, instruments, legislation and non-spending activities is a priority of the European Commission in order to demonstrate accountability and to promote lesson learning to improve policy and practice. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The generic purpose of the evaluation is to identify key lessons and to produce recommendations to improve current and inform future choices on the sector reform contracts in Ukraine and on the cooperation between the EU in Ukraine in the sphere of the removal of technical barriers in the trade in industrial goods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 130 days (until May 2017)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category I Expertise  in Technical Barriers to Trade – 50 working days&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in a field related to the assignment – economic, legal, financial, international relations, engineering etc. or at least extra 5 years of experience additional to that described below under the general professional experience; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;be proficient in English (level C1 in reading, speaking and writing);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;have excellent communication and analytical skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;be capable using modern IT technologies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;excellent writing skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The working knowledge of Ukrainian or Russian (at least level B2) will be an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least 12 years of relevant professional experience in the areas of technical regulation and quality infrastructure (non-food products), including standardisation, metrology, conformity assessment, market surveillance or accreditation institutions,;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least 1 year of professional experience in development cooperation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience in budget support implementation or evaluation would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the ENP countries, including Ukraine, will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category I Expertise in Evaluation</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-expertise-in-evaluation</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 19:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-expertise-in-evaluation</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation of the Sector Policy Support Programme &amp;lsquo;Promoting mutual trade by removing technical barriers to trade between Ukraine and the European Union&amp;rsquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific purpose for undertaking this evaluation is to evaluate the Technical Barriers to Trade in Sector Budget Support according to the standard OECD criteria and finally study the effects of EU-funded cooperation in the area of technical barriers to trade on the business climate in Ukraine and of the perceptions by the business community of the reforms supported by the TBT SBS and other EU-funded programmes on the subject.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a matter of fact, systematic and timely evaluation of its programmes, activities, instruments, legislation and non-spending activities is a priority of the European Commission in order to demonstrate accountability and to promote lesson learning to improve policy and practice. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The generic purpose of the evaluation is to identify key lessons and to produce recommendations to improve current and inform future choices on the sector reform contracts in Ukraine and on the cooperation between the EU in Ukraine in the sphere of the removal of technical barriers in the trade in industrial goods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 130 days (until May 2017)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category I Expertise in Evaluation – 50 working days&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in a field related to the assignment – economic, legal, financial, international relations, engineering etc. or at least extra 5 years of experience additional to that described below under the general professional experience; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;be proficient in English (level C1 in reading, speaking and writing);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;have excellent communication and analytical skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;be capable using modern IT technologies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;excellent writing skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Ukrainian or Russian (at least level B2) will be an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least 12 years of professional experience gained after obtaining the higher education diploma;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least seven years of experience in development cooperation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;proven experience in at least three evaluations; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in budget support implementation or evaluation will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert Spécialiste des Filières Agricoles 
CAT II</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-specialiste-des-filieres-agricoles-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-specialiste-des-filieres-agricoles-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mission d&amp;#39;assistance technique aupres du Ministere de l&amp;#39;Agriculture de l&amp;#39;Elevage (Phase transitoire)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général de l&amp;#39;intervention est de contribuer à la mise en place d&amp;#39;un partenariat efficace et pertinent entre la République du Bénin et l&amp;#39;Union Européenne pour le développement du secteur agricole et la sécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle du Bénin. L’objectif particulier consiste à appuyer le Ministère de l’Agriculture, de l’Elevage et de la Pêche (MAEP), dans la conception de la nouvelle stratégie de développement du secteur agricole et de ses modalités de mise en oeuvre et de pilotage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert Spécialiste des Filières Agricoles 
CAT II – 100 j/h&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;expert doit être titulaire d&amp;#39;un BAC+5 minimum en agronomie, économie rurale ou agricole, sociologie rurale, ou équivalent. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Il doit disposer d&amp;#39;au moins 6 ans d&amp;#39;expérience dans le diagnostic de filières agricoles et les stratégies de développement des filières et la mise en place d&amp;#39;interprofession. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La connaissance de la législation sur les interprofessions en Afrique de l&amp;#39;Ouest est souhaitée. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Il doit disposer d&amp;#39;une bonne connaissance du secteur agricole au Bénin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert Spécialiste du Financement du Secteur Agricole, CAT I</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-specialiste-du-financement-du-secteur-agricole-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 15:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-specialiste-du-financement-du-secteur-agricole-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mission d&amp;#39;assistance technique aupres du Ministere de l&amp;#39;Agriculture de l&amp;#39;Elevage (Phase transitoire)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général de l&amp;#39;intervention est de contribuer à la mise en place d&amp;#39;un partenariat efficace et pertinent entre la République du Bénin et l&amp;#39;Union Européenne pour le développement du secteur agricole et la sécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle du Bénin. L’objectif particulier consiste à appuyer le Ministère de l’Agriculture, de l’Elevage et de la Pêche (MAEP), dans la conception de la nouvelle stratégie de développement du secteur agricole et de ses modalités de mise en oeuvre et de pilotage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Expert Spécialiste du Financement du Secteur Agricole, CAT I – 100 j/h
*&lt;/em&gt;
BAC+5 minimum en agronomie, agroéconomie ou équivalent &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Le consultant doit disposer d’au moins 12 ans d&amp;#39;expérience dans le développement rural. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Il disposera d&amp;#39;au moins 6 ans d&amp;#39;expérience dans le financement du secteur agricole, avec au moins une expérience réussi d&amp;#39;octroi de subventions publiques et de (micro) crédit dans le monde agricole, au moins une expérience réussie en matière d’ingénierie de formation et l&amp;#39;élaboration de plan de formation basé sur l&amp;#39;analyse des besoins et des profils. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Il doit avoir une très bonne connaissance des institutions de financement du secteur agricole et du secteur agricole au Bénin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
