<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 16:47:15 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Senior Experts and a Junior Expert in Democracy/Governance or Rule of Law and IPA Experience (one TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/two-senior-experts-and-a-junior-expert-in-democracy-governance-or-rule-of-law-and-ipa-experience-one-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 16:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/two-senior-experts-and-a-junior-expert-in-democracy-governance-or-rule-of-law-and-ipa-experience-one-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation of Sector Approach under IPA II Assistance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The generic purpose of the evaluation is to provide an overall independent assessment and evidence on the use and scope of sector approach3 in planning, programming and implementation processes under IPA II, while also considering the evolution of the sector approach since the launch of the idea in the Conference on Effective Support for Enlargement held in Brussels in October 2009.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To provide an assessment in both qualitative and quantitative terms on the relevance, conditions of implementation and performance of EU pre-accession assistance in its sector approach, particularly its efficiency, effectiveness and added value as regards the achievement by candidate countries of their commitments for EU membership.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To provide to the Commission lessons learned and recommendations to improve the Sector Approach uptake under IPA II.
Results of the evaluation should also feed the finalisation of the Staff Working Document related to the IPA II Mid Term Review (to be finalised in the third quarter of 2017).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location visits&lt;/strong&gt;: Brussels and IPA II countries (Albania, Bosnia and Herzegovina, the former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, Iceland, Kosovo, Montenegro, Serbia and Turkey)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Two Senior Experts and a Junior Expert in Democracy/Governance or Rule of Law and IPA Experience (one TL)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience in relation to EU enlargement policy and strategy and pre-accession assistance (IPA) is required;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant expertise in candidate countries will be an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the EU institutional framework;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of evaluation methods and techniques and, preferably, of complex policy and strategy evaluations in the field of external relations. In particular the team needs to demonstrate experience in analytical methods which can evaluate change and contribution. This includes Quantitative and qualitative data collection and analysis;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technical/sector knowledge in the following areas is required:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Democracy and governance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rule of Law and fundamental rights&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analytical skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The team leader should have excellent communication, team co-ordination, presentation and proven report writing and editing skills in English.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The evaluation team will have excellent writing and editing skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one of the experts should have operational knowledge of implementation of budget support modalities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The evaluation team should have an excellent command of English – both spoken and written.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert en Finances Publiques / Financement du Développement Local (Catégorie I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-finances-publiques-financement-du-developpement-local-categorie-i</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 21:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-finances-publiques-financement-du-developpement-local-categorie-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appui au demarrage du Programme d&amp;#39;appui au Developpement Territorial 11eme FED Benin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif général de ce project est d’appuyer le Benin pour le démarrage de la mise en œuvre du Programme d&amp;#39;Appui au Développement Territorial (PADT) – 11ème FED. Les objectifs particuliers seront : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appuyer le Ministère de l’Economie et des Finances (Ordonnateur National) dans l’élaboration du Dossier d&amp;#39;appel d&amp;#39;offres pour le marché de services de recrutement du bureau qui fournira l’Assistance Technique long terme sur le PADT.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appuyer le démarrage de la mise en œuvre de la composante d’appui institutionnel  aux structures responsables de la mise en œuvre de la PONADEC, dans le cadre d&amp;#39;un Devis Programme (DP).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Réaliser le travail préparatoire en vue de définir les lignes directrices de l&amp;#39;Appel à propositions visant à financer des projets de territoire; et appuyer à la rédaction de ces lignes directrices. L&amp;#39;Appel à propositions sera inclus dans le DP.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Suivre de près la situation du FADEC: d&amp;#39;une part, sur le sujet d&amp;#39;une possible réforme du FADEC, et d&amp;#39;autre part sur les différents FADEC affectés (agriculture, éducation, santé, eau, etc.) au cours des derniers exercices 2014 à 2016 ainsi que les perspectives de ce mécanisme spécifique en vue notamment de fournir les éléments d&amp;#39;analyse nécessaires à la formulation du futur Projet d&amp;#39;appui à l&amp;#39;agriculture 11ème FED. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert en Finances Publiques / Financement du Développement Local (Catégorie I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formation, qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme d’études supérieures en sciences administratives, sciences économiques ou sciences sociales (bac + 5 minimum);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parfaite maîtrise du français écrit et oral;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise parfaite des outils informatiques courants;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonnes capacités de rédaction, de synthèse, de modération et de présentation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellentes capacités de communication orale et écrite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle&lt;/strong&gt; :    &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience d’au moins 12 ans dans le domaine des finances locales, des mécanismes de financement du  développement local et/ou des investissements communaux en Afrique sub-saharienne;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience avérée d&amp;#39;au moins 5 ans dans la mise en place de procédures administratives et financières de programmes et projets de développement local et/ou des investissements communaux en Afrique sub-saharienne;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience en préparation et élaboration de documents de projet avec les procédures FED/UE serait considérée comme un atout;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience en facilitation d&amp;#39;atelier de réflexion et de planification sur le développement serait considérée comme un atout;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience dans les thèmes transversaux tels que la bonne gouvernance, le genre et l&amp;#39;environnement serait considérée comme un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience au Bénin serait considérée comme un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert en Décentralisation et Renforcement Institutionnel des Administrations Territoriales</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-decentralisation-et-renforcement-institutionnel-des-administrations-territoriales</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 20:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-decentralisation-et-renforcement-institutionnel-des-administrations-territoriales</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appui au demarrage du Programme d&amp;#39;appui au Developpement Territorial 11eme FED Benin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif général de ce project est d’appuyer le Benin pour le démarrage de la mise en œuvre du Programme d&amp;#39;Appui au Développement Territorial (PADT) – 11ème FED. Les objectifs particuliers seront : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appuyer le Ministère de l’Economie et des Finances (Ordonnateur National) dans l’élaboration du Dossier d&amp;#39;appel d&amp;#39;offres pour le marché de services de recrutement du bureau qui fournira l’Assistance Technique long terme sur le PADT.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appuyer le démarrage de la mise en œuvre de la composante d’appui institutionnel  aux structures responsables de la mise en œuvre de la PONADEC, dans le cadre d&amp;#39;un Devis Programme (DP).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Réaliser le travail préparatoire en vue de définir les lignes directrices de l&amp;#39;Appel à propositions visant à financer des projets de territoire; et appuyer à la rédaction de ces lignes directrices. L&amp;#39;Appel à propositions sera inclus dans le DP.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Suivre de près la situation du FADEC: d&amp;#39;une part, sur le sujet d&amp;#39;une possible réforme du FADEC, et d&amp;#39;autre part sur les différents FADEC affectés (agriculture, éducation, santé, eau, etc.) au cours des derniers exercices 2014 à 2016 ainsi que les perspectives de ce mécanisme spécifique en vue notamment de fournir les éléments d&amp;#39;analyse nécessaires à la formulation du futur Projet d&amp;#39;appui à l&amp;#39;agriculture 11ème FED. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chef de Mission (Catégorie I) – Expert en Décentralisation et Renforcement Institutionnel des Administrations Territoriales&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formation, qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme d’études supérieures en sciences administratives, sciences économiques, sciences politiques, sciences sociales ou autres domaines pertinents et équivalents (bac + 5 minimum);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parfaite maîtrise du français écrit et oral;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise parfaite des outils informatiques courants;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonnes capacités de rédaction, de synthèse, de modération et de présentation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellentes capacités de communication orale et écrite.
Expérience professionnelle :&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience d’au moins 12 ans dans le domaine du renforcement/ accompagnement institutionnel de l&amp;#39;administration territoriale et des processus de décentralisation et déconcentration en Afrique sub-saharienne;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience avérée d&amp;#39;au moins 5 ans en préparation et conduite de réflexions et programmations stratégiques d&amp;#39;appuis aux politiques nationales dans les domaines du développement local et de la décentralisation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience d&amp;#39;au moins 5 ans dans la gouvernance locale, le développement local et l&amp;#39;aménagement du territoire en Afrique de l&amp;#39;Ouest.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience avérée en préparation et élaboration de documents de projet avec les procédures FED/UE, notamment dans la formulation et l&amp;#39;évaluation de programmes de coopération utilisant des modalités mixtes (approche projet et appui budgétaire sectoriel).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience avérée en facilitation d&amp;#39;atelier de réflexion et de planification sur le développement;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience dans les thèmes transversaux tels que la bonne gouvernance, le genre et l&amp;#39;environnement serait considérée comme un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience au Bénin serait considérée comme un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decentralization Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/decentralization-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 13:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/decentralization-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Evaluation of LGU PFM Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of the assignment is to report on progress and results achieved during implementation compared to the initial objectives of the programme as well as lessons learnt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Systematic and timely evaluation of its programmes and activities is an established priority of the European Commission. The focus of evaluations is on the assessment of achievements, the quality and the results of interventions in the context of an evolving cooperation policy with an increasing emphasis on result-oriented approaches. Evaluations should provide an understanding of the cause and effects links between activities and results. Evaluations should serve decision making, learning and management purposes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of the evaluation are to provide the relevant external co-operation services of the European Union, the partner government and, when appropriate, the wider public with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an overall independent assessment of the past performance of the intervention &amp;ldquo;Support to the Local Government Units for more Effective and Accountable Public Finance  Management&amp;rdquo;, paying particularly attention to the results of the project against its objectives;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;key lessons and recommendations in order to improve sustainability and mainstreaming of the results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2: Decentralization expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post Graduate Degree or equivalent in Economics, Development Management, Development Studies, or equivalent professional experience of at least 10 years in Decentralization;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of relevant professional experience in fields related to this assignment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 4 years professional experience in decentralisation processes, including fiscal decentralization,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years of work experience with capacity-building and institutional development, including needs assessment and evaluation of capacity-building interventions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous relevant experience in the Philippines will be an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Soft skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good culturally sensitive communication, facilitation and presentation skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An excellent verbal and written command of English is essential.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Tagalog would be an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Public Finance Management Expert (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-public-finance-management-expert-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 13:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-public-finance-management-expert-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Evaluation of LGU PFM Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of the assignment is to report on progress and results achieved during implementation compared to the initial objectives of the programme as well as lessons learnt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Systematic and timely evaluation of its programmes and activities is an established priority of the European Commission. The focus of evaluations is on the assessment of achievements, the quality and the results of interventions in the context of an evolving cooperation policy with an increasing emphasis on result-oriented approaches. Evaluations should provide an understanding of the cause and effects links between activities and results. Evaluations should serve decision making, learning and management purposes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;
The specific objectives of the evaluation are to provide the relevant external co-operation services of the European Union, the partner government and, when appropriate, the wider public with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an overall independent assessment of the past performance of the intervention &amp;ldquo;Support to the Local Government Units for more Effective and Accountable Public Finance  Management&amp;rdquo;, paying particularly attention to the results of the project against its objectives;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;key lessons and recommendations in order to improve sustainability and mainstreaming of the results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 1 : Public Finance Management Expert -Team leader&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post Graduate Degree or equivalent in Economics, Development Management,
Development Studies, or equivalent professional experience of at least 20 years in Public Finance Management;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of relevant professional experience in fields related to this assignment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven in depth knowledge and experience in at least three different developing countries, for at least one year in each of the three countries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 8 years professional experience in Public Finance Management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience with sub-national level PFM and public administration reform;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with EU Guidelines on Project Cycle Management and with evaluation procedures used by the EU for development projects is an advantage Experience in South East Asia is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years&amp;#39; experience in team management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Soft skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good culturally sensitive communication, facilitation and presentation skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An excellent verbal and written command of English is essential.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gender/Development Expert (Cat.III)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/gender-development-expert-catiii</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 13:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/gender-development-expert-catiii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gender Study for Central Asia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objective of the study is to provide the EU with a review of the gender situation in Central Asia and in each of the 5 countries of the region (i.e. Kazakhstan, Uzbekistan, Tajikistan, Turkmenistan, and Kyrgyzstan) as well as specific recommendations. The review will provide an understanding whether gender inequalities persist both formally and informally in each country of Central Asia, i.e. Kazakhstan, Uzbekistan, Tajikistan, Turkmenistan, Kyrgyzstan and in the Central Asia region considered as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gender/Development Expert (Cat.III)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree or equivalent in political or social science; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good communication skills, both oral and written; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer literacy (minimum MS word, Excel).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 years extensive experience in the context of gender and development and/ or as a consultant from both short and long-term assignments on gender related studies; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of the development context of the Central Asian region; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience of EU practices in development programmes; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in data analysis is a plus; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Local Central Asia expertise would be considered as an advantage &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in oral and written English; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in oral and written Russian. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Governance Issues and/or Social Development and/or Gender Analysis (Cat I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-governance-issues-and-or-social-development-and-or-gender-analysis-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 13:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-governance-issues-and-or-social-development-and-or-gender-analysis-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gender Study for Central Asia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objective of the study is to provide the EU with a review of the gender situation in Central Asia and in each of the 5 countries of the region (i.e. Kazakhstan, Uzbekistan, Tajikistan, Turkmenistan, and Kyrgyzstan) as well as specific recommendations. The review will provide an understanding whether gender inequalities persist both formally and informally in each country of Central Asia, i.e. Kazakhstan, Uzbekistan, Tajikistan, Turkmenistan, Kyrgyzstan and in the Central Asia region considered as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Governance Issues and/or Social Development and/or Gender Analysis (Cat I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Postgraduate university degree or equivalent in political or social sciences; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong writing and communication skills; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer literacy (minimum MS Word, Excel). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 12 years’ experience in governance issues and/or social development and/or gender analysis; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific experience and expertise on gender analysis, gender mainstreaming and women&amp;rsquo;s participation; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience working on national gender policies in developing countries; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working in the countries of Central Asia is essential, other field experience being desirable; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organisational development and capacity building experience; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of international/regional agreements and initiatives on gender (UN, CEDAW, Beijing, etc.); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in managing a team of experts; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Up-to-date and comprehensive knowledge and experience of EU development, policies, instruments and facilities. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in oral and written English; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in oral and written Russian is an asset &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring and Evaluation Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/monitoring-and-evaluation-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 10:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/monitoring-and-evaluation-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance to NCHR to Manage, Monitor and Evaluate the Beneficiaries and the Grants Awarded under EU Support to CS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The overall objective of this contract is to provide Technical Assistance to manage the implementation of the EU Support to Civil Society in Jordan Project. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The overall objective of this contract is to provide Technical Assistance to NCHR and project staff on Grant Management, M&amp;amp;E and reporting on the results of the EU Support to Civil Society in Jordan Project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring and Evaluation Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post graduate degree (Master or equivalent) in development, human rights, political or social/behavioural science, or equivalent experience in other relevant fields; a post-graduate degree in one of the relevant fields mentioned will be considered an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10 years of professional experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in project management, as well as in outreach, communication and coordination skills; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High communication skills with the &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;institutional beneficiaries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 7 years subject-related experience in Monitoring and Evaluation for Civil Society Grants;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 years technical experience related to CSO cooperation (community development, civil society capacity building, human rights, good governance);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English, i.e. minimum level C1 as per Common European Framework of Reference for &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Languages; Excellent command of Arabic (level C1).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;Aurelie_Durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Civil Society Grants Management Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/civil-society-grants-management-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 10:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/civil-society-grants-management-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance to NCHR to Manage, Monitor and Evaluate the Beneficiaries and the Grants Awarded under EU Support to CS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The overall objective of this contract is to provide Technical Assistance to manage the implementation of the EU Support to Civil Society in Jordan Project. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The overall objective of this contract is to provide Technical Assistance to NCHR and project staff on Grant Management, M&amp;amp;E and reporting on the results of the EU Support to Civil Society in Jordan Project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Civil Society Grants Management Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post graduate degree (Master or equivalent) in development, human rights, political or social/behavioural science, or equivalent experience in &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;other relevant fields;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10 years of professional experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 7 years Civil Society Grants experience within EU-funded projects and programs and under the EU thematic focus area of civil society;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;7 years technical experience related to government- civil society cooperation in the fields of community development, civil society capacity building, human rights, good governance and other relevant areas if focus under the European Neighbourhood Policies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English, i.e. minimum level C1 as per Common European Framework of Reference for &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Languages - Working knowledge of Arabic would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;Aurelie_Durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experto Categoría III – Informático</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-categoria-iii-informatico</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 16:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-categoria-iii-informatico</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Asistencia Tecnica para el Sistema de Planificacion Integral del Estado (SPIE)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;El contrato tiene como objetivo general reforzar el proceso de planificación de Bolivia para asegurar el continuo éxito de las operaciones de Apoyo Presupuestario Sectorial entre la Unión Europea y el Gobierno de Bolivia.
El contrato tiene como objetivo específico apoyar al Ministerio de Planificación del Desarrollo en la implementación del Sistema de Planificación Integral del Estado (SPIE). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Servicios Requeridos&lt;/strong&gt;:
Proporcionar documentos metodológicos, técnicos, normativos que sean útiles para la asistencia técnica a los Gobiernos Autónomos Departamentales y Municipales y entidades públicas para, entre otros, facilitar el cumplimiento de formulación de los Planes Territoriales de Desarrollo Integral (PTDI) por parte de dichos gobiernos autónomos. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experto Categoría III – Informático&lt;/strong&gt;  (80 días laborales)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preparación y calificaciones&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formación académica en el rubro de informática&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competencia en elaboración y manejo de tutoriales web y conocimiento de redes, programación y administración de plataformas web e  interfaces web para bases de datos (digitalización de datos y consultas)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competencia deseable en lenguajes de programación y herramientas informáticas (SQL y PHP, HTML, Javascript)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debe hablar y escribir fluidamente en español &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experiencia profesional general&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mínimo 3 años de experiencia en preparación y puesta en marcha de tutoriales y/o gestión de sistemas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mínimo 3 años de experiencia laboral en Bolivia, que permita un conocimiento de las condiciones de sistemas informáticos en el país&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia en apoyo a sistemas informáticos gubernamentales&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experto Categoría III – Experto en Medios  </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-categoria-iii-experto-en-medios</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 16:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-categoria-iii-experto-en-medios</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Asistencia Tecnica para el Sistema de Planificacion Integral del Estado (SPIE)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;El contrato tiene como objetivo general reforzar el proceso de planificación de Bolivia para asegurar el continuo éxito de las operaciones de Apoyo Presupuestario Sectorial entre la Unión Europea y el Gobierno de Bolivia.
El contrato tiene como objetivo específico apoyar al Ministerio de Planificación del Desarrollo en la implementación del Sistema de Planificación Integral del Estado (SPIE). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Servicios Requeridos&lt;/strong&gt;:
Proporcionar documentos metodológicos, técnicos, normativos que sean útiles para la asistencia técnica a los Gobiernos Autónomos Departamentales y Municipales y entidades públicas para, entre otros, facilitar el cumplimiento de formulación de los Planes Territoriales de Desarrollo Integral (PTDI) por parte de dichos gobiernos autónomos. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experto Categoría III – Experto en medios  (80 días laborales)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preparación y calificaciones&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formación académica en ciencias de la comunicación,  periodismo o ramas afines;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competencia en elaboración y manejo de manuales de usuario de sistemas gubernamentales de seguimiento, evaluación e información &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competencia en elaboración de videos, cuñas radiales, cartillas informativas y otros productos audiovisuales&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excelente dominio del idioma español, oral y escrito.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experiencia profesional general&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mínimo 3 años de experiencia en el área de comunicación, en medios de prensa, agencias gubernamentales o internacionales;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia en elaboración y administración de sistemas de información, comunicación, seguimiento y monitoreo de entidades gubernamentales.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia en manejo de formatos audiovisuales multilingües
Experiencia profesional específica deseable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Haber realizado al menos dos consultorías en comunicación institucional, de preferencia en organismos gubernamentales en Bolivia.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dominio de criterios gráficos y audiovisuales.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia en trabajo dentro de o en apoyo a instituciones gubernamentales a nivel central o sub-nacional. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experto Categoría II – Coordinador y Experto en Gestión Pública</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-categoria-ii-coordinador-y-experto-en-gestion-publica</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-categoria-ii-coordinador-y-experto-en-gestion-publica</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Asistencia Tecnica para el Sistema de Planificacion Integral del Estado (SPIE)
*&lt;/em&gt;
El contrato tiene como objetivo general reforzar el proceso de planificación de Bolivia para asegurar el continuo éxito de las operaciones de Apoyo Presupuestario Sectorial entre la Unión Europea y el Gobierno de Bolivia.
El contrato tiene como objetivo específico apoyar al Ministerio de Planificación del Desarrollo en la implementación del Sistema de Planificación Integral del Estado (SPIE). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Servicios Requeridos&lt;/strong&gt;:
Proporcionar documentos metodológicos, técnicos, normativos que sean útiles para la asistencia técnica a los Gobiernos Autónomos Departamentales y Municipales y entidades públicas para, entre otros, facilitar el cumplimiento de formulación de los Planes Territoriales de Desarrollo Integral (PTDI) por parte de dichos gobiernos autónomos. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experto Categoría II – Coordinador y experto en gestión pública  (80 días laborales)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preparación y calificaciones&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formación académica en los rubros de economía, administración de empresas o derecho. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Al menos maestría en temáticas relacionadas a la gestión pública, administración territorial, planificación del desarrollo, gestión de financiamiento externo o inversión pública&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debe hablar y escribir fluidamente en español. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debe tener facilidad de comunicación y negociación para relacionarse con autoridades nacionales, sub-nacionales y organizaciones sociales, competencia intercultural.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experiencia profesional general&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mínimo de 6 años de experiencia en los sectores de economía, descentralización o planificación del desarrollo. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia en ámbito de la gestión pública y administración territorial que incluya elementos jurídicos, administrativos, normativos, reglamentarios, de planificación, de monitoreo y seguimiento así como los referidos a la gestión de financiamiento externo e inversión pública.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experiencia profesional específica deseable&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mínimo de 6 años de experiencia en la elaboración de normas y/o reglamentos de leyes, decretos o resoluciones de entidades estatales en América Latina. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia en trabajo dentro de o en apoyo a instituciones gubernamentales a nivel central o sub-nacional.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia laboral de al menos 3 años en Bolivia &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junior Design and Layout Expert (Cat. II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-design-and-layout-expert-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 09:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-design-and-layout-expert-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;External Support - Background Analysis and Brochure on Transparency and Traceability in the Garment Value Chain&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General objective&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The present external support is aimed at assisting the Commission in compiling relevant information on transparency and traceability in the garment sector. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The output will be a background analysis and brochure to explain how traceability can turn the challenge of transparency into new opportunities: A growing reliable garment industry in which social and environmental standards are respected. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The target group of the brochure (leaflet/brochure/fact sheet) is in the first place interested citizens/consumers of clothing, however the various representatives of civil society and private sector active in the garment sector are also target audience (i.e. including companies, organizations, associations, academic institutions etc) in particular as a leverage to a wider audience, coming from all EU Member States and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The *&lt;em&gt;specific *&lt;/em&gt;objectives of the assignment are to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;support the Commission in carrying out a background analysis to feed into work carried out on responsible management of the value chain in the garment sector,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;provide a tangible output in the form of a brochure to be published to  inform relevant stakeholders and the general public, in particular to help consumers  of clothing to make informed purchasing decisions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Junior Design and Layout expert (Cat. II)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 years&amp;#39; experience in designing layout of brochures aimed at the target audience as described in these terms of reference;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in a wide range of graphic design software (including InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop, Flash, QuarkXpress, Dreamweaver);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent creative graphic design, layout skills, with work samples to be attached to CV; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent knowledge in printing requirements and output;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in sourcing appropriate visual material suitable to illustrate the theme;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in designing and laying out European Commission communication material is considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;Aurelie_Durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Text Expert (Cat. II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-text-expert-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 08:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-text-expert-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;External Support - Background Analysis and Brochure on Transparency and Traceability in the Garment Value Chain&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General objective&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The present external support is aimed at assisting the Commission in compiling relevant information on transparency and traceability in the garment sector. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The output will be a background analysis and brochure to explain how traceability can turn the challenge of transparency into new opportunities: A growing reliable garment industry in which social and environmental standards are respected. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The target group of the brochure (leaflet/brochure/fact sheet) is in the first place interested citizens/consumers of clothing, however the various representatives of civil society and private sector active in the garment sector are also target audience (i.e. including companies, organizations, associations, academic institutions etc) in particular as a leverage to a wider audience, coming from all EU Member States and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt; of the assignment are to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;support the Commission in carrying out a background analysis to feed into work carried out on responsible management of the value chain in the garment sector,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;provide a tangible output in the form of a brochure to be published to  inform relevant stakeholders and the general public, in particular to help consumers  of clothing to make informed purchasing decisions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Text Expert (Cat. II)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent drafting skills in English; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5 years of professional experience in production of brochures;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in drafting European Commission communication material; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of the topics to be covered is an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;Aurelie_Durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junior Garment Supply Chain Expert (Cat. II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-garment-supply-chain-expert-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 08:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-garment-supply-chain-expert-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;External Support - Background Analysis and Brochure on Transparency and Traceability in the Garment Value Chain&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General objective&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The present external support is aimed at assisting the Commission in compiling relevant information on transparency and traceability in the garment sector. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The output will be a background analysis and brochure to explain how traceability can turn the challenge of transparency into new opportunities: A growing reliable garment industry in which social and environmental standards are respected. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The target group of the brochure (leaflet/brochure/fact sheet) is in the first place interested citizens/consumers of clothing, however the various representatives of civil society and private sector active in the garment sector are also target audience (i.e. including companies, organizations, associations, academic institutions etc) in particular as a leverage to a wider audience, coming from all EU Member States and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of the assignment are to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;support the Commission in carrying out a background analysis to feed into work carried out on responsible management of the value chain in the garment sector,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;provide a tangible output in the form of a brochure to be published to  inform relevant stakeholders and the general public, in particular to help consumers  of clothing to make informed purchasing decisions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Junior Garment Supply Chain Expert (Cat. II)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in development studies, economics, business administration, law or equivalent;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 years of professional experience in economic/trade/supply chain analysis in the public or private sector, including with EU institutions or the design and delivery of EU cooperation programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of traceability systems, certification and auditing procedures applied in the garment sector on sustainability standards;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of trends and data/IT-solutions concerning transparency and traceability in supply chains; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in collection, screening and analysis of large amounts of information from different sources including its consolidation and targeted condensation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent analytical and research-oriented skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency and excellent English report writing skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;Aurelie_Durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;lsquo;Phone interviews&lt;/strong&gt; to be held on 9th/10th November.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Garment Supply Chain Expert (Cat. I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-garment-supply-chain-expert-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-garment-supply-chain-expert-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;External Support - Background Analysis and Brochure on Transparency and Traceability in the Garment Value Chain&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General objective&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The present external support is aimed at assisting the Commission in compiling relevant information on transparency and traceability in the garment sector. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The output will be a background analysis and brochure to explain how traceability can turn the challenge of transparency into new opportunities: A growing reliable garment industry in which social and environmental standards are respected. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The target group of the brochure (leaflet/brochure/fact sheet) is in the first place interested citizens/consumers of clothing, however the various representatives of civil society and private sector active in the garment sector are also target audience (i.e. including companies, organizations, associations, academic institutions etc) in particular as a leverage to a wider audience, coming from all EU Member States and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of the assignment are to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;support the Commission in carrying out a background analysis to feed into work carried out on responsible management of the value chain in the garment sector,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;provide a tangible output in the form of a brochure to be published to  inform relevant stakeholders and the general public, in particular to help consumers  of clothing to make informed purchasing decisions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;Aurelie_Durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;lsquo;Phone interviews&lt;/strong&gt; to be held on 9th/10th November.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cat.II Expert in Sustainable Energy</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/catii-expert-in-sustainable-energy</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 16:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/catii-expert-in-sustainable-energy</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Provision of Technical Assistance and preparation of Programming Documents for the 11th EDF Thematic OCT Programme&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of the assignment is to assist OCTA in the programming process for the thematic programme. This assignment will be carried out following the Programming instructions for the 11th EDF, and should consider the wider impact of interventions, studies and when applicable, projects that will be executed in its context.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in Sustainable Energy (Cat II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree or equivalent in Energy engineering or other relevant field or, in its absence, 5 years professional experience in sustainable/renewable energy sector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A high level of written and spoken English and French. He/she must be an excellent communicator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years&amp;#39; experience in the execution of sustainable/renewable energy programmes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Following experience&lt;/strong&gt; will be considered as advantage:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in EU/EDF procedures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in EDF programme identification and formulation, possibly at regional level.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience in the design and formulation of supported programmes and projects in renewable energy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Following experience&lt;/strong&gt; will be considered as advantage:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with project or programme in small and isolated island territories.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with projects in Outermost Regions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with similar projects in the OCTs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert – Climate Change/DRR Expert (Cat I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-climate-change-drr-expert-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 16:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-climate-change-drr-expert-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Provision of Technical Assistance and preparation of Programming Documents for the 11th EDF Thematic OCT Programme&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of the assignment is to assist OCTA in the programming process for the thematic programme. This assignment will be carried out following the Programming instructions for the 11th EDF, and should consider the wider impact of interventions, studies and when applicable, projects that will be executed in its context.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Senior Expert – Climate Change/DRR Expert (Cat I)
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree or equivalent in Environmental Engineering, Natural Sciences, or other relevant field or, in its absence, 5 years professional experience in project management for environmental/climate change/ORR change projects . &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; A high level of written and spoken English and French. He/she must be an excellent communicator. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; At least 12 years international experience in project or programme management in the area of climate change adaptation and mitigation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Experience in EU/EDF procedures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Following experience&lt;/strong&gt; will be considered as advantage:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Experience in coordination, communications and interactions with different stakeholders including high level government officials, international donors, academic sector and research centres, NGO&amp;rsquo;s etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; At least 5 years&amp;#39; experience in EDF programme identification and formulation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Experience with project or programme management or formulation in OCT&amp;rsquo;s or small and isolated island territories or Outermost regions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Following experience&lt;/strong&gt; will be considered as advantage:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Experience with similar regional projects in small island states&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Experience with similar regional projects in Outermost Regions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Experience with similar regional projects in the OCTs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cat.II Expert in Wildlife Management and Monitoring, Bio-Informatics and Information systems</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/catii-expert-in-wildlife-management-and-monitoring-bio-informatics-and-information-systems</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 15:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/catii-expert-in-wildlife-management-and-monitoring-bio-informatics-and-information-systems</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to Large Carnivore Sustainable Trophy Hunting&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project is aimed at improving the sustainability of exports of leopard and lion hunting trophies to the EU, and more generally at improving the sustainable management of Zambia&amp;rsquo;s leopard and lion population. The project should in particular aim at providing support to the DNPW to ensure that the hunting and export quotas established by the Zambian authorities for leopards and lions are conservative and sustainable, and to ensure that these quotas are based on adaptive management schemes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cat.II Expert in Wildlife Management and Monitoring, Bio-Informatics and Information systems&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master’s Degree in the field of environment. In the absence of a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree, the expert must have an equivalent extra professional experience (two years) in the below mentioned sectors, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of experience in the sector(s) related to the Lot; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in large databases management, data analysis and information delivery to end users. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in written and spoken English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key experts&lt;/strong&gt; should collectively have expertise in: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive work experience in the field of ecology, in particular wildlife management, research and monitoring. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific experience regarding the biology of leopards, lions, their prey and the relevant conservation and management issues facing them will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated extensive experience and recognized expertise on sustainable management and conservation of large carnivore and the monitoring of trophy hunted wildlife populations, in particular leopard and lions. Respective experience in Zambia will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific experience regarding wildlife trade and implementation of the Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species of Fauna and Flora (CITES). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific experience in bio-informatics and information systems regarding wildlife hunting and trade would be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific experience in the management of sustainable trophy hunting activities. Respective experience in Zambia will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the specific institutional context and organization of leopard and lion management and conservation in Zambia, as well as working experience with the Zambian authorities in charge of wildlife would be important assets. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project management &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience in development and implementation of hunting database systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dail.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cat.II Expert (TL) in Wildlife Management and Monitoring, Trophy Hunting and Trade (CITES)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/catii-expert-tl-in-wildlife-management-and-monitoring-trophy-hunting-and-trade-cites</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/catii-expert-tl-in-wildlife-management-and-monitoring-trophy-hunting-and-trade-cites</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to Large Carnivore Sustainable Trophy Hunting&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project is aimed at improving the sustainability of exports of leopard and lion hunting trophies to the EU, and more generally at improving the sustainable management of Zambia&amp;rsquo;s leopard and lion population. The project should in particular aim at providing support to the DNPW to ensure that the hunting and export quotas established by the Zambian authorities for leopards and lions are conservative and sustainable, and to ensure that these quotas are based on adaptive management schemes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team leader – Wildlife Management and Monitoring, Trophy Hunting and Trade (CITES) Expert (Cat II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in the field of Ecology, Natural Resources Management or equivalent. In the absence of a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree, the expert must have an equivalent extra professional experience (six years) in the below mentioned sectors, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of experience in the sector(s) related to the Lot; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Workshop planning and coordination, field activity coordination &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in written and spoken English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key experts&lt;/strong&gt; should collectively have expertise in: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive work experience in the field of ecology, in particular wildlife management, research and monitoring. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific experience regarding the biology of leopards, lions, their prey and the relevant conservation and management issues facing them will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated extensive experience and recognized expertise on sustainable management and conservation of large carnivore and the monitoring of trophy hunted wildlife populations, in particular leopard and lions. Respective experience in Zambia will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific experience regarding wildlife trade and implementation of the Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species of Fauna and Flora (CITES). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific experience in bio-informatics and information systems regarding wildlife hunting and trade would be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific experience in the management of sustainable trophy hunting activities. Respective experience in Zambia will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the specific institutional context and organization of leopard and lion management and conservation in Zambia, as well as working experience with the Zambian authorities in charge of wildlife would be important assets. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project management &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience in development and implementation of hunting database systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
