<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2015 22:35:27 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert on Equipment for the Purposes of Border Control of Persons</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-on-equipment-for-the-purposes-of-border-control-of-persons</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2015 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-on-equipment-for-the-purposes-of-border-control-of-persons</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pre-feasibility Study for projects to be possibly funded under the Eastern Partnership Integrated Border Management Flagship Initiative&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To facilitate preparation of action document for financing four projects concerning integrated border management at the Moldova-Ukraine border.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert on Equipment for the Purposes of Border Control of Persons&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in a field related to the assignment  (border management, law enforcement),  or specialised diploma from police/military  academy, or equivalent professional experience of 4 years in border management or law enforcement in addition to the general professional experience required below;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Excellent English communication skills, both spoken and written;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Good command of Russian will be an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A  minimum  of  10  years  of  experience  working  for  border  management  institution  (relevant department in Ministry of internal Affairs, Border Guards service, Border Police);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At  least  5  years of  practical  experience  in  procuring  modern  equipment,  compliant  with  EU standards, for control of persons and vehicles at BCPs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least 3 years of experience in developing and/or procuring soft and hardware for national databases/IT  systems  to  support  the  exchange  of  information  (including  real  time  information transfer,  secure  communication  link)  between  border agencies  in  the  same  country  and  between agencies of neighbouring countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Senior Climate Change Experts </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/three-senior-climate-change-experts</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2015 21:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/three-senior-climate-change-experts</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mainstreaming Climate Change within the EUD in Turkey&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objective of the assignment is to ensure better management and monitoring of the EU funds via safeguarding compliance with the relevant EU climate action priorities and to increase the value added created by the EU financial assistance in Turkey through mainstreaming on climate action within the EU Delegation for the second period of IPA 2014-2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Three Senior Climate Change Experts&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With expertise on:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development and/or review and/or assessment of planning documents on climate action&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development of guidelines on screening/mainstreaming climate change into policy and planning documents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Setting up indicator based monitoring and evaluation schemes at project and program levels on climate change&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in results and/or outcome based evaluations of climate change projects and programmes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Existing monitoring and evaluation schemes that are internationally acknowledged e.g. UNFCC, GEF, UN, EU&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Long-term EU and international climate policies and practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert in Property Rights and Property Legislation in Kosovo or Region</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-property-rights-and-property-legislation-in-kosovo-or-region</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2015 21:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-property-rights-and-property-legislation-in-kosovo-or-region</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation of the Project: Support to Civil Code and Property Rights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Provide an overall independent assessment of the project &amp;ldquo;Support to Civil Code and Property Rights&amp;rdquo; (IPA/2014/344-574), paying particularly attention to sustainability of results and impact of the project and develop in a participatory process key lessons and recommendations for future EU support and the overall reforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in Property Rights and Property Legislation in Kosovo or Region&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A degree in Law, international public law, property law, bar exam or other relevant;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;strong command of written and spoken English and Albanian, Serbian language skills are considered an asset,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 6 years of experience as legal professional, judge and/or academic working on issues related the area of property rights and property legislation, such experience acquired in Kosovo or a country with a comparable legislative environment in the region is considered a strong asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in evaluation of at least one project in the field of property rights related reforms. This must be evidenced by at least one report in English language co-authored by the expert and to be submitted as part of the offer,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in working on evaluation of international donor funded projects in relation to property rights reform in Kosovo or a country with a comparable legislative environment in the region is considered a strong asset (this experience would need to be evidenced by submission of at least one relevant report as part of the offer).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Justice Sector Institutions (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-justice-sector-institutions-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2015 21:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-justice-sector-institutions-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Provide an overall independent assessment of the project &amp;ldquo;Support to Civil Code and Property Rights&amp;rdquo; (IPA/2014/344-574), paying particularly attention to sustainability of results and impact of the project and develop in a participatory process key lessons and recommendations for future EU support and the overall reforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Justice Sector Institutions (TL)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The team leader is responsible for delivery of the evaluation and all reports timely, in good order and quality. Also the team leader is managing the team, the inputs of the other experts, work-planning and ensuring that all logistical issues are smoothly taken care off. In summary the team leader is in charge of delivering the project results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A degree in Law or associated fields or a bar exam or membership in the bar or other relevant;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skills for management of a team and deliver under tight deadlines;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of written and spoken English, excellent communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 6 years relevant professional experience working for in justice sector institutions, working experience on civil law issues in a continental law system is considered an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in working on civil legislation reform in third countries, such experience acquired in Kosovo or a country with a similar context is considered an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience as Team Leader in at least one similar evaluation or assessment. This experience must be evidenced by one report written by the proposed Team Leader and
submitted as part of the offer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert en monitoring des medias en période de campagne électorale (cat. I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-monitoring-des-medias-en-periode-de-campagne-electorale-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2015 20:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-monitoring-des-medias-en-periode-de-campagne-electorale-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif générale de la mission est de contribuer au bon déroulement, dans un climat apaisé et dans des conditions de transparence, des élections processus électoral (élections locales, législatives et présidentielle) qui vont se tenir au Niger au cours du premier semestre 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif particulier c’est appuyer le Conseil Supérieur de la Communication dans sa mission d’évaluation de la  ouverture, par les médias, de la campagne électorale lors des élections législatives et présidentielle ainsi que de l&amp;#39;environnement médiatique global.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert en monitoring des medias en période de campagne électorale (cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire niveau Master ou équivalent en sciences sociales, politiques, juridiques, de la communication ou équivalent un une expérience professionnelle équivalent d’au moins 15 ans;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;15 Ans d&amp;#39;expérience prouvée en matière de monitoring des médias en période électorale, d&amp;#39;analyse qualitative des contenus des médias, de rédaction de rapport de monitoring, de formation des journalistes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10 ans d&amp;#39;expérience dans la gestion d&amp;#39;une équipe de monitoring des médias en période de campagne électorale au sein d&amp;#39;une mission d&amp;#39;observation électorale ou d&amp;#39;un autre organe indépendant de monitoring des médias ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;L&amp;#39;expert apportera la preuve de sa familiarité avec les différents systèmes électoraux existants et avec les normes internationales en matière électorale ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Il doit avoir des aptitudes à travailler en équipe et sous pression ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience en Afrique subsaharienne sera considérée un atout ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;La connaissance des procédures FED et de la gestion du cycle du projet est un atout ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maitrise de la langue française et connaissance de base de l&amp;#39;anglais.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junior External Assessor - Experience in Forest Governance and/or REDD+</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-external-assessor-experience-in-1</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2015 16:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-external-assessor-experience-in-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To assist the Contracting Authority in the assessment of proposals under the call on “Non-State Actors Participation on Forest Governance, FLEGT and REDD+” and on “Marine and coastal Biodiversity in the Caribbean Sea basin”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years’ experience in implementation or conception/design or monitoring/evaluation of development cooperation projects in forest governance and/or REDD+;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in assessment of CfP;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in empowerment or strengthening of civil society organisations is an added-value;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work experience in one or several of the regions covered by this CfP is an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent level of English and French and/or Spanish&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junior External Assessor - Experience in marine/coastal biodiversity or natural resources management project</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-external-assessor-experience-in</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2015 16:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-external-assessor-experience-in</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To assist the Contracting Authority in the assessment of proposals under the call on “Non-State Actors Participation on Forest Governance, FLEGT and REDD+” and on “Marine and coastal Biodiversity in the Caribbean Sea basin”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years’ experience in implementation or conception/design or monitoring/evaluation of development cooperation projects in marine/coastal biodiversity or natural resources management;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in assessment of CfP;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in empowerment or strengthening of civil society organisations is an added-value;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work experience in one or several of the regions covered by this CfP is an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent level of English and French and/or Spanish&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_herandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Marine/coastal biodiversity, Forest Governance or REDD+ and CfPs (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-marine-coastal-biodiversity-forest-governance-or-redd-and-cfps</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2015 15:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-marine-coastal-biodiversity-forest-governance-or-redd-and-cfps</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To assist the Contracting Authority in the assessment of proposals under the call on “Non-State Actors Participation on Forest Governance, FLEGT and REDD+” and on “Marine and coastal Biodiversity in the Caribbean Sea basin”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in marine/coastal biodiversity, forest governance or REDD+ and CfPs (TL)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years’ experience in implementation or conception/design or evaluation/monitoring of development projects, in at least one of the following sectors: marine/coastal biodiversity, forest governance, REDD+;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience as TL, including the management of team of experts; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in assessment of CfP;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in: empowerment or strengthening of civil society organisations and, sector policy making;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work experience in one or several of the regions covered by this CfP is an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent level of English and French and/or Spanish&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deux Experts en Monitoring et Evaluation de Projets 1 (Cat I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/deux-experts-en-monitoring-et-evaluation-de-projets-1-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 11:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/deux-experts-en-monitoring-et-evaluation-de-projets-1-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Les objectifs généraux de cette mission sont d&amp;#39;une part de contribuer à la bonne mise en œuvre des projets et d&amp;#39;autre part d&amp;#39;identifier les leçons apprises utiles pour la formulation et la mise en œuvre des futurs programmes et projets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les objectifs spécifiques sont:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assurer une analyse indépendante et régulière de la mise en œuvre des projets encore en cours afin d&amp;#39;optimiser l&amp;#39;atteinte de leurs objectifs ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyser et faire des recommandations sur la viabilité et la durabilité des effets des projets après leur clôture (monitoring ex post), afin d&amp;#39;en tirer des enseignements pour de futurs projets ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyser les thèmes transversaux les plus pertinents pour l&amp;#39;action de l&amp;#39;union européenne dans les domaines de l&amp;#39;agriculture et la sécurité alimentaire. Une liste de thèmes transversaux (à laquelle ne devra pas manquer le genre, l&amp;#39;environnement, la visibilité) sera proposée par les consultants et discutée avec la DUE qui décidera les thèmes à retenir; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conseiller et appuyer les projets pour la mise en œuvre d&amp;#39;une méthodologie d&amp;#39;estimation de leurs effets sur la production agricole et la sécurité alimentaire ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organiser un séminaire pour débattre des leçons apprises des projets avec des représentants du gouvernement et des partenaires techniques et financiers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project location&lt;/strong&gt;: Kinshasa , Kasai Oriental, Bas Congo, Kwuilu, Bandundu, Katanga&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deux Experts en Monitoring et Evaluation de Projets 1 (Cat I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissances de la gestion du cycle de projet ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Des expériences en matière de monitoring et évaluation de projets;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formation de niveau universitaire de type agronomique, agroéconomiste, nutritionniste et/ou vétérinaire ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience en Afrique centrale ou de l&amp;#39;ouest et en RDC en particulier constituera un avantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Category III Experts in Evaluations in Field of EUROsociAL II Actions</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-iii-experts-in-evaluations-in-field-of-eurosocial-ii-actions</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 11:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-iii-experts-in-evaluations-in-field-of-eurosocial-ii-actions</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This project will carry out a comprehensive evaluation of the results and potential impacts that the EUROsociaAL programme has achieved, as well as the added value of the methodology that EUROsociAL has put in place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category III Experts in Evaluations in Field of EUROsociAL II Actions 
(approx. 33 w/d each)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PhD or Master’s degree in social sciences, economics, law, engineering, international relations or development studies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of professional experience in development cooperation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive and relevant professional experience in project/programme evaluation in the field of EUROsociAL II actions (social policies, fiscal policies, democratic institutions, and justice and citizen security);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience with projects/programmes evaluation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant professional experience in/with Latin America;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in English and Spanish. Desirable knowledge of Portuguese&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Field experience is an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to Veronica Hernandez Castilla &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;Veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert in Evaluations in Field of EUROsociAL II Actions </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-evaluations-in-field-of-eurosocial-ii-actions</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-evaluations-in-field-of-eurosocial-ii-actions</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This project will carry out a comprehensive evaluation of the results and potential impacts that the EUROsociaAL programme has achieved, as well as the added value of the methodology that EUROsociAL has put in place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project location&lt;/strong&gt;: Belgium, Madrid, and Latin American countries (16 out of 18 LA countries will be visited)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in Evaluations in Field of EUROsociAL II Actions (Category II, 72 w/d)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PhD or Master’s degree in social sciences, economics, law, engineering, international relations or development studies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years of professional experience in development cooperation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive and relevant professional experience in project/programme evaluation in the field of EUROsociAL II actions (social policies, fiscal policies, democratic institutions, and justice and citizen security);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of professional experience with EC projects/programmes evaluation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of professional experience in/with Latin America;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in English and Spanish. Desirable knowledge of Portuguese&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Field experience is an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to Veronica Hernandez Castilla &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;Veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Evaluations in Field of EUROsociAL II Actions (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-evaluations-in-field-of-eurosocial-ii-actions-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 09:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-evaluations-in-field-of-eurosocial-ii-actions-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This project will carry out a comprehensive evaluation of the results and potential impacts that the EUROsociaAL programme has achieved, as well as the added value of the methodology that EUROsociAL has put in place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Location&lt;/strong&gt;: Belgium, Madrid, and Latin American countries (16 out of 18 LA countries will be visited)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Evaluations in Field of EUROsociAL II Actions (TL)
(Category I, 72 w/d)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PhD or Master’s degree in social sciences, economics, law, engineering, international relations or development studies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive and relevant experience (min. 15 years) in the field of development cooperation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive and relevant professional experience in project/programme evaluation in the field of EUROsociAL II actions (social policies, fiscal policies, democratic institutions, and justice and citizen security);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 8 years of professional experience with EC projects/programmes evaluation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years of professional experience in/with Latin America;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in English and Spanish. Desirable knowledge of Portuguese&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent knowledge of EC procedures and informatics applications, including financial and contractual management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Field experience is an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to Veronica Hernandez Castilla &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;Veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert élevage : de formation universitaire de préférence liée au développement rural et/ou à la sécurité alimentaire / à la santé animale</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-elevage-de-formation-universitaire-de-preference-liee-au-developpement-rural-et-ou-a-la-securite-alimentaire-a-la-sante-animale</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 21:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-elevage-de-formation-universitaire-de-preference-liee-au-developpement-rural-et-ou-a-la-securite-alimentaire-a-la-sante-animale</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;La présente mission a pour objet l’évaluation finale du Programme d’Appui à la Sécurité Alimentaire (PASA Mali 5) ainsi que la formulation de recommandations opérationnelles afin d’améliorer la qualité des interventions de l’Union européenne en matière de sécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle au Mali. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les experts présenteront à la Délégation de l’Union européenne au Mali, au Gouvernement du Mali - Ministère des Affaires Etrangères, de l’Intégration Africaine et de la Coopération Internationale (CONFED), Ministère du Développement Rural, Commissariat à la Sécurité Alimentaire (CSA – rang de ministère), Ministère de la Santé et de l’Hygiène Publique - ainsi qu’aux partenaires de mise en œuvre et aux bénéficiaires : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une analyse critique de l’approche et du processus de mise en œuvre du PASA Mali 5 avec un accent particulier sur la conception du programme, le suivi-évaluation et la capitalisation; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;un examen approfondi des modalités de ciblage (géographique et socio-économique) des bénéficiaires des différents projets mis en œuvre dans le cadre du PASA Mali 5 et la pertinence de celles-ci eu égard aux objectifs du programme; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une appréciation globale des résultats atteints dans le cadre de la mise en œuvre du PASA Mali 5, en s’attachant plus particulièrement aux résultats du programme par rapport à ses objectifs ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une analyse stratégique assortie de recommandations opérationnelles afin d’appuyer la Délégation de l’Union européenne dans la programmation de ces futures interventions en matière de sécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle au Mali. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert élevage : de formation universitaire de préférence liée au développement rural et/ou à la sécurité alimentaire / à la santé animale (BAC+5 min)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins douze (12) ans d’expérience professionnelle dans le secteur du développement rural et/ou de la sécurité alimentaire, dont au moins dix (10) années dans les pays en voie de développement ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une expérience opérationnelle d’au moins six (6) ans dans la mise en œuvre d’actions d’appui aux moyens d’existence des populations vulnérables (intégrant notamment des activités liées au petit élevage); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une connaissance solide des enjeux internationaux et régionaux autour de la « résilience » des populations vulnérables à l’insécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle sera considérée comme un atout; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une pratique avérée de la conduite des évaluations de projets/programmes dans le secteur du développement rural et/ou dans le domaine de la sécurité alimentaire; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une maîtrise de la gestion du cycle de projet, du cadre logique et des procédures FED; une bonne connaissance ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une bonne connaissance de l’Afrique de l’Ouest est primordiale et du Mali recommandée ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une parfaite maîtrise de la langue française. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert Nutrition, de formation universitaire de préférence liée à la santé publique et/ou à la nutrition </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-nutrition</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-nutrition</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;La présente mission a pour objet l’évaluation finale du Programme d’Appui à la Sécurité Alimentaire (PASA Mali 5) ainsi que la formulation de recommandations opérationnelles afin d’améliorer la qualité des interventions de l’Union européenne en matière de sécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle au Mali. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les experts présenteront à la Délégation de l’Union européenne au Mali, au Gouvernement du Mali - Ministère des Affaires Etrangères, de l’Intégration Africaine et de la Coopération Internationale (CONFED), Ministère du Développement Rural, Commissariat à la Sécurité Alimentaire (CSA – rang de ministère), Ministère de la Santé et de l’Hygiène Publique - ainsi qu’aux partenaires de mise en œuvre et aux bénéficiaires : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une analyse critique de l’approche et du processus de mise en œuvre du PASA Mali 5 avec un accent particulier sur la conception du programme, le suivi-évaluation et la capitalisation; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;un examen approfondi des modalités de ciblage (géographique et socio-économique) des bénéficiaires des différents projets mis en œuvre dans le cadre du PASA Mali 5 et la pertinence de celles-ci eu égard aux objectifs du programme; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une appréciation globale des résultats atteints dans le cadre de la mise en œuvre du PASA Mali 5, en s’attachant plus particulièrement aux résultats du programme par rapport à ses objectifs ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une analyse stratégique assortie de recommandations opérationnelles afin d’appuyer la Délégation de l’Union européenne dans la programmation de ces futures interventions en matière de sécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle au Mali. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert Nutrition, de formation universitaire de préférence liée à la santé publique et/ou à la nutrition (BAC+5 min)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins douze (12) ans d’expérience professionnelle dans le secteur de la santé publique et/ou de la nutrition dans les pays en voie de développement; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une expérience significative d’au moins dix (10) années dans l’appui à la mise en œuvre d’enquêtes nutritionnelles (conception et développement des outils d’enquêtes nutritionnelles, suivi des enquêtes nutritionnelles, analyse des données des enquêtes nutritionnelles, etc.) et/ou de systèmes d’informations nutritionnelles; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une pratique avérée de la conduite des évaluations de programmes de sécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle dont au moins cinq (5) évaluations de projets de nutrition; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une expérience spécifique sur les questions liées au genre et sa prise en compte dans les projets de développement; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une connaissance solide des enjeux internationaux et régionaux autour de la « résilience » des populations vulnérables à l’insécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle sera considérée comme un atout; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une maîtrise de la gestion du cycle de projet, du cadre logique et des procédures FED; une bonne connaissance des outils/méthodologie d’évaluation des projets de l’Union européenne constitue un atout ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une bonne connaissance de l’Afrique de l’Ouest est primordiale et du Mali recommandée ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une parfaite maîtrise de la langue française. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert sécurité alimentaire (Chef de Mission)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-securite-alimentaire-chef-de-mission</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 20:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-securite-alimentaire-chef-de-mission</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;La présente mission a pour objet l’évaluation finale du Programme d’Appui à la Sécurité Alimentaire (PASA Mali 5) ainsi que la formulation de recommandations opérationnelles afin d’améliorer la qualité des interventions de l’Union européenne en matière de sécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle au Mali. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les experts présenteront à la Délégation de l’Union européenne au Mali, au Gouvernement du Mali - Ministère des Affaires Etrangères, de l’Intégration Africaine et de la Coopération Internationale (CONFED), Ministère du Développement Rural, Commissariat à la Sécurité Alimentaire (CSA – rang de ministère), Ministère de la Santé et de l’Hygiène Publique - ainsi qu’aux partenaires de mise en œuvre et aux bénéficiaires : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une analyse critique de l’approche et du processus de mise en œuvre du PASA Mali 5 avec un accent particulier sur la conception du programme, le suivi-évaluation et la capitalisation; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;un examen approfondi des modalités de ciblage (géographique et socio-économique) des bénéficiaires des différents projets mis en œuvre dans le cadre du PASA Mali 5 et la pertinence de celles-ci eu égard aux objectifs du programme; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une appréciation globale des résultats atteints dans le cadre de la mise en œuvre du PASA Mali 5, en s’attachant plus particulièrement aux résultats du programme par rapport à ses objectifs ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une analyse stratégique assortie de recommandations opérationnelles afin d’appuyer la Délégation de l’Union européenne dans la programmation de ces futures interventions en matière de sécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle au Mali. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert sécurité alimentaire : de formation universitaire de préférence liée au développement rural et/ou à la sécurité alimentaire (TL)&lt;/strong&gt; 
(BAC+5 min) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins douze (12) ans d’expérience professionnelle dans le secteur du développement rural et/ou de la sécurité alimentaire, dont au moins dix (10) années dans les pays en voie de développement ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une expérience opérationnelle d’au moins six (6) ans dans la mise en œuvre d’actions d’appui aux moyens d’existence des populations vulnérables (intégrant notamment des transferts monétaires et/ou filets sociaux); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une expérience dans l&amp;#39;une ou l&amp;#39;autre des activités suivantes sera considérée comme un atout: appui au renforcement des mécanismes de prévention et de gestion des crises alimentaires ; appui aux systèmes d’information pour la sécurité alimentaire ; appui à des projets d’adaptation au changement climatique ; appui à l’articulation des actions humanitaires et de développement (LRRD) ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une connaissance solide des enjeux internationaux et régionaux autour de la « résilience » des populations vulnérables à l’insécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle sera considérée comme un atout; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une pratique avérée de la conduite des évaluations de projets/programmes dans le secteur du développement rural et/ou dans le domaine de la sécurité alimentaire; une expérience en tant que chef d&amp;#39;équipe d&amp;#39;une mission d&amp;#39;évaluation sera considérée comme un atout ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une maîtrise de la gestion du cycle de projet, du cadre logique et des procédures FED; une bonne connaissance des outils/méthodologie d’évaluation des projets de l’Union européenne constitue un atout ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une bonne connaissance de l’Afrique de l’Ouest est primordiale et du Mali recommandée ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une parfaite maîtrise de la langue française. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junior Economist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-economist</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 20:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-economist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overall purpose is to support EU trade policy-making towards China through the development of key tactical market intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Junior Economist *&lt;/em&gt;
(Junior category, 129 w/d):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education at the level of Masters&amp;#39; Degree in the field related to Economics, or 6 years of professional experience (in addition to the minimum number of years of general professional experience required below) in the sector related to economics. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years&amp;#39; experience in the various disciplines in the field of economics, international trade, or any other related area. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in working with microeconomics and accounting. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth knowledge of the Chinese economy, Chinese industrial policy and development. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record of Fluency in Chinese legal and economic language terms. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record in the analysis and clear and concise reporting in legal, economic and/or trade-related areas. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;Veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junior Expert – Overcapacities</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-expert-overcapacities</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 20:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-expert-overcapacities</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overall purpose is to support EU trade policy-making towards China through the development of key tactical market intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Junior Expert – Overcapacities&lt;/strong&gt; 
(Junior category, 148 w/d):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education at the level of Masters&amp;#39; Degree in the field related to Economics, or 6 years of professional experience (in addition to the minimum number of years of general professional experience required below) in the sector related to trade, or economic policy, or industrial policy. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years&amp;#39; experience in the various disciplines in the field of economics, international trade, or economic policy, or industrial policy, or any other related area. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in working with macroeconomic and statistical and/or econometric analysis tools. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth knowledge of the Chinese economy, Chinese industrial policy and development. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record of Fluency in Chinese legal and economic language terms. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record in the analysis and clear and concise reporting in legal, and/or economic, and/or trade-related areas. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;Veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junior Expert – Subsidies</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-expert-subsidies</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 20:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-expert-subsidies</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overall purpose is to support EU trade policy-making towards China through the development of key tactical market intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Junior Expert – Subsidies&lt;/strong&gt; 
(Junior Category, 148 w/d):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education at the level of Masters&amp;#39; Degree in the field of Chinese law related to trade (including commercial law, business law, corporate law), or 6 years of professional experience (in addition to the minimum number of years of general professional experience required below) in the sector related to trade. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years&amp;#39; experience in the various disciplines in the field of law, international trade or any other related area. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in working with legal texts drafted in Chinese. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record of Fluency in Chinese legal and economic language terms. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record in the analysis and clear and concise reporting in legal, economic and/or trade-related areas. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 2 years&amp;#39; experience in WTO disciplines on subsidies and countervailing measures and in trade remedy investigations, in particular in the area of countervailing duty investigations. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;Veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert – Subsidies</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-subsidies</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-subsidies</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overall purpose is to support EU trade policy-making towards China through the development of key tactical market intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert – Subsidies 
(Senior category, 127w/d)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education at the level of Masters&amp;#39; Degree in a field related to Trade, or 6 years of professional experience (in addition to the minimum number of years of general professional experience required below) in the sector related to Trade;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years&amp;#39; experience in the various disciplines in the field of Economics / Trade Law, international trade or any other related areas;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 5 years&amp;#39; experience on Chinese economic and legal analysis;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 5 years&amp;#39; experience in WTO disciplines on subsidies and countervailing measures and in trade remedy investigations, in particular in the area of countervailing duty investigations. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 3 years&amp;#39; experience in at least two different assignments related to EU external trade, with focus on subsidies &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;Veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader – Senior Expert in Overcapacities and Export/Import</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-expert-in-overcapacities-and-export-import</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 12:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-expert-in-overcapacities-and-export-import</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overall purpose is to support EU trade policy-making towards China through the development of key tactical market intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader – Senior Expert in Overcapacities and Export/Import (Senior category, 90w/d)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s Degree in a field related to Trade, or 6 years of professional experience in the sector (in addition to the general experience below);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years’ experience in the various disciplines in the field of Economics/Trade Law, and international trade or related areas;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in leading and coordinating international teams in at least two different assignments with a minimum duration of 1 year each;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 5 years’ experience on Chinese economic and legal analysis;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 3 years’ experience in at least two different assignments related to EU external trade, with focus on import/export statistics and trends, and overcapacities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;Veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
