<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2015 10:47:22 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Senior Human Rights Experts preferably with EIDHR and Asia Experience</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/two-senior-human-rights-experts-preferably-with-eidhr-and-asia-experience</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2015 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/two-senior-human-rights-experts-preferably-with-eidhr-and-asia-experience</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of this specific contract is to recruit experts/ assessors to assist the Contracting Authority in the selection of the best proposals received under a call for
proposals that was launched early 2015 for Bangladesh under the EIDHR Counry Based Support Scheme and to achieve a high-quality, complete and coherent selection process of projects in line with the criteria set in the Guidelines for applicants and the general principles underlying the EU PCM approach as well as the European Instrument for Democracy and Human Rights and its policies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Two Senior Human Rights Experts preferably with EIDHR and Asia Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree with at least 3 years of studies in law or international human rights law, social or political science or humanities, law, development studies, or other relevant;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A least 10 years general professional experience working with civil society organisations on the implementation of human rights related programmes in developing countries comparable to Bangladesh. Such work experience in Bangladesh or South Asia will be considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience during the last three years in the assessment of human rights project proposals funded under programmes similar to the EIDHR or the EIDHR programme itself;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with the EIDHR calls for proposals or in the implementation of projects funded under the EIDHR is considered an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer skills (word, excel) and excellent English drafting skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:adeline_vanhoutte@dai.com&quot;&gt;Adeline_VanHoutte@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Knowledge Management Expert, Category I</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-knowledge-management-expert-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2015 17:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-knowledge-management-expert-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This assignment will provide expert technical assistance to the National Treasury: IDC to effectively and innovatively revise, implement and leverage its knowledge management (KM) strategy and introduce niche areas and tools to enhance the IDCs KM focus and reach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Knowledge Management Expert, Category I&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:  Preferably, the Category I Expert should have a minimum of a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree or equivalent post graduate degree in the disciplines related to development: development studies, knowledge management, communication, economics, public or business administration or social sciences. The expert must have demonstrable research skills and have appropriate skills for the evaluation of development practise and programmes. The expert must be computer literate and have high level writing and presentation skills. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: The expert should have at least 12 years of general working experience in the development sector, preferably in a knowledge management, research and development, or socio-economic analysis environment.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: The expert should be able to demonstrate experience in: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge and experience of knowledge management practices, methodologies, application and development of strategic interventions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound knowledge and experience of conducting assessments of knowledge systems for development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent writing skills and demonstrable experience in the development of publications (hard and or soft copy) such as journals, newsletters, websites, strategic documents;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable experience in documentary planning and compilations, and its quality assurance;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coaching, mentoring and facilitation skills and an illustration of methodologies utilised or preferred;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working with multiple stakeholders, including government and international development partners;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing and executing KM research and or policy-implementation projects within the development sector;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of the ODA and development cooperation environment will be advantageous; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound knowledge of public sector procedures, public financial management and performance monitoring and evaluation systems will be advantageous; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the Southern African region will be advantageous.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;: The expert must be fluent in English – written and spoken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:roxanne_garrana@dai.com&quot;&gt;roxanne_garrana@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Category I Experts in Rural Development and Evaluation (one Team Leader)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/two-category-i-experts-in-rural-development-and-evaluation-one-team-leader</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2015 13:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/two-category-i-experts-in-rural-development-and-evaluation-one-team-leader</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The aim of the present Request for Services is to perform the final evaluation of two 10th EDF-funded programmes titled Northern Uganda Agricultural Livelihoods Recovery Programme (FED/2008/20287) and Karamoja Livelihoods Programme (FED/2008/20280).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Two Category I Experts in Rural Development and Evaluation (one Team Leader)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;12 years of relevant experience in managing, monitoring and evaluating development programmes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of current evaluation theory and practice (EU, DAC-OECD)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in evaluating large and complex development projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience as team leader in short term assignments, including mid-term or final evaluations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in complex Rural Development programme&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Northern Uganda post conflict policy framework, failing this, experience in Sub-Saharan Africa semi-arid areas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Relations (PR) Manager</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/public-relations-pr-manager</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/public-relations-pr-manager</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Incentive Fund (IF)&lt;/strong&gt; has been operating for 14 years and it is the most recognized component of the Australian Aid program. The incentive fund provides technical and funding support, and delivers visible outputs, good human development, strengthens organisations, expands service delivery through partners and can stimulate economic development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DFAT has directed the Incentive Fund IV design to target health, education, economic development and other sectors. The post-program goal of the program is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; To improve the capacity of organisations to meet the service delivery and economic development needs of the women, children and men of Papua New Guinea.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Public Relations (PR) Manager&lt;/strong&gt; will maintain a close working relationship with the DFAT Public Diplomacy office and will be responsible for keeping DFAT updated on the support that is being provided through IF (IV) and any changes being made.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IF (IV) has a responsibility to highlight gender equality issues consistent with the Pacific Women Shaping Pacific Development programme and so the PR Manager will constantly and actively promote activities relating to the empowerment of women and social equity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The successful candidate should have experience of engaging with the private sector and of working in strategic communications and media. S/He will know how to produce professional media and communication material, which will then be used by DFAT more broadly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV  with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting Incentive Fund (IV) in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please note that due to high volumes of applications, only shortlisted candidates will be contacted&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring and Evaluation (M&amp;E) Manager</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/monitoring-and-evaluation-me-manager</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 16:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/monitoring-and-evaluation-me-manager</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Incentive Fund (IF)&lt;/strong&gt; has been operating for 14 years and it is the most recognized component of the Australian Aid program. The incentive fund provides technical and funding support, and delivers visible outputs, good human development, strengthens organisations, expands service delivery through partners and can stimulate economic development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DFAT has directed the &lt;strong&gt;Incentive Fund IV&lt;/strong&gt; design to target health, education, economic development and other sectors. The post-program goal of the program is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To improve the capacity of organisations to meet the service delivery and economic development needs of the women, children and men of Papua New Guinea.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring &amp;amp; Evaluation Manager&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Monitoring and Evaluation (M&amp;amp;E) management must deliver a quality evaluation of Incentive Fund Phases I-III. The evaluation is essential to the direction of the programme and should be conducted within the first four months.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Monitoring and Evaluation management must work closely with DFAT and the Independent Review Team and is responsible for ensuring that all monitoring and evaluation functions of IF (IV) are established and being delivered by qualified people. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; The M&amp;amp;E manager will support and performance manage all people involved with delivering IF (IV) monitoring and evaluation activities at all times.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; M&amp;amp;E management must also ensure that all delivery of IF (IV) is guided by the DFAT Monitoring and Evaluation Standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting Incentive Fund (IV) in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please note that due to high volumes of applications, only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader, Papua New Guinea Incentive Fund IV</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 16:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Incentive Fund (IF)&lt;/strong&gt; has been operating for 14 years and it is the most recognized component of the Australian Aid program. The incentive fund provides technical and funding support, and delivers visible outputs, good human development, strengthens organisations, expands service delivery through partners and can stimulate economic development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DFAT has directed the Incentive Fund IV design to target health, education, economic development and other sectors. The post-program goal of the program is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To improve the capacity of organisations to meet the service delivery and economic development needs of the women, children and men of Papua New Guinea.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; The successful candidate will have a good understanding of the local context and political economy.  Papua New Guinea is a complex working environment and is likely to become ever more complex in the next few years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; An understanding and instinct for how the private sector works is equally important and will be necessary for the programme to engage with stakeholders in a meaningful way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; The Team Leader must advocate for gender equality at all levels and through all opportunities.  The Incentive Fund IV will be expected to work with the Pacific Women Shaping Pacific Development programme which is currently operating across the region.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; The successful candidate will understand the need for adopting and enforcing rigorous funding criteria and must be able to navigate the complexities of a range of organisations to find suitable partners.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; The Team Leader should be experienced in the management of funds and have appropriate communication and awareness skills to facilitate a fair and transparent application process. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; S/He should have experience of managing large, complex donor programmes and teams of mixed national and international staff.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting Incentive Fund (IV) in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please note that due to high volumes of applications, only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deputy Team Leader, Infrastructure, Papua New Guinea Incentive Fund IV</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/deputy-team-leader-infrastructure-</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2015 19:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/deputy-team-leader-infrastructure-</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Incentive Fund (IF)&lt;/strong&gt; has been operating for 14 years and it is the most recognized component of the Australian Aid program. The incentive fund provides technical and funding support, and delivers visible outputs, good human development, strengthens organisations, expands service delivery through partners and can stimulate economic development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DFAT has directed the &lt;strong&gt;Incentive Fund IV&lt;/strong&gt; design to target health, education, economic development and other sectors. The post-program goal of the program is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To improve the capacity of organisations to meet the service delivery and economic development needs of the women, children and men of Papua New Guinea.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deputy Team Leader, Infrastructure&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IV (IV) will assist, design, and deliver infrastructure to the value of more than A$36 million through sub-contract management arrangements controlled by more than 13 partners.  The Deputy Team Leader will have visibility of all stages with each partner and will manage a team of technical support to ensure quality, fitness-for-purpose, sustainable operational costs and maintenance schedules and demonstrated value-for-money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Required experience:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree qualified (or equivalent) in Civil Engineering from a reputable University&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional chartership is desirable &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10-15 years post graduate experience &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Min 5 years of experience with a main contractor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to large international projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience of working with donors, especially DFAT (desirable)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting Incentive Fund (IV) in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please note that due to high volumes of applications, only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWP 2 Projects Review</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Beyond WTO Program (B-WTO) was developed in response to a request from the Government of Vietnam (GoV) for donor support to help with managing economic integration and the transition to a market economy following WTO accession. The B-WTO goal is “to strengthen government’s capacity to manage the integration of Vietnam into the global economy and the transition of Vietnam to a socialist market economy”. The immediate objective is “implementation of priority policy actions from the GoV’s Action Plan to enhance Vietnam’s capacity to sustain pro-poor growth (GAP)”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The remit of this project was a review of the 2nd annual work plan’s implementation (AWP2) of Phase 2 of the B-WTO in May 2013. The objectives of the review were to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the project implementation performance and project results relative to the logical framework targets and evaluation criteria. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the results achieved at the Component and Program’s level according to the Monitoring and Evaluation (M&amp;amp;E) framework of the Program.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify lessons learned from implementation, make recommendations for the remaining duration of the program and the Independent Completion Report process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program 2013 Performance and Quality Mapping Exercise</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID’s PNG Program is looking to improve its performance and quality (P&amp;amp;Q) standards and systems. The purpose of this project was to map the PNG Program’s current P&amp;amp;Q capacity and systems, to address the risk of AusAID being unable to demonstrate results for its increased investments in PNG over the next four years. Over the last several years, the PNG Program has undertaken a number of M&amp;amp;E assessments and reviews which have identified key strengths and challenges within the program. This project was intended to pick up where these assessments left off. Through a desk review and consultations with sector teams, the Review Team were to distil key P&amp;amp;Q risks and issues for the PNG Program. The Review Team’s brief included the provision of recommendations on priority activities to support sector approaches to M&amp;amp;E, strengthen the Program’s ability to collect evidence, provide critical analysis and report on results.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID required a consultant to assist with the development and finalisation of its Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework. Development of a humanitarian monitoring and evaluation framework is a key commitment outlined in AusAID’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy (HAP) and its associated Implementation Plan. In line with the agency focus on results reporting, the HAP and HAP Implementation Plan commit AusAID to develop a monitoring and evaluation framework to support the initial performance assessment framework contained within the HAP and AusAID annual reporting under the Comprehensive Aid Policy Framework.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key objective of this assignment was to build the Humanitarian program’s capacity for monitoring and reporting results by:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In consultation with AusAID’s Humanitarian team, redraft and finalise the Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework, to ensure it provides a platform to:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track implementation of key commitments in Australia’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy; and,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish a set of measurable humanitarian performance indicators (in addition to the two CAPF indicators) to enable AusAID to track achievements, lessons learned and to report on the results achieved from AusAID’s humanitarian work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of Pacific Forum Compact Reporting</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The purpose of the assignment was to examine country views of aid effectiveness and regional organisations expressed through Forum Compact reporting, particularly peer review of Forum Island Countries’ national development plan processes. The services provided included the preparation of a think piece which outlines key aid effectiveness issues arising from country reporting under the Compact reporting and discusses options for addressing these issues.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study on Community-based Social Protection</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/study-on-community-based-social-protection</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/study-on-community-based-social-protection</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Poverty and Social Analysis is the process of using and generating evidence on poverty throughout the aid management cycle. Most poverty and social analysis focuses on economic and human capital, but there are two oft neglected elements: voice and influence, and social capital. Yet more and more development practitioners are recognizing the importance of social capital, particularly informal social capital, in preventing and addressing poverty and vulnerability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This project supported AusAID to explore:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the role of informal social capital in the Fijian context and whether it lends itself to fair redistribution of resources and, if so, the ways in which AusAID can engage with local communities to strengthen existing social capital structures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;how such structures can enable the disempowered and poor to claim their entitlements in the three domains discussed in the PSA framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the potential challenges that can arise from such efforts. For instance, the poorest are often included on less favorable terms within social networks, and have access to fewer and lower-quality networks. Further, we need to better understand how poverty and disempowerment intersect with an absence of informal social capital, the repercussions this has, and the options available for tackling this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Provision of a Child Protection Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/provision-of-a-child-protection-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/provision-of-a-child-protection-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For this project HTSPE was contracted to provide a child protection specialist and handle all the associated management and administrative work. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The child protection specialist provided by HTSPE was required to work on an assignment designed to assist the Pacific Division (PACD) to improve its approach to child protection and managing risks to children. AusAID has a number of partners in the Pacific who work with children or come into contact with children through their activities. The AusAID-wide child protection stocktake, conducted in May 2013 found that there are a number of organisations funded by AusAID in the Pacific with a high or very high inherent child protection risk. Consistent with the stocktake report PACD proposes to escalate efforts to ensure partner organisations policies, procedures and practices are in accordance with AusAID’s Child Protection Policy 2013 and to make child protection a more explicit focus of PACD’s risk management system.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Environment and Biology Expert (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/opportunities/senior-environment-and-biology-expert-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 20:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/opportunities/senior-environment-and-biology-expert-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Expert 2 is expected to contribute the implementation of all of the related modules and the preparation of both training materials and Training Evaluation Report in the context of related chapter/s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in Biology, Ecology, Chemistry or other Natural Sciences related to assignment. In the absence of the degree required, at least 17 years of professional experience in the related areas is requested.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good command of both written and spoken English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General professional experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in the sector(s) related to the Lot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience in technical and/or scientific fields required for the implementation of the Water Framework Directive and/or Habitat Directive and/or other related Directives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 river basin management plans experience in terms of setting of environmental objectives and/or setting, design and upgrade of biological monitoring programme and/or execution and assessment of biological monitoring.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in development of measures for water pollution reduction and/or improving ecological status, and/or river basin characterisation/analysis will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in projects related to Integrated Water Resources Management will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
