<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 07:59:51 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Inclusion Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/social-inclusion-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 07:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/social-inclusion-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation of EU support to Juvenile Justice in Kosovo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Provide a mix of ex-post and mid-term evaluation (towards the end of implementation period) of Support to Juvenile Justice in Kosovo phases I,II and III.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project location&lt;/strong&gt;:  Prishtina and Kosovo-Serb areas of Mitrovicë/ Mitrovica North and Zveçan /Zvečan &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 93 calendar days maximum&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Social Inclusion Expert&lt;/strong&gt;
(50 working days of total input for team)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Combined experience between the two experts should include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least three (3) evaluations covering areas (separately or jointly) of judiciary, juvenile justices and social inclusion; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one member of the team: 10 years of experience in judiciary &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one member of the team: 5 years of experience in social development and/or child protection and/or social service provision.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&quot;&gt;gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analyste des politiques et lois (Cat. II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/analyste-des-politiques-et-lois-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 05:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/analyste-des-politiques-et-lois-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cartographie et analyse du Secteur prive au Burundi&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Par une analyse approfondie, la Délégation de l’Union Européenne au Burundi souhaiterait mener une réflexion sur le rôle et les capacités du secteur privé dans le développement national et régional à court, moyen et long termes et l’identification de recommandations permettant de renforcer ce rôle. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Analyste des politiques et lois (Cat. II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Qualifications professionnelles pertinentes en droit des affaires ou autres domaines similaires ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 6 ans d’expertise approfondie en affaires/secteur privé, commerce et investissement (services de développement des entreprises, formulation de politiques et renforcement des capacités) ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance de l’environnement des affaires au Burundi sera un avantage ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience et capacité d’analyse politique prouvées ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne connaissance du cadre juridique et règlementaire burundais ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aptitude démontrée à recueillir, analyser et synthétiser des textes règlementaires pour produire des données économiques ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compétences en communication et en rédaction ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maitrise du Français et du Kirundi (oral et écrit pour les deux langues)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance du Swahili sera un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;lina_forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef de mission, (Cat. I), expert en secteur privé</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-cat-i-expert-en-secteur-prive</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 05:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-cat-i-expert-en-secteur-prive</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cartographie et analyse du Secteur prive au Burundi&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Par une analyse approfondie, la Délégation de l’Union Européenne au Burundi souhaiterait mener une réflexion sur le rôle et les capacités du secteur privé dans le développement national et régional à court, moyen et long termes et l’identification de recommandations permettant de renforcer ce rôle. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chef de mission, (Cat. I), expert en secteur privé&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formation au moins Master en économie ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 12 ans d’expertise dans le domaine des affaires/secteur privé, du commerce et des investissements (politiques, stratégies et initiatives de compétitivité des entreprises) ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compétences et connaissances reconnues dans le développement du secteur privé, telles que le Développement économique durable, le renforcement des capacités institutionnelles des entreprises, l’analyse SWOT des organisations, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance des cadres opérationnels du secteur privé et des processus d’intégration régionale, en particulier l’Union Douanière et le Protocole sur le Marché commun ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compétences en recherche, élaboration de base de données et en analyse ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capacités d’analyse et de rédaction de rapports en français prouvées et documentées ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience de missions similaires et bonne maitrise des procédures et instruments de financements de l’UE ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bon communicateur, rédacteur, leader expérimenté et modérateur ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maitrise du français. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;lina_forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert  CAT  II, en gestion financière et administrative (120  jours  à  prester)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-cat-ii-en-gestion-financiere-et-administrative-120-jours-a-prester</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 05:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-cat-ii-en-gestion-financiere-et-administrative-120-jours-a-prester</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assistance Technique d&amp;#39;appui transversal au demarrage des activites du programme SAN&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général de la mission est de contribuer à l&amp;#39;opérationnalisation de la convention de financement du projet SAN 11ème FED.
L’objectif particulier est d’assurer une mise en œuvre rapide, effective et efficace des activités de démarrage du programme SAN (pré- et post- signature de la convention de financement), à travers des appuis à la coordination nationale et aux composantes sectorielles en matière de renforcement des capacités et de gestion- administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visits to the regions of&lt;/strong&gt;:  Ouaddaï, Wadi Fira, Guéra, Tandjilé, Logone occidental.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert  CAT  II, en gestion financière et administrative (120  jours  à  prester,  dont  115 au Tchad)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Formation *&lt;/em&gt;:
Une formation d&amp;#39;études supérieures sanctionnée par un diplôme d&amp;#39;au moins niveau Master (bac+5) en comptabilité, finance, business &amp;amp; administration, logistique ou autre diplôme équivalent / similaire&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 6 ans d&amp;#39;expérience professionnelle en appui à la gestion financière/administrative de projets et programmes dans les secteurs liés à la mission (développement rural au sens large, sécurité alimentaire, santé communautaire et nutrition, infrastructures rurales, développement local etc.).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience avérée (justifiée par au moins trois missions) en analyse des besoins en ressources humaines, définition des postes et profils, ainsi que formation, appui-conseil, renforcement des capacités.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans la mise en place d&amp;#39;un système efficace de gestion comptable et financière, y compris système de contrôle et reporting financier.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne connaissance des instruments UE pour le financement des actions extérieures et une parfaite maîtrise des règles et procédures FED, justifiée par au moins 4 missions d&amp;#39;expertise dans le cadre de projets et programme FED, préférablement en Afrique sub-saharienne, comprenant l&amp;#39;élaboration/gestion de devis-programmes, l&amp;#39;élaboration de DAO (y compris niveau international) et dossiers d&amp;#39;appels à propositions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans l&amp;#39;élaboration de procurement plans.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  La connaissance et/ou la familiarité avec le contexte national/régional, les institutions, les politiques nationales et stratégies sectorielles sera un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellente capacité analytique, de synthèse, de conception et de rédaction; bonne capacité de communication et de concertation avec des acteurs divers. Maîtrise des outils et des moyens de communication et visibilité.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Efficacité dans l&amp;#39;organisation du travail en fonction des objectifs à atteindre et des échéances, initiative, résilience au travail sous pression.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parfaite maîtrise du Français, écrit et oral.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;lina_forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef de mission, développement rural </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-developpement-rural</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 21:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-developpement-rural</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assistance Technique d&amp;#39;appui transversal au demarrage des activites du programme SAN&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général de la mission est de contribuer à l&amp;#39;opérationnalisation de la convention de financement du projet SAN 11ème FED.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif particulier est d’assurer une mise en œuvre rapide, effective et efficace des activités de démarrage du programme SAN (pré- et post- signature de la convention de financement), à travers des appuis à la coordination nationale et aux composantes sectorielles en matière de renforcement des capacités et de gestion- administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project location&lt;/strong&gt;: Visits to the regions of:  Ouaddaï, Wadi Fira, Guéra, Tandjilé, Logone occidental.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert CAT I, Chef de mission, développement rural (130 jours à prester, dont 120 au Tchad)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formation&lt;/strong&gt;
Une formation d&amp;#39;études supérieures sanctionnée par un diplôme d&amp;#39;au moins niveau Master (bac+5) en économie du développement, agroéconomie, sociologie rurale ou autre diplôme équivalent/ similaire&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 12 ans d&amp;#39;expérience professionnelle dans le(s) secteur(s) directement lié(s) à la mission: développement rural intégré comprenant investissements en infrastructures rurales, sécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle, WASH, développement local.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 4 ans d’expérience en tant que chef de mission sur contrats d’assistance technique en appui à la gestion, planification et coordination de projets et programmes de développement, y compris développement communautaire et développement local (plans de développement local), de préférence en pays fragiles d&amp;#39;Afrique sub-saharienne ou sahélienne.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience avérée (justifiée par au moins trois missions d&amp;#39;expertise) en élaboration de documents de gestion opérationnelle, à savoir devis-programmes, TdR, cahiers de charges, dossiers d’appels d’offres et lignes directrices  pour appels à propositions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellente maîtrise des règles et procédures FED, justifiée par 2 missions minimum en appui à la gestion de projets et programmes FED.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en analyse – diagnostic des ressources / capacités institutionnelles et renforcement des capacités (coaching, formation, appui-conseil etc.).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;La connaissance et/ou la familiarité avec le contexte national/régional, les institutions, les politiques nationales et stratégies sectorielles sera un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellente capacité analytique, de synthèse, de conception et de rédaction; bonne capacité de communication et de concertation avec des acteurs divers. Maîtrise des outils et des moyens de communication et visibilité.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Efficacité dans l&amp;#39;organisation du travail en fonction des objectifs à atteindre et des échéances, initiative, résilience au travail sous pression.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parfaite maîtrise du Français, écrit et oral.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;lina_forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category II Expert: Trade Economist, Evaluation &amp; Monitoring Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-expert-trade-economist-evaluation-monitoring-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 20:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-expert-trade-economist-evaluation-monitoring-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Evaluation: Trade Related Technical Assistance Programme, Private Sector Development Phase Three (TRTA / PSD-III)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Delegation seeks to contract expert to conduct a final evaluation of the entire Trade Related Technical Assistance Programme, Private Sector Development Phase Three (TRTA / PSD-III) programme and its two sectors based contracts i.e. Leather Sector and Gems &amp;amp; jewellery development sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category II Expert: Trade Economist, Evaluation &amp;amp; Monitoring Specialist&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The category II expert should have: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least master degree in trade or international trade, economics, private sector development or in filed closely related to international trade and trade policy areas form a recognised institution. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least six years of general professional experience working in the field of trade and private sector development, economic cooperation, business and economic development. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Special expertise required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least the experts should: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;have experience of 07 years of project evaluation for trade, economic cooperation and development, private and public sectors at policy level as well as implementation level. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;have a minimum of 06 years’ specific experience of general projects evaluation. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;have a specific experience in evaluating at least 06 trade related projects; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;have a specific experience of evaluating at least 05 EU funded trade project; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;be fully conversant with the principles and working methods of project cycle management and EU aid delivery methods; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;have familiarity with EU Aid for Trade agenda and multilateral trade related issues &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;excellent knowledge of private sector development EU funded programme &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills of the team&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;have excellent command of spoken and written English &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;have excellent report writing skills, good commination, adoptability and social awareness &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&quot;&gt;gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:Francesca_Giordano@dai.com&quot;&gt;Francesca_Giordano@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert on Legal framework </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-legal-framework</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 07:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-legal-framework</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance to promote a more enabling environment for civil society development in Albania&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To contribute to the creation of an enabling environment for civil society development in Albania by supporting civil society and government bodies in developing effective cooperation with CSOs based on common vision, shared values and mutual trust. With the following specific objectives:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To enhance capacities of civil society organizations, members of the National Council of Civil Society to engage in a systematic and continues dialogue with relevant governmental institutions and as well as other platforms of civil society, advising and influencing issues of strategic priority in the country.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To conduct a mid-term review of the implementation of the Roadmap on Enabling Environment for Civil Society in Albania, through a wide consultation process with civil society and relevant responsible institutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To provide technical support to Government efforts in fulfilling their commitments in improving the legal, financial and fiscal regulatory framework related to civil society sector as a key layer in ensuring appropriate fiscal and legal environment for operation of civil society.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 300 days&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert on Legal framework&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt; 
Master’s Degree or equivalent, in Law. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt; 
At least 3 years of experience in the area of legislation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience and expertise in regard to development of legal framework analysis, establishing, technical recommendations in regard to legal environment for CSO&amp;rsquo;s operation in the context of EU Members States or EU candidate/potential candidate countries and/or transition economies. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in supporting government capacities or civil society sector to develop specific measures/ legal frameworks/ analysis on the legal framework related to civil society in Albania would be an advantage. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert  in Information and Communication Technologies</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-information-and-communication-technologies</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 21:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-information-and-communication-technologies</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preparation of supply tender dossiers for Serbian Ministry of Interior (MUP)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of this assignment is to support Serbia’s commitment in meeting EU standards in the field of safety and security through implementation of Action Plan on Chapter 24 and Chapter 23.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of this assignments is to provide preliminary assessments, market researches, preparation of technical specifications and tender dossiers and providing input during clarifications and  in the tender evaluations for the following tender procedures:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supply of ICT equipment, security equipment, software solutions and analytical tools for strengthening capacities within Home Affairs Sector for the fight against organized crime by implementation of: Intelligence Led Policing, National Criminal Intelligence System and Strengthening international police cooperation (in line with EUROPOL standards)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supply of video, audio and IT equipment for strengthening capacity of Internal Control Unit to fight against corruption within the police&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2 Expert  in Information and Communication Technologies - Category 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree /Master Degree (where a university degree has been awarded on completion of four years study or equivalent institutions) in the field of engineering, information and technology or other field related to this contract.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least twelve (12) years, preferably 15 years of working experience in the design of integrated ICT and networking systems on multi-vendor platform &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English, both written and spoken&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 1, preferably 2 projects in consulting experience with public sector organizations in the area of design and implementation of complex ICT infrastructure systems (such as data centres, data back-up, archive and restore, basic network and communication systems, CLOUD technology, security of information systems – identity management, smart cards, RFID technologies, risk management etc.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least one (1) ICT project within Home Affaires sector  in the area of design and  implementation of security and protection systems for complex ICT and Networking infrastructure is an advantage &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience acquired within the last 6 calendar years in at least one (1) project related to implementation and managing of continuity of service in ICT system due to be available 24/7/365 is an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in preparation of technical specifications for 1, preferably 2, IT supply projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in BI &amp; Data Warehouse System (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-bi-data-warehouse-system-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 21:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-bi-data-warehouse-system-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preparation of supply tender dossiers for Serbian Ministry of Interior (MUP)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of this assignment is to support Serbia’s commitment in meeting EU standards in the field of safety and security through implementation of Action Plan on Chapter 24 and Chapter 23.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of this assignments is to provide preliminary assessments, market researches, preparation of technical specifications and tender dossiers and providing input during clarifications and  in the tender evaluations for the following tender procedures:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supply of ICT equipment, security equipment, software solutions and analytical tools for strengthening capacities within Home Affairs Sector for the fight against organized crime by implementation of: Intelligence Led Policing, National Criminal Intelligence System and Strengthening international police cooperation (in line with EUROPOL standards)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supply of video, audio and IT equipment for strengthening capacity of Internal Control Unit to fight against corruption within the police&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 1 Expert in BI &amp;amp; Data Warehouse System (TL)- Category 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree /Master Degree (where a university degree has been awarded on completion of four years study or equivalent institutions) in the field of engineering, information and technology or other field related to this contract.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years, preferably 15 years of relevant experience with databases, data warehousing, and database management software &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English, both written and spoken&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 2, preferably 3 projects in design, configuring and implementation of Data warehouse systems and/or business intelligence solution within Home Affaires sector &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in preparation of technical specifications and /or Terms of References for 1, preferably 2, IT projects in accordance with EU-PRAG rules.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience as senior expert/team leader in at least 1, preferably 2 projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the design of Integrated Criminal Intelligence System for law enforcement bodies (police /prosecutor) is an advantage. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of IBM Cognos system is an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Justice Public Administration Sector</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-justice-public-administration-sector</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 11:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-justice-public-administration-sector</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Short-term Technical Assistance to the Department of Justice&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;PLEAD (Programme for Legal Empowerment and Aid Delivery)&lt;/strong&gt; is a programme funded by the 11th EDF under the NIP sector entitled &amp;ldquo;accountability of public institutions&amp;rdquo;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The programme purpose is to develop an integrated approach at central and local level aimed at equality of all before the law, through improved access to and the expeditious delivery of justice, particularly in high-risk counties in Kenya.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The short term preparatory Technical Assistance will facilitate the inception and the kick-off of the direct decentralised operations component (i.e. the programme estimates) and contribute to the overall integration of this component in the programme.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Justice Public Administration Sector&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Profile per expert&lt;/strong&gt; or expertise required:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Category I: At least 12 years’ experience in the sector(s) related to Lot 7 &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;: University level education&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience in supporting the Justice Public Administration sector in a senior or advisory capacity: at least 6 years
• Experience with Legal Aid policy and/or provision: at least 3 years 
• Demonstrated and thorough experience working with or preparing EU Programme Estimates
• Knowledge of the Kenyan &amp;ldquo;access to justice&amp;rdquo; context will be an added advantage&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;: Fluency in English.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Four  Senior Experts, Formulation Mission for a Sector Reform Contract in JLOS and the Accountability Sector in Uganda</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/four-senior-experts-</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/four-senior-experts-</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this assignment is to assist the European Union Delegation in Uganda in the formulation of a Sector Reform Contract in the area of governance under the 11th European Development Fund.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this assignment is to provide all required elements for the formulation of a Sector Reform Contract in a sector to be confirmed by QSG-1 (provisionally JLOS and the Accountability Sector) in line with the EU budget support guidelines. The mission outputs will enable the EU Delegation to complete all required documents for a 2017 Financing Decision under the 11th EDF.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt; of the assignment are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Sector study&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;analyse the eligibility conditions for sector budget support in line with the EC&amp;rsquo;s guidelines: 1) the country has an adequate, stability-oriented macroeconomic framework, 2) there is a credible and relevant programme to improve public financial management, 3) sufficient level of budgetary transparency and 4) a credible and relevant sector policy with an appropriate monitoring framework;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Identify weaknesses and sector priorities where the EU programme could contribute to progress, taking into account the division of labour and EC&amp;rsquo;s strategic priorities&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Programme identification&lt;/strong&gt;: consider the findings of the sector study and in consultation with different stakeholders identify the programme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Programme formulation&lt;/strong&gt;: in consultation with decision makers provide all required elements for the finalisation of the action document and build a common understanding of the functioning of the SRC and the necessary coordination mechanism to be established.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4 Senior Experts (cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The team must collectively offer the following expertise and experience:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least an advanced university degree in public financial management, macroeconomics, public administration or other relevant fields. Qualification in the fields of public financial management, a qualification as a Chartered Accountant or Chartered Management Accountant will be accepted as an alternative to Master&amp;rsquo;s degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least an advanced university degree in law. Expertise in JLOS performance management and monitoring systems and structures in support of achieving development objectives. Knowledge of the systems used in Uganda will be an added advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in PFM disciplines, including (but not limited to) public finance management, accountancy, budgeting, performance monitoring, internal control, auditing and PFM capacity building, developing and implementing comprehensive PFM improvement and reform initiatives in a decentralized setting;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development expertise, including knowledge of development priorities and challenges. Knowledge of accountability and anti-corruption policies, strategies and programmes specific to Uganda will be advantageous.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of MDGs - SDGs and EU action plans and programmes in support of them. Proven experience in gender targeting and mainstreaming in programme formulation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in public service capacity development and reform initiatives and programmes. Recent experience of working in or with the Ugandan public service will be advantageous.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum expertise required&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5, preferably 10 years&amp;#39; experience in supporting and advising governments in PFM reforms. Experience in Uganda and /or in federal and decentralised contexts will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in developing PFM and budget transparency annual reporting mechanisms and in related policy dialogue on PFM.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5, preferably 10 years&amp;#39; experience in supporting and advising governments in JLOS and anti-corruption. Experience with EU budget support, preferably in the JLOS and PFM sectors, will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good understanding and knowledge of various models to finance the JLOS and PFM sectors and/or in national and decentralised contexts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in developing budget support in the JLOS and PFM sectors in national and decentralised contexts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience with gender sensitive budgeting, and its operationalisation such as through gender compacts and/or similar approaches&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in analysing gender-equality, the rights-based approach, environment and climate change as cross-cutting issues in EU-financed development programmes and in mainstreaming these issues into programme formulation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5, preferably 10 years&amp;#39; experience with formulating EU budget support and proven experience in training senior government officials on EU budget support.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recent working experience in conducting reviews of the key (eligibility) areas of assessment in decentralised governance structure for budget support by the EU.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recent EU programming expertise covering financing modalities including BS, SBS (SRC), and Pool Funding in the context of EC General Budget procedures. Experience with SRCs in the area of governance is considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of EC management modes including but not limited to centralised and decentralised management, is also required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All experts should be fluent in spoken and written English, and should have excellent technical writing skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 2: Sugar Sector Senior Expert (Cat. I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-sugar-sector-senior-expert-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 17:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-sugar-sector-senior-expert-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance for the Sugar Sector&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;overall objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the project of which this contract will be part is to advance the implementation of the Jamaica Country Strategy for the Adaptation of the Sugar Industry 2006 to 2020, and in particular the development of a sustainable sugar cane sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In particular the team will have to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop a comprehensive financial and economic model of the sugar cane industry in Jamaica, including feasibility of ethanol production;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revise the existing sugar cane payment system, including the cane payment formula to reflect and anticipate the changes in the mix of commercial products produced from the sugar cane.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2: Sugar Sector Senior Expert (Cat. I, approx. 90 WD)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master level Degree in Agronomy, Agricultural Economics, Management or other relevant field or alternatively a relevant professional experience in the field of minimum 15 years;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High level of written and spoken English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of general professional experience related to the sector of the lot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 10 years of professional experience in the sugar cane sector with at least 4 years of professional experience at international level;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proved experience working with Sugar Cane Payment Formula will be an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader and Senior Expert on Econometric Modelling (Cat. I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-and-senior-expert-on-econometric-modelling-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 11:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-and-senior-expert-on-econometric-modelling-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance for the Sugar Sector, Jamaica&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project of which this contract will be part is to advance the implementation of the Jamaica Country Strategy for the Adaptation of the Sugar Industry 2006 to 2020, and in particular the development of a sustainable sugar cane sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In particular the team will have to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop a comprehensive financial and economic model of the sugar cane industry in Jamaica, including feasibility of ethanol production;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revise the existing sugar cane payment system, including the cane payment formula to reflect and anticipate the changes in the mix of commercial products produced from the sugar cane.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 1: Team Leader and Senior Expert on Econometric Modelling (Cat. I)  approx. 90 WD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master level Degree in Econometrics, Mathematics, Statistics, Economics or other relevant field or alternatively a relevant professional experience of minimum 15 years in the field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High level of written and spoken English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of general professional experience related to the sector of the lot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience as Head of a team or Deputy Head of a team in at least 2 projects in the field of development of econometric models for a duration of at least 3 months in each project;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 10 years of professional experience developing econometric models;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the sugar sector will be an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the Caribbean region is a plus;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assessors (Cat I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/assessors-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 18:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/assessors-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recruitment of assessors to assist in the evaluation of grant applications received in the framework of the call for proposals 2016/159933, South Sudan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overall objective&lt;/strong&gt;: To recruit assessors to assist the Contracting Authority in the selection of the best proposals received under “ZEAT BEAD Component 2:  Sustainable supply of agriculture and livestock inputs and services through the private sector” and to achieve a high-quality, complete and coherent selection process of projects in line with the criteria set in the guidelines for applicants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assessors (Cat I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree or, in its absence, equivalent professional experience of 5 years above the minimum general professional experience requirement in Rural Development, Agricultural sciences,  development studies  or any other relevant field; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent analytical and drafting skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written English is essential.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least 10 years&amp;#39; experience gained in sectors 9. FOOD SECURITY or 10. RURAL DEVELOPMENT.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years&amp;#39; experience working in sub-Saharan Africa in programmes implemented by Non-Governmental Organisations (NGOs) in food security and/or rural development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience participating in the selection of grant recipients as an assessor on behalf of a national authorising officer or an international organisation is essential;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work experience in post-conflict areas, in particular in fragile states;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very good knowledge of project cycle management and of EU grants contract procedures;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work experience in South Sudan is an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;lina_forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Food security and/or Rural Development (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-food-security-and-or-rural-development-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-food-security-and-or-rural-development-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recruitment of assessors to assist in the evaluation of grant applications received in the framework of the call for proposals 2016/159933, South Sudan
**
**Overall objective&lt;/strong&gt;: To recruit assessors to assist the Contracting Authority in the selection of the best proposals received under “ZEAT BEAD Component 2:  Sustainable supply of agriculture and livestock inputs and services through the private sector” and to achieve a high-quality, complete and coherent selection process of projects in line with the criteria set in the guidelines for applicants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team leader (cat I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree or, in its absence, equivalent professional experience of 5 years above the minimum general professional experience requirement, in Rural Development, Agricultural sciences,  development studies  or any other relevant field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent analytical and drafting skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer literacy;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written English is essential;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track record in the timely reporting and adherence to deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least 10 years&amp;#39; experience gained in one of the sectors of Lot 1.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very good knowledge of project cycle management and of EU grants contract procedures;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience participating in the selection of grant recipients on behalf of a national authorising officer or an international organisation is essential;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience coordinating the work of independent experts and reviewing inputs to ensure high quality deliverables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years&amp;#39; experience working in sub-Saharan Africa in programmes implemented by Non-Governmental Organisations (NGOs) in food security and/or rural development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;lina_forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assistant au Chef de Mission – Expert en développement des capacités dans le secteur de la Coopération</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/assistant-au-chef-de-mission-expert-en-developpement-des-capacites-dans-le-secteur-de-la-cooperation</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/assistant-au-chef-de-mission-expert-en-developpement-des-capacites-dans-le-secteur-de-la-cooperation</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation finale PAON 10eme FED&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La République Gabonaise bénéficie de l’ensemble des instruments prévus par la Convention de Lomé et l’Accord de Cotonou à laquelle s’est ajoutée la volonté manifeste de  financement par la Banque Européenne d’Investissement (BEI). L’Accord de Cotonou confie à l’Ordonnateur national (ON), des responsabilités très larges dans la conception, le pilotage, le contrôle et la mise en œuvre des projets et programmes de coopération ACP-UE. En effet afin de mettre en œuvre les principes de Cotonou, qui sont axés sur les résultats, le partenariat et l’appropriation, la programmation et la mise en œuvre du FED sont conçues comme une responsabilité commune. L’UE et le bénéficiaire souhaitent pour la mise en œuvre du programme suivant d’appui à l’Ordonnateur National (Ref GAD/FED/25-065) disposer d’un avis externe, garanti par l&amp;#39;indépendance d&amp;#39;appréciation des évaluateurs, afin de tirer des leçons ainsi que sur les éventuelles réorientations et recommandations qui pourraient contribuer à une meilleure efficience et efficacité dans l’utilisation des fonds et, plus spécialement, garantir la pérennisation des actions engagées dans un contexte en forte évolution.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Le résultat attendu est une analyse et une appréciation qualitative ainsi que la formulation de recommandations concernant l’efficacité, l’efficience, et l’impact de l’appui à l’Ordonnateur National du FED dans la mise en œuvre de la coopération avec la Commission Européenne.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duration&lt;/strong&gt;: Les experts seront mobilisés un maximum de 20 jours ouvrables par expert dont 15 jours minimum au Gabon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2 – Assistant au Chef de Mission – Expert en développement des capacités dans le secteur de la Coopération&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification et Compétences&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une formation de niveau supérieur (BAC+4) en économie, droit, administration publique ou domaine équivalent &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Français : Excellent en lecture, oral et écrit (capacités de synthèse et de rédaction). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise des outils informatiques &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance souhaitable des méthodologies « qualité » (ISO, TQM, …) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience Professionnelle Générale&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience d’au moins 6 ans dans le domaine du développement des capacités des autorités nationales relatives à la mise en œuvre des projets de coopération &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience Professionnelle Spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience d’au moins 6 ans (dont 2 ans en Afrique Subsaharienne) dans l’identification et la formulation des projets de développement des capacités (Cellules d’Appui à l’Ordonnateur National, Facilité de Coopération Technique …) dans les pays en développement &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience dans une évaluation d’un projet de caractéristiques similaires au cours des deux dernières années sera considérée comme un atout &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience dans l’évaluation des thèmes transversaux promus par l’UE tels que l’implication de la société civile, la prise en compte des questions de genre et l’approche basée sur les droits de l’homme sera considérée comme un atout &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une bonne maitrise des procédures du FED&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert I - Chef de Mission – Expert en Evaluation du Secteur de la Coopération </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-i-chef-de-mission-expert-en-evaluation-du-secteur-de-la-cooperation</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 18:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-i-chef-de-mission-expert-en-evaluation-du-secteur-de-la-cooperation</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Evaluation finale PAON 10eme FED
*&lt;/em&gt;
La République Gabonaise bénéficie de l’ensemble des instruments prévus par la Convention de Lomé et l’Accord de Cotonou à laquelle s’est ajoutée la volonté manifeste de  financement par la Banque Européenne d’Investissement (BEI). L’Accord de Cotonou confie à l’Ordonnateur national (ON), des responsabilités très larges dans la conception, le pilotage, le contrôle et la mise en œuvre des projets et programmes de coopération ACP-UE. En effet afin de mettre en œuvre les principes de Cotonou, qui sont axés sur les résultats, le partenariat et l’appropriation, la programmation et la mise en œuvre du FED sont conçues comme une responsabilité commune. L’UE et le bénéficiaire souhaitent pour la mise en œuvre du programme suivant d’appui à l’Ordonnateur National (Ref GAD/FED/25-065) disposer d’un avis externe, garanti par l&amp;#39;indépendance d&amp;#39;appréciation des évaluateurs, afin de tirer des leçons ainsi que sur les éventuelles réorientations et recommandations qui pourraient contribuer à une meilleure efficience et efficacité dans l’utilisation des fonds et, plus spécialement, garantir la pérennisation des actions engagées dans un contexte en forte évolution.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Le résultat attendu est une analyse et une appréciation qualitative ainsi que la formulation de recommandations concernant l’efficacité, l’efficience, et l’impact de l’appui à l’Ordonnateur National du FED dans la mise en œuvre de la coopération avec la Commission Européenne.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duration&lt;/strong&gt;: Les experts seront mobilisés un maximum de 20 jours ouvrables par expert dont 15 jours minimum au Gabon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert I - Chef de Mission – Expert en Evaluation du Secteur de la Coopération&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Qualification et Compétences *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une formation de niveau supérieur (BAC+5) en économie, droit, administration publique ou domaine équivalent &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Français : Excellent en lecture, oral et écrit (capacités de synthèse et de rédaction). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise des outils informatiques &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience Professionnelle Générale&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience d’au moins 6 ans dans le domaine de l’évaluation de l’aide internationale &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience générale solide de 6 ans dans la conduite d’évaluations de projets de coopération &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Expérience Professionnelle Spécifique *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une connaissance approfondie des méthodes d’évaluation de l’UE appliquée aux actions de coopération &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans le domaine de l&amp;#39;appui aux ordonnateurs nationaux souhaitable &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A conduit au moins 2 évaluations similaires dans des pays ACP &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une bonne maîtrise des procédures du FED &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience dans une mission de long terme dans le cadre d’un projet aux caractéristiques similaires au cours des dix dernières années sera considérée comme un atout &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience dans une évaluation d’un projet aux caractéristiques similaires au cours des deux dernières années sera considérée comme un atout&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert IV – Multimedia, Graphic, Designer and edition (category III)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-iv-multimedia-graphic-designer-and-edition-category-iii</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 08:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-iv-multimedia-graphic-designer-and-edition-category-iii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visibility Portfolio for EASE and Environment-related Projects&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To contribute to provide visibility to the impact of EASE, as well as other EU-funded environment and climate change mitigation related interventions in Nigeria.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To promote the results of EU funded interventions in Nigeria with environment and climate change mitigation activities, linking them to broader development goals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To raise awareness about the linkages between energy and environmental protection, climate change mitigation. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The products under this assignment will form part of the EU Delegation to Nigeria and ECOWAS project portfolio and will be used as PR, media tool and raising awareness material in different events and through different online mediums (websites, print media, social platforms, among others).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following outputs and deliverables are required:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 success stories, a minimum of 1 page and maximum 1,5 pages per project story in accordance with the visibility guidelines and in a standard format for printing (in Pdf). The stories will include testimonies by beneficiaries and implementing partners, as appropriate. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 videoclips of between 15 and 90 seconds (indicative time), which convey through a succession of images and sounds the projects stories. The videos can include interviews with beneficiaries, partners and project implementers and could be posted online by the delegation, namely on its website and social media (Instagram, facebook, etc), as well as screened at visibility events, in Nigeria. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 4 audioclips of between 40 and 300 seconds (indicative time), which convey through a succession of sounds the project stories. Some of the footage from the videoclips can be used but the audioclips should have its own creative logic. The sound artist/reporter/engineer is expected to also provide support for sound capture to the videographer, as needed. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;150 high-resolution photographs accompanying the pre-selected project stories and reflecting the impact, change and improvements in peoples’ lives and the environment. The photos will depict the activities per project in TIF or RAW, as well as in jpg (low resolution for website use). The contractor should provide the digital storage (hard disks) to support collection of stories mentioned above and to organise the archive. The caption of each photograph should include details such as the location taken, name of the person (for portraits), activity and any other relevant information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;18 photos of all the projects visited should be reworked in detail in post-production (colour correction, touch up, enhancements, all in high resolution for printing) that could serve for a photo exhibition promoting European Cooperation in Nigeria (EU Development Days, Europe Day, Climate Change week, other events). The photos will be printed and made readily available to be exposed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 to 10 minutes animated multimedia presentation summarizing the success stories.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert IV – Multimedia, Graphic, Designer and edition (category III)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education, and duration of equivalent experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possession of undergraduate degree in Graphic Design, Motion Graphics, or equivalent professional experience of more than 3 years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 years&amp;#39; experience with photo and video edition.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with producing print, web interactive work and with creating and managing websites and social media platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;technical proficiency in Macintosh OS and expert knowledge of edition software and other mark-up languages (e.g. Creative Suite and Microsoft Office, Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign Adobe Flash, HTML, HTML 5, CSS3).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work independently. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of maintaining archive of images, photos and graphic materials. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The expert is required to have proficiency of English both written and oral.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert in Resilient Agriculture (cat II) </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-resilient-agriculture-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-resilient-agriculture-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formulation of the Climate Change and Research (REACH) Programme&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of this mission is to support the formulation of the REACH programme, a component of the EU’s supports to Agriculture Development in Ghana to be implemented with the resources mobilised under 11th EDF (2014 – 2020) as from 2017 onwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this regard, a fully-fledged Action Document must be produced with annexes, all in line with procedures and standards prevailing for such an Action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in Resilient Agriculture (cat II) 42 working days&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The expert must be graduated in Environment/Natural resources management, agro/socioeconomy or engineering studies linked to the above topics, with at least a Master Degree. Alternatively, he may have an equivalent professional experience of at least 2 years on top of the general required experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General required experience&lt;/strong&gt;: 
The expert must have at least 6 years of general experience in sustainable agriculture or sustainable environment programmes, or any other related activities aiming at implementing actions in resilient agriculture in an African context.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific required experience&lt;/strong&gt;:
1/ Fields to be covered: Evaluation/management of Development Projects on minimum 2 among the 3 below-listed sectors:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agriculture development/rural development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Environment protection/ management of natural resources/resilience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Climate adaptation/mitigation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2/ At least one field of the list below constitutes a minimum requirement (all fields will be scored maximum):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in promoting capacity building, local knowledge development, community development through cooperation programmes in Africa, particularly sub-Saharan Africa,;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formulation of programmes (ability for reasoning and strategizing ideas).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth knowledge of EDF procedures;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experience in *&lt;em&gt;Ghana *&lt;/em&gt;will be considered as an asset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;lina_forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWP 2 Projects Review</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Beyond WTO Program (B-WTO) was developed in response to a request from the Government of Vietnam (GoV) for donor support to help with managing economic integration and the transition to a market economy following WTO accession. The B-WTO goal is “to strengthen government’s capacity to manage the integration of Vietnam into the global economy and the transition of Vietnam to a socialist market economy”. The immediate objective is “implementation of priority policy actions from the GoV’s Action Plan to enhance Vietnam’s capacity to sustain pro-poor growth (GAP)”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The remit of this project was a review of the 2nd annual work plan’s implementation (AWP2) of Phase 2 of the B-WTO in May 2013. The objectives of the review were to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the project implementation performance and project results relative to the logical framework targets and evaluation criteria. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the results achieved at the Component and Program’s level according to the Monitoring and Evaluation (M&amp;amp;E) framework of the Program.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify lessons learned from implementation, make recommendations for the remaining duration of the program and the Independent Completion Report process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
