<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2014 08:37:55 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert en Relations Internationales (Chef de Mission, Cat.I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-relations-internationales-chef-de-mission-cati</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2014 08:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-relations-internationales-chef-de-mission-cati</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Cette évaluation correspond à une évaluation de mi-parcours de l&amp;#39;ensemble du programme de coopération binationale République Dominicaine – Haïti, conçu comme un ensemble cohérent, mais divisé pour des raisons de gestion  administrative en deux conventions de financement. L&amp;#39;une couvre le &amp;ldquo;Programme de coopération binationale: appui à la coopération binationale dans les domaines du commerce, de l&amp;#39;environnement et du développement local transfrontalier&amp;rdquo;. L&amp;#39;autre couvre le &amp;ldquo;Programme de cooperation binationale: appui aux infrastructures du Corridor Nord&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Projet duree&lt;/strong&gt;: 76 jours calendrier&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert en Relations Internationales (Chef de Mission ; Cat.I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme de maîtrise en relations internationales, sciences politiques, droit international, sciences économiques ou domaines semblables. Le diplôme universitaire peut être remplacé par une expérience professionnelle d&amp;#39;au moins 12 ans dans ces domaines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;expérience en évaluation de programmes de développement. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience du contexte dominico-haïtien. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;De préférence expérience de la politique de développement de l&amp;#39;UE.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne connaissance des langues espagnole et française. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bon capacité de gestion d&amp;#39;équipe et de rédaction. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicolas_fichers@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicolas_fichers@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experto en Seguridad Fronteriza/Evaluación  ( Cat. I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-en-seguridad-fronteriza-evaluacion-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2014 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-en-seguridad-fronteriza-evaluacion-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Evaluación Final del Programa Regional de Seguridad Fronteriza en Centroamérica (SEFRO).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location visits&lt;/strong&gt;: Costa Rica, El Salvador, Guatemala, Honduras, Nicaragua, Panamá&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experto en Seguridad Fronteriza/Evaluación  ( Cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Características generales&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formación universitaria, de preferencia en Ciencias Sociales o equivalente, siendo una ventaja estudios de post grado en temas relacionados con la misión.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia sólida y diversificada en el campo/ámbito del conocimiento específico necesario y requerido, incluyendo experiencia no menor a 5 años en monitoreo y/o evaluación de proyectos, en particular de al menos 5 años en proyectos relacionados con la temática de la evaluación.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia en Centroamérica y conocimiento de los procesos políticos y dinámicas existentes en la región.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capacidad y experiencia no menor de 7 años en la planificación y gestión del ciclo de proyectos y de procedimientos de cooperación.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Profundo conocimiento del idioma castellano, hablado, y escrito, así como capacidad comprobada de redacción de Informes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;manejo de herramientas informáticas y conocimiento de las fases del ciclo del proyecto y del Marco Lógico según la Unión Europea, así como de la metodología de evaluación de la ayuda exterior de la UE.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Características específicas&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;mínimo siete (7) años de experiencia en planificación, ejecución y evaluación de proyectos. Preferiblemente 5 (cinco) relacionados con la temática de la misión en el ámbito de uno de los temas relacionados con la seguridad fronteriza (policía, migración y aduanas). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Se valorará positivamente la experiencia en Centroamérica.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicolas_fichers@dai.com&quot;&gt;Nicolas_fichers@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experto en Seguridad Fronteriza/Evaluación  (Jefe de equipo – Cat.I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-en-seguridad-fronteriza-evaluacion-jefe-de-equipo-cati</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2014 08:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-en-seguridad-fronteriza-evaluacion-jefe-de-equipo-cati</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Evaluación Final del Programa Regional de Seguridad Fronteriza en Centroamérica (SEFRO).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experto en Seguridad Fronteriza/Evaluación  (Jefe de equipo – Categoría I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Características generales:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formación universitaria, de preferencia en Ciencias Sociales o equivalente, siendo una ventaja estudios de post grado en temas relacionados con la misión.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia sólida y diversificada en el campo/ámbito del conocimiento específico necesario y requerido, incluyendo experiencia no menor a 5 años en monitoreo y/o evaluación de proyectos, en particular de al menos 5 años en proyectos relacionados con la temática de la evaluación.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia en Centroamérica y conocimiento de los procesos políticos y dinámicas existentes en la región.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capacidad y experiencia no menor de 7 años en la planificación y gestión del ciclo de proyectos y de procedimientos de cooperación.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Profundo conocimiento del idioma castellano, hablado, y escrito, así como capacidad comprobada de redacción de Informes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;manejo de herramientas informáticas y conocimiento de las fases del ciclo del proyecto y del Marco Lógico según la Unión Europea, así como de la metodología de evaluación de la ayuda exterior de la UE.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Características específicas:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;mínimo cinco (7) años de experiencia (10 años preferible) en diseño o ejecución o monitoreo y evaluación de programas, de los cuales se pide 4 años de experiencia en temas relacionados con la temática de la misión. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Se requiere un sólido conocimiento de los métodos y técnicas de evaluación de proyectos. Es imprescindible tener experiencia en evaluación de proyectos de la Unión Europea.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicolas_fichers@dai.com&quot;&gt;Nicolas_fichers@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert for Strategic planning and Committees (Deputy Team Leader)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-for-strategic-planning-and-committees-deputy-team-leader</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 17:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-for-strategic-planning-and-committees-deputy-team-leader</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Deputy Team Leader/Strategic Planning and Committees&amp;#39; expert&lt;/strong&gt; will lead on the strategic advice, conceptualisation, implementation and oversight of actions related to Result 1 and Result 2 of the project and in particular to the assistance for Strategic Plans exercise, overall systematic committee support and strengthened committee functioning (review/amendment of Rules of Procedure), Human Resource assessments and parliamentary cadre for the Secretariat. To perform these tasks, the expert will be supported by long term and short term senior expertise as well by the junior expertise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deputy Team Leader/Senior Expert for Strategic Planning and Committees&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree at Masters&amp;#39; level in social and/or political science, public and/or business administration, law, economics or related discipline or with experience of at least 15 years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent leadership, management, communication (written and oral), networking and reporting skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work at senior parliamentary level; ability to work under pressure and to meet strict deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in written and oral English language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least ten years professional experience in parliamentary-related work and/or public administration, extensive experience in institutional strengthening and strategies, institutional capacity-building, parliamentary committee system and rules of procedure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project management, including in the design, budgeting, implementation and monitoring of projects, preferably related to parliamentary or public administration affairs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to international committee parliamentary practices is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with EU procedures is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with parliamentary committees functioning, parliamentary Rules of Business and in strategic planning&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in institutional related support to public administration, the legislative sector and/or the private sector and in matters pertaining to oversight of the executive in developing countries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in cooperating with donors, international organisations, public administrations and civil society&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good familiarity with gender concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to apply&lt;/strong&gt;: Please paste the following link into your browser - &lt;a href=&quot;http://ch.tbe.taleo.net/CH13/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=1730&quot;&gt;http://ch.tbe.taleo.net/CH13/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=1730&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Please note that all profiles are indicative only and therefore subject to change once the ToR is made available.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader – Pakistan: Support to Democratic Institutions</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-pakistan-support-to-democratic-institutions</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-pakistan-support-to-democratic-institutions</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; will support the EU Delegation, the Assemblies&amp;#39; stakeholders and the Technical Assistance (TA) team in achieving the overall objective and purpose of the project. In particular, the Team Leader will lead the TA team in assisting, supporting and building the capacities of the Provincial Assemblies and Legislative Assemblies to strengthen the three parliamentary functions and the performance of the Assemblies. The Team Leader is responsible for the overall project coordination and execution, including (but not limited to) supervision of professional staff and experts, establishment and review of programmatic and budgetary priorities, submission of required work plans and reports, and communication and coordination with all stakeholders. The Team Leader will also assist the EU Delegation in tasks related to the facilitation of donor coordination as well as in task related to the Project Steering Committee and specific working committees for the four Provincial Assemblies. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader – Pakistan: Support to Democratic Institutions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree at Masters&amp;#39; level in social and/or political science, public and/or business administration, law or related discipline. Can be substituted with relevant professional experience of at least 15 years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent leadership, management, communication (written and oral), networking and reporting skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work at senior parliamentary level - ability to work under pressure and to meet strict deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in written and oral English language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least ten years professional experience in the field of development work related to parliamentary work, institutional development and strengthening, public administration, good governance, institutional and civil society capacity building, political parties&amp;#39; development, and/or other areas related to formulation of public policy and/or scrutiny, including five years of management experience. Prior experience of a combination of all these areas is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project management, including in the design, budget preparation, implementation, and monitoring of projects and programmes, preferably in parliamentary institutional development. Experience in a management position or as project Team Leader&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in working in multi-donor context; Experience in EU funded cooperation projects is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with EU procedures is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound knowledge of EU policies and programmes in the area of human rights, democratisation and good governance is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good familiarity with gender concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in managing comprehensive parliamentary development actions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of and working experience in the areas of parliamentary work including provision of technical assistance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;International parliamentary experience and/or exposure to international parliamentary practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in providing institutional support to public administrations/parliaments in matters pertaining to parliamentary regulatory frameworks and processes in developing countries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to apply&lt;/strong&gt;:Please paste the following link into your browser - &lt;a href=&quot;http://ch.tbe.taleo.net/CH13/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=1729&quot;&gt;http://ch.tbe.taleo.net/CH13/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=1729&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Please note that all profiles are indicative only and therefore subject to change once the ToR is made available.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Communications Expert </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-communications-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 17:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-communications-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Communications Expert&lt;/strong&gt; shall lead in the advice, conceptualisation, implementation and oversight of actions related to Result 3 of this project relating to improving the transparency and accessibility of assemblies. The expert will lead on the development and implementing communication strategies, increasing the Assemblies&amp;#39; capabilities to disseminate information to the public for more participatory governance and to deliver timely information and documents to the members. The expert will work closely with the Secretariat&amp;rsquo;s respective branches, Parliamentary leadership, Committees, media. Together with the other experts, the expert will also assist on effective parliamentary and Committees&amp;#39; engagement with the media and the public (civil society, lawyers, bar associations, think tanks) for provision of input into parliamentary legislative and oversight business) and for improving the quantity and quality of media repotting on parliamentary business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Communications Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree at Masters&amp;#39; level in media and communication, public relations, law, in social and/or political science, public administration or related discipline with experience of at least 15 years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent leadership, management, communication (written and oral), networking and reporting skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent analytical skills and ability to conceptualise policy formulation within the subject area&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work at senior parliamentary level; ability to work under pressure and to meet strict deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in written and oral English language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least ten years professional experience working within media and/or communication and/or Public Relations (PR)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with international donor-funded programmes or experience on management position preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to international parliamentary practices in the areas of communication/PR is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth understanding of and experience with media, in the sectors of communications as well as public relations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in strategic communications, development and implementation of communication strategies and systems for the public administration, private sector and/or legislative sector (parliament)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid knowledge of digital media, communication and outreach, and web content management system and process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of information and communication technologies is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in liaising with civil society, lawyers, bar associations, think tanks, public administration and others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the concept and practice of the representation function of the parliament involving timely and quality public outreach and public input into parliamentary business&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to apply&lt;/strong&gt;: please paste the following link into your browser &lt;a href=&quot;http://ch.tbe.taleo.net/CH13/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=1732&quot;&gt;http://ch.tbe.taleo.net/CH13/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=1732&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;&lt;strong&gt;Please note that all profiles are indicative only and therefore subject to change once the ToR is made available.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert Oversight and Accountability</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-oversight-and-accountability</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 17:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-oversight-and-accountability</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The expert &lt;strong&gt;Oversight and Accountability&lt;/strong&gt; will lead on the strategic advice, conceptualisation and implementation of actions part of Result 1 and Result 2 of the project related in particular to fiscal and budgetary oversight of Committees and Secretariat Branches providing support in these areas. The expert will work for ensuring that Committees and Members have a role and are capacitated to actively participate in budget formulation, mid-year budget reviews and scrutiny of expenditures. The work with the corresponding specialised Secretariat Branches should have as ultimate purpose to ensure stronger internal assembly input for the decision-making and public accounts scrutiny of Committees. The expert should also build mechanisms and pull expertise from think tanks, academia, research and civil society etc, and to make them available on a regular and sustainable basis to the assemblies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree at Masters&amp;#39; level in social and/or political science, public/business administration, management, economics, law or related discipline or with experience of at least 15 years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent leadership, management, communication (written and oral), networking and reporting skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work at senior parliamentary level; ability to work under pressure and to meet strict deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in written and oral English language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least ten years professional experience in the field of development and institutional work related to budgetary process and public accounts&amp;#39; oversight and related research and analysis, parliamentary development, capacity building and strategies for parliamentary institutional strengthening, public administration and capacity-building, parliamentary committees, Prior experience of a combination of all these areas is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project management, including in the design, budgeting, implementation and monitoring of projects, preferably related to budget and oversight and parliamentary or public administration affairs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to international parliamentary practices is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with parliamentary work related to budget including scrutiny of the budget and of public expenditures, understanding of budgetary and oversight tools and mechanisms available to parliament&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in budgetary related research, analysis and process. Experience in the process of formulation of the budget is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in institutional and budget related support to public administration, the legislative sector and/or the private sector and in matters pertaining to budget regulatory frameworks, public accounts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of the oversight of public spending&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in cooperating with donors, international organisations, public administrations and civil society&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with gender budgeting concept, output based budgeting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to apply&lt;/strong&gt;:please paste this link into your browser: &lt;a href=&quot;http://ch.tbe.taleo.net/CH13/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=1731&quot;&gt;http://ch.tbe.taleo.net/CH13/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=1731&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Please note that all profiles are indicative only and therefore subject to change once the ToR is made available.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring and Evaluation Specialist, MAHKOTA – Towards a Strong and Prosperous Indonesian Society</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/monitoring-and-evaluation-specialist-</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/monitoring-and-evaluation-specialist-</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;MAHKOTA Indonesia – Menuju Masyarakat Indonesia Yang Kokoh Sejahtera (&lt;strong&gt;Towards a Strong and Prosperous Indonesian Society&lt;/strong&gt;) – aims to improve the quality and effectiveness of Indonesia’s poverty reduction programmes. It will support policy reform of existing social protection programmes and help Indonesia better reach and benefit the poorest as well as address key binding constraints to growth, competitiveness and rising inequality through ongoing labour market and social protection reforms. It will foster a wider range of policy debate in the country by supporting national think tanks and support the Indonesian Government in making important reforms towards social security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Addressing the critical constraints to poverty reduction, economic growth and improved competitiveness goes beyond a single initiative. To reach these outcomes, MAHKOTA will work closely with other Australian development programmes including economic governance, education, health and women’s empowerment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Monitoring and Evaluation Specialist&lt;/strong&gt; will support M&amp;amp;E for individual activities, as well as developing and reporting against the MAHKOTA M&amp;amp;E framework.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Applicants should be able to demonstrate the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WORK EXPERIENCE&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5-7 years of relevant professional experience, including 3 years in a long-term M&amp;amp;E position with an international donor-funded development project/organization; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated knowledge and experience in application of the logical framework approach, Performance Monitoring Plan development, and environmental assessment and impact monitoring; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in developing countries is required, preferably in the Asia-Pacific region. Experience of working in Indonesia will be an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EDUCATION&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in Social Sciences (International Development), Business Administration, Economics or other related fields; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SKILLS AND KNOWLEDGE&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in participatory design (outcome mapping, after action review, structured interviews, focus groups, case studies, surveys, and secondary data analysis techniques); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of survey design, data collection and data management, and data analysis using rigorous statistics and appropriate software; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with economic development programs and gender mainstreaming. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to explain M&amp;amp;E processes to staff and partners and ensure that they adhere to the highest standards of quality, relevance and timeliness in their M&amp;amp;E efforts; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical skills and ability to write clear reports; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to explain highly technical results to non-technical audiences; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written English skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Bahasa Indonesian an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in DFAT format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting &lt;strong&gt;DFAT/AOP/011 MAHKOTA&lt;/strong&gt; in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Manager, Towards a Strong and Prosperous Indonesian Society</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/technical-manager-</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/technical-manager-</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;MAHKOTA Indonesia – Menuju Masyarakat Indonesia Yang Kokoh Sejahtera (&lt;strong&gt;Towards a Strong and Prosperous Indonesian Society&lt;/strong&gt;) – aims to improve the quality and effectiveness of Indonesia’s poverty reduction programmes. It will support policy reform of existing social protection programmes and help Indonesia better reach and benefit the poorest as well as address key binding constraints to growth, competitiveness and rising inequality through ongoing labour market and social protection reforms. It will foster a wider range of policy debate in the country by supporting national think tanks and support the Indonesian Government in making important reforms towards social security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Addressing the critical constraints to poverty reduction, economic growth and improved competitiveness goes beyond a single initiative. To reach these outcomes, MAHKOTA will work closely with other Australian development programmes including economic governance, education, health and women’s empowerment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Technical Manager&lt;/strong&gt; will primarily be responsible for ensuring the overall quality of activities and outputs and systems to support that.
Applicants should be able to demonstrate the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WORK EXPERIENCE&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Five years’ experience of working in development cooperation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 years’ experience on quality management of similarly large and complex programs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in developing countries is required, preferably in the Asia-Pacific region. Experience of working in Indonesia will be an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EDUCATION&lt;/strong&gt;:
Master’s degree in Political Science, International Development, or related field preferred&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SKILLS AND KNOWLEDGE&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Substantial knowledge of the Indonesian social protection and poverty reduction programmes – including recent reforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in quality management of complex development programs &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written English skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Bahasa Indonesian an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in DFAT format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting DFAT/AOP/011 MAHKOTA in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader - MAHKOTA – Towards a Strong and Prosperous Indonesian Society</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-mahkota-towards-a-strong-and-prosperous-indonesian-society</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 16:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-mahkota-towards-a-strong-and-prosperous-indonesian-society</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;MAHKOTA Indonesia – Menuju Masyarakat Indonesia Yang Kokoh Sejahtera (&lt;strong&gt;Towards a Strong and Prosperous Indonesian Society&lt;/strong&gt;) – aims to improve the quality and effectiveness of Indonesia’s poverty reduction programmes. It will support policy reform of existing social protection programmes and help Indonesia better reach and benefit the poorest as well as address key binding constraints to growth, competitiveness and rising inequality through ongoing labour market and social protection reforms. It will foster a wider range of policy debate in the country by supporting national think tanks and support the Indonesian Government in making important reforms towards social security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Addressing the critical constraints to poverty reduction, economic growth and improved competitiveness goes beyond a single initiative. To reach these outcomes, MAHKOTA will work closely with other Australian development programmes including economic governance, education, health and women’s empowerment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; is responsible for setting and maintaining MAHKOTA strategic direction, navigating multiple and sometimes competing needs for support, and should have a good understanding of social protection and poverty reduction and excellent cross cultural and interpersonal skills. She/He will need to establish and implement a strategic vision for MAHKOTA that is grounded in the political and institutional reality of Indonesia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This includes: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leading engagement with a wide range of stakeholders at the district, provincial and national level to support problem identification, planning and prioritisation of activities, and enthusiastically stimulate innovation and risk taking. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing a complex program of research, pilot and analytical activities that is implemented across a range of locations and focused on identifying affordable, local solutions to improving student learning. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing and implementing a stakeholder engagement and communications strategy that supports sharing of knowledge and findings generated by MAHKOTA and adaptability and replication of tested strategies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Applicants should be able to demonstrate the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WORK EXPERIENCE&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ten years’ experience of working in development cooperation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 years’ experience as a Team Leader on similarly large and complex programs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in developing countries is required, preferably in the Asia-Pacific region. Experience of working in Indonesia will be an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EDUCATION&lt;/strong&gt;:
Master’s degree in Political Science, International Development, or related field preferred&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SKILLS AND KNOWLEDGE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Substantial knowledge of the Indonesian social protection and poverty reduction programmes – including recent reforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly developed stakeholder engagement, communication and relationship management skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly developed strategic planning skills and experience leading complex development programs and leading an effective cross-cultural team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written English skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Bahasa Indonesian an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in DFAT format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting &lt;strong&gt;DFAT/AOP/011 MAHKOTA&lt;/strong&gt; in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Operations Manager</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/operations-manager</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/operations-manager</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;MAHKOTA Indonesia – &lt;strong&gt;Menuju Masyarakat Indonesia Yang Kokoh Sejahtera (Towards a Strong and Prosperous Indonesian Society)&lt;/strong&gt; – aims to improve the quality and effectiveness of Indonesia’s poverty reduction programmes. It will support policy reform of existing social protection programmes and help Indonesia better reach and benefit the poorest as well as address key binding constraints to growth, competitiveness and rising inequality through ongoing labour market and social protection reforms. It will foster a wider range of policy debate in the country by supporting national think tanks and support the Indonesian Government in making important reforms towards social security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Addressing the critical constraints to poverty reduction, economic growth and improved competitiveness goes beyond a single initiative. To reach these outcomes, MAHKOTA will work closely with other Australian development programmes including economic governance, education, health and women’s empowerment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Operations Manager&lt;/strong&gt; is responsible for human resources, finance and procurement, IT services, facility logistics and all other operational matters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt; include (but are not limited to):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All operations including but not limited to administration, logistics, procurement, budgeting, financial, and property. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensuring that program implementation is in accordance with DFAT regulations and procedures and the specifications determined in the project Service Order. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assuring that the most reasonable, fair, expeditious and appropriate procurement choices were made pursuant to DAI’s Procurement Guide.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supervision of DAI’s day‐to‐day field presence in the areas of operations (including the project&amp;rsquo;s facilities such as office space, equipment and project vehicles), administration, logistics, procurement, budgeting and financial accounting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supervision of the daily financial operations of the contract, which include cash flow management, time sheet recording, reporting to DAI on the financial aspects of the project, and daily monitoring of obligations, budgets, and expenditures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensuring continuous liquidity for the project, including handling all human resource issues and investigating and identifying new ways of achieving project efficiencies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Applicants should be able to demonstrate the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WORK EXPERIENCE&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ten years’ experience of working in development cooperation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of experience working on donor‐funded projects in a related role and with some demonstrated supervisory experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in developing countries is required, preferably in the Asia-Pacific region. Experience of working in Indonesia will be an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EDUCATION&lt;/strong&gt;:
Master’s degree in Political Science, International Development, or related field preferred&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SKILLS AND KNOWLEDGE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience and knowledge in operations management, overseeing program start-up under limited time constraints and programme management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Human resources and adviser management, especially in recruitment; Logistics and procurement; Capacity building and training; Financial management, budgeting and reporting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written English skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Bahasa Indonesian an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in DFAT format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting DFAT/AOP/011 MAHKOTA in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Capacity Building Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/capacity-building-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 10:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/capacity-building-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Menuju Masyarakat Indonesia Yang Kokoh Sejahtera&lt;/strong&gt; (Towards a Strong and Prosperous Indonesian Society) – aims to improve the quality and effectiveness of Indonesia’s poverty reduction programmes. It will support policy reform of existing social protection programmes and help Indonesia better reach and benefit the poorest as well as address key binding constraints to growth, competitiveness and rising inequality through ongoing labour market and social protection reforms. It will foster a wider range of policy debate in the country by supporting national think tanks and support the Indonesian Government in making important reforms towards social security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Addressing the critical constraints to poverty reduction, economic growth and improved competitiveness goes beyond a single initiative. To reach these outcomes, MAHKOTA will work closely with other Australian development programmes including economic governance, education, health and women’s empowerment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Capacity Building Specialist&lt;/strong&gt; will be responsible for developing the facility’s capacity development strategy and coordinating needs assessments and capacity building activities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Applicants should be able to demonstrate the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WORK EXPERIENCE&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Five years’ experience of working in development cooperation, proven ability to deliver a suite of development activities in a developing country.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 years’ experience on quality management of similarly large and complex programs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in developing countries is required, preferably in the Asia-Pacific region. Experience of working in Indonesia will be an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in designing and delivering training courses, development of culturally relevant materials and evaluation of the effectiveness of training and capacity building.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EDUCATION&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in Political Science, International Development, or related field preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the education, training and human development sectors in the region.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SKILLS AND KNOWLEDGE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive knowledge of contemporary human resource development strategies, planning and implementation, and the conduct and analysis of training needs assessments/analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven capacity to build and maintain effective relationships with senior personnel in government and donor agencies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written English skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Bahasa Indonesian an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in DFAT format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting &lt;strong&gt;DFAT/AOP/011 MAHKOTA&lt;/strong&gt; in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert(e) Catégorie II – Formateur/rice </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-categorie-ii-formateur-rice</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 09:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-categorie-ii-formateur-rice</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;L’objectif général du présent marché est d’organiser des ateliers d’échange et de formation afin d’améliorer la qualité et l&amp;#39;efficacité de l&amp;#39;aide extérieure de l&amp;#39;Union européenne par rapport à la promotion de l&amp;#39;égalité entre les hommes et les femmes en Algérie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project location&lt;/strong&gt; : Bruxelles, Algiers et mission missions de terrain  dans des zones identifiées avec la Délégation de l’Union européenne.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert(e) Catégorie II – Formateur/rice&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert(e) en genre avec au moins 6 ans d&amp;#39;expérience professionnelle, portant sur la formulation et / ou la mise en œuvre et / ou l&amp;#39;évaluation des projets, programmes et politiques dans le domaine de l&amp;#39;égalité des sexes et l&amp;#39;intégration du genre dans la coopération au développement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elle/Il doit avoir des connaissances et une expérience pertinente dans le domaine des statistiques ventilées par sexe et des indicateurs objectivement vérifiables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elle/Il aura également une expérience en matière d&amp;#39;égalité entre les sexes dans les nouvelles modalités d&amp;#39;aide et doit avoir une connaissance des programmes de coopération de la CE au
développement;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elle/Il doit être d&amp;#39;excellences compétences rédactionnelles et orales en Français ; la connaissance de l’Arabe est un atout&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une ou plusieurs expérience(s) de travail dans plusieurs pays sur la même problématique serait un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une connaissance du contexte socio-culturel de la région et de l’Algérie en particulier sur ces questions serait un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:francesca_giordano@dai.com&quot;&gt;Francesca_Giordano@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Un(E) Expert(E) En Genre et en Matière de Formation des Adultes (Cat. I) (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/une-experte-en-genre-et-en-matiere-de-formation-des-adultes-cat-i-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 08:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/une-experte-en-genre-et-en-matiere-de-formation-des-adultes-cat-i-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;L’objectif général du présent marché est d’organiser des ateliers d’échange et de formation afin d’améliorer la qualité et l&amp;#39;efficacité de l&amp;#39;aide extérieure de l&amp;#39;Union européenne par rapport à la promotion de l&amp;#39;égalité entre les hommes et les femmes en Algérie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project location&lt;/strong&gt;: Bruxelles, Algiers et mission missions de terrain  dans des zones identifiées avec la Délégation de l’Union européenne.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Un(E) Expert(E) En Genre et en Matière de Formation des Adultes (Cat. I) (TL)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spécialiste sur les questions du genre, l&amp;#39;expert(e) doit avec au moins 12 ans d&amp;#39;expérience professionnelle couvrant la formulation et / ou la mise en œuvre et / ou l&amp;#39;évaluation des projets, programmes et politiques dans le domaine de l&amp;#39;égalité des sexes et l&amp;#39;intégration du genre dans la coopération au développement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elle/Il doit avoir des compétences et au moins 6 ans d&amp;#39;expérience en matière de formation des adultes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elle/Il sera familier avec la politique de développement de l&amp;#39;UE et devra avoir une bonne connaissance des programmes de coopération de la CE au développement et des procédures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elle/Il aura au moins 5 ans d&amp;#39;expérience en gestion d&amp;#39;équipe pour des actions similaires &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elle/Il doit être d&amp;#39;excellences compétences rédactionnelles et orales en français ; la connaissance de l’Arabe est un atout&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une ou plusieurs expérience(s) de travail dans plusieurs pays sur la même problématique serait un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une connaissance du contexte socio-culturel de la région et de l’Algérie en particulier sur ces questions serait un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:francesca_giordano@dai.com&quot;&gt;Francesca_Giordano@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Junior experts in Human Rights, Democracy, Anti-Discrimination, International Justice, Peace/Conflict Resolution With Grant Evaluation Experience</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/4-junior-experts-in-human-rights-democracy-anti-discrimination-international-justice-peace-conflict-resolution-with-grant-evaluation-experience</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 08:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/4-junior-experts-in-human-rights-democracy-anti-discrimination-international-justice-peace-conflict-resolution-with-grant-evaluation-experience</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overall duration of the assignment should not exceed 8 months. The duration of the assignment depends on the time of the publication of the Call for Proposals for EIDHR CBSS 2014-2015 and the number of concept notes/full applications to be evaluated from the referenced call.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Junior experts in Human Rights, Democracy, Anti-Discrimination, International Justice, Peace/Conflict Resolution With Grant Evaluation Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education at least up to University degree2 (where a university degree has been awarded on completion of four years study in a university or equivalent institution) in social sciences, law, political science or other related disciplines. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years in the field of human rights, democracy, international relations, economic, political, culture and social rights, anti-discrimination, international justice, peace/conflict resolution, and/or other related disciplines. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 evaluations of grant schemes according to rules and procedures applying to EU external aid contracts financed from EU budget (PRAG rules); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least 1 grant scheme evaluation supporting civil society organisations; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in evaluation of at least 1 grant scheme in the fields of democracy and/or human rights will be considered as an asset &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working in pre-accession countries will be considered as an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of written and spoken English is required. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:francesca_giordano@dai.com&quot;&gt;Francesca_Giordano@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert en Formulation, Montage, Gestion et Evaluation de Projets de Développement (Cat.II) </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-formulation-montage-gestion-et-evaluation-de-projets-de-developpement-catii</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 08:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-formulation-montage-gestion-et-evaluation-de-projets-de-developpement-catii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Evaluer l&amp;#39;efficacité, l&amp;#39;efficience et l&amp;#39;impact des activités du PAMEC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dresser un bilan d’étape de l’exécution du PAMEC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proposer des recommandations opérationnelles pour renforcer l&amp;#39;efficacité, l&amp;#39;efficience et l&amp;#39;impact du PAMEC pour la durée restante du projet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project location&lt;/strong&gt; : Dakar et autres regions du Senegal selons les besoins de l’evaluation et les activities realisees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert en Formulation, Montage, Gestion et Evaluation de Projets de Développement (Cat.II)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; : formation de niveau universitaire et, de préférence post universitaire, en administration publique, droit, gouvernance, sciences sociales, gestion de projet, ou équivalent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience générale&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;au moins six années d&amp;#39;expérience professionnelle dans la formulation, montage, gestion et évaluation de projets de développement ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;bonne connaissance de la gestion du cycle de projet et l&amp;#39;utilisation du cadre logique ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;facilités de communication, excellente capacité de rédaction et de synthèse ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;aptitude à travailler en équipe ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;connaissance des instruments et procédures de l’aide extérieure de l’UE &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;au moins trois années d&amp;#39;expérience en matière de réforme de l’administration publique ou services publics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une expérience de l’Etat civil ou en Afrique subsaharienne sera considéré un atout;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissances linguistiques&lt;/strong&gt; : 
Une parfaite maîtrise du français (écrit et parlé) est requise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:francesca_giordano@dai.com&quot;&gt;Francesca_Giordano@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert en la Formulation, Montage, Gestion Et Evaluation de Projets de Développement </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-la-formulation-montage-gestion-et-evaluation-de-projets-de-developpement</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 08:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-la-formulation-montage-gestion-et-evaluation-de-projets-de-developpement</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Evaluer l&amp;#39;efficacité, l&amp;#39;efficience et l&amp;#39;impact des activités du PAMEC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dresser un bilan d’étape de l’exécution du PAMEC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proposer des recommandations opérationnelles pour renforcer l&amp;#39;efficacité, l&amp;#39;efficience et l&amp;#39;impact du PAMEC pour la durée restante du projet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project location&lt;/strong&gt;: Dakar et autres regions du Senegal selons les besoins de l’evaluation et les activities realisees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert en la Formulation, Montage, Gestion Et Evaluation De Projets De Développement (Cat.I) (TL)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; : formation de niveau universitaire et, de préférence post universitaire, en administration publique, droit, gouvernance, sciences sociales ou équivalent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience générale&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;au moins douze années d&amp;#39;expérience professionnelle dans la formulation, montage, gestion et évaluation de projets de développement ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;bonne connaissance de la gestion du cycle de projet et l&amp;#39;utilisation du cadre logique ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;facilités de communication, excellente capacité de rédaction et de synthèse ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;aptitude à gérer une équipe ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;connaissance des instruments et procédures de l’aide extérieure de l’UE ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;au moins six années d&amp;#39;expérience en matière de réforme de l’administration publique et/ou services publics ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;au moins trois années d&amp;#39;expérience dans le secteur de l’Etat civil ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une expérience de l’Etat civil en Afrique subsaharienne sera considéré un atout;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissances linguistiques&lt;/strong&gt; : 
Une parfaite maîtrise du français (écrit et parlé) est requise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:francesca_giordano@dai.com&quot;&gt;Francesca_Giordano@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert In Decentralisation Support In Africa</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-decentralisation-support-in-africa</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-decentralisation-support-in-africa</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of this assignment is to map out and identify a possible EU  response in support to the &amp;ldquo;Common Programming framework to end drought emergencies -Pillar II Climate Proof Infrastructure&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project location&lt;/strong&gt;: Nairobi, Brussels and field visits in a sample of 4 Asal counties&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert In Decentralisation Support In Africa&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;university degree, preferably at Masters’ degree level or equivalent, in socio economic or a related field of study&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 6 years&amp;#39; experience in support to the local administration/authorities in Africa in the field of rural development programme implementation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 recent assignments (during the last 5 years) of minimum duration of 2 months supporting rural local entities in Kenya&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in rural development programmes &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be fluent in English and Kiswahili.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert in Rural Infrastructure Development Programme (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-rural-infrastructure-development-programme-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 12:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-rural-infrastructure-development-programme-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of this assignment is to map out and identify a possible EU  response in support to the &amp;ldquo;Common Programming framework to end drought emergencies -Pillar II Climate Proof Infrastructure&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project location&lt;/strong&gt;: Nairobi, Brussels and field visits in a sample of 4 Asal counties&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in Rural Infrastructure Development Programme (TL)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree, preferably at Masters’ degree level or equivalent, in agricultural economics, rural development or a related field of study.  A relevant post-graduate degree for this assignment will be favoured;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 12 years&amp;#39; experience in Africa in implementation Rural development programme, Including an infrastructure component;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 years&amp;#39; experience in development programme in arid and semi-arid areas of Africa;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 recent assignments (during the last 5 years) in formulation of programmes of minimum 5M€, in the field of rural development, including infrastructure component;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one of this assignment should have been related to an EU funded programme;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be perfectly fluent in English &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Senior Experts: Cluster Leaders/Chairs of Expert Roundtables</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/7-senior-experts-cluster-leaders-chairs-of-expert-roundtables</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2014 21:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/7-senior-experts-cluster-leaders-chairs-of-expert-roundtables</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project is to gather a critical mass of expertise to stimulate a wider discussion on post-Cotonou issues, and define issues at stake notably for the time horizon 2020-2030. This will be done in the form of expert roundtables around a set of clusters (details of each cluster are provided in the ToR).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HTSPE/DAI are particularly interested in hearing from think-tanks or organisations who can provide a full, highly qualified team.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: until May 2015&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7 Senior Experts: Cluster Leaders/Chairs of Expert Roundtables&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They should have a minimum of 10 years&amp;#39; professional experience in development policy broadly speaking (in an NGO, the private sector, or a political institution). Those 10 years should encompass specific experience in the field relevant to the cluster that the expert is chairing. Strong knowledge of EU activities related to that field would be an asset. Proven ability to work under time constraints is important. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in development studies, political science, economics, law, international relations, European Studies or a related area. A PhD would be an advantage. In absence of the afore-mentioned degrees, equivalent professional experience (e.g. 5 years) in a relevant field will also be considered. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Excellent working knowledge of English is required, and working knowledge of French would be an advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
