<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 15:45:08 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert de Catégorie I </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-de-categorie-i</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 15:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-de-categorie-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identification des obstacles juridiques et reglementaires pouvant entraver la divulgation de la propriete reelle des entreprises extractive&lt;/strong&gt;s&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général&lt;/strong&gt; de la prestation demandée consiste à identifier et diagnostiquer les obstacles juridiques à la divulgation de la propriété réelle des industries extractives au Mali et proposer au Comité de Pilotage de l’ITIE des options juridiques et ou réglementaires pour une divulgation systématique de l’identité des propriétaires réels des entreprises opérant dans le secteur extractif d’ici le 1er janvier 2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif(s) particulier(s)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Faire le diagnostic du cadre juridique, institutionnel et organisationnel et identifier tout obstacle susceptible d’entraver la divulgation des propriétaires réels (PR) des entreprises extractives et leurs sous-traitants&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Définir les données nécessaires à l’identification des PR ainsi que le seuil d’intérêt (% participation) à retenir pour la déclaration de la propriété réelle; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Définir le périmètre de divulgation de la PR conformément aux exigences ITIE (la Norme vise une divulgation pour toutes les entreprises qui soumissionnent, opèrent, ou investissent dans les actifs extractifs) ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Définir les cadres, les mécanismes de collecte et de conservation  des données sur la Propriété Réelle des entreprises assujetties ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assurer la fiabilité des données à divulguer ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Permettre un accès facile aux données sur les Propriétaires Réels.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proposer des sanctions contre  les personnes ou les entreprises qui fournissent délibérément de fausses informations ou qui refusent de fournir des informations demandées dans le délai requis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert de Catégorie I - 50 jours de prestation&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme de troisième cycle universitaire (ou équivalent) en Droit, Gestion des Administrations Publiques, Relations Internationales ou Economie ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 12 ans d&amp;#39;expérience professionnelle en matière de réforme des administrations publiques et révision de cadre réglementaire ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 2 missions d&amp;#39;expertise internationale liée à la mise en place et au respect des normes de l&amp;#39;Initiative pour la Transparence dans les Industries Extractives ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Savoir communiquer, tant à l&amp;#39;oral qu&amp;#39;à l&amp;#39;écrit, avec différentes parties prenantes issues de domaines multisectoriels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une connaissance du Mali et/ou des pays de la sous-région sera considérée comme un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert de Catégorie I (Chef de Mission)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-de-categorie-i-chef-de-mission</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-de-categorie-i-chef-de-mission</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identification des obstacles juridiques et reglementaires pouvant entraver la divulgation de la propriete reelle des entreprises extractives&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général&lt;/strong&gt; de la prestation demandée consiste à identifier et diagnostiquer les obstacles juridiques à la divulgation de la propriété réelle des industries extractives au Mali et proposer au Comité de Pilotage de l’ITIE des options juridiques et ou réglementaires pour une divulgation systématique de l’identité des propriétaires réels des entreprises opérant dans le secteur extractif d’ici le 1er janvier 2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif(s) particulier(s)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Faire le diagnostic du cadre juridique, institutionnel et organisationnel et identifier tout obstacle susceptible d’entraver la divulgation des propriétaires réels (PR) des entreprises extractives et leurs sous-traitants;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Définir les données nécessaires à l’identification des PR ainsi que le seuil d’intérêt (% participation) à retenir pour la déclaration de la propriété réelle ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Définir le périmètre de divulgation de la PR conformément aux exigences ITIE (la Norme vise une divulgation pour toutes les entreprises qui soumissionnent, opèrent, ou investissent dans les actifs extractifs) ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Définir les cadres, les mécanismes de collecte et de conservation  des données sur la Propriété Réelle des entreprises assujetties ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assurer la fiabilité des données à divulguer ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Permettre un accès facile aux données sur les Propriétaires Réels.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proposer des sanctions contre  les personnes ou les entreprises qui fournissent délibérément de fausses informations ou qui refusent de fournir des informations demandées dans le délai requis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert de Catégorie I (Chef de Mission) - 50 jours de prestation&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme de troisième cycle universitaire (ou équivalent) en Droit, Gestion des Administrations Publiques, Relations Internationales ou Economie ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 12 ans d&amp;#39;expérience professionnelle en matière de réforme des administrations publiques et révision de cadre réglementaire ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 4 missions d&amp;#39;expertise internationale liées à la mise en place et au respect des normes de l&amp;#39;Initiative pour la Transparence dans les Industries Extractives ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise avérée du vocabulaire juridique et excellentes capacités rédactionnelles en français ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonne capacité d’analyse de contexte et de modération d’atelier ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une connaissance du Mali et/ou des pays de la sous-région sera considérée comme un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATION&lt;/strong&gt;S&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Veterinary Doctor </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/veterinary-doctor</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/veterinary-doctor</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assessment Mission on Animal Health in Timor Leste&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;
The objective of the Framework Contract is to support MAF in developing of long term plan to control animal diseases in partnerships with development partners and neighbouring countries (Indonesia, Australia). The current assignment is to assess the current situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Objectives&lt;/strong&gt;
The Framework Contractor is required to assess the animal health services currently provided by government (MAF) and private veterinarians. The
Framework Contractor will provide a general assessment of the livestock sector with recommendations toward on integrated whole-of-Timor control programme. The assessment will include an overview of Development Partners actions regarding animal health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Veterinary Doctor&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Category I Expert with at least a Master Degree in Animal Production / Science / Veterinary Science or equivalent and at least 12-year of proven relevant professional experience or equivalent professional experience of at least 15 years1 in the sector, if the candidate does not possess a Master Degree relevant to Lot No. 1.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 previous professional experiences similar to this assignment, in particular the evaluation of the performance of veterinary services.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 professional experiences in the coordination with multi-donor environment and assessment of Development Partners&amp;#39; interventions in the livestock sector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 missions to analyse national veterinary services in ACP beneficiaries&amp;#39; countries and or the in the APAC region (APAC: Australia, Bangladesh, Cambodia, China, Fiji, French Polynesia, Guam, Hong Kong, India, Japan, South Korea, Laos, Malaysia, Micronesia, Myanmar, New Zealand, Pakistan, Singapore, Taiwan, Thailand and Vietnam.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language Skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in written and spoken Portuguese;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Desired Assets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous working experience in Asia;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of English and Bahasa&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note that civil servants and other staff of the public administration of the beneficiary country cannot be proposed as experts, unless prior written approval has been obtained from the European Commission.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert sectoriel </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-sectoriel</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 20:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-sectoriel</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Évaluation à mi-parcours du Programme d’appui à la diversification de l’économie – Secteur pêche (DIVECO 2)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dans un but d&amp;#39;accompagner la mise en oeuvre effective des plans de réforme du secteur de la pêche et de l&amp;#39;aquaculture en Algérie, l&amp;#39;Union européenne et l&amp;#39;Etat Algérien ont convenu de lancer un Programme d’appui à la diversification de l’économie &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Secteur pêche (DIVECO 2)&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Le programme DIVECO 2 a fait l’objet d’une Convention de financement (CF) signée entre l’Union européenne et le représentant du gouvernement algérien le 19 décembre 2013.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Son financement est assuré par l’Union européenne à concurrence de 15 millions d’euros, dont 11 millions d&amp;#39;euros pour des marchés de services, 1,5 millions d&amp;#39;euros pour des marchés de fournitures et 1 million d&amp;#39;euros pour des subventions. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général&lt;/strong&gt; du projet DIVECO 2 est de contribuer à rendre l’économie algérienne plus diversifiée et moins dépendante des hydrocarbures. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; est d&amp;#39;augmenter la contribution du secteur de la pêche et de l’aquaculture à la diversification de l’économie algérienne par le développement durable et en améliorant les performances économiques. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les résultats du programme portent sur : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;R1. Le renforcement des capacités d&amp;#39;encadrement et de gestion des institutions publiques &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;R2. La promotion et la valorisation des filières &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;R3. Le renforcement des capacités des organisations professionnelles &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les activités du projet prévues dans la Convention de financement pour l&amp;#39;atteinte de ces résultats sont reprises dans le tableau à l&amp;#39;annexe VI. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La Convention de financement prévoit également le lancement d&amp;#39;un appel à propositions afin de renforcement les groupements de professionnels et leur organisation en réseau au sein du résultat 3. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sur le plan de la gestion, le programme dispose d’une Direction nationale sous la responsabilité d’un Directeur national de programme (DNP). La Direction du projet et les bénéficiaires sont assistés par une Unité d’appui du programme (UAP) constituée d’experts nationaux et internationaux. La Direction du projet et l’UAP sont basées à Alger, au sein de la Direction générale de la pêche et de l&amp;#39;aquaculture du MADRP. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les organes d&amp;#39;appui à la mise en oeuvre du projet (comités) sont : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;un comité de pilotage &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;un comité de suivi. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Le comité de pilotage se réunissent avec une cadence d&amp;#39;une réunion par an minimum, et intègrent, outre la Délégation de l’Union européenne et les principales parties prenantes nationales du programme (voir ci-dessus), d’autres ministères clé tels que le Ministère des Affaires Etrangères. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Un volet dédié au suivi, évaluation externe et audit du projet est aussi prévu. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 zones pilotes ont été désignées par le Ministère pour la mise en oeuvre des activités, il s&amp;#39;agit des wilayas d&amp;#39;Aïn Temouchent, Skikda et Setif. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La durée initiale de la période de mise en oeuvre du projet est de 4 ans à compte de la date de signature de la Convention de financement (19 décembre 2013). Celle-ci a été prolongée d&amp;#39;un an par le biais d&amp;#39;un avenant à la Convention de financement signé le 29 août 2016. A cette période suivra une phase de clôture de 2 ans qui se rendra nécessaire pour la clôture comptable et la réalisation des dernières activités prévues dans la Convention de financement (évaluation et audit finaux si nécessaire). Sur cette base, la date de fin de la période de mise en oeuvre du projet est le 18 décembre 2018. La date limite de signature de tous les contrats mettant en oeuvre la convention était le 18 décembre 2016. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Un deuxième avenant à la Convention de financement a été signé le 24 novembre 2016 ayant pour but de réallouer le budget dédié aux subventions (1 millions d&amp;#39;euros) vers la rubrique services, et ce suite à l&amp;#39;issue infructueuse de l’appel à propositions EuropeAid/152641/DD/ACT/DZ lancé dans le cadre du R3 du projet (voir ci-dessus).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert sectoriel&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;Catégorie II, 6 ans&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formation&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Il/elle doit avoir un diplôme de niveau Master. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;En l&amp;#39;absence de diplôme niveau Master, une expérience professionnelle additionnelle de 3 ans dans un ou plusieurs domaines d&amp;#39;intervention du projet (cfr. résultats du projet) est requise. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Avoir au moins 6 ans et préférablement 9 ans d’expérience professionnelle dans un ou plusieurs domaines d&amp;#39;intervention du projet (cfr. résultats du projet). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;a) Expérience considérée comme indispensable&lt;/strong&gt; : 
Avoir une expérience confirmée dans la gestion des actions de développement dans les domaines d&amp;#39;intervention du projet (au moins dix (10) interventions en lien avec les thèmes abordés par le projet, cfr. résultats du projet). 
Avoir participé à au moins deux missions d’évaluation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;b) Expériences considérées comme des atouts supplémentaires&lt;/strong&gt; : 
Avoir été membre d&amp;#39;une équipe d&amp;#39;assistance technique pour la mise en oeuvre d&amp;#39;une politique nationale de pêche ou d&amp;#39;aquaculture .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef de mission, Expert évaluateur </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-expert-evaluateur</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-expert-evaluateur</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Évaluation à mi-parcours du Programme d’appui à la diversification de l’économie – Secteur pêche (DIVECO 2)
*&lt;/em&gt;
Dans un but d&amp;#39;accompagner la mise en oeuvre effective des plans de réforme du secteur de la pêche et de l&amp;#39;aquaculture en Algérie, l&amp;#39;Union européenne et l&amp;#39;Etat Algérien ont convenu de lancer un Programme d’appui à la diversification de l’économie &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Secteur pêche (DIVECO 2)&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Le programme DIVECO 2 a fait l’objet d’une Convention de financement (CF) signée entre l’Union européenne et le représentant du gouvernement algérien le 19 décembre 2013.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Son financement est assuré par l’Union européenne à concurrence de 15 millions d’euros, dont 11 millions d&amp;#39;euros pour des marchés de services, 1,5 millions d&amp;#39;euros pour des marchés de fournitures et 1 million d&amp;#39;euros pour des subventions. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général&lt;/strong&gt; du projet DIVECO 2 est de contribuer à rendre l’économie algérienne plus diversifiée et moins dépendante des hydrocarbures. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; est d&amp;#39;augmenter la contribution du secteur de la pêche et de l’aquaculture à la diversification de l’économie algérienne par le développement durable et en améliorant les performances économiques. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les résultats du programme portent sur : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;R1&lt;/strong&gt;. Le renforcement des capacités d&amp;#39;encadrement et de gestion des institutions publiques 
&lt;strong&gt;R2&lt;/strong&gt;. La promotion et la valorisation des filières 
&lt;strong&gt;R3&lt;/strong&gt;. Le renforcement des capacités des organisations professionnelles &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les activités du projet prévues dans la Convention de financement pour l&amp;#39;atteinte de ces résultats sont reprises dans le tableau à l&amp;#39;annexe VI. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La Convention de financement prévoit également le lancement d&amp;#39;un appel à propositions afin de renforcement les groupements de professionnels et leur organisation en réseau au sein du résultat 3. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sur le plan de la gestion, le programme dispose d’une Direction nationale sous la responsabilité d’un Directeur national de programme (DNP). La Direction du projet et les bénéficiaires sont assistés par une Unité d’appui du programme (UAP) constituée d’experts nationaux et internationaux. La Direction du projet et l’UAP sont basées à Alger, au sein de la Direction générale de la pêche et de l&amp;#39;aquaculture du MADRP. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les organes d&amp;#39;appui à la mise en oeuvre du projet (comités) sont : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;un comité de pilotage &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;un comité de suivi. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Le comité de pilotage se réunissent avec une cadence d&amp;#39;une réunion par an minimum, et intègrent, outre la Délégation de l’Union européenne et les principales parties prenantes nationales du programme (voir ci-dessus), d’autres ministères clé tels que le Ministère des Affaires Etrangères. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Un volet dédié au suivi, évaluation externe et audit du projet est aussi prévu. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 zones pilotes ont été désignées par le Ministère pour la mise en oeuvre des activités, il s&amp;#39;agit des wilayas d&amp;#39;Aïn Temouchent, Skikda et Setif. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La durée initiale de la période de mise en oeuvre du projet est de 4 ans à compte de la date de signature de la Convention de financement (19 décembre 2013). Celle-ci a été prolongée d&amp;#39;un an par le biais d&amp;#39;un avenant à la Convention de financement signé le 29 août 2016. A cette période suivra une phase de clôture de 2 ans qui se rendra nécessaire pour la clôture comptable et la réalisation des dernières activités prévues dans la Convention de financement (évaluation et audit finaux si nécessaire). Sur cette base, la date de fin de la période de mise en oeuvre du projet est le 18 décembre 2018. La date limite de signature de tous les contrats mettant en oeuvre la convention était le 18 décembre 2016. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Un deuxième avenant à la Convention de financement a été signé le 24 novembre 2016 ayant pour but de réallouer le budget dédié aux subventions (1 millions d&amp;#39;euros) vers la rubrique services, et ce suite à l&amp;#39;issue infructueuse de l’appel à propositions EuropeAid/152641/DD/ACT/DZ lancé dans le cadre du R3 du projet (voir ci-dessus).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chef de mission, Expert évaluateur&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Catégorie I, 12 ans&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formation&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Il/elle doit avoir un diplôme de niveau Master. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;En l&amp;#39;absence de diplôme niveau Master, une expérience professionnelle additionnelle de 3 ans dans un ou plusieurs domaines d&amp;#39;intervention du projet (cfr. résultats du projet) est requise. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Avoir au moins 12 ans et préférablement 15 ans d’expérience professionnelle dans le secteur de la coopération au développement. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;a) Expérience considérée comme indispensable&lt;/strong&gt; : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir une (1) expérience confirmée dans la coordination et l’encadrement d&amp;#39;équipes dans le cadre des projets de coopération au développement (avoir été chef d’équipe ou chef de mission dans au moins trois (3) missions ou contrats d&amp;#39;assistance technique) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir participé à au moins trois (3) missions d’évaluation. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;b) Expériences considérées comme des atouts supplémentaires&lt;/strong&gt; : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir été formateur dans le cycle du projet et la gestion du cadre logique des projets &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir participé à des missions ou des projets portant sur les thématiques de la protection de l&amp;#39;environnement &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir participé à des missions ou des projets intégrant l&amp;#39;analyse de l&amp;#39;intégration des aspects d&amp;#39;égalité des chances hommes/femmes. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Langues *&lt;/em&gt;
Parfaite maîtrise de la langue française.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Rural Development/Agriculture (Cat. I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-rural-development-agriculture-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-rural-development-agriculture-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final evaluation of the Programme AIESRP (Apoyo a la Integracion Economica del Sector Rural Paraguayo)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;objective of this assignment&lt;/strong&gt; is to conduct a Final Evaluation of the AIESRP (Apoyo a la integration Economica del Sector Exportador Paraguayo), a programme that aimed at supporting local producers while strengthening local Institutions and Public-private, public-public relations. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Rural Development/Agriculture (Cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education: Degree in Rural Development, Rural Administration, Veterinary, Agro-economics or related fields&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Postgraduate Degree in Agricultural and Husbandry Sciences will be an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Language: Spanish (Native level, C2), English (Proficient, C1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific knowledge of agri-food chains competitiveness or economic diversification will be an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6 years of relevant experience in economic and rural development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 years of professional experience in Institutional strengthening&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 years of experience in value chain development, partnerships with the private sector, economic regional integration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid experience in formulation, implementation and evaluation of EU cooperation programmes, as well as with the logical framework methodology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proved relevant experience in Latin America, and in particular Paraguay, would be a distinct advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thai-speaking Social Development/ CSO Expert (Category II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/thai-speaking-social-development-cso-expert-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 14:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/thai-speaking-social-development-cso-expert-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support Measures in Strengthening Capacity of CSOs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Provide technical assistance in strengthening capacity of CSOs to be more efficient in participating in country&amp;rsquo;s development process in attaining Thailand&amp;rsquo;s Sustainable Development Goals particularly in the context of the EU CSOs Roadmap for the benefit of CSOs communities in Thailand at large.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thai-speaking Social Development/ CSO Expert (Category II)&lt;/strong&gt; – &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced university degree (minimum Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree) in social sciences fields relevant to development, certified by a Diploma (or equivalent professional experience of at least 8 years if candidate does not possess an advanced university degree.)9; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;S/he must possess facilitation, communication skills, and excellent command of oral and written English; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer literacy (minimum MS Word, PowerPoint, Excel). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of professional experience in design, formulation, project management, supporting civil society (e.g. grant project, capacity development, direct support to networks, facilitation of policy dialogue). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of proven professional experience in organisation and facilitation of consultation sessions for multi - stakeholders&amp;#39; dialogues including CSOs, academic, think tanks organisations and public authorities. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 1 working experience with CSOs in at least 1 ASEAN country; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 1 assignment associated with CSOs engagements in the implementation and or monitoring of SDGs; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WORKING KNOWLEDGE OF THAI IS COMPULSORY&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&quot;&gt;gabriela_Georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Project Management Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/financial-project-management-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/financial-project-management-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Civil Society and Local Authorities (CSO-LA) in Development Programme Monitoring in Armenia 2018-2019&lt;/strong&gt;
 
&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt; 
  
The 2016 CSO-LA allocation for Armenia will result in a handful contracts that will need support in their launch phase (first six months) to be implemented in an effective and sound manner and in identifying and planning synergies between the projects. At the same time, the EU Delegation is looking for monitoring support that will identify shortcomings, challenges and concerns related to management of the CSO-LA portfolio in Armenia.&lt;br&gt;
 
The global objective of this assignment is to contribute to the effective implementation of the selected projects and monitoring projects against the overall CSO-LA portfolio objectives and effective project management. 
 
*&lt;em&gt;Specific objective(s) *&lt;/em&gt;
  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; 1)  monitor and provide quality information on the pace of projects implementation to the EU Delegation through monitoring the project preparations, planning, technical expertise and implementation of specific activities, including mandatory sub-granting, with an overall attention to their impact on Armenian citizens&amp;#39; lives taking into account their opinions and views;
 &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; 2) provide technical assistance to the individual projects on overall and specific implementation issues related to financial and operational efficiency, effectiveness, impact and sound financial management of EU funds. Provide guidance and good practices on i.a. financial transparency in grant management, (purchases and HR documenting, archiving, accounting etc.) as well as support the projects in their initial operational and financial report preparations as well as quality compliance before report submissions; Finally in grant management, identify and advice on synergies between the CSO-LA projects. 
 &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; 3) advise on project-specific and joint communication activities that would make EU support to local governance, expansion of outdoor activities, and investments in rural and tourism development more visible and attractive to Armenian citizens.
 
The priority of tasks is very likely to reflect the order of presentation 1-3. 
 
&lt;strong&gt;Requested services&lt;/strong&gt;
 
All services must be planned and conducted in close collaboration with the EU Delegation. All in-country activities will require prior approval incl. mission dates (6 in-country missions are foreseen), in-country monitoring, support, and training activities. 
 
** 1.   Monitor the implementation of the projects, including****:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the project management structure, baseline data collection, technical capacity, work plans, administrative management and the overall effectiveness;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the financial management arrangements, financial effectiveness, and the arrangements in place for financial support to third parties, and adherence to EU grant regulations,  by the contractor and other project partners if relevant;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess and advice on procurement and transfer of the equipment arrangements;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the efficiency of the project implementation as to how well work processes are carried out to produce expected results;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the potential impact of activities on target groups and direct beneficiaries, which would include gathering their opinion and views on the relevance, sustainability and contribution to lasting capacity development;
 &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Quality assurance and support to project management and implementation&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess and ensure that opportunities of citizens involvement and ownership, gender equality and youth empowerment and the contractor&amp;rsquo;s collaboration with project partners and stakeholders, are seriously pursued and maximised:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct mock (=test) reporting exercises for each of the project (some aspects can be joint) after 6 and 9 months of implementation; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess and analyse practical aspects (calls, selection criteria, monitoring and reporting plans) related to financial support to third parties;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify issues of concern, share these with the contractors and suggest solutions to challenges;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Based on feedback from projects and the EU Delegation, prepare a training plan and implement jointly agreed activities;
 
&lt;strong&gt;3.    Communication and visibility:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess and propose improvements to planned/suggested communication and visibility activities to ensure that they are interesting, engaging, empowering and effective communication tools;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify communication and visibility activities that involve the EU delegation and/or could be utilised beyond the project;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess and suggest joint communication activities e.g. documentaries, exhibitions etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 3 – Financial Project Management Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree or equivalent academic qualifications in financial management, business administration, audit or a closely related field
Or&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of relevant professional experience (as defined below) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to analyze financial data and recommend appropriate actions and to prepare reporting documents &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and facilitation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent in spoken and written English and Armenian&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in financial monitoring/consultancy/audit in the field is required, financial monitoring of EC grant projects is an advantage &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive knowledge of principles, regulations and practices of accounting and financial management including those in Armenia &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of EC financial and contractual rules &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:anju_english@dai.com&quot;&gt;anju_english@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 2 – Local Governance, Citizens Empowerment and Participation Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-local-governance-citizens-empowerment-and-participation-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-local-governance-citizens-empowerment-and-participation-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Civil Society and Local Authorities (CSO-LA) in Development Programme Monitoring in Armenia 2018-2019&lt;/strong&gt;
 
&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt; 
     
The 2016 CSO-LA allocation for Armenia will result in a handful contracts that will need support in their launch phase (first six months) to be implemented in an effective and sound manner and in identifying and planning synergies between the projects. At the same time, the EU Delegation is looking for monitoring support that will identify shortcomings, challenges and concerns related to management of the CSO-LA portfolio in Armenia.&lt;br&gt;
 
The global objective of this assignment is to contribute to the effective implementation of the selected projects and monitoring projects against the overall CSO-LA portfolio objectives and effective project management. 
 
*&lt;em&gt;Specific objective(s) *&lt;/em&gt;
  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; 1)  monitor and provide quality information on the pace of projects implementation to the EU Delegation through monitoring the project preparations, planning, technical expertise and implementation of specific activities, including mandatory sub-granting, with an overall attention to their impact on Armenian citizens&amp;#39; lives taking into account their opinions and views;
 &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; 2) provide technical assistance to the individual projects on overall and specific implementation issues related to financial and operational efficiency, effectiveness, impact and sound financial management of EU funds. Provide guidance and good practices on i.a. financial transparency in grant management, (purchases and HR documenting, archiving, accounting etc.) as well as support the projects in their initial operational and financial report preparations as well as quality compliance before report submissions; Finally in grant management, identify and advice on synergies between the CSO-LA projects. 
 &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; 3) advise on project-specific and joint communication activities that would make EU support to local governance, expansion of outdoor activities, and investments in rural and tourism development more visible and attractive to Armenian citizens.
 
The priority of tasks is very likely to reflect the order of presentation 1-3. 
 
&lt;strong&gt;Requested services&lt;/strong&gt;
 
All services must be planned and conducted in close collaboration with the EU Delegation. All in-country activities will require prior approval incl. mission dates (6 in-country missions are foreseen), in-country monitoring, support, and training activities. 
 
** 1.   Monitor the implementation of the projects, including****:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the project management structure, baseline data collection, technical capacity, work plans, administrative management and the overall effectiveness;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the financial management arrangements, financial effectiveness, and the arrangements in place for financial support to third parties, and adherence to EU grant regulations,  by the contractor and other project partners if relevant;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess and advice on procurement and transfer of the equipment arrangements;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the efficiency of the project implementation as to how well work processes are carried out to produce expected results;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the potential impact of activities on target groups and direct beneficiaries, which would include gathering their opinion and views on the relevance, sustainability and contribution to lasting capacity development;
 &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Quality assurance and support to project management and implementation&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess and ensure that opportunities of citizens involvement and ownership, gender equality and youth empowerment and the contractor&amp;rsquo;s collaboration with project partners and stakeholders, are seriously pursued and maximised:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct mock (=test) reporting exercises for each of the project (some aspects can be joint) after 6 and 9 months of implementation; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess and analyse practical aspects (calls, selection criteria, monitoring and reporting plans) related to financial support to third parties;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify issues of concern, share these with the contractors and suggest solutions to challenges;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Based on feedback from projects and the EU Delegation, prepare a training plan and implement jointly agreed activities;
 
&lt;strong&gt;3.    Communication and visibility:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess and propose improvements to planned/suggested communication and visibility activities to ensure that they are interesting, engaging, empowering and effective communication tools;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify communication and visibility activities that involve the EU delegation and/or could be utilised beyond the project;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess and suggest joint communication activities e.g. documentaries, exhibitions etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2 – Local Governance, Citizens Empowerment and Participation Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree or equivalent academic qualifications in social sciences, rural development, anthropology or any other discipline relevant to the assignment
Or&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of relevant professional experience (as defined below) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and facilitation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent in spoken and written English and Armenian and/or Russian&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth understanding of the national and regional economic, political and administrative structures and citizens engagement, including of women and youth, in these processes in Armenia is essential;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in community-led local development in other countries than Armenia and innovative approaches to citizens engagement;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowledge of regional/Marz and community development planning, income generation and opportunities linked to tourism, cultural and outdoor activity resources/potentials in Armenia;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proven ability in managing and/or monitoring development projects funded by the EU or other donors at the local level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:anju_english@dai.com&quot;&gt;anju_english@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader and Senior Rural/Community Development Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-and-senior-rural-community-development-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-and-senior-rural-community-development-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Civil Society and Local Authorities (CSO-LA) in Development Programme Monitoring in Armenia 2018-2019&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt; 
 
The 2016 CSO-LA allocation for Armenia will result in a handful contracts that will need support in their launch phase (first six months) to be implemented in an effective and sound manner and in identifying and planning synergies between the projects. At the same time, the EU Delegation is looking for monitoring support that will identify shortcomings, challenges and concerns related to management of the CSO-LA portfolio in Armenia.     &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to contribute to the effective implementation of the selected projects and monitoring projects against the overall CSO-LA portfolio objectives and effective project management. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Specific objective(s) *&lt;/em&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1)  monitor and provide quality information on the pace of projects implementation to the EU Delegation through monitoring the project preparations, planning, technical expertise and implementation of specific activities, including mandatory sub-granting, with an overall attention to their impact on Armenian citizens&amp;#39; lives taking into account their opinions and views;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2) provide technical assistance to the individual projects on overall and specific implementation issues related to financial and operational efficiency, effectiveness, impact and sound financial management of EU funds. Provide guidance and good practices on i.a. financial transparency in grant management, (purchases and HR documenting, archiving, accounting etc.) as well as support the projects in their initial operational and financial report preparations as well as quality compliance before report submissions; Finally in grant management, identify and advice on synergies between the CSO-LA projects. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3) advise on project-specific and joint communication activities that would make EU support to local governance, expansion of outdoor activities, and investments in rural and tourism development more visible and attractive to Armenian citizens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The priority of tasks is very likely to reflect the order of presentation 1-3. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requested services&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All services must be planned and conducted in close collaboration with the EU Delegation. All in-country activities will require prior approval incl. mission dates (6 in-country missions are foreseen), in-country monitoring, support, and training activities. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;** 1.   Monitor the implementation of the projects, including****:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the project management structure, baseline data collection, technical capacity, work plans, administrative management and the overall effectiveness;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the financial management arrangements, financial effectiveness, and the arrangements in place for financial support to third parties, and adherence to EU grant regulations,  by the contractor and other project partners if relevant;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess and advice on procurement and transfer of the equipment arrangements;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the efficiency of the project implementation as to how well work processes are carried out to produce expected results;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the potential impact of activities on target groups and direct beneficiaries, which would include gathering their opinion and views on the relevance, sustainability and contribution to lasting capacity development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Quality assurance and support to project management and implementation&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess and ensure that opportunities of citizens involvement and ownership, gender equality and youth empowerment and the contractor&amp;rsquo;s collaboration with project partners and stakeholders, are seriously pursued and maximised:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct mock (=test) reporting exercises for each of the project (some aspects can be joint) after 6 and 9 months of implementation; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess and analyse practical aspects (calls, selection criteria, monitoring and reporting plans) related to financial support to third parties;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify issues of concern, share these with the contractors and suggest solutions to challenges;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Based on feedback from projects and the EU Delegation, prepare a training plan and implement jointly agreed activities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3.    Communication and visibility:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess and propose improvements to planned/suggested communication and visibility activities to ensure that they are interesting, engaging, empowering and effective communication tools;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify communication and visibility activities that involve the EU delegation and/or could be utilised beyond the project;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess and suggest joint communication activities e.g. documentaries, exhibitions etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 1 – Team Leader and Senior Rural/Community Development Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree or equivalent academic qualifications in social sciences, economics or any other discipline relevant to the assignment
Or&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of relevant professional experience (as defined below) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and facilitation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of written and spoken English and report writing
Specific Professional Experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with the EC CSO-LA instrument and/or community-led local development, citizens empowerment and poverty reduction through civil society grant instruments;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound management experience in programs of rural/regional social and economic development, promotion of tourism, outdoor and cultural activities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some knowledge of the current socio-economic context of the Eastern Neighbourhood and Western Balkan region, especially challenges related to local development and decentralisation as well as impact-oriented community and citizens empowerment;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitoring, training, coaching and capacity building experience is required;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:anju_english@dai.com&quot;&gt;anju_english@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Analyst  </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/data-analyst</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/data-analyst</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Study on agriculture based on quantitative model and quantitative &amp;amp; qualitative indicators&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the present assignment is to contribute to the development of effective policy formulation tools, based on modelling tools that can be used by the Government of Armenia GoA for development and regular updating of the policy implemented in the field of agriculture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the present assignment is to develop a modelling tool for Armenia covering: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;main macro-economic data, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;demographic data, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;main agricultural markets, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;agricultural goods grown or processed in Armenia (focus on a number of products to be further defined with the EU Delegation and Ministry of Agriculture of Armenia and EU Del) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Information on areas harvested, yields, animal numbers, production, domestic use, stocks, exports, imports as well as the associated prices, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;main characteristics of Armenia’s agricultural commodity markets, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;adjustable policy tools, including taxation, price support measures, production quota, trade protection measures, etc. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possibility to make projections for 15 years based on the collected baseline data. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requested services&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; The contractor will propose a country market model (based on MSs and/or ENI region). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The proposed model should be adapted to cover requirements of Armenia and to cover all main agricultural markets that will be further defined with the Ministry of Agriculture of Armenia. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The contractor will provide and install an electronic version of the developed model in computers of institutions that will be indicated at a later stage by the Ministry of Agriculture of Armenia. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A manual will be provided on the model and its operation/application. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quantitative &amp;amp; qualitative analysis of local agriculture policy &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Training sessions will be provided for representatives of the Government of Armenia and other stakeholders on the model and its implementation/operation. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The model will be run by the contractor in order to obtain a 15 year projections and scenarios. Based on the provided model projections, a revision of the agriculture policy implemented by the Government of Armenia should be proposed and recommendations for the improvement of future EU support to the agricultural sector should be provided to EUD Armenia.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 5 – Data Analyst&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree or equivalent academic qualification in business management, economics, statistics or other disciplines related to economic development or socioeconomic analysis or at least 15 years of relevant professional experience (as defined below) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication (oral and written) and coordination skills are required &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of English and Armenian &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;: Professional experience in quantitative market analysis, data analysis, statistical analysis, economic analysis. Professional experience in quantitative analysis of agricultural sector would be an asset. Knowledge of the agricultural sector in Armenia would be an asset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&quot;&gt;gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agricultural Economist </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/agricultural-economist</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 16:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/agricultural-economist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Study on agriculture based on quantitative model and quantitative &amp;amp; qualitative indicators&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the present assignment is to contribute to the development of effective policy formulation tools, based on modelling tools that can be used by the Government of Armenia GoA for development and regular updating of the policy implemented in the field of agriculture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the present assignment is to develop a modelling tool for Armenia covering: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;main macro-economic data, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;demographic data, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;main agricultural markets, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;agricultural goods grown or processed in Armenia (focus on a number of products to be further defined with the EU Delegation and Ministry of Agriculture of Armenia and EU Del) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Information on areas harvested, yields, animal numbers, production, domestic use, stocks, exports, imports as well as the associated prices, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;main characteristics of Armenia’s agricultural commodity markets, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;adjustable policy tools, including taxation, price support measures, production quota, trade protection measures, etc. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possibility to make projections for 15 years based on the collected baseline data. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requested services&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; The contractor will propose a country market model (based on MSs and/or ENI region). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The proposed model should be adapted to cover requirements of Armenia and to cover all main agricultural markets that will be further defined with the Ministry of Agriculture of Armenia. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The contractor will provide and install an electronic version of the developed model in computers of institutions that will be indicated at a later stage by the Ministry of Agriculture of Armenia. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A manual will be provided on the model and its operation/application. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quantitative &amp;amp; qualitative analysis of local agriculture policy &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Training sessions will be provided for representatives of the Government of Armenia and other stakeholders on the model and its implementation/operation. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The model will be run by the contractor in order to obtain a 15 year projections and scenarios. Based on the provided model projections, a revision of the agriculture policy implemented by the Government of Armenia should be proposed and recommendations for the improvement of future EU support to the agricultural sector should be provided to EUD Armenia.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 4 – Agricultural Economist&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master equivalent academic qualification in agricultural economics or other disciplines related to economic development or at least 15 years of relevant professional experience (as defined below) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication (oral and written) and coordination skills are required &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of English and Armenian &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;: Professional experience in implementation of agricultural sector researches and studies, participation in technical assistance projects aimed at development of agribusiness sector, economic analysis. Experience with implementation of market outlook models would be an asset. Knowledge of the agricultural sector in Armenia would be an asset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&quot;&gt;gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Socioeconomic Analyst/ Macroeconomic Expert </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/socioeconomic-analyst-macroeconomic-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 16:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/socioeconomic-analyst-macroeconomic-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Study on agriculture based on quantitative model and quantitative &amp;amp; qualitative indicators&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the present assignment is to contribute to the development of effective policy formulation tools, based on modelling tools that can be used by the Government of Armenia GoA for development and regular updating of the policy implemented in the field of agriculture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the present assignment is to develop a modelling tool for Armenia covering: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;main macro-economic data, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;demographic data, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;main agricultural markets, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;agricultural goods grown or processed in Armenia (focus on a number of products to be further defined with the EU Delegation and Ministry of Agriculture of Armenia and EU Del) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Information on areas harvested, yields, animal numbers, production, domestic use, stocks, exports, imports as well as the associated prices, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;main characteristics of Armenia’s agricultural commodity markets, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;adjustable policy tools, including taxation, price support measures, production quota, trade protection measures, etc. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possibility to make projections for 15 years based on the collected baseline data. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requested services&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; The contractor will propose a country market model (based on MSs and/or ENI region). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The proposed model should be adapted to cover requirements of Armenia and to cover all main agricultural markets that will be further defined with the Ministry of Agriculture of Armenia. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The contractor will provide and install an electronic version of the developed model in computers of institutions that will be indicated at a later stage by the Ministry of Agriculture of Armenia. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A manual will be provided on the model and its operation/application. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quantitative &amp;amp; qualitative analysis of local agriculture policy &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Training sessions will be provided for representatives of the Government of Armenia and other stakeholders on the model and its implementation/operation. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The model will be run by the contractor in order to obtain a 15 year projections and scenarios. Based on the provided model projections, a revision of the agriculture policy implemented by the Government of Armenia should be proposed and recommendations for the improvement of future EU support to the agricultural sector should be provided to EUD Armenia.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 3 –Socioeconomic Analyst/ Macroeconomic Expert&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree or equivalent academic qualification in economics or other disciplines related to economic development and socioeconomic analysis or at least 15 years of relevant professional experience (as defined below) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication (oral and written) and coordination skills are required &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of English. Knowledge of Armenian will be an asset &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;: Professional experience in macroeconomic analysis, statistical data collection and analysis, sector analysis, including studies of agricultural value chain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&quot;&gt;gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>International Modelling Expert </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/international-modelling-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/international-modelling-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Study on agriculture based on quantitative model and quantitative &amp;amp; qualitative indicators&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the present assignment is to contribute to the development of effective policy formulation tools, based on modelling tools that can be used by the Government of Armenia GoA for development and regular updating of the policy implemented in the field of agriculture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the present assignment is to develop a modelling tool for Armenia covering: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;main macro-economic data, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;demographic data, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;main agricultural markets, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;agricultural goods grown or processed in Armenia (focus on a number of products to be further defined with the EU Delegation and Ministry of Agriculture of Armenia and EU Del) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Information on areas harvested, yields, animal numbers, production, domestic use, stocks, exports, imports as well as the associated prices, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;main characteristics of Armenia’s agricultural commodity markets, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;adjustable policy tools, including taxation, price support measures, production quota, trade protection measures, etc. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possibility to make projections for 15 years based on the collected baseline data. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requested services&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; The contractor will propose a country market model (based on MSs and/or ENI region). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The proposed model should be adapted to cover requirements of Armenia and to cover all main agricultural markets that will be further defined with the Ministry of Agriculture of Armenia. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The contractor will provide and install an electronic version of the developed model in computers of institutions that will be indicated at a later stage by the Ministry of Agriculture of Armenia. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A manual will be provided on the model and its operation/application. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quantitative &amp;amp; qualitative analysis of local agriculture policy &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Training sessions will be provided for representatives of the Government of Armenia and other stakeholders on the model and its implementation/operation. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The model will be run by the contractor in order to obtain a 15 year projections and scenarios. Based on the provided model projections, a revision of the agriculture policy implemented by the Government of Armenia should be proposed and recommendations for the improvement of future EU support to the agricultural sector should be provided to EUD Armenia. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2 – International Modelling Expert&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree or equivalent academic qualification in business management, economics, statistics or other disciplines related to economic development or at least 15 years of relevant professional experience (as defined below) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication (oral and written) and coordination skills are required &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of English &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;: Professional experience in the development and calibration of general and sectorial econometric models.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&quot;&gt;gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 1 – International team leader - Expert in agriculture or quantitative analysis </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-1-international-team-leader-expert-in-agriculture-or-quantitative-analysis</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 11:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-1-international-team-leader-expert-in-agriculture-or-quantitative-analysis</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Study on agriculture based on quantitative model and quantitative &amp;amp; qualitative indicators&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the present assignment is to contribute to the development of effective policy formulation tools, based on modelling tools that can be used by the Government of Armenia GoA for development and regular updating of the policy implemented in the field of agriculture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the present assignment is to develop a modelling tool for Armenia covering: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;main macro-economic data, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;demographic data, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;main agricultural markets, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;agricultural goods grown or processed in Armenia (focus on a number of products to be further defined with the EU Delegation and Ministry of Agriculture of Armenia and EU Del) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Information on areas harvested, yields, animal numbers, production, domestic use, stocks, exports, imports as well as the associated prices, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;main characteristics of Armenia’s agricultural commodity markets, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;adjustable policy tools, including taxation, price support measures, production quota, trade protection measures, etc. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possibility to make projections for 15 years based on the collected baseline data. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requested services&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; The contractor will propose a country market model (based on MSs and/or ENI region). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The proposed model should be adapted to cover requirements of Armenia and to cover all main agricultural markets that will be further defined with the Ministry of Agriculture of Armenia. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The contractor will provide and install an electronic version of the developed model in computers of institutions that will be indicated at a later stage by the Ministry of Agriculture of Armenia. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A manual will be provided on the model and its operation/application. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quantitative &amp;amp; qualitative analysis of local agriculture policy &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Training sessions will be provided for representatives of the Government of Armenia and other stakeholders on the model and its implementation/operation. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The model will be run by the contractor in order to obtain a 15 year projections and scenarios. Based on the provided model projections, a revision of the agriculture policy implemented by the Government of Armenia should be proposed and recommendations for the improvement of future EU support to the agricultural sector should be provided to EUD Armenia. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 1 – International team leader - Expert in agriculture or quantitative analysis&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PhD degree or equivalent academic qualification in agriculture or quantitative analysis, statistics and modelling, econometrics, economics or other disciplines related to economic development or at least 15 years of relevant professional experience (as defined below) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication (oral and written) and coordination skills are required &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of English &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;: Professional experience leading similar scale projects for EU institutions, in EU Member States, EU ENP or NIS countries, demonstrated experience in quantitative analyses of agricultural policy, agricultural markets and international trade, in agricultural sector analysis and quantitative modelling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&quot;&gt;gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Justice management/Communications expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/justice-management-communications-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/justice-management-communications-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assistance to Justice Sector&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project of which this contract will be a part is to ensure incorporation of EU standards and best practices within the new Justice Reform Strategy and establishment of relevant implementation mechanisms to ensure strong control the implementation of the justice Reform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert E2 – Justice management/Communications expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least bachelor Degree in law or finance/economics/public administration &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of financial aspects of Justice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent English, knowledge of Armenian or Russian would be an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in designing communication campaign would be an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in issues related to the reform of justice chain its optimization and management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of professional work experience in fields related to Judiciary, advocacy, courts or prosecution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Training, coaching and capacity building experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of Armenian Judicial sector would be an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in judicial policy development, monitoring and management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in social partnership in judicial sector would be an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in working on E-justice solutions would be an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garica-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Justice reform Expert/Team Leader</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/justice-reform-expert-team-leader</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 11:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/justice-reform-expert-team-leader</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assistance to Justice Sector&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project of which this contract will be a part is to ensure incorporation of EU standards and best practices within the new Justice Reform Strategy and establishment of relevant implementation mechanisms to ensure strong control the implementation of the justice Reform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert E1 – Justice reform Expert/Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s Degree in law, or at least 10 years of equivalent professional experience in the field of judicial reforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of legal aspects of information management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent English, knowledge of Armenian or Russian would be an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience within international organizations (EC preferred) or within EU/EU member funded projects working on reform in Justice sector would be an asset &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of professional experience in the area of justice sector monitoring and/or reforms or public expenditure management reform programs in justice, preferably in CIS countries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in issues related to training and programme budgeting in justice sphere would be an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in budgetary assistance programmes and Sector Support Programs (SSP), especially in development of concept papers/policy papers or relevant legal acts, and resource allocation of public programs in Justice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in managing at least one project in the field of design and application of justice reforms monitoring systems, including application of qualitative and quantitative primary and secondary data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in implementation of institutional and human resource capacity building activities for state and civil society organizations in the justice sector would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garica-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KE3 - Monitoring Des Projets Dans Le Domaine De La Santé </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/ke3-monitoring-des-projets-dans-le-domaine-de-la-sante</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/ke3-monitoring-des-projets-dans-le-domaine-de-la-sante</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation A Mi-Parcours Du Programme D&amp;#39;appui A La Compétitivité Des Services&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fournir aux instances décisionnelles du gouvernement de la Tunisie, a la DUE et aux autres parties concernées des informations suffisantes pour:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apprécier globalement et de manière indépendante la conception du PACS, sa pertinence, son efficacité et son efficience, et apporter une appréciation sur la viabilité de l’approche, sa visibilité et les corrections à effectuer, notamment sur les indicateurs de résultats et de performance ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluer la gestion du PACS et de ses activités par les différents intervenants (MC, BERD, UAP, DUE…), les manuels de procédures, la gestion des jumelages, la gestion financière et administrative, la gestion des ressources humaines, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tirer des enseignements de l’intervention en vue d’une meilleure gestion du PACS et des nouveaux projets, a financier par l’Union européenne ou par d’autres bailleurs dans les domaines d’interventions ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fournir une série de recommandations et identifier les besoins en vue d’éventuelles actions futures dans le domaine de la compétitivité des services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KE3 - Monitoring Des Projets Dans Le Domaine De La Santé (Cat. II)&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diplôme de l&amp;#39;enseignement supérieur de niveau Master ou équivalent dans un domaine pertinent, ou expérience équivalente (minimum 5 ans en plus des 6 ans demandés ci-dessous) ; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale d&amp;#39;au moins 6 ans dans les projets dans les domaines de la santé, des structures hospitalières, etc. ; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expérience d&amp;#39;au moins 5 ans dans la formulation, la mise en œuvre et/ou l&amp;#39;évaluation de projets dans les domaines de la santé, des structures hospitalières, etc. ; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expérience dans l&amp;#39;évaluation et/ou monitoring d&amp;#39;au moins un projet dans le domaine de la santé. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bonne connaissance des procédures de l&amp;#39;UE sera un atout ; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Une expérience dans le domaine dans les pays de la région Voisinage de l&amp;#39;UE, serait un avantage ; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellente maitrise du français ; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Une très bonne maîtrise des logiciels bureautiques. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to  &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;Veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KE2 - Monitoring des projets (partie opérationnelle)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/ke2-monitoring-des-projets-partie-operationnelle</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 11:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/ke2-monitoring-des-projets-partie-operationnelle</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation A Mi-Parcours Du Programme D&amp;#39;appui A La Compétitivité Des Services&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fournir aux instances décisionnelles du gouvernement de la Tunisie, a la DUE et aux autres parties concernées des informations suffisantes pour:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apprécier globalement et de manière indépendante la conception du PACS, sa pertinence, son efficacité et son efficience, et apporter une appréciation sur la viabilité de l’approche, sa visibilité et les corrections à effectuer, notamment sur les indicateurs de résultats et de performance ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluer la gestion du PACS et de ses activités par les différents intervenants (MC, BERD, UAP, DUE…), les manuels de procédures, la gestion des jumelages, la gestion financière et administrative, la gestion des ressources humaines, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tirer des enseignements de l’intervention en vue d’une meilleure gestion du PACS et des nouveaux projets, a financier par l’Union européenne ou par d’autres bailleurs dans les domaines d’interventions ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fournir une série de recommandations et identifier les besoins en vue d’éventuelles actions futures dans le domaine de la compétitivité des services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KE2 - Monitoring des projets (partie opérationnelle) ; Cat. I&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diplôme de l&amp;#39;enseignement supérieur de niveau Master ou équivalent dans un domaine pertinent (discipline liée au développement économique / appui au secteur privé ou équivalent). En l&amp;#39;absence de ce diplôme, une expérience professionnelle équivalente (minimum 5 ans en plus des 12 ans demandés ci-dessous) ; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expérience d&amp;#39;au moins 12 ans dans le domaine du développement économique, soutien au secteur privé, secteur des services, etc. ; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expérience internationale d&amp;#39;au moins 5 ans dans le montage et/ou l&amp;#39;accompagnement et/ou l&amp;#39;évaluation de projets relatifs à la compétitivité des entreprises et au développement économique ; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expérience dans l&amp;#39;évaluation et/ou le monitoring d&amp;#39;au moins 2 projets de jumelages et/ou de projets d&amp;#39;assistance technique ; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Une expérience dans le domaine dans les pays de la région Voisinage de l&amp;#39;UE serait un avantage ; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bonne connaissance du PRAG et du manuel des jumelages sera un atout ; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Connaissance de contrats en gestion déléguée (PAGODA) sera un avantage ;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellente maitrise du français ; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Une très bonne maîtrise des logiciels bureautiques. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to  &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;Veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader – Monitoring du Programme (partie Administrative et Financière) – Cat. I</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-monitoring-du-programme-partie-administrative-et-financiere-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-monitoring-du-programme-partie-administrative-et-financiere-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation A Mi-Parcours Du Programme D&amp;#39;appui A La Compétitivité Des Services&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fournir aux instances décisionnelles du gouvernement de la Tunisie, a la DUE et aux autres parties concernées des informations suffisantes pour:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apprécier globalement et de manière indépendante la conception du PACS, sa pertinence, son efficacité et son efficience, et apporter une appréciation sur la viabilité de l’approche, sa visibilité et les corrections à effectuer, notamment sur les indicateurs de résultats et de performance ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluer la gestion du PACS et de ses activités par les différents intervenants (MC, BERD, UAP, DUE…), les manuels de procédures, la gestion des jumelages, la gestion financière et administrative, la gestion des ressources humaines, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tirer des enseignements de l’intervention en vue d’une meilleure gestion du PACS et des nouveaux projets, a financier par l’Union européenne ou par d’autres bailleurs dans les domaines d’interventions ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fournir une série de recommandations et identifier les besoins en vue d’éventuelles actions futures dans le domaine de la compétitivité des services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader – Monitoring du Programme (partie Administrative et Financière) – Cat. I&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diplôme de l&amp;#39;enseignement supérieur de niveau Master ou équivalent dans un domaine relatif à la gestion technique et financière de programmes de coopération. En l&amp;#39;absence de ce diplôme, une expérience professionnelle équivalente (minimum 5 ans en plus des 12 ans demandés ci-dessous) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale d&amp;#39;au moins 12 ans dans les programmes de coopération ; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expérience dans la formulation et/ou la mise en œuvre de programmes en gestion décentralisée ; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expérience dans la gestion et/ou l&amp;#39;évaluation d&amp;#39;au moins 2 programmes en gestion décentralisée partielle (fonctionnement d&amp;#39;une unité de gestion, devis programmes ayant une partie opérationnelle et de fonctionnement, projets centralisés à la DUE) ; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Avoir participé, en tant que Team leader à au moins deux missions de terrain concernant l&amp;#39;évaluation/monitoring de projets et/ou programmes de coopération technique. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Une expérience dans le domaine dans les pays de la région Voisinage de l&amp;#39;UE, serait un avantage ; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bonne connaissance du guide des devis programmes et du PRAG sera un atout &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellente maitrise du français ; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Une très bonne maîtrise des logiciels bureautiques. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to  &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;Veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
