<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 22:34:02 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 2 – Public Administration Reform Expert </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-public-administration-reform-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 22:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-public-administration-reform-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Provision of Technical Assistance to the Mayor and City Councillors of Georgetown&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; is to prepare an overall strategy and implementation plan to advise the operations of the M&amp;amp;CC (Mayor and City Council of Georgetown) and also to provide technical assistance for capacity building of the M&amp;amp;CC in the area of financial management and corporate governance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2 – Public Administration Reform Expert (Cat. I, 39 WD)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s Degree in Public Administration, Accounting or related field (e.g. Law, Political Science or similar) or, in its absence, equivalent professional experience of 7 years which must be above the general professional experience below;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years post-degree relevant professional experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 4 previous assignments advising on strengthening central government/municipal governance including proposing efficient revenue collection models for central government and municipalities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent oral and writing skills in English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific experience and knowledge on incorporating gender issues to financial management/corporate governance/public administration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 1 – Public Finance Management (PFM) Specialist </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-1-public-finance-management-pfm-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 22:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-1-public-finance-management-pfm-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Provision of Technical Assistance to the Mayor and City Councillors of Georgetown&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; is to prepare an overall strategy and implementation plan to advise the operations of the M&amp;amp;CC (Mayor and City Council of Georgetown) and also to provide technical assistance for capacity building of the M&amp;amp;CC in the area of financial management and corporate governance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 1 – Public Finance Management (PFM) Specialist (Cat. I, 39 WD)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s Degree in Economics or Finance, or, in its absence, equivalent professional experience of 7 years which must be above the general professional experience below;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of post-degree relevant professional experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 4 previous assignments related to the provision of PFM specialist services to central governments or municipalities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent oral and writing skills in English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific experience and knowledge on incorporating gender issues to financial management/corporate governance/public administration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category III Experts in Public Administration Reform</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-iii-experts-in-public-administration-reform</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 15:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-iii-experts-in-public-administration-reform</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Compliance Review: Sector Reform Contract for Public Administration Reform&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this Contract is to ensure implementation of PAR in Albania. The specific objective of this Contract is to assess the degree of compliance with the general and specific conditions, criteria and verification indicators for the purpose of disbursements of tranches under the Sector Reform Contract for PAR (SRC PAR) under IPA 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category III Experts in Public Administration Reform&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a master degree in political or social sciences or law, or, in its absence, at least 7 years&amp;#39; general experience as a consultant in the sectors related to the Lot 7, Section A4: &amp;ldquo;Public administration reform, and civil service reform&amp;rdquo;;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years&amp;#39; general experience in the public administration reform sector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Major contribution under at least one EU budget support programmes review, preferably in the good governance sector; a copy of the Aide Memoire (co-)drafted by the proposed expert or under her/his direct supervision and responsibility after 2011 will need to be provided&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;em&gt;[Lina&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;](mailto:&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;lina_forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category II Expert in Public Administration Reform (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-expert-in-public-administration-reform-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 15:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-expert-in-public-administration-reform-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Compliance Review: Sector Reform Contract for Public Administration Reform&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this Contract is to ensure implementation of PAR in Albania. The specific objective of this Contract is to assess the degree of compliance with the general and specific conditions, criteria and verification indicators for the purpose of disbursements of tranches under the Sector Reform Contract for PAR (SRC PAR) under IPA 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category II Expert in Public Administration Reform (TL)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a master degree in political or social sciences or law, or, in its absence, at least 10 years&amp;#39; general experience as a consultant in the sectors related to the Lot 7, Section A4: &amp;ldquo;Public administration reform, and civil service reform&amp;rdquo;;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years&amp;#39; general experience in the area of support to public administration reform;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Major contribution under at least three EU budget support programmes reviews, preferably in the good governance sector; a copy of one Aide Memoire (co)drafted by the proposed expert or under her/his direct&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;supervision and responsibility after 2011 will need to be provided&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;team leader&lt;/strong&gt; shall provide major contribution, directly supervise and be primarily responsible for the proper coordination and execution of missions, submission of reports and all other activities and services required under this Contract. S/he shall be in direct and prompt contact with all relevant stakeholders and the EU Project Manager.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;em&gt;[Lina&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;](mailto:&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;lina_forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category III Expert in Information Technologies</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-iii-expert-in-information-technologies</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-iii-expert-in-information-technologies</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to the establishment of the State Aid Control System&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective is to support the establishment of an effective State aid control system in Ukraine as required under the EU-Ukraine Association agreement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective of the assignment is to assist the Antimonopoly Committee of Ukraine to establish a State aid control system by 2 August 2017 in accordance with the Law of Ukraine on State aid to undertakings. This assignment will provide &amp;ldquo;bridging assistance&amp;rdquo; until a dedicated technical assistance project can take over the work sometime in the third quarter of 2017. The specific issues that require immediate assistance have been identified in section 2.3 below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category III Expert in Information Technologies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in natural or technical sciences or equivalent (at least  5 years of experience additional to that required below under the general professional experience); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience in information technologies; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years of experience in the development of management information systems; Experience in the implementation of IT projects with State Authorities in Ukraine would be an asset, in particular in public finance management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Command of English (at least B2 level); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Command of Ukrainian or Russian language (at least B2 level).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;Aurelie_Durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category I Expert on EU State Aid law and Team Leader </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-expert-on-eu-state-aid-law-and-team-leader</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 22:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-expert-on-eu-state-aid-law-and-team-leader</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to the establishment of the State Aid Control System&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective is to support the establishment of an effective State aid control system in Ukraine as required under the EU-Ukraine Association agreement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective of the assignment is to assist the Antimonopoly Committee of Ukraine to establish a State aid control system by 2 August 2017 in accordance with the Law of Ukraine on State aid to undertakings. This assignment will provide &amp;ldquo;bridging assistance&amp;rdquo; until a dedicated technical assistance project can take over the work sometime in the third quarter of 2017. The specific issues that require immediate assistance have been identified in section 2.3 below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category I Expert on EU State Aid law and Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in law, economics, business administration or public administration. Alternatively, a minimum of 7 years of relevant experience in the field of competition law, in addition to the minimum number of years of general professional experience required below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of professional experience in the field or law, economics or public administration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferably 5  years (with a minimum of 3 years) within the last 15 years of experience in the field of state aid gained in an EU institution, a public authority in an EU Member State, an EEA country, a country operating a fully functioning State aid regulatory system or in a pre-accession country to the EU or an EU candidate country;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferably 2 years (with minimum 1 year) of experience in establishing, implementing or operating a State aid control and monitoring system in line with EU rules;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in implementing technical assistance projects would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Command of English (at least B2 level); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Command of Ukrainian or Russian would be an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;Aurelie_Durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experts en Système d’information Géographique,  des Questions de Mécanisation Agricole, en Comptabilité/Finances  et en Gestion des Ressources Humaines</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-en-systeme-dinformation-geographique-des-questions-de-mecanisation-agricole-en-comptabilite-finances-et-en-gestion-des-ressources-humaines</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 15:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-en-systeme-dinformation-geographique-des-questions-de-mecanisation-agricole-en-comptabilite-finances-et-en-gestion-des-ressources-humaines</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Etude, audit et formulation sur le secteur cotonnier au Cameroun&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif global&lt;/strong&gt; de l&amp;#39;appui est de renforcer le développement du secteur cotonnier afin d’améliorer sa contribution à l’émergence socioéconomique et à la création d’emplois dans la zone cotonnière. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;L’objectif particulier&lt;/strong&gt; est de :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Poser un diagnostic du potentiel du secteur cotonnier dans la perspective :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;d’une analyse sectorielle du secteur coton en termes de création d’emploi et de retombées économiques d’une part, et de la réalisation d’un audit organisationnel et fonctionnel de la SODECOTON en vue de l’amélioration des performances de l’entreprise d’autre part,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;de la formulation, à partir des enseignements et leçons tirés de l’analyse sectorielle du secteur coton d’une part, et de l’audit organisationnel et fonctionnel de la SODECOTON d’autre part, d&amp;#39;un programme de juvénilisation et de modernisation de la production cotonnière.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tous les experts doivent être indépendants et n&amp;#39;avoir aucun conflit d&amp;#39;intérêt dans les responsabilités qui leur incombent. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Autres Experts Principaux (2, 3, 5 et 6)&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum BAC+4 dans les domaines d’expertise définis ci-dessus ou équivalent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les quatre (04) experts principaux dont un spécialiste en système d’information géographique, un spécialiste des questions de mécanisation agricole, un expert en comptabilité/finances  et, un expert en gestion des ressources humaines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Les quatre (04) experts principaux doivent avoir au minimum 3 expériences dans des missions similaires. Ils auront d’excellentes capacités de communication et de rédaction en français et maîtriseront l’outil informatique.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience de travail au Cameroun ou dans des pays d’Afrique sub-saharienne aux caractéristiques semblables (en fonction des régions où seront postés les experts proposés).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience avérée de formulation des projets sur financement FED est un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert Audit Organisationnel et Fonctionnel, Chef d&#39;équipe Audit</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-audit-organisationnel-et-fonctionnel-chef-dequipe-audit</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 11:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-audit-organisationnel-et-fonctionnel-chef-dequipe-audit</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Etude, audit et formulation sur le secteur cotonnier au Cameroun&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif global de l&amp;#39;appui est de renforcer le développement du secteur cotonnier afin d’améliorer sa contribution à l’émergence socioéconomique et à la création d’emplois dans la zone cotonnière. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif particulier est de :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Poser un diagnostic du potentiel du secteur cotonnier dans la perspective :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;d’une analyse sectorielle du secteur coton en termes de création d’emploi et de retombées économiques d’une part, et de la réalisation d’un audit organisationnel et fonctionnel de la SODECOTON en vue de l’amélioration des performances de l’entreprise d’autre part,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;de la formulation, à partir des enseignements et leçons tirés de l’analyse sectorielle du secteur coton d’une part, et de l’audit organisationnel et fonctionnel de la SODECOTON d’autre part, d&amp;#39;un programme de juvénilisation et de modernisation de la production cotonnière.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tous les experts doivent être indépendants et n&amp;#39;avoir aucun conflit d&amp;#39;intérêt dans les responsabilités qui leur incombent. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert principal 4: Expert Audit Organisationnel et Fonctionnel, Chef d&amp;#39;équipe Audit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum Bac + 5, dans les domaines suivants : économie, finance, ressources humaines, agronomie, sociologie du développement, ou équivalent (cf. champs d’expertise ci-dessus)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’expert principal 4 doit justifier d’une expérience d’au moins dix (10) ans dans les audits organisationnels et/ou fonctionnels des institutions du secteur agricole/rural.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;L’expert principal 4 doit avoir au minimum 5 expériences dans la réalisation des missions d&amp;#39;audit des institutions du secteur agricole en Afrique sub-saharienne.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Il aura d’excellentes capacités de communication et de rédaction en français et maîtrisera l’outil informatique.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une connaissance approfondie du Cameroun, et en particulier la zone ciblée, est un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agroéconomiste, Chef de mission</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/agroeconomiste-chef-de-mission</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/agroeconomiste-chef-de-mission</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Etude, audit et formulation sur le secteur cotonnier au Cameroun&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif global de l&amp;#39;appui est de renforcer le développement du secteur cotonnier afin d’améliorer sa contribution à l’émergence socioéconomique et à la création d’emplois dans la zone cotonnière. 
L’objectif particulier est de :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Poser un diagnostic du potentiel du secteur cotonnier dans la perspective :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;d’une analyse sectorielle du secteur coton en termes de création d’emploi et de retombées économiques d’une part, et de la réalisation d’un audit organisationnel et fonctionnel de la SODECOTON en vue de l’amélioration des performances de l’entreprise d’autre part,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;de la formulation, à partir des enseignements et leçons tirés de l’analyse sectorielle du secteur coton d’une part, et de l’audit organisationnel et fonctionnel de la SODECOTON d’autre part, d&amp;#39;un programme de juvénilisation et de modernisation de la production cotonnière.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tous les experts doivent être indépendants et n&amp;#39;avoir aucun conflit d&amp;#39;intérêt dans les responsabilités qui leur incombent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert principal 1: Agroéconomiste, Chef de mission&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum Bac + 5, dans les domaines suivants : économie, aménagement du territoire, agronomie, sociologie du développement, ou équivalent (cf. champs d’expertise ci-dessus)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’expert principal 1 doit justifier d’une expérience d’au moins dix (10) ans dans les programmes de développement rural en Afrique sub-saharienne, en préférence dans le secteur coton.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;L’expert principal 1 doit avoir au minimum 5 expériences comme chef de mission dans des missions d&amp;#39;évaluation ou de formulation ou de gestion de projets de développement rural, en préférence dans le secteur coton, et au minimum 3 expériences dans l&amp;#39;évaluation ou la formulation ou la gestion de projets FED de l’Union Européenne.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Il aura d’excellentes capacités de communication et de rédaction en français et maîtrisera l’outil informatique.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une connaissance approfondie du Cameroun, du secteur cotonnière et en particulier la zone ciblée, est un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impact Assessment Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/impact-assessment-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 12:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/impact-assessment-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation - for RDI II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mid-term evaluation mission and the subsequent recommendations of the assignment shall contribute to the improvement of the Research, Development and Innovation Programme II (RDI II), particularly the PIO performance in terms of the effective achievement of its objectives and the programme goals. The evaluation will provide the decision-makers in the Government of Egypt, the relevant external co-operation services of the European Union and the wider public with sufficient information to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make an overall independent assessment about the performance of the programme, paying particularly attention to the impact of the project actions against its objectives;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify key lessons and to propose practical recommendations for any future programming in this sector, taking into account the financial constraints of the programme and EU rules and procedures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 3: – Impact Assessment Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Masters&amp;#39; degree in one or more of the relevant disciplines (i.e. Public Policy, Economics, Engineering, Innovation Management or Business Administration)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of experience in evaluations and impact assessment of international programmes, especially in EU Funded programmes, related to the field of Research and Innovation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Substantial professional experience in assessing the socioeconomic impact of research and innovation projects, especially the academia-industry interface, especially in the fields of agriculture, renewable energy, water, ICT, education, health and other thematic priorities identified by the RDI-II Programme.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in/Good knowledge of the Egyptian context and cooperation with the EU, including the European Neighbourhood Policy. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full awareness of the principles and working methods of project cycle management and EU aid delivery methods.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full working knowledge of English and excellent report writing skills. Knowledge of Arabic would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;em&gt;[Lina&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;](mailto:&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;lina_forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 2: – Monitoring and Evaluation Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-monitoring-and-evaluation-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-monitoring-and-evaluation-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation - for RDI II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mid-term evaluation mission and the subsequent recommendations of the assignment shall contribute to the improvement of the Research, Development and Innovation Programme II (RDI II), particularly the PIO performance in terms of the effective achievement of its objectives and the programme goals. The evaluation will provide the decision-makers in the Government of Egypt, the relevant external co-operation services of the European Union and the wider public with sufficient information to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make an overall independent assessment about the performance of the programme, paying particularly attention to the impact of the project actions against its objectives;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify key lessons and to propose practical recommendations for any future programming in this sector, taking into account the financial constraints of the programme and EU rules and procedures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2: – Monitoring and Evaluation Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Masters&amp;#39; degree in one or more of the relevant disciplines (i.e. Science, Economics, Engineering, Information Technology, Innovation Management or Business Administration)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of experience in Monitoring and Evaluating of international projects, especially in EC funded projects in decentralized management operations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Substantial professional experience in assessing, monitoring and evaluating research and innovation projects, academia-industry interface, especially in the fields of agriculture, renewable energy, water, ICT, education, health and other thematic priorities identified by the RDI-II Programme.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in/Good knowledge of the Egyptian context and cooperation with the EU, including the European Neighbourhood Policy. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in monitoring and evaluating projects under FP7 and Horizon 2020 is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full awareness of the principles and working methods of project cycle management and EU aid delivery methods.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full working knowledge of English and excellent report writing skills. Knowledge of Arabic would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;em&gt;[Lina&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;](mailto:&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;lina_forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation Expert – Team Leader</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/evaluation-expert-team-leader</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 11:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/evaluation-expert-team-leader</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation - for RDI II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mid-term evaluation mission and the subsequent recommendations of the assignment shall contribute to the improvement of the Research, Development and Innovation Programme II (RDI II), particularly the PIO performance in terms of the effective achievement of its objectives and the programme goals. The evaluation will provide the decision-makers in the Government of Egypt, the relevant external co-operation services of the European Union and the wider public with sufficient information to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make an overall independent assessment about the performance of the programme, paying particularly attention to the impact of the project actions against its objectives;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify key lessons and to propose practical recommendations for any future programming in this sector, taking into account the financial constraints of the programme and EU rules and procedures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 1: Evaluation Expert – Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced university degree in one or more of the relevant disciplines (i.e. Science, Economics, Engineering, Information Technology, Innovation Management or Business Administration)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in Monitoring and Evaluating of international projects, especially in EC funded projects in decentralized management operations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Substantial professional experience in assessing, monitoring and evaluating research and innovation projects, academia-industry interface, especially in the fields of agriculture, renewable energy, water, ICT, education, health and other thematic priorities identified by the RDI-II Programme.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years&amp;#39; experience in leading a team of consultants working within the framework of international projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in/Good knowledge of the Egyptian context and cooperation with the EU, including the European Neighbourhood Policy. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with national research and innovation strategy/reform agenda and priorities, thematic areas such as health-related applications, waste management, food and agriculture, water, environment and renewable energy, information and communication technology, education, materials, and space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Evaluating projects under FP7 and Horizon 2020 is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full awareness of the principles and working methods of project cycle management and EU aid delivery methods.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent Communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full working knowledge of English and excellent report writing skills. Knowledge of Arabic would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;em&gt;[Lina&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;](mailto:&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;lina_forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert en Cooperation au Développement (Experience en Projets UE) – Cat. II</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-cooperation-au-developpement-experience-en-projets-ue-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 09:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-cooperation-au-developpement-experience-en-projets-ue-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recrutement d&amp;#39;une Assistance Technique pour la Formulation du Nouveau Programme d&amp;#39;appui aux Organisations de la Societe Civile au Mali dans le cadre du 11e FED&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;L’objectif général&lt;/strong&gt; de la mission est d’appuyer la Délégation de l’Union Européenne (DUE) dans la formulation du nouveau programme d’appui aux OSC du Mali.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;L’objectif spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; de la présente mission est de fournir une analyse et différents scénarios de contenu et de mise en oeuvre du PAOSC III pour contribuer à la phase deformulation pour le nouveau programme des OSC du Mali.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert en Cooperation au Développement (Experience en Projets UE) – Cat. II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Catégorie et expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Un Expert de Catégorie II avec 6 années d’expérience professionnelle générale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Formation *&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’expert proposé doit justifier d’un diplôme de l’enseignement supérieur, minimum mastère en sciences sociales de préférence (ou expérience professionnelle équivalente de 10 ans au total).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Doit justifier&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;D&amp;#39;au moins 5 ans dans le domaine de la coopération au développement, dont 4 ans spécifiquement avec l’UE&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;D&amp;#39;un minimum de 2 missions d&amp;#39;identification ou de formulation pour l&amp;#39;UE, dont 1 dans un pays d&amp;#39;Afrique Subsaharienne francophone&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;D&amp;#39;une expérience dans l&amp;#39;identification/formulation ou la mise en oeuvre d&amp;#39;un appui à la société civile financé par un partenaire technique et financier au développement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;D&amp;#39;une bonne maîtrise des procédures UE&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;D&amp;#39;une excellente connaissance du français à l&amp;#39;écrit et à l&amp;#39;oral.
Une connaissance des langues locales sera considérée comme un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissances linguistiques&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La maitrise du français parlé et écrit est obligatoire (voir expérience spécifique requise ci-dessus).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;Nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert en Societé Civil (Experience en Projets UE) – Cat. I</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-societe-civil-experience-en-projets-ue-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-societe-civil-experience-en-projets-ue-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recrutement d&amp;#39;une Assistance Technique pour la Formulation du Nouveau Programme d&amp;#39;appui aux Organisations de la Societe Civile au Mali dans le cadre du 11e FED&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif général de la mission est d’appuyer la Délégation de l’Union Européenne (DUE) dans la formulation du nouveau programme d’appui aux OSC du Mali.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif spécifique de la présente mission est de fournir une analyse et différents scénarios de contenu et de mise en oeuvre du PAOSC III pour contribuer à la phase deformulation pour le nouveau programme des OSC du Mali.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert en Societé Civil (Experience en Projets UE) – Cat. I&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Catégorie et expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Un Expert de Catégorie I avec 12 années d’expérience professionnelle générale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Formation *&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’expert proposé doit justifier d’un diplôme de l’enseignement supérieur, minimum mastère en sciences sociales de préférence (ou expérience professionnelle équivalente de 16 ans au total).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique :&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Doit justifier :&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;D&amp;#39;une expérience dans l&amp;#39;appui aux organisations de la société civile d&amp;#39;un total de 8 ans au moins, comprenant une part substantielle de travail pour ou avec la coopération de l&amp;#39;UE&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;D&amp;#39;un minimum de 3 missions d&amp;#39;identification ou de formulation pour l&amp;#39;UE, dont 2 dans un pays d&amp;#39;Afrique Subsaharienne francophone&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;D&amp;#39;une excellente maîtrise des procédures UE&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;D&amp;#39;une excellente connaissance du français à l&amp;#39;écrit et à l&amp;#39;oral.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une connaissance approfondie de la sous-région et particulièrement du Mali serait un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissances linguistiques&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La maitrise du français parlé et écrit est obligatoire (voir expérience spécifique requise ci-dessus).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;Nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Energy Expert (Category II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/energy-expert-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/energy-expert-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation of the EU support provided at regional and bilateral level in the field of energy in the Neighbourhood South Countries (2010-2016)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of the assignment is to assess the EU support at regional level, bilateral level and through the blending mechanism (the NIF) to the partner countries of the Neighbourhood South in the field of energy (gas, electricity market integration, renewable energy and energy efficiency) over the period 2010-2016, and to propose recommendations for further EU support for the forthcoming programming period 2017-2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experts are also required to consider how the political relationships between the EU and its partner countries as well as the relations between partner countries affect both the implementation of the EU support and the development of harmonised energy policies in the Mediterranean region (e.g.: energy markets legislation, market integration etc.).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location visits&lt;/strong&gt;: Belgium, Algeria, Egypt, Jordan, Israel, Lebanon, Morocco, Palestine, Tunisia&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 150 days&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2: Energy Expert (Category II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in one or more of the following fields: energy engineering; energy economics; energy, oil and gas management; energy systems engineering; power engineering; energy resources management; renewable energy or related fields;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of the English language (written and oral);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least eight (8) years of professional experience related to energy;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least four (4) years of experience in the framework of technical assistance projects in transition and/or developing economies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least four (4) years of experience in international projects related to energy;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least six (6) years of demonstrable experience and a proven track record in technical, regulatory and socio-economic fields required for the implementation of energy policies that are relevant to the Mediterranean region;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least five (5) years of experience demonstrating a solid understanding of the energy sector and its challenges with regard to energy regulation, energy policy reform, renewable energies&amp;#39; development and energy efficiency in the Mediterranean region;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acquaintance with energy market integration processes and demonstrated knowledge of the EU energy policy and its external dimension;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in project/programme evaluation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Arabic language (written and oral).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, at least one of the experts must have:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with IFIs and/or international organisations;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in energy policy analysis;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in institution-building initiatives in the energy sector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader, Senior Energy Policy Expert (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-energy-policy-expert-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 08:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-energy-policy-expert-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation of the EU support provided at regional and bilateral level in the field of energy in the Neighbourhood South Countries (2010-2016)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of the assignment is to assess the EU support at regional level, bilateral level and through the blending mechanism (the NIF) to the partner countries of the Neighbourhood South in the field of energy (gas, electricity market integration, renewable energy and energy efficiency) over the period 2010-2016, and to propose recommendations for further EU support for the forthcoming programming period 2017-2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experts are also required to consider how the political relationships between the EU and its partner countries as well as the relations between partner countries affect both the implementation of the EU support and the development of harmonised energy policies in the Mediterranean region (e.g.: energy markets legislation, market integration etc.).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location visits&lt;/strong&gt;: Belgium, Algeria, Egypt, Jordan, Israel, Lebanon, Morocco, Palestine, Tunisia&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 150 days&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 1: Team Leader, Senior Energy Policy Expert (Category I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in one or more of the following fields: energy engineering; energy economics; public policy; management; political science or related fields;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of the EU energy policy and its external dimension;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and management skills, demonstrable capacity to lead a multinational team and to work with government institutions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of the English language (written and oral);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of the European Union procedures and practices in external cooperation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least twelve (12) years professional experience related to energy policy;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least eight (8) years of experience in the framework of technical assistance projects in developing economies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least four (4) years of professional experience with technical assistance projects in the energy field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least five (5) years of professional experience in the evaluation/assessment of technical assistance programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General experience demonstrating an understanding of the challenges: a) faced by energy authorities in the Neighbourhood South countries; b) associated to the establishment of a harmonised energy market for electricity and gas in the Mediterranean region; c) associated with the development/promotion of renewable energy and energy efficiency in the Mediterranean region;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least ten (10) years of experience demonstrating a solid understanding of the energy sector and its challenges with regard to energy regulation, energy policy reform, renewable energies&amp;#39; development and energy efficiency in the Mediterranean region;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant professional experience in the Mediterranean region;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Arabic language (written and oral).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Evaluation Expert in Food Safety (Cat.I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-evaluation-expert-in-food-safety-cati</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 16:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-evaluation-expert-in-food-safety-cati</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation of the impact of IPA funds on fostering the reforms in the sector of internal market&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;main objectives&lt;/strong&gt; are to identify key lessons and to produce recommendations in order to improve current and inform future choices on use of the EU funds, and to provide an overall independent assessment of the use of the EU funds in the former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this assignment is to assess the effectiveness and impact of the EU funds in the area of internal market, including free movement of goods, services, capital, workers, public procurement, competition &amp;amp; state aid, as well as veterinary and phytosanitary security and food safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Macedonia&lt;/strong&gt;. Local travel in the country will be required depending on the location of the selected projects&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Evaluation Expert in Food Safety (Cat.I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master’s degree or at least equivalent 15 years of general professional experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent spoken and written English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to speak the local language will be an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of professional experience, preferably in the field of internal market and/or management of the EU funds including programming, monitoring or evaluation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience from an EU member state or candidate/accession country will be considered an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participation in at least 2 projects focused on evaluation or 5 years of evaluation experience in institutional context is required. The expert must be able to demonstrate good understanding in evaluation methods and techniques in general, and in particular good skills in collection, processing and analysing qualitative and quantitative data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participation in at least 2 previous projects in the sector of internal market/food safety or 5 years in institutional context. The expert must be able to demonstrate good understanding of the EU policies in the sector of internal market/food safety.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This expert may be assigned with the role of &lt;strong&gt;Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt;. In addition to the above criteria, the Team Leader must demonstrate skills and previous experience in:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Management and coordination: the proposed expert must be able to demonstrate a participation in at least 1 previous assignment as a team leader/project director and strong ability to coordinate a team, manage processes and resources;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Presentation and communication, including good writing and editing skills in English: the proposed expert must be able to demonstrate a participation in at least 1 previous assignment where his/her responsibility included report preparation and public presentation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;Aurelie_Durand@dai.com
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Evaluation Expert in Internal Markets</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-evaluation-expert-in-internal-markets</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-evaluation-expert-in-internal-markets</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation of the impact of IPA funds on fostering the reforms in the sector of internal market&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;main objectives&lt;/strong&gt; are to identify key lessons and to produce recommendations in order to improve current and inform future choices on use of the EU funds, and to provide an overall independent assessment of the use of the EU funds in the former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this assignment is to assess the effectiveness and impact of the EU funds in the area of internal market, including free movement of goods, services, capital, workers, public procurement, competition &amp;amp; state aid, as well as veterinary and phytosanitary security and food safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Macedonia&lt;/strong&gt;. Local travel in the country will be required depending on the location of the selected projects&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Evaluation Expert in Internal Markets (Cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master’s degree or at least equivalent 15 years of general professional experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent spoken and written English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to speak the local language will be an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of professional experience, preferably in the field of internal market and/or management of the EU funds including programming, monitoring or evaluation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience from an EU member state or candidate/accession country will be considered an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participation in at least 2 projects focused on evaluation or 5 years of evaluation experience in institutional context is required. The expert must be able to demonstrate good understanding in evaluation methods and techniques in general, and in particular good skills in collection, processing and analysing qualitative and quantitative data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participation in at least 2 previous projects in the sector of internal market/food safety or 5 years in institutional context. The expert must be able to demonstrate good understanding of the EU policies in the sector of internal market/food safety.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This expert may be assigned with the role of &lt;strong&gt;Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt;. In addition to the above criteria, the Team Leader must demonstrate skills and previous experience in: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Management and coordination: the proposed expert must be able to demonstrate a participation in at least 1 previous assignment as a team leader/project director and strong ability to coordinate a team, manage processes and resources;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Presentation and communication, including good writing and editing skills in English: the proposed expert must be able to demonstrate a participation in at least 1 previous assignment where his/her responsibility included report preparation and public presentation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;Aurelie_Durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cat.II Expert in EU Evaluations, Research and Programme Management</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/catii-expert-in-eu-evaluations-research-and-programme-management</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 14:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/catii-expert-in-eu-evaluations-research-and-programme-management</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Evaluation of &amp;lsquo;Programme in the field of Technical Barriers to Trade&amp;rsquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation exercise will provide stakeholders with evidence and analytical elements about the performance, good practices and lessons learned of the Technical Barriers to Trade programme and will be part of a continuous knowledge building effort to enhance the effectiveness of the Commission&amp;rsquo;s trade assistance programmes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The evaluation will give special attention to following matters:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The impact of the programme in terms of achievement of tangible results;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build on good practices and lessons learned from a parallel knowledge management initiative to make recommendations for regional initiatives in the field of TBT;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added value of ACP level intervention to the EU supported regional and national level project;s&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comparison of TBT project with other intervention modalities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cat.II Expert in EU Evaluations, Research and Programme Management&lt;/strong&gt;
(60 working days)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;: Education at least Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree relevant to international trade, law or economics or, in its absence, equivalent professional experience related to international trade.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: At least 3 years&amp;#39; experience in the sector(s) related to the Lot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt; should include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience with research and EU programme management. He/she will have a very good knowledge of the EU evaluation methodology, research and financial management of EU programmes proven by at least two different working experiences. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she is expected to be fully familiar with the EC’s Project Cycle Management, communication and Logical Framework Approach. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Soft skills&lt;/strong&gt;: tactical in communicating with programme stakeholders, good analytical skills, advanced presentation skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;: Excellent drafting and writing skills in English, very good reading and communication skills in French.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;Aurelie_Durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader Cat.II Trade Expert with ACP Region Experience</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-trade-expert-with-acp-region-experience</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-trade-expert-with-acp-region-experience</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Evaluation of &amp;lsquo;Programme in the field of Technical Barriers to Trade&amp;rsquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation exercise will provide stakeholders with evidence and analytical elements about the performance, good practices and lessons learned of the Technical Barriers to Trade programme and will be part of a continuous knowledge building effort to enhance the effectiveness of the Commission&amp;rsquo;s trade assistance programmes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The evaluation will give special attention to following matters:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The impact of the programme in terms of achievement of tangible results;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build on good practices and lessons learned from a parallel knowledge management initiative to make recommendations for regional initiatives in the field of TBT;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added value of ACP level intervention to the EU supported regional and national level project;s&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comparison of TBT project with other intervention modalities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader Senior Trade Expert with ACP Region Experience&lt;/strong&gt;
(Category II, 60 working days) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;: Education at least Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree relevant to international trade, law or economics or, in its absence, equivalent professional experience related to international trade.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: At least 6 years&amp;#39; experience in the sector(s) related to the Lot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt; should include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with trade promotion programme and EU programme management. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she will have at least three years of international experience in assessing trade related assistance in developing countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In terms of geographical coverage, the expert is expected to have at least two relevant experiences in the ACP region on TBT matters. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A very good knowledge of the EU evaluation methodology gained through relevant past experiences would be considered an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The team leader is expected to be fully familiar with the &lt;strong&gt;EC’s Project Cycle Management and Logical Framework Approach&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Soft skills&lt;/strong&gt;: tactical in communicating with programme stakeholders, good analytical skills, advanced presentation skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;: Excellent drafting and writing skills in English, very good reading and communication skills in French.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;Aurelie_Durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
