<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2015 09:48:43 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Locally Engaged) Finance and Program Coordinator </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/locally-engaged-finance-and-program-coordinator</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/locally-engaged-finance-and-program-coordinator</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DFAT’s new investment in vocational skills is designed to help close the gap between industry demand for, and Solomon Islands&amp;#39; supply of skilled labour. The Skills for Economic Growth program aims to shift Solomon Islands’ current technical vocational training system from a postcolonial supply driven model to a suite of demand driven training that meets the needs of industry and fills critical skills shortages. The program will include support to the Ministry for Education to develop a new national qualifications framework and a gradual shift to competency based training. There will be tangible investments in developing the quality of courses in high need areas such as in construction, trades, tourism, and early childhood. As well as working in the formal employment sector, there will also be a focus on linking short courses to small business development in the informal economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectives of the role&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Assist in the financial management and program coordination of an Australian Government program of assistance for the Solomon Islands TVET sector. The role includes human resource management and communications responsibilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Length of the project&lt;/strong&gt;: 48 Months
&lt;strong&gt;Start Date&lt;/strong&gt;: October 2015&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree qualification in accounting/finance/program management or other relevant discipline. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in education and training programs in developing country contexts, preferably in the Pacific. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in working in development programs and supporting high level financial and technical reporting documentation to donor and government agencies. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in managing budgets in line with contractual and corporate requirements. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in providing administrative, logistical and technical support to consultants who are providing technical assistance services. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated competency in the use of MS Word, MS Program, MS Excel, email and the Internet. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in the contract management of donor funded Programs. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in working in Solomon Islands. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Solomon Islands Pijin.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High level written and oral communication skills. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to develop strong working relationships in cross-cultural multi-lingual environments. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to liaise with a range of government and non-government stakeholders. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to deal with politically sensitive issues. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven problem-solving skills. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to apply&lt;/strong&gt;:
If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in DFAT format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:William_rogerson@dai.com&quot;&gt;William_rogerson@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting Solomon Islands in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please not that due to high volumes of applications, only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline for Application&lt;/strong&gt;: 25th June 2015&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;**Please note that all profiles are indicative only and subject to change once the ToR is made available.&lt;/em&gt;* &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skills Development Adviser </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/skills-development-adviser</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/skills-development-adviser</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DFAT’s new investment in vocational skills is designed to help close the gap between industry demand for, and Solomon Islands&amp;#39; supply of skilled labour. The Skills for Economic Growth program aims to shift Solomon Islands’ current technical vocational training system from a postcolonial supply driven model to a suite of demand driven training that meets the needs of industry and fills critical skills shortages. The program will include support to the Ministry for Education to develop a new national qualifications framework and a gradual shift to competency based training. There will be tangible investments in developing the quality of courses in high need areas such as in construction, trades, tourism, and early childhood. As well as working in the formal employment sector, there will also be a focus on linking short courses to small business development in the informal economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectives of the role&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In collaboration with provincial governments and provincial productive sector departments develop and implement flexible approaches to skill development that is directly linked to provincial economic development priorities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Length of the project&lt;/strong&gt;: 24 - 48 Months
&lt;strong&gt;Start Date&lt;/strong&gt;: October 2015
&lt;strong&gt;ARF Level&lt;/strong&gt;: B3&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A degree in education and training. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skills and experience with provincially based skills development planning and quality based, demand driven training delivery in developing countries, preferably in Pacific Island contexts. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in the analysis of provincial economic development priorities and in designing appropriate skill development responses. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in preparing strategic planning documentation and reporting for Government agencies. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated professional commitment to inclusive processes and experience in developing gender and disability sensitive programs and activities. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competency in the use of MS Word, MS Excel, email and the Internet. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in a provincial setting in the Pacific, preferably Solomon Islands. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in training provider management or equivalent level post-school education and training institution in a developing country.. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong monitoring and evaluation experience in a development context. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong financial skills including preparation and management of budgets and provision of financial reporting. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to converse in Solomon Islands Pijin &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A first aid qualification &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent cross-cultural communication skills, both oral and written. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to establish strong working relationships with a range of government and industry stakeholders. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to provide leadership and professional direction within a small but relatively complex environment. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to develop and maintain professional and industry networks. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to deal with politically and culturally sensitive issues. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly developed problem solving skills. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to apply&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in DFAT format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:William_rogerson@dai.com&quot;&gt;William_rogerson@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting Solomon Islands in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please not that due to high volumes of applications, only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline for Application:&lt;/strong&gt; 25th June 2015&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;**Please note that all profiles are indicative only and subject to change once the ToR is made available *&lt;/em&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior TVET Adviser</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-tvet-adviser</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 15:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-tvet-adviser</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DFAT’s new investment in vocational skills is designed to help close the gap between industry demand for, and Solomon Islands&amp;#39; supply of skilled labour. The Skills for Economic Growth program aims to shift Solomon Islands’ current technical vocational training system from a postcolonial supply driven model to a suite of demand driven training that meets the needs of industry and fills critical skills shortages. The program will include support to the Ministry for Education to develop a new national qualifications framework and a gradual shift to competency based training. There will be tangible investments in developing the quality of courses in high need areas such as in construction, trades, tourism, and early childhood. As well as working in the formal employment sector, there will also be a focus on linking short courses to small business development in the informal economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectives of the role:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Work closely with the management of the Solomon Islands National University (SINU) and the School of Technology and Maritime Studies (STMS) as Senior TVET Adviser and principal counterpart to the Dean of the STMS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Length of the project&lt;/strong&gt;: 24 - 48 Months
&lt;strong&gt;Start Date&lt;/strong&gt;: October 2015
&lt;strong&gt;ARF Level: B3&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A degree in education and training. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Senior-level experience in the management of a TVET or equivalent level post-secondary education and training institution. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;TVET planning and quality based, demand driven training delivery in developing countries, preferably in Pacific Island contexts. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in labour market analysis and in designing training in response to identified labour market demand. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated professional commitment to inclusive processes and experience in developing gender and disability sensitive programs and activities. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competency in the use of MS Word, MS Excel, email and the Internet. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in the Pacific, preferably Solomon Islands. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in preparing strategic planning documentation and reporting for Government agencies. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and understanding of Commonwealth Government contracting and procurement policies and procedures. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A first aid qualification &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent cross-cultural communication skills, both oral and written. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to establish strong working relationships with a range of government and industry stakeholders. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to provide leadership and professional direction within a small but relatively complex environment. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to develop and maintain professional and industry networks. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to deal with politically and culturally sensitive issues. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly developed problem solving skills. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to apply&lt;/strong&gt;:
If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please apply via the following link &lt;a href=&quot;http://chc.tbe.taleo.net/chc06/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=2064&quot;&gt;http://chc.tbe.taleo.net/chc06/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=2064&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please not that due to high volumes of applications, only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline for Application&lt;/strong&gt;: 25th June 2015&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;**Please note that all profiles are indicative only and subject to change once the ToR is made available.&lt;/em&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert en Gestion Transparente de Ressources Naturelles en Milieu Forestiers</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-gestion-transparente-de-ressources-naturelles-en-milieu-forestiers</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 07:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-gestion-transparente-de-ressources-naturelles-en-milieu-forestiers</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général de la présente mission est d&amp;#39;appuyer le gouvernement du Cameroun dans:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;L&amp;#39;évaluation finale de la Convention de Financement &amp;ldquo;Appui à la gouvernance forestière au Cameroun à travers une contribution à la mise en œuvre du processus FLEGT&amp;rdquo; (FED/2008/020-957)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;La préparation des programmes/projets relatifs à la gouvernance des ressources naturelles dans le cadre du 11ème Fonds Européen de Développement (FED). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La prestation comprendra deux volets distincts : i) évaluation finale de la Convention de Financement FED/2008/020-957 et ii) préparation d&amp;#39;une action relative à la gouvernance des ressources naturelles du 11ème Fonds Européen de Développement (FED). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les objectifs particuliers de la présente mission sont:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Volet &amp;ldquo;Evaluation finale de la Convention de Financement FED/2008/020-957&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;De manière spécifique les objectifs de l&amp;#39;évaluation finale sont les suivants:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Procéder à un état des lieux des réalisations des trois contrats d&amp;#39;assistance technique ainsi que des engagements spécifiques pour l&amp;#39;acquisition de matériel  mis en œuvre dans le cadre de la Convention de Financement &amp;ldquo;Appui à la gouvernance forestière au Cameroun à travers une contribution à la mise en œuvre du processus FLEGT&amp;rdquo; (FED/2008/020-957)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyser la qualité des livrables des différentes interventions &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluer la pertinence, l’efficacité, l’efficience, l’impact de la mise en œuvre, les principales contraintes, les problèmes rencontrés ainsi que l&amp;#39;engagement du Maître d&amp;#39;ouvrage (MINEPAT) et du Maître d&amp;#39;œuvre (MINFOF) et son degré d’appropriation du Projet&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Déterminer si les éléments d&amp;#39;appropriation, de durabilité et de viabilité, autant techniques que financiers, des acquis de ces différentes interventions sont suffisants pour amélioration la gouvernance des ressources forestières sur le moyen et le long terme&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Volet &amp;quot;Préparation du 11ème FED&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;De manière spécifique l&amp;#39;objectif de la préparation des programmes/projets relatifs à la gouvernance des ressources naturelles dans le cadre du 11ème Fonds Européen de Développement (FED) est le suivant:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifier et formuler un programme dans le domaine de la gouvernance des ressources naturelles ainsi que produire l&amp;#39;ensemble de documents de projet nécessaires (Document d&amp;#39;Action avec comme parties intégrantes notamment les Dispositions Techniques et Administratifs et ses annexes).&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Le but est donc de réaliser sur la base de consultations élargies un diagnostic de la gouvernance des ressources naturelles, d&amp;#39;identifier les priorités d&amp;#39;action sur la base des critères de cohérence avec la vision stratégique sectorielle du Cameroun, d&amp;#39;efficience et de la valeur ajoutée et faire la formulation du projet en proposant des options pour la mise en œuvre adéquate et réaliste sous la forme de programme ou projets concrets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sans être restrictif, les principaux volets d’intervention suivants devront être considérés et coordonnés dans les objectifs du programme:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appui à la mise en œuvre de l’APV-FLEGT sur la base des activités déjà engagées dans les domaines suivants :&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appui à la représentation et la participation de tous les groupes d’acteurs du secteur forestier dans la mise en œuvre de l’Accord ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appui à la mobilisation d’une nouvelle phase de l’Auditeur Indépendant du système FLEGT ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Poursuite du déploiement du Système Informatique de Gestion de l&amp;#39;Information Forestière (SIGIF) ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appui à au développement des synergies entre les pays de la sous-région au regard des flux de bois en transit ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appui à la mise en œuvre de l’Annexe de l’APV sur les informations du secteur forestier à rendre publique ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appui à la formalisation du secteur artisanal et des PME du secteur forestier et de la première et seconde transformation ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluation indépendante du système de vérification de la légalité ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appui à la réalisation du suivi des impacts de l&amp;#39;APV ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Renforcement des synergies entre mécanismes FLEGT et REDD  dans les domaines où elles sont pertinentes ;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Soutien aux initiatives d’Observation Indépendante (OI) du secteur forestier et (y compris le mécanisme d&amp;#39;OI institutionnelle)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Soutien aux initiatives d’Observation Indépendante du secteur minier&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Appui à la politique d’aménagement du territoire dans les secteurs agricoles et forestiers en rapport avec l’exploitation des ressources naturelles et les filières agro-industrielles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Développement des initiatives anti-corruption et de renforcement de la transparence dans la gestion et l’exploitation des ressources naturelles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Appui à la mise en œuvre de l&amp;#39;Initiative de Transparence des Industries Extractives (ITIE) au Cameroun en lien avec les initiatives déjà existantes (Projet PRECASEM de la BM etc.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Renforcement de la responsabilité sociale des industries extractives au Cameroun en lien avec les initiatives déjà existantes (Projet REMAP de la GIZ etc.) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Promotion des initiatives améliorant la gouvernance des ressources naturelles au Cameroun (renforcement de la compétitivité des industries extractives)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recommandation pour l&amp;#39;adaptation du cadre législatif national et de l&amp;#39;APV-FLEGT et renforcement des législations des administrations partenaires du MINFOF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;****Appui aux initiatives permettant une amélioration de la protection des ressources faunistiques &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expert en Gestion Transparente de Ressources Naturelles en Milieu Forestiers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Titulaire d&amp;#39;un diplôme universitaire en agroéconomie, économie, foresterie ou équivalent de niveau Bac + 4 minimum (critère minimal);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum de 10 ans d&amp;#39;expérience professionnelle dans le secteur concerné (critère minimal);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en suivi-évaluation de projets de développement ou dans l&amp;#39;instruction et/ou la mise en œuvre de projets dans un domaine pertinent par rapport au contrat évalué dans plusieurs pays (minimum deux pays) en Afrique subsaharienne (10 points);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance et expérience avec les procédures de programmation du (critère minimal);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience pratique d&amp;#39;évaluation des projets financés par le FED et la maitrise du Guide de Gestion de Cycle de Projets constitue un atout (5 points);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonne connaissance technique en termes de définition des stratégies sectorielles et de politiques de développement pour promouvoir la bonne gouvernance de ces secteurs (10 points);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne connaissance du FLEGT, EITI, processus de Kimberley et d&amp;#39;autres initiatives visant à promouvoir la bonne gouvernance (10 points);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise dans l&amp;#39;analyse des problèmes, des parties prenantes et la préparation des cadres logiques est obligatoire (5 points);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;La compréhension des questions de gouvernance des ressources naturelles au Cameroun constitue un atout (5 points);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une bonne connaissance de la langue française et de l&amp;#39;anglais à l&amp;#39;oral et à l&amp;#39;écrit est indispensable (critère minimal);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Disponibilité pour voyager à l&amp;#39;intérieur du Cameroun, notamment dans les zones concernées par l&amp;#39;exploitation forestière, minière et agro-industrielle &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;Nicte_Garcia-Soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef de mission: Expert en Gestion des Ressources Forestières et FLEGT </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-expert-en-gestion-des-ressources-forestieres-et-flegt</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 07:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-expert-en-gestion-des-ressources-forestieres-et-flegt</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général de la présente mission est d&amp;#39;appuyer le gouvernement du Cameroun dans:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;L&amp;#39;évaluation finale de la Convention de Financement &amp;ldquo;Appui à la gouvernance forestière au Cameroun à travers une contribution à la mise en œuvre du processus FLEGT&amp;rdquo; (FED/2008/020-957)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;La préparation des programmes/projets relatifs à la gouvernance des ressources naturelles dans le cadre du 11ème Fonds Européen de Développement (FED). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La prestation comprendra deux volets distincts : i) évaluation finale de la Convention de Financement FED/2008/020-957 et ii) préparation d&amp;#39;une action relative à la gouvernance des ressources naturelles du 11ème Fonds Européen de Développement (FED). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les objectifs particuliers de la présente mission sont:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Volet &amp;ldquo;Evaluation finale de la Convention de Financement FED/2008/020-957&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;De manière spécifique les objectifs de l&amp;#39;évaluation finale sont les suivants:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Procéder à un état des lieux des réalisations des trois contrats d&amp;#39;assistance technique ainsi que des engagements spécifiques pour l&amp;#39;acquisition de matériel  mis en œuvre dans le cadre de la Convention de Financement &amp;ldquo;Appui à la gouvernance forestière au Cameroun à travers une contribution à la mise en œuvre du processus FLEGT&amp;rdquo; (FED/2008/020-957)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyser la qualité des livrables des différentes interventions &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluer la pertinence, l’efficacité, l’efficience, l’impact de la mise en œuvre, les principales contraintes, les problèmes rencontrés ainsi que l&amp;#39;engagement du Maître d&amp;#39;ouvrage (MINEPAT) et du Maître d&amp;#39;œuvre (MINFOF) et son degré d’appropriation du Projet&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Déterminer si les éléments d&amp;#39;appropriation, de durabilité et de viabilité, autant techniques que financiers, des acquis de ces différentes interventions sont suffisants pour amélioration la gouvernance des ressources forestières sur le moyen et le long terme&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Volet &amp;quot;Préparation du 11ème FED&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;De manière spécifique l&amp;#39;objectif de la préparation des programmes/projets relatifs à la gouvernance des ressources naturelles dans le cadre du 11ème Fonds Européen de Développement (FED) est le suivant:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifier et formuler un programme dans le domaine de la gouvernance des ressources naturelles ainsi que produire l&amp;#39;ensemble de documents de projet nécessaires (Document d&amp;#39;Action avec comme parties intégrantes notamment les Dispositions Techniques et Administratifs et ses annexes).&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Le but est donc de réaliser sur la base de consultations élargies un diagnostic de la gouvernance des ressources naturelles, d&amp;#39;identifier les priorités d&amp;#39;action sur la base des critères de cohérence avec la vision stratégique sectorielle du Cameroun, d&amp;#39;efficience et de la valeur ajoutée et faire la formulation du projet en proposant des options pour la mise en œuvre adéquate et réaliste sous la forme de programme ou projets concrets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sans être restrictif, les principaux volets d’intervention suivants devront être considérés et coordonnés dans les objectifs du programme:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appui à la mise en œuvre de l’APV-FLEGT sur la base des activités déjà engagées dans les domaines suivants :&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appui à la représentation et la participation de tous les groupes d’acteurs du secteur forestier dans la mise en œuvre de l’Accord ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appui à la mobilisation d’une nouvelle phase de l’Auditeur Indépendant du système FLEGT ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Poursuite du déploiement du Système Informatique de Gestion de l&amp;#39;Information Forestière (SIGIF) ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appui à au développement des synergies entre les pays de la sous-région au regard des flux de bois en transit ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appui à la mise en œuvre de l’Annexe de l’APV sur les informations du secteur forestier à rendre publique ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appui à la formalisation du secteur artisanal et des PME du secteur forestier et de la première et seconde transformation ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluation indépendante du système de vérification de la légalité ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appui à la réalisation du suivi des impacts de l&amp;#39;APV ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Renforcement des synergies entre mécanismes FLEGT et REDD  dans les domaines où elles sont pertinentes ;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Soutien aux initiatives d’Observation Indépendante (OI) du secteur forestier et (y compris le mécanisme d&amp;#39;OI institutionnelle)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Soutien aux initiatives d’Observation Indépendante du secteur minier&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;amp; Appui à la politique d’aménagement du territoire dans les secteurs agricoles et forestiers en rapport avec l’exploitation des ressources naturelles et les filières agro-industrielles&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Développement des initiatives anti-corruption et de renforcement de la transparence dans la gestion et l’exploitation des ressources naturelles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Appui à la mise en œuvre de l&amp;#39;Initiative de Transparence des Industries Extractives (ITIE) au Cameroun en lien avec les initiatives déjà existantes (Projet PRECASEM de la BM etc.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Renforcement de la responsabilité sociale des industries extractives au Cameroun en lien avec les initiatives déjà existantes (Projet REMAP de la GIZ etc.) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Promotion des initiatives améliorant la gouvernance des ressources naturelles au Cameroun (renforcement de la compétitivité des industries extractives)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recommandation pour l&amp;#39;adaptation du cadre législatif national et de l&amp;#39;APV-FLEGT et renforcement des législations des administrations partenaires du MINFOF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Appui aux initiatives permettant une amélioration de la protection des ressources faunistiques &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chef de mission: Expert en Gestion des Ressources Forestières et FLEGT&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Titulaire d&amp;#39;un diplôme universitaire en agroéconomie, économie, foresterie ou équivalent de niveau Bac + 4 minimum (critère minimal) ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum de 15 ans d&amp;#39;expérience professionnelle dans le secteur concerné (critère minimal);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en suivi-évaluation de projets de développement ou dans l&amp;#39;instruction et/ou la mise en œuvre de projets dans un domaine pertinent par rapport au contrat évalué dans plusieurs pays (minimum trois pays) en Afrique subsaharienne (15 points);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance et expérience avec les procédures de programmation du FED (critère minimal);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience pratique d&amp;#39;évaluation des projets financés par le FED et la maitrise du Guide de Gestion de Cycle de Projets constitue un atout (10 points);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonne connaissance technique en termes de définition des stratégies sectorielles et de politiques de développement pour promouvoir la bonne gouvernance (5 points);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne connaissance du FLEGT et d&amp;#39;autres initiatives visant à promouvoir la bonne gouvernance (10 points);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise dans l&amp;#39;analyse des problèmes, des parties prenantes et la préparation des cadres logiques est obligatoire (5 points);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;La préparation de programmes/projets d&amp;#39;assistance technique et de renforcement des capacités dans le domaine la gouvernance des ressources naturelles sera considérée comme un atout (5 points);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;La compréhension des questions de gouvernance des ressources naturelles au Cameroun constitue un atout (5 points);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une bonne connaissance de la langue française et de l&amp;#39;anglais à l&amp;#39;oral et à l&amp;#39;écrit est indispensable (critère minimal);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Disponibilité pour voyager à l&amp;#39;intérieur du Cameroun, notamment dans les zones concernées par l&amp;#39;exploitation forestière, minière et agro-industrielle &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;Nicte_Garcia-Soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team 4  - Justice Reform Expert </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-4-justice-reform-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2015 12:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-4-justice-reform-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The mid-term evaluation of 3 projects (Drugs and Crime, Anti-corruption and Justice) will provide the EU and other partners with an assessment of the projects&amp;#39; performance and recommendations on how to improve the intervention to achieve expected goals and outcomes taking into account problems and opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team 4  - Justice Reform Expert (25 working days)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University Degree (Academic level) in Law, Political Science or a relevant, directly related discipline, or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience as programme manager/expert in the Justice sector, or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effective verbal and written communication skills and ability to write reports in a clear and concise manner in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Sub-Saharan Africa;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 3 years&amp;#39; experience in project management and evaluation of development project in complex political environments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of professional experience as programme manager/expert in the Rule of Law, Justice Sector Reform, Police or Prison reform, or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with capacity development projects as per guidance provided by the &amp;ldquo;EU backbone strategy&amp;rdquo; (&lt;a href=&quot;http://ec.europa.eu/development/icenter/repository/backbone_strategy_technical_cooperation_en.pdf&quot;&gt;http://ec.europa.eu/development/icenter/repository/backbone_strategy_technical_cooperation_en.pdf&lt;/a&gt;) and the &amp;ldquo;Guidelines on &amp;quot;Making technical cooperation more effective&amp;rdquo;&amp;ldquo; (&lt;a href=&quot;http://ec.europa.eu/europeaid/how/ensure-aideffectiveness/&quot;&gt;http://ec.europa.eu/europeaid/how/ensure-aideffectiveness/&lt;/a&gt;
documents/guidelines&lt;em&gt;on&lt;/em&gt;tc&lt;em&gt;finale&lt;/em&gt;en.pdf).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with international standards and methods regarding justice delivery and justice sector reform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly developed interpersonal skills to relate to counterparts on all levels of hierarchy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IT literate, very good data-processing knowledge, and of office automation software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in communication, negotiation and dialogue at high level&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:benjamin_symonds@dai.com&quot;&gt;benjamin_symonds@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team 4 – Justice Team Leader </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-4-justice-team-leader</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2015 12:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-4-justice-team-leader</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The mid-term evaluation of 3 projects (Drugs and Crime, Anti-corruption and Justice) will provide the EU and other partners with an assessment of the projects&amp;#39; performance and recommendations on how to improve the intervention to achieve expected goals and outcomes taking into account problems and opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team 4 – Justice Team Leader (25 working days)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master Degree (Academic level) in Law, Political Science or a relevant,directly related discipline, or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in monitoring and evaluation of large development project in complex political environments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience as programme manager/expert in Rule of Law, Justice Sector Reform, or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 12 years of professional experience as programme manager/expert in the Rule of Law, Justice Sector Reform, Police or Prison reform, or equivalent; at international level (worked in at least two countries) some of which should have been acquired in a developing country&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 7 years of professional experience in leading missions for project
evaluations &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 3 years’ experience with EDF programming procedures will be an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with capacity development projects as per guidance provided by the &amp;ldquo;EU backbone strategy&amp;rdquo; (&lt;a href=&quot;http://ec.europa.eu/development/icenter/repository/backbone_strategy_technical_cooperation_en.pdf&quot;&gt;http://ec.europa.eu/development/icenter/repository/backbone_strategy_technical_cooperation_en.pdf&lt;/a&gt;) and the &amp;ldquo;Guidelines on &amp;quot;Making technical cooperation more effective&amp;rdquo;&amp;ldquo; (&lt;a href=&quot;http://ec.europa.eu/europeaid/how/ensure-aideffectiveness/&quot;&gt;http://ec.europa.eu/europeaid/how/ensure-aideffectiveness/&lt;/a&gt;
documents/guidelines&lt;em&gt;on&lt;/em&gt;tc&lt;em&gt;finale&lt;/em&gt;en.pdf)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with international standards and methods regarding justice delivery and justice sector reform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative ability to identify practical solutions to overcome challenges to time-critical projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent interpersonal skills to relate to counterparts on all levels of hierarchy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IT literate, very good data-processing knowledge, and of office automation software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in communication, negotiation and dialogue at high level&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:benjamin_symonds@dai.com&quot;&gt;benjamin_symonds@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team 3 – Anti-corruption Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-3-anti-corruption-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2015 11:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-3-anti-corruption-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The mid-term evaluation of 3 projects (Drugs and Crime, Anti-corruption and Justice) will provide the EU and other partners with an assessment of the projects&amp;#39; performance and recommendations on how to improve the intervention to achieve expected goals and outcomes taking into account problems and opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team 3 – Anti-corruption Expert (25 working days)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in Law, Political Science, or other related social science disciplines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project management and/or evaluation of development project in developing countries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effective verbal and written communication skills and ability to write reports in a clear and concise manner in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of anti-corruption professional experience at international level, some of which should have been acquired in a developing country&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 6 years’ experience in participatory planning and management of large anti-corruption projects in complex political environments, including specific working experience in law enforcement, dealing with anti-corruption cases&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 5 years&amp;#39; experience in project management and/or evaluation of development project in developing countries &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with working with civil society groups is an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in donors-government co-ordination and strategic understanding to ensure overall coordination of the project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative ability to identify practical solutions to overcome challenges to time-critical projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly developed interpersonal skills to constructively interact with stakeholders at all levels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge/Experience in Nigeria and/or West Africa or similar countries is an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:benjamin_symonds@dai.com&quot;&gt;benjamin_symonds@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert II- Capacity Building and Institutional Development</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-ii-capacity-building-and-institutional-development</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-ii-capacity-building-and-institutional-development</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The global objective is to assess and continually improve the quality of EU assistance projects in order to support better Mozambique&amp;rsquo;s development efforts. There are 2 Key experts allocated 39 working days each, with an additional 10 to be allocated to the Expert acting as Team Leader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is required that at least one of the experts has team leader experience combined with a very good experience in evaluations, as he/she will be the team leader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert II- Capacity Building and Institutional Development&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in economics, law, development studies, public administration, ICT engineering or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 12 years of professional experience in development cooperation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience in:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;evaluation of learning and training interventions,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;monitoring and evaluation of capacity development projects and programmes, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;cost-benefit analysis of programmes, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in performance management systems, organisational and institutional capacity assessment,&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in conducting evaluations of EU funded projects is an advantage. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent management, drafting and communication skills in English, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic Portuguese for reading reports and day to day communication.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:benjamin_symonds@dai.com&quot;&gt;benjamin_symonds@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert I, Law Enforcement and Security</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-i-law-enforcement-and-security</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 14:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-i-law-enforcement-and-security</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The global objective is to assess and continually improve the quality of EU assistance projects in order to support better Mozambique&amp;rsquo;s development efforts. There are 2 Key experts allocated 39 working days each, with an additional 10 to be allocated to the Expert acting as Team Leader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is required that at least one of the experts has team leader experience combined with a very good experience in evaluations, as he/she will be the team leader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert I, Law Enforcement and Security&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in law enforcement administration, criminology, forensics, social sciences, socio-psychology or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Senior expert with at least 15 years of professional experience in the field of security or law enforcement is required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience in&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;police service delivery improvement, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;change management and reform of police services, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;crime prevention, national crime strategies, crime scene investigation, laboratory and educational products, fingerprint identification systems, forensic databases,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;evaluation of learning and training interventions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellent drafting and communication skills in English. Portuguese is an advantage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience in developing countries with democratisation, rule of law, security, justice is an advantage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:benjamin_symonds@dai.com&quot;&gt;benjamin_symonds@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team 3 – Anti-corruption Team Leader </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-3-anti-corruption-team-leader</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 14:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-3-anti-corruption-team-leader</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The mid-term evaluation of 3 projects (Drugs and Crime, Anti-corruption and Justice) will provide the EU and other partners with an assessment of the projects&amp;#39; performance and recommendations on how to improve the intervention to achieve expected goals and outcomes taking into account problems and opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team 3 – Anti-corruption Team Leader (25 working days)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in law, political/social sciences or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years’ Experience in monitoring and evaluation of large development projects in complex political environments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 12 years professional experience in monitoring anti-corruption related projects and/or implementation of activities at international level (worked in at least two countries) some of which should have been acquired in a developing country&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 7 years’ experience in at least in three of the following anti-corruption areas: law enforcement, prosecution, prevention, reform and procurement and with specific expertise in designing technical assistance, capacity development and training programmes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effective verbal and written communication skills and ability to write reports in a clear and concise manner in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 7 years of professional experience in leading missions for project
evaluations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 3 years’ experience with EDF programming procedures will be an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of anti-corruption legislation, policies and strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in problem analysis, stakeholders&amp;#39; analysis and preparation of Log frames&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge/Experience in Nigeria and/or West Africa or similar countries is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full working knowledge of English, as well as excellent field research report writing and communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:benjamin_symonds@dai.com&quot;&gt;benjamin_symonds@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team 2 – Drugs/Organised Crime/Public Health Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-2-drugs-organised-crime-public-health-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 14:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-2-drugs-organised-crime-public-health-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The mid-term evaluation of 3 projects (Drugs and Crime, Anti-corruption and Justice) will provide the EU and other partners with an assessment of the projects&amp;#39; performance and recommendations on how to improve the intervention to achieve expected goals and outcomes taking into account problems and opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team 2 – Drugs/Organised Crime/Public Health Specialist (25 working days)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A University Degree in Public Health, Law, Political Science, Development Cooperation or relevant, directly related discipline, or equivalent &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project management and evaluation of development projects in developing countries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effective verbal and written communication skills and ability to write reports in a clear and concise manner in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 6 years of professional experience as programme manager/expert in Drugs and/or Crime Prevention, Health and Social Protection related sectors, or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with capacity development projects as per guidance provided by the &amp;ldquo;EU backbone strategy&amp;rdquo;
(&lt;a href=&quot;http://ec.europa.eu/development/icenter/repository/backbone_strategy_technical_cooperation_en.pdf&quot;&gt;http://ec.europa.eu/development/icenter/repository/backbone_strategy_technical_cooperation_en.pdf&lt;/a&gt;) and the &amp;ldquo;Guidelines on &amp;quot;Making technical cooperation more effective&amp;rdquo;&amp;ldquo; (&lt;a href=&quot;http://ec.europa.eu/europeaid/how/ensure-aideffectiveness/&quot;&gt;http://ec.europa.eu/europeaid/how/ensure-aideffectiveness/&lt;/a&gt;
documents/guidelines&lt;em&gt;on&lt;/em&gt;tc&lt;em&gt;finale&lt;/em&gt;en.pdf).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with international standards and methods regarding drug related health and social sector reforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly developed interpersonal skills to relate to counterparts on all levels of hierarchy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IT literate, very good data-processing knowledge, and of office automation software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in communication, negotiation and dialogue at high level&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:benjamin_symonds@dai.com&quot;&gt;benjamin_symonds@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team 2 – Drugs and Organised Crime Team Leader</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-2-drugs-and-organised-crime-team-leader</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 14:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-2-drugs-and-organised-crime-team-leader</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The mid-term evaluation of 3 projects (Drugs and Crime, Anti-corruption and Justice) will provide the EU and other partners with an assessment of the projects&amp;#39; performance and recommendations on how to improve the intervention to achieve expected goals and outcomes taking into account problems and opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Team 2 – Drugs and Organised Crime Team Leader (25 working days)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master Degree (Academic level) in Public Health, Law, Political Science, Development Cooperation or relevant, directly related discipline, or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in monitoring and evaluation of large development project in complex political environments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effective verbal and written communication skills and ability to write reports in a clear and concise manner in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 12 years of professional experience as programme manager/expert in the fight against drugs and related crime sector, or equivalent; and/or implementation of activities at international level (worked in at least two countries) some of which should have been acquired in a developing country&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 7 years of professional experience in leading missions for project evaluations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 3 years&amp;#39; experience with EDF programming procedures will be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with capacity development projects as per guidance provided by the &amp;ldquo;EU backbone strategy&amp;rdquo;
(&lt;a href=&quot;http://ec.europa.eu/development/icenter/repository/backbone_strategy_technical_cooperation_en.pdf&quot;&gt;http://ec.europa.eu/development/icenter/repository/backbone_strategy_technical_cooperation_en.pdf&lt;/a&gt;) and the &amp;ldquo;Guidelines on &amp;quot;Making technical cooperation more effective&amp;rdquo;&amp;ldquo; (&lt;a href=&quot;http://ec.europa.eu/europeaid/how/ensure-aideffectiveness/&quot;&gt;http://ec.europa.eu/europeaid/how/ensure-aideffectiveness/&lt;/a&gt;
documents/guidelines&lt;em&gt;on&lt;/em&gt;tc&lt;em&gt;finale&lt;/em&gt;en.pdf)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with international standards and methods regarding fight against drugs and related crime sector reform, especially with regards to legal aspects and law enforcement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven field research and report writing skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative ability to identify practical solutions to overcome challenges to time-critical projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent interpersonal skills to relate to counterparts on all levels of hierarchy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IT literate, very good data-processing knowledge, and of office automation software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in communication, negotiation and dialogue at high level&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:benjamin_symonds@dai.com&quot;&gt;benjamin_symonds@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team 1 – Organisational Development Specialist </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-1-organisational-development-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 13:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-1-organisational-development-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The mid-term evaluation of 3 projects (Drugs and Crime, Anti-corruption and Justice) will provide the EU and other partners with an assessment of the projects&amp;#39; performance and recommendations on how to improve the intervention to achieve expected goals and outcomes taking into account problems and opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team 1 – Organisational Development Specialist (25 working days)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A University Degree (Academic level) in Public Administration, Business Administration, Law, Political Science, Development Cooperation or relevant, directly related discipline, or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience in monitoring and evaluation of development projects in
developing countries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effective verbal and written communication skills and ability to write reports in a clear and concise manner in English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 6 years of experience with organisational and institutional development and efficiency, preferably in an UN environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Sub-Saharan Africa&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with capacity development projects as per guidance provided by the &amp;ldquo;EU backbone strategy&amp;rdquo;
(&lt;a href=&quot;http://ec.europa.eu/development/icenter/repository/backbone_strategy_technical_cooperation_en.pdf&quot;&gt;http://ec.europa.eu/development/icenter/repository/backbone_strategy_technical_cooperation_en.pdf&lt;/a&gt;) and the &amp;ldquo;Guidelines on &amp;quot;Making technical cooperation more effective&amp;rdquo;&amp;ldquo; (&lt;a href=&quot;http://ec.europa.eu/europeaid/how/ensure-aideffectiveness/&quot;&gt;http://ec.europa.eu/europeaid/how/ensure-aideffectiveness/&lt;/a&gt;
documents/guidelines&lt;em&gt;on&lt;/em&gt;tc&lt;em&gt;finale&lt;/em&gt;en.pdf).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven field research and report writing skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative ability to identify practical solutions to overcome challenges to time-critical projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent interpersonal skills to relate to counterparts on all levels of hierarchy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IT literate, very good data-processing knowledge, and of office automation software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in communication, negotiation and dialogue at high level&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:benjamin_symonds@dai.com&quot;&gt;benjamin_symonds@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team 1 – Organisational Development Specialist; Evaluation Team Leader</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-1-organisational-development-specialist-evaluation-team-leader</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 13:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-1-organisational-development-specialist-evaluation-team-leader</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The mid-tem evaluation of 3 projects (Drugs and Crime, Anti-corruption and Justice) will provide the EU and other partners with an assessment of the projects&amp;#39; performance and recommendations on how to improve the intervention to achieve expected goals and outcomes taking into account problems and opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team 1 – Organisational Development Specialist; Evaluation Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; (25 working days)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master Degree (Academic level) in Management, Business Administration Project and Programme Management, Finance Management, Public Administration, Political Science, Law or relevant, directly related discipline, or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in monitoring and evaluation of large development projects in complex political environments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 12 years of professional experience with organisational and institutional development and efficiency, and project/programme management preferably in a UN environment; and/or implementation of activities at international level (worked in at least two countries) some of which should have been acquired in a developing country&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effective verbal and written communication skills and ability to write reports in a clear and concise manner in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with capacity development projects as per guidance provided by the &amp;ldquo;EU backbone strategy&amp;rdquo; 
(&lt;a href=&quot;http://ec.europa.eu/development/icenter/repository/backbone_strategy_technical&quot;&gt;http://ec.europa.eu/development/icenter/repository/backbone_strategy_technical&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;em&gt;cooperation&lt;/em&gt;en.pdf) and the &amp;ldquo;Guidelines on &amp;quot;Making technical cooperation more effective&amp;rdquo;&amp;ldquo; (&lt;a href=&quot;http://ec.europa.eu/europeaid/how/ensure-aideffectiveness/&quot;&gt;http://ec.europa.eu/europeaid/how/ensure-aideffectiveness/&lt;/a&gt;
documents/guidelines&lt;em&gt;on&lt;/em&gt;tc&lt;em&gt;finale&lt;/em&gt;en.pdf)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with international standards and methods regarding good governance and rule of law &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with contractual and tender procedures in United Nations Environment;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 3 years&amp;#39; experience with EDF programming procedures will be an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven field research and report writing skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative ability to identify practical solutions to overcome challenges to time-criticalprojects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent interpersonal skills to relate to counterparts on all levels of hierarchy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IT literate, very good data-processing knowledge, and of office automation software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in communication, negotiation and dialogue at high level&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:benjamin_symonds@dai.com&quot;&gt;benjamin_symonds@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert en Processus Electoraux (Cat. I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-processus-electoraux-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 10:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-processus-electoraux-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Le projet a comme objectif l’appui du Gouvernement et de la CENI dans la préparation des élections du Président de l’Union et des Gouverneur des îles autonomes, afin de garantir le droit de vote a tous les citoyens comoriens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Le projet a comme objectif aussi identifier les modalités les plus adaptées et les moyens techniques et financiers qui permettront au Gouvernement de l’Union des Comores et a la CENI de réviser et de compléter le fichier électoral en prévision des scrutins de 2015/2016, en conformité avec les dispositions du code électoral en vigueur et les recommandations des missions d’observation électorale déployées lors des scrutins du 25 janvier et 22 février 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert en Processus Electoraux (cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Niveau académique master (BAC+5) ou 14 ans d’expérience dans des domaines liés à la gouvernance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;12 ans d’expérience professionnelle, dont au moins 4 ans d’expérience dans le domaine électoral (préférablement expérience précédente dans la révision des listes électorales).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expérience précédent comme chef d’équipe sur des projets similaires à l’international.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assessors – Experience in Rural Development/Food Security in Sub-Saharan Africa </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/assessors-experience-in-rural-development-food-security-in-sub-saharan-africa</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 11:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/assessors-experience-in-rural-development-food-security-in-sub-saharan-africa</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The objective is to recruit assessors to assist the Contracting Authority in the selection of the best proposals received under &amp;ldquo;Pro-Resilience Action (PRO-ACT): building resilience through crisis prevention and post-crisis response strategy&amp;rdquo; and to achieve a high-quality, complete and coherent selection process of projects in line with the criteria set in the Guidelines for applicants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Project duration: 180 days&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assessors – Experience in Rural Development/Food Security in Sub-Saharan Africa (25 working days per expert)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s Degree in relevant subject.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years’ experience gained in sectors 9 and 10: Rural Development and Food Security.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years’ experience in Sub-Saharan Africa.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience participating in the selection of grant recipients as an assessor on behalf of a national authorising officer or an international organisation is essential.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work experience in post-conflict areas, in particular in fragile states.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very good knowledge of project cycle management and of EU grants contract procedures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work experience in South Sudan is an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:benjamin_symonds@dai.com&quot;&gt;benjamin_symonds@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert with Experience in BENEF Lot 1 and Selection of Grant Recipients (Team Leader)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-with-experience-in-benef-lot-1-and-selection-of-grant-recipients-team-leader</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 11:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-with-experience-in-benef-lot-1-and-selection-of-grant-recipients-team-leader</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The objective is to recruit assessors to assist the Contracting Authority in the selection of the best proposals received under &amp;ldquo;Pro-Resilience Action (PRO-ACT): building resilience through crisis prevention and post-crisis response strategy&amp;rdquo; and to achieve a high-quality, complete and coherent selection process of projects in line with the criteria set in the Guidelines for applicants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duration of project&lt;/strong&gt;: 180 days&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Senior Expert with Experience in BENEF Lot 1 and Selection of Grant Recipients (Team Leader) *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s Degree in relevant subject.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years&amp;#39; experience gained in one of the sectors of Lot 1.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very good knowledge of project cycle management and of EU grants contract procedures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience participating in the selection of grant recipients on behalf of a national authorising officer or an international organisation is essential.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience coordinating the work of independent experts and reviewing inputs to ensure high quality deliverables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:benjamin_symonds@dai.com&quot;&gt;benjamin_symonds@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert Economiste ou Agroéconomiste (catégorie I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-economiste-ou-agroeconomiste-categorie-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 10:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-economiste-ou-agroeconomiste-categorie-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;L’étude a mener contribue par ses conseils a l’amélioration durable de la compétitivité (quantitative et qualitative) de la filière bananière camerounaise, en appuyant des activités qui favorisent la rentabilité sur le marché mondial, dans le strict respect des normes sociales et environnementales de la production, tout en améliorant la balance commerciale du pays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duree&lt;/strong&gt;: 3 mois&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert Economiste ou Agroéconomiste (catégorie I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Qualifications *&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Economiste ou équivalent en gestion ou commerce, ayant une expertise dans l’analyse de filière et l’étude de marches du secteur agro-alimentaire (école ou universitaire, minimum BAC+5)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 12 ans dans les études de marche des filières (agricoles) et les domaines du marketing et du commerce international.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 6 ans d’expérience professionnelle en diagnostic et conseil en économie ou gestion des filières agro-alimentaires, dont une filière fruit ou légume&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissances suffisantes des normes alimentaires et phytosanitaires régissant l’importation de bananes en Europe&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience technique ou juridique sur les règles et procédures commerciales, accords commerciaux, instruments de facilitation du commerce, politique commerciale.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne connaissance des stratégies commerciales et marketing dans le domaine des produits agricoles et avoir une bonne connaissance des circuits de commercialisation des produits agricoles, particulièrement d’Afrique.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans la conduite et la rédaction de diagnostics et de plans d’action et de cahier de charges.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une bonne capacité de communication est indispensable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne maitrise d’anglais et français.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Préférable d’avoir une bonne connaissance de langue allemande.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;Veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWP 2 Projects Review</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Beyond WTO Program (B-WTO) was developed in response to a request from the Government of Vietnam (GoV) for donor support to help with managing economic integration and the transition to a market economy following WTO accession. The B-WTO goal is “to strengthen government’s capacity to manage the integration of Vietnam into the global economy and the transition of Vietnam to a socialist market economy”. The immediate objective is “implementation of priority policy actions from the GoV’s Action Plan to enhance Vietnam’s capacity to sustain pro-poor growth (GAP)”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The remit of this project was a review of the 2nd annual work plan’s implementation (AWP2) of Phase 2 of the B-WTO in May 2013. The objectives of the review were to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the project implementation performance and project results relative to the logical framework targets and evaluation criteria. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the results achieved at the Component and Program’s level according to the Monitoring and Evaluation (M&amp;amp;E) framework of the Program.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify lessons learned from implementation, make recommendations for the remaining duration of the program and the Independent Completion Report process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
