<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 11:10:43 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contractor Representative / Program Director</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/contractor-representative-program-director</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 11:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/contractor-representative-program-director</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overarching purpose of this work will be to support the Government of Indonesia (GoI) to strengthen the capacity of all levels of Indonesian government and communities for improved services and economic growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Three substantive pillars will support the long-term goal of a prosperous and stable Indonesia, by contributing to the development of active, inclusive communities and of a capable, responsive state as summarized below, interacting as necessary with sectoral investments under the frontline framework:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work under Pillar 1 will foster active, inclusive communities to support community development in Indonesia;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If implemented under Pillar 2, AIPD2 (Australia-Indonesia Partnership for Decentralisation) would foster a capable, responsive Indonesian state by supporting central and subnational governments for improved service delivery; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If implemented under Pillar 3, NGO support and strengthening would support efforts to foster active, inclusive communities and a capable, responsive Indonesian state.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contractor Representative / Program Director&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Bachelor’s degree required in development studies, management, or other relevant topic. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least ten years of relevant and progressively responsible field-based experience in international development, including experience at management level. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to generate options that consider an appropriate range of capacity development supports and to translate agreed support into action. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in creating and implementing systems for logistics and procurement, contract management, human resources and adviser management, and financial and office management. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to contribute to strategic thinking and planning as part of multidisciplinary teams; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Awareness of social inclusivity and gender equality issues for implementation; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with M4P market development approach; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience leading and managing staff in a complex cross-cultural environment. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to adhere to the requirements of working in an Australian Aid Program, including compliance with DFAT procedures and policies and the DFAT Code of Conduct.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong verbal and written communication skills and excellent spoken and written English. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent reader/speaker of Bahasa Indonesian (desirable)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in DFAT format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;strong&gt;DFAT/AOP/006&lt;/strong&gt; in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junior Expert in Evaluation/assistance to ENP Cuntries </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-expert-in-evaluation-assistance-to-enp-cuntries</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 11:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-expert-in-evaluation-assistance-to-enp-cuntries</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this evaluation is to assess the contribution of the EU Advisory Group in supporting the Republic of Armenia to implement its reform agenda in core areas of the EU-Armenia ENP Action Plan and the preparations for an Association Agreement, as well as the extent to which its policy advice has led to concrete policy, legal, institutional and other reforms by the Government of Armenia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Junior Expert in Evaluation/assistance to ENP Cuntries&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum Masters Degree in social sciences or 10 years professional experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Community programmes and EU policies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in written and oral English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in Armenian or Russian is an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PC literacy, excellent writing and communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 years experience of evaluation of international donor development/cooperation and assistance in ENP, candidate or transition countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 2 years experience in monitoring state reform processes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous knowledge and experience of the ENP region is an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20nicolas_fichers@dai.com&quot;&gt;Nicolas_fichers@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Evaluation/assistance to ENP Countries</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-evaluation-assistance-to-enp-countries</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 11:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-evaluation-assistance-to-enp-countries</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this evaluation is to assess the contribution of the EU Advisory Group in supporting the Republic of Armenia to implement its reform agenda in core areas of the EU-Armenia ENP Action Plan and the preparations for an Association Agreement, as well as the extent to which its policy advice has led to concrete policy, legal, institutional and other reforms by the Government of Armenia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Evaluation/assistance to ENP Countries&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum Masters Degree in social sciences or 10 years professional experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of EU programmes and policies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in written and oral English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in Armenian or Russian is an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PC literacy, excellent writing and communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 10 years experience of evaluation of international donor development/cooperation and assistance to ENP, candidate or transition countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 years experience in monitoring state reform processes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous knowledge and experience of the ENP region is an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20nicolas_fichers@dai.com&quot;&gt;Nicolas_fichers@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Evaluation Expert with Experience of UN Projects
</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-evaluation-expert-with-experience-of-un-projects</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 17:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-evaluation-expert-with-experience-of-un-projects</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General objective:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To ensure that EC programming and contributions provide effective returns to addressing climate change in the developing world. The UNDP and Climate Parliament have managed the EU contribution. Since the EC has not managed this activity directly, this evaluation will serve as a basis for understanding lessons learned and details on the effectiveness/ appropriate use of EU funds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective of this assignment is to conduct an evaluation of the ED&amp;rsquo;s contribution to the PARE project. Areas such as impact, sustainability, value for money and the use of EU visibility must be examined, along with  the funding  of  workshops and workshop materials. Identification of lessons learned and recommendations for future EC contributions (support areas with maximum impact, visibility and sustainability) must also be included. An assessment of stakeholders&amp;#39; level of satisfaction with the outputs used under the EU contribution and an examination of the sustainability of implemented activities and inventions in the medium and longer term, are also requested from the consultant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The work will be &lt;strong&gt;home-based&lt;/strong&gt; with 2 missions to Brussels and a field mission to one of the 10 Climate Parliament countries (Bangladesh, Congo-Brazzaville, India, Jordan, Lebanon, Morocco, Senegal, South Africa, Tanzania and Tunisia).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Evaluation Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Senior expert, with at least 10 years of experience in evaluation  of UN projects, including experience in analysing individual donor contributions of multi-donor funded projects&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;: University degree in evaluation, project management, public administration, economics,  environmental   studies   or  technically   relevant  field,  and  Master  Degree  in evaluation,   project   management,   environment,   business  administration   or  similar  field. (Where the second  is lacking,  15 years overall  experience  in evaluation  of donor funded projects is required).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;at least 12 years of professional experience in the field of evaluation in developing countries, especially evaluating individual donor components of multi-donor projects/contributions;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;excellent writing and presentation skills, proved analytical skills and strategic thinking;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;native proficiency in English, professional competency in French&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;a good knowledge of the UN system, project finance, performance management frameworks and results-based management for development projects;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;proven experience in policy evaluations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to%20agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;agnese_ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert on Public Financial Management</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-public-financial-management</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-public-financial-management</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to assess the implementation performance of the Support to the Implementation of the VLAP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s):&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of this assignment are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To evaluate the Government of Moldova compliance with the General Conditions defined in Section 3 of Appendix 2 and the relevant Specific Conditions defined in Section 4 of Appendix 2 of the Financing Agreement on Support to the Implementation of the VLAP, for the disbursement of the 1st instalment (see the Financing Agreement attached).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To advise the European Commission on payment (total, partial, or non-payment) of the 1st instalment of the Support to the Implementation of the VLAP. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert on Public Financial Management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master Degree in finance or economics, or a university degree in the above areas with equivalent professional experience of at least 10 years in the relevant field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the EU procurement rules and excellent reporting and drafting skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in written and spoken English. Knowledge of Romanian or Russian would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Moldovan context would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General and specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 12 years of professional experience in Public Finance Management;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 5 years of professional experience in public finance management agencies, preferably in CIS or/and a country covered by the European Neighbourhood Policy;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of the latest developments and best practices in public financial management;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working with various levels of Government;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of EU external aid procedures, project cycle management principles and budget support methodology and evaluation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in performance assessment and review of EU budget support programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project management and preparation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert on Public Order and Security</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-public-order-and-security</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-public-order-and-security</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Objective:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to assess the implementation performance of the Support to the Implementation of the VLAP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s):&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of this assignment are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To evaluate the Government of Moldova compliance with the General Conditions defined in Section 3 of Appendix 2 and the relevant Specific Conditions defined in Section 4 of Appendix 2 of the Financing Agreement on Support to the Implementation of the VLAP, for the disbursement of the 1st instalment (see the Financing Agreement attached).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To advise the European Commission on payment (total, partial, or non-payment) of the 1st instalment of the Support to the Implementation of the VLAP. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert on Public Order and Security&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master Degree in law or any filed related to security and law enforcement, or a university degree in the above areas with equivalent professional experience of at least 15 years in the relevant field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the EU procurement rules and excellent reporting and drafting skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in written and spoken English. Knowledge of Romanian or Russian would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Moldovan context would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General and specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 12 years of professional experience in security and law enforcement area;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 5 years of professional experience in law enforcement agencies, preferably in CIS or/and a country covered by the European Neighbourhood Policy;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of the latest developments and best practices in fighting organized crime and Intelligence-led Policing;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working with various levels of Government;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of EU external aid procedures, project cycle management principles and budget support methodology and evaluation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in performance assessment of EU budget support programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project management and preparation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team leader/Expert on Border and Migration Management</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-expert-on-border-and-migration-management-1</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 15:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-expert-on-border-and-migration-management-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to assess the implementation performance of the Support to the Implementation of the VLAP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s):&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of this assignment are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To evaluate the Government of Moldova compliance with the General Conditions defined in Section 3 of Appendix 2 and the relevant Specific Conditions defined in Section 4 of Appendix 2 of the Financing Agreement on Support to the Implementation of the VLAP, for the disbursement of the 1st instalment (see the Financing Agreement attached).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To advise the European Commission on payment (total, partial, or non-payment) of the 1st instalment of the Support to the Implementation of the VLAP. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team leader/Expert on Border and Migration Management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master Degree in law or any filed related to border and migration management, or a university degree in the above areas with equivalent professional experience of at least 15 years in the relevant field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the EU procurement rules and excellent reporting and drafting skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in written and spoken English. Knowledge of Romanian or Russian would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Moldovan context would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General and specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 12 years of professional experience in border or migration management;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 5 years of professional experience in border or migration agencies, preferably in CIS or/and a country covered by the European Neighbourhood Policy;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of the latest developments and best practices in Integrated Border Management and migration policies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working with various levels of Government;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of EU external aid procedures, project cycle management principles and budget support methodology and evaluation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in performance assessment of EU budget support programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leadership skills to manage and motivate a team and to interact with project partners, the European Union Delegation to Moldova, civil society and the donor community;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project management and preparation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team leader/Expert on Border and Migration Management</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-expert-on-border-and-migration-management</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-expert-on-border-and-migration-management</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to assess the implementation performance of the Support to the Implementation of the VLAP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Objectives:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt; of this assignment are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To evaluate the Government of Moldova compliance with the General Conditions defined in Section 3 of Appendix 2 and the relevant Specific Conditions defined in Section 4 of Appendix 2 of the Financing Agreement on Support to the Implementation of the VLAP, for the disbursement of the 1st instalment (see the Financing Agreement attached).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To advise the European Commission on payment (total, partial, or non-payment) of the 1st instalment of the Support to the Implementation of the VLAP. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team leader/Expert on Border and Migration Management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master Degree in law or any filed related to border and migration management, or a university degree in the above areas with equivalent professional experience of at least 15 years in the relevant field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the EU procurement rules and excellent reporting and drafting skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in written and spoken English. Knowledge of Romanian or Russian would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Moldovan context would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General and specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 12 years of professional experience in border or migration management;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 5 years of professional experience in border or migration agencies, preferably in CIS or/and a country covered by the European Neighbourhood Policy;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of the latest developments and best practices in Integrated Border Management and migration policies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working with various levels of Government;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of EU external aid procedures, project cycle management principles and budget support methodology and evaluation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in performance assessment of EU budget support programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leadership skills to manage and motivate a team and to interact with project partners, the European Union Delegation to Moldova, civil society and the donor community;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project management and preparation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
