<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 07:41:40 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef de mission – Expert en Evaluation et Développement Local/ Sécurité Alimentaire</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-expert-en-evaluation-et-developpement-local-securite-alimentaire</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 07:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-expert-en-evaluation-et-developpement-local-securite-alimentaire</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;La présente mission  porte sur la réalisation d’une évaluation de performances tant au niveau stratégique, institutionnel, organisationnel, technique et opérationnel des deux programmes d’appui au développement local, financés sous le 10ème FED au Tchad : Programmes d’Appui au Développement Local et à la Gestion des Ressources Naturelles (10FED/2009-021320 PADL GRN) et d’Appui au Développement Local II (10FED/2010-022061 PADL II), composante.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chef de mission – Expert en Evaluation et Développement Local/ Sécurité Alimentaire&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Formation *&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Un niveau d&amp;#39;enseignement correspondant à un cycle complet d&amp;#39;études universitaires de quatre années ou plus, sanctionné par un diplôme de fin d&amp;#39;études.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Qualifications *&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Domaine(s) d’expertise&lt;/strong&gt; : développement rural/local, agronomie, sociologie/économie du développement, géographie ou tout autre domaine pertinent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Expérience *&lt;/em&gt;;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 12 ans d&amp;#39;expérience professionnelle dans le(s) secteur(s) pertinents par rapport à la mission
Ou
Une expérience professionnelle équivalente pour une durée minimale de 15 années si l’expert n’a pas la formation académique demandée &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 3 ans d’expérience avérée dans le domaine du développement local/ rural et des programmes de sécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle en Afrique subsaharienne &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir réalisé au moins 2 missions d’évaluation de programmes de développement local/rural&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir été chef d&amp;#39;équipe d&amp;#39;au moins deux missions dont une dans le domaine du développement local &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir réalisé au moins 1 mission d’évaluation/audit de performances d’un programme  de développement rural/local en Afrique subsaharienne&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellente connaissance démontrée des politiques et modalités de la coopération européenne, des mécanismes de coordination institutionnelle, de communication, des procédures FED et du cycle de Projet&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une grande maîtrise du français avec une excellente capacité d’analyse, de synthèse et rédactionnelle démontrée par, notamment, au moins une publication ou un rapport à fournir. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cat.II Expert in M&amp;E and Agriculture</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/catii-expert-in-me-and-agriculture</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 07:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/catii-expert-in-me-and-agriculture</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the midterm review is to provide an overview of the activities carried out in the first phase of the implementation of the programme and appraise the context and methodological approach for the smooth implementation of a second phase. The MTR shall provide recommendations for the way forward and confirm one of the two scenarios:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scenario. Continuity - no major changes in the programme’s orientation and objectives but with suggestions for revisions that may be necessary to adapt the programme to emerging needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scenario. Overhaul - a complete change in the programme’s orientation, objectives and implementation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category II Expert in M&amp;amp;E and Agriculture&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in social sciences or a related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven communication and reporting skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of six years&amp;#39; experience of the LFA and PCM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in Monitoring and Evaluation of donor funded programmes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in programme in the agricultural sector&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Eritrean context will be an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Eritrean legal context will be an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fluency in English is required. Knowledge of other languages used in Eritrea will be an advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Food Safety/SPS Expert (Cat.I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-food-safety-sps-expert-cati</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 09:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-food-safety-sps-expert-cati</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The objective of the assignment is to prepare a draft Action Document (AD) to implement the agricultural part of the NIP 2014-2020 for Suriname which has allocated €13.0 M.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requested services&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collect and review information and documents relevant for the development of the Action Document &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyse the value chain(s) for Horticulture and identify main entry points for programme interventions &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyse the food safety environment in agriculture. Identify main funding gaps and identify priority interventions. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely and consult with relevant Ministries, in particular the Ministry of Agriculture (LVV) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consult with the relevant stakeholders, including GoSur, Civil Society Organisations (CSO) in the field, Private Sector associations &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consult with EU Delegation in Guyana and other development partner, in particular IDB, FAO, IICA, Netherland Embassy &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Critically review the various options that emerge before or from the assignment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Food Safety/SPS Expert (Cat.I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General requirements&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University Degree in Agriculture or equivalent in Food Science or Food Technology &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in Agriculture and Rural Development or related fields. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of EU Project Cycle Management, identification and formulation and EDF implementation procedures would be an asset &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent reporting and communication skills &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English and in Dutch &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific requirements&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have 10 years&amp;#39; experience on Food Safety Systems (from the producer to the export gate) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in identifying and formulating food safety projects (or project components) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be familiar with validation and verification of food safety systems and be knowledgeable of the CARICOM Market requirements and the EU Directives for Food Safety. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be familiar with HACCP (Hazard Analysis and Critical Control Points) principles, Good Manufacturing Practices and standard requirements for trade.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:adeline_vanhoutte@dai.com&quot;&gt;Adeline_VanHoutte@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Horticulture Value Chain Expert (TL/Cat.I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-horticulture-value-chain-expert-tl-cati</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 08:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-horticulture-value-chain-expert-tl-cati</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The objective of the assignment is to prepare a draft Action Document (AD) to implement the agricultural part of the NIP 2014-2020 for Suriname which has allocated €13.0 M.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requested services&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collect and review information and documents relevant for the development of the Action Document &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyse the value chain(s) for Horticulture and identify main entry points for programme interventions &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyse the food safety environment in agriculture. Identify main funding gaps and identify priority interventions. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely and consult with relevant Ministries, in particular the Ministry of Agriculture (LVV) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consult with the relevant stakeholders, including GoSur, Civil Society Organisations (CSO) in the field, Private Sector associations &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consult with EU Delegation in Guyana and other development partner, in particular IDB, FAO, IICA, Netherland Embassy &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Critically review the various options that emerge before or from the assignment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Horticulture Value Chain Expert (TL/Cat.I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General requirements&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University Degree in Agriculture or equivalent Agricultural Economics, Agronomics, Agribusiness or a related field &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in Agriculture and Rural Development. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent reporting and communication skills &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent knowledge of EU Project Cycle Management, identification and formulation and EDF implementation procedures &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English and in Dutch &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific requirements&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in identifying and formulating agriculture/horticulture projects (or project components) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work experience in EDF project identification and formulation of project under decentralized management. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10 years’ experience in tropical agriculture is a requirement, experience in the Caribbean&amp;rsquo;s an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 5 years of agricultural sector multi-disciplinary value chain experience &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in modern horticulture husbandry practices including crop/site matching, varieties, orchard establishment, harvest and post harvesting quality management, marketing of the concerned value chain &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical experience as project manager in a transformation process of fruits or vegetables would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:adeline_vanhoutte@dai.com&quot;&gt;Adeline_VanHoutte@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SME Finance Expert (Category II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/sme-finance-expert-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 20:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/sme-finance-expert-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The main objective of the Mid-Term Evaluation is to review the project progress, under each of the Components, to check the achievements against the expected results and set of activities. The Evaluation will provide a clear and concise opinion as to how the project has progressed including recommendations regarding the course of actions to be taken until the end of implementation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this respect the mission will assess the relevance, efficiency, effectiveness, impact and sustainability of each of the Components of the entire INSPIRED Programme related to the stated purpose and results. It will identify weaknesses and challenges, whilst proposing measures and recommendations to tackle them, including recommendations for any required change/modification to the project scope in order to support effective implementation and delivery of as sustainable benefit stream.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SME Finance Expert (Category II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum Bachelor Degree in Economics of relevant subject or in absence equivalent of 10 years professional experience in the area of SMEs banking or financial sector development &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of the challenges in SMEs financing and experience related to capacity building of financial training institutes &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of private sector development would be an advantage &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with EC project evaluation procedures and related documentation is mandatory; previous experience in monitoring and evaluation is a must &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English both written and oral &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Bangla would be an advantage &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent reporting skills &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in standard computer technology packages (word, excel, internet) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of professional experience in the sector of SME finance providers, with specific focus on credit and financial analysis, risk management, and SME lending, non-performing loan management, identification of key lending risks &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of professional experience in the evaluation, design, and/or management of SME banking related technical assistance projects in developing countries, preferably in South Asia &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical experience and proven track record in organising and delivering professional bank training programmes and development of curricula and training materials &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in institutional strengthening and capacity building of banking/financial training institutes &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant professional experience in Bangladesh would be an added advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:francesca_giordano@dai.com&quot;&gt;francesca_giordano@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SME Competitiveness through BIO and SME Clusters development (Category II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/sme-competitiveness-through-bio-and-sme-clusters-development-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/sme-competitiveness-through-bio-and-sme-clusters-development-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The main objective of the Mid-Term Evaluation is to review the project progress, under each of the Components, to check the achievements against the expected results and set of activities. The Evaluation will provide a clear and concise opinion as to how the project has progressed including recommendations regarding the course of actions to be taken until the end of implementation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this respect the mission will assess the relevance, efficiency, effectiveness, impact and sustainability of each of the Components of the entire INSPIRED Programme related to the stated purpose and results. It will identify weaknesses and challenges, whilst proposing measures and recommendations to tackle them, including recommendations for any required change/modification to the project scope in order to support effective implementation and delivery of as sustainable benefit stream.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SME Competitiveness through BIO and SME Clusters development (Category II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum Bachelor Degree in Economics of relevant subject or in absence equivalent of 10 years professional experience in the area of SMEs development and competitiveness related issues &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of the challenges in SMEs including related to Business Intermediary Organisations and SMEs clusters and networking &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of private sector development &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with EC project evaluation procedures and related documentation is mandatory; previous experience in monitoring and evaluation is a must &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English both written and oral &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Bangla would be an advantage &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent reporting skills &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in standard computer technology packages (word, excel, internet) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of professional experience in the sector of SMEs or BIOs &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of professional experience in the evaluation, design, and/or management of SME competitiveness technical assistance projects in developing countries, preferably in South Asia &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in institutional strengthening and capacity building of BIOs and SME Clusters &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant professional experience in Bangladesh would be an added advantage. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:francesca_giordano@dai.com&quot;&gt;francesca_giordano@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader/ SME Development Expert (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-sme-development-expert-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 20:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-sme-development-expert-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation of the &amp;lsquo;Integrated Support to Poverty and Inequality Reduction through Enterprise Development&amp;rsquo; (INSPIRED)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main objective of the Mid-Term Evaluation is to review the project progress, under each of the Components, to check the achievements against the expected results and set of activities. The Evaluation will provide a clear and concise opinion as to how the project has progressed including recommendations regarding the course of actions to be taken until the end of implementation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this respect the mission will assess the relevance, efficiency, effectiveness, impact and sustainability of each of the Components of the entire INSPIRED Programme related to the stated purpose and results. It will identify weaknesses and challenges, whilst proposing measures and recommendations to tackle them, including recommendations for any required change/modification to the project scope in order to support effective implementation and delivery of as sustainable benefit stream.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader/ SME Development Expert (Category I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s Degree in Economics/Business Management or other relevant subjects or in absence of diploma, equivalent professional experience of at least 15 years, in SME related issues: Enterprise policy, SME support programmes (at national, regional and local levels), SME Development Strategy and Policy, SME promotion (financial and non-financial support schemes, investment support, training and networking &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good understanding and knowledge of private sector development issues in developing countries, preferably in South Asia. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with EC project evaluation procedures and related documentation is mandatory; previous experience in monitoring and evaluation is a must &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English both written and oral. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent reporting and presentation skills &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong interpersonal skills (communication, interviewing, analytical, neutral and objective attitude) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in standard computer technology packages (word, excel, internet) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 12 years professional experience in SME development and in particular in development SME policies including financial and non-financial support measures, clustering, networking, etc. with actions implemented by SME agencies or governments. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 8 years of professional experience in the management and/or participation in projects involving technical aspects, such as: business development services, economic planning, SME sector development, investment facilitation, institutional capacity development, provision of economic-related capacity building to public authorities. Experience in the provision of such assistance to countries of South Asia would be an advantage. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid experience in evaluating technical assistance projects in developing countries &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Management and/or participation in projects involving international teams of experts of different technical backgrounds &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven knowledge of European Union project management procedures and financial regulations, preferably through management and participation in EU-funded technical assistance projects would be an advantage &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of dealing at a senior level with governmental or private sector institutions; experience in working in a complex structure of government ministries and agencies, and private sector organisations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:francesca_giordano@dai.com&quot;&gt;francesca_giordano@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Evaluation</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-evaluation</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-evaluation</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identification/Mapping of Social Protection Sector Programmes Administered by the PA and UNRWA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective of this macro-level study is to assist UNRWA and the PA Ministry of Social Affairs (MoSA) to make informed decisions, develop and enhance cooperation and partnerships between both structures, and to complement each other&amp;rsquo;s models for the delivery of social assistance
services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The contractor will carry out a ‘mapping study&amp;#39; of the aforementioned entities (MoSA and UNRWA). The mapping shall provide an overview of these institutions and shall assess the capacity of these organisations, the role they play and the challenges they face, in terms of social assistance delivery capacities, advocacy and policy dialogue at the national level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Evaluation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree (or equivalent) in Social Sciences, Public or Business Administration, Economics or similar, or at least five years of professional experience in addition to the minimum required under General Professional experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years of experience conducting evaluation/ reviews/ assessment/mapping of large-scale donor funded projects or programmes in an international context;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in social services delivery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in crisis and/or post-conflict aid delivery would be an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of experience working on assessment/evaluation of social services delivery, with a focus on social services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in service delivery reforms (health, education, social protection, gender) would be an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English, both orally and written;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good analytical and research skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:francesca_giordano@dai.com&quot;&gt;francesca_giordano@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader / Senior Expert in Mapping Analyses</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-expert-in-mapping-analyses</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 15:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-expert-in-mapping-analyses</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identification/Mapping of Social Protection Sector Programmes Administered by the PA and UNRWA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective of this macro-level study is to assist UNRWA and the PA Ministry of Social Affairs (MoSA) to make informed decisions, develop and enhance cooperation and partnerships between both structures, and to complement each other&amp;rsquo;s models for the delivery of social assistance
services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The contractor will carry out a ‘mapping study&amp;#39; of the aforementioned entities (MoSA and UNRWA). The mapping shall provide an overview of these institutions and shall assess the capacity of these organisations, the role they play and the challenges they face, in terms of social assistance delivery
capacities, advocacy and policy dialogue at the national level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader / Senior Expert in Mapping Analyses&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree (or equivalent) in Social Sciences, Public or Business Administration, Economics or equivalent, or at least five years of professional experience in addition to the minimum required under General Professional experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years of experience conducting evaluation/ reviews/ assessment/ mapping of largescale donor funded projects or programmes in an international context;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of monitoring and evaluation techniques;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in social services delivery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in crisis and/or post-conflict aid delivery would be an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of experience working on assessment/evaluation of social service delivery, with a focus on social assistance;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in policy reform and/or service delivery reforms (health, education, social protection, gender)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience mapping/monitoring/evaluation assignments;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English, both orally and written;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good analytical and research skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:francesca_giordano@dai.com&quot;&gt;francesca_giordano@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IТ Expert- Category III</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/i-expert-category-iii</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 07:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/i-expert-category-iii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to the alignment of the Cross-border and Transnational Programmes with the requirement of IPA II 2014-2020&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Specific Objective&lt;/strong&gt; is to provide Serbia with the assistance necessary for establishing proper  contro1 and management  system, re1ated procedures and  documents  for the implementation  of СВС and ТN prograrmnes financed under IPА II, inc1uding the capita1isation of the lessons learned and sharing experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IТ Expert- Category III&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in computer sciences or other disciplines related to this assignment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of both written and spoken English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum three (3) preferably five (5) years of experience in public administration management information systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven  experience  in  design or development  of at least one (1) preferably two  (2) management information system&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven  experience  in software  deployment,  web  applications in the field  of  public administration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience  in delivery of users training  in one (1) preferably two (2) projects relevant to this assignment and of similar complexity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legal Expert Category II</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/legal-expert-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 07:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/legal-expert-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to the alignment of the Cross-border and Transnational Programmes with the requirement of IPA II 2014-2020&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Specific Objective&lt;/strong&gt; is to provide Serbia with the assistance necessary for establishing proper  contro1 and management  system, re1ated procedures and  documents  for the implementation  of СВС and ТN prograrmnes financed under IPА II, inc1uding the capita1isation of the lessons learned and sharing experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Legal Expert Category II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MSc in Law&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Serbian Language (asset)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum six (б), preferably eight (8) years of professional experience in the area of legislation, regulations and approximation of legislation in Member States and/or Candidate/Potential Candidate Countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum three (3) preferably four (4) years of experience in the management and/or implementation of European Territorial Cooperation programmes (between Member States and/or between Member States and Candidate/Potential Candidate Countries);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven practical experience in drafting and/or amending legal documents related to the participation   of  Member   States   or   Candidate/Potential   Candidate  countries   in European Territorial Cooperation programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Serbian legal framework relevant to the implementation of IPА II funds is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader /Management and Control System Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-management-and-control-system-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 07:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-management-and-control-system-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to the alignment of the Cross-border and Transnational Programmes with the requirement of IPA II 2014-2020&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Specific Objective&lt;/strong&gt; is to provide Serbia with the assistance necessary for establishing proper  contro1 and management  system, re1ated procedures and  documents  for the implementation  of СВС and ТN prograrmnes financed under IPА II, inc1uding the capita1isation of the lessons learned and sharing experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader /Management and Control System Expert&lt;/strong&gt;    &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MSc in economics, business administration, public administration, information technology, social sciences or equivalent (in the absence of diploma, minimum 8 years of relevant professional experience in addition to the minimum number of years demonstrated under general professional experience specified below)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Excellent command of both written and spoken English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum twelve (12) years preferably fifteen (15) years of professional experience in the area of pre-accession and/or Structural funds in Member States and/or Candidate/Potential Candidate Countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience  in  information  technology,  audit  reporting  and/or  auditing  techniques would bе considered an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum  three (3) preferably five  (5)  years  of experience in management and/or implementation  of European Territorial  Cooperation  programmes (between Member States and/or between Member States and Candidate/Potential Candidate Countries);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in designing procedures and drafting documents for the bodies responsible for the implementation of European Territorial Cooperation programmes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven  experience as Team Leader ш at  least two  (2)  projects relevant  to  this assignment and of similar complexity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert, Evaluation and Statistics</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-evaluation-and-statistics</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2015 12:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-evaluation-and-statistics</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Specific objectives of this evaluation concern the need to provide a clear picture of the Statistics sector in Ukraine (status of the SSSU, remit and objectives, financial resources, strengths and weaknesses, etc.) in order to better identify areas where the EU could support Ukraine in the next period. This evaluation will be based on well-grounded evidence collected through the successive EU Twinning projects implemented during the last period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert, Evaluation and Statistics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in a field related to the assignment (Economics, Statistics, Demography), or
equivalent professional experience of minimum 10 years;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent English communication skills, both spoken and written.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Ukrainian or Russian would be an asset (preferred)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years of professional experience in Statistics (starting at the date the diploma was
obtained);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years of experience on evaluation of programmes/projects;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 years of experience in the formulation, implementation, monitoring and evaluation
of development programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in evaluation of projects carried-out in the field of Statistics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in a National State Statistics Service would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert en Communication</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-communication</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2015 08:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-communication</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif particulier 1&lt;/strong&gt; : Appui au processus d’élaboration de la stratégie nationale sur le changement climatique (INDC)
Il s’agit de l’appui d&amp;#39;une part au COMNACC (comité national sur le changement climatique) et aux COMRECC (comités régionaux sur le changement climatique) dans le processus de décentralisation de la politique relative au climat et d’autre part, à l’identification des outils nécessaires à la mise en place d’un système MRV (monitoring review and verification) dans le cadre de la définition des INDC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif particulier 2&lt;/strong&gt; : Appui au processus de diffusion et de validation politique des documents stratégiques DD et CC
L’objectif est de lancer un dialogue national, intersectoriel, multi acteur et interministériel pour la validation et l’adoption politique de la stratégie nationale de développement durable, des objectifs du développement durable (ODD) et les Contributions Prévues Déterminés au Niveau National (CPDN, INDC en anglais) avant le sommet des nations unies sur le développement post-2015 et la COP21.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert en Communication&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Catégorie et durée de l&amp;#39;expérience équivalente&lt;/strong&gt; - 
Expert de catégorie II avec 6 ans d&amp;#39;expérience au minimum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formation&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Diplôme supérieur, Master ou équivalent dans le domaine des sciences de l’information avec une spécialisation dans l’environnement, le climat ou le développement durable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Au moins 6 ans d’expérience dans la couverture d’évènements environnementaux et DD de haut niveau ;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans la formation aux techniques et méthodes de diffusion de l’information environnementale acquises au moins dans 5 projets;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en Afrique francophone serait souhaitée.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tous les experts doivent être indépendants et n&amp;#39;avoir aucun conflit d&amp;#39;intérêt dans les responsabilités qui leur incombent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissances linguistiques&lt;/strong&gt; - Bilingue français/anglais de préférence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;agnese_ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert en Changement Climatique</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-changement-climatique</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2015 08:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-changement-climatique</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif particulier 1&lt;/strong&gt; : Appui au processus d’élaboration de la stratégie nationale sur le changement climatique (INDC)
Il s’agit de l’appui d&amp;#39;une part au COMNACC (comité national sur le changement climatique) et aux COMRECC (comités régionaux sur le changement climatique) dans le processus de décentralisation de la politique relative au climat et d’autre part, à l’identification des outils nécessaires à la mise en place d’un système MRV (monitoring review and verification) dans le cadre de la définition des INDC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif particulier 2&lt;/strong&gt; : Appui au processus de diffusion et de validation politique des documents stratégiques DD et CC. L’objectif est de lancer un dialogue national, intersectoriel, multi acteur et interministériel pour la validation et l’adoption politique de la stratégie nationale de développement durable, des objectifs du développement durable (ODD) et les Contributions Prévues Déterminés au Niveau National (CPDN, INDC en anglais) avant le sommet des nations unies sur le développement post-2015 et la COP21.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert en Changement Climatique&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Catégorie et durée de l&amp;#39;expérience équivalente&lt;/strong&gt; :
Expert de catégorie I avec 12 ans d&amp;#39;expérience au minimum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formation&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Diplômes supérieurs appropriés (au moins Bac+5) dans le domaine suivants: sciences politiques ou économiques ou équivalent avec une spécialisation sur le climat et Environnement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expérience d’au moins 12 ans sur des projets/programmes liés aux Changements climatiques en particuliers dans les pays en développement;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordination de groupes intersectoriels et multi acteurs dans le domaine des Changements climatiques acquis au moins dans deux (2) projets ou expériences ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise des instruments juridiques et financiers liés au Climat et à la gouvernance climatique internationale existante et celle en cours de négociation (au moins deux projets ou expériences);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une bonne appréciation des perspectives climatiques internationales post-2020 liées aux INDC et aux MRV acquises dans des formations et/ou conférences et/ou en poste;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;La connaissance ou expérience dans la mise en place d’un système MRV existant tel que VCS (Verified Carbon Standard) serait appréciée.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissances linguistiques&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Excellentes capacités de communication écrite et orale en français et en anglais.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;agnese_ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert Environnement et Développement Durable (Cat.I) – Chef de Mission</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-environnement-et-developpement-durable-cati-chef-de-mission</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2015 07:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-environnement-et-developpement-durable-cati-chef-de-mission</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif particulier 1&lt;/strong&gt; : Appui au processus d’élaboration de la stratégie nationale sur le changement climatique (INDC)
Il s’agit de l’appui d&amp;#39;une part au COMNACC (comité national sur le changement climatique) et aux COMRECC (comités régionaux sur le changement climatique) dans le processus de décentralisation de la politique relative au climat et d’autre part, à l’identification des outils nécessaires à la mise en place d’un système MRV (monitoring review and verification) dans le cadre de la définition des INDC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif particulier 2&lt;/strong&gt; : Appui au processus de diffusion et de validation politique des documents stratégiques DD et CC
L’objectif est de lancer un dialogue national, intersectoriel, multi acteur et interministériel pour la validation et l’adoption politique de la stratégie nationale de développement durable, des objectifs du développement durable (ODD) et les Contributions Prévues Déterminés au Niveau National (CPDN, INDC en anglais) avant le sommet des nations unies sur le développement post-2015 et la COP21.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert Environnement et Développement Durable (Cat.I) – Chef de Mission&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Catégorie et durée de l&amp;#39;expérience équivalente: Expert de catégorie I avec 12 ans d&amp;#39;expérience au minimum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formation&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Diplôme supérieur approprié (Minimum BAC + 5) dans le domaine suivants: sciences politiques, économique, sociales ou équivalent avec une spécialisation en Environnement, ou Développement durable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Expérience Professionnelle Générale *&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Au moins 12 ans d&amp;#39;expérience dans la coordination d’initiatives de développement en lien avec l’environnement, le développement durable ;
Au moins 8 ans d’expérience dans le développement de documents politiques liés au développement durable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 5 ans d’expérience d’animation et de coordination de dialogues inter-acteurs sur les politiques de Développement Durable;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en Afrique acquise dans au moins deux projets relatifs au développement durable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Les compétences suivantes constituent des atouts&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compréhension et appréciation claire du paysage légal et politique du Sénégal en termes de politique de développement socio-économique;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellentes capacité à travailler avec les institutions publiques est un solide avantage ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en Afrique de l’ouest;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonne maîtrise des enjeux internationaux liés au DD et les agendas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissances linguistiques&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Excellentes capacités de communication écrite et orale en français et en anglais&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;agnese_ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert 3 –Policy Analysis</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-3-policy-analysis</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2015 15:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-3-policy-analysis</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To enhance the process of identification and formulation of EU support to the justice sector, the following specific objectives have been identified:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establishing a comprehensive an informed analysis of the distribution and operation of power and of key aspects of political, social and economic practice, vision, organisation and interactions in the justice sector in Azerbaijan.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributing to the future EU programming and policy dialogue in the justice sector, by identifying the scope, obstacles, opportunities and entry points for productive policy dialogue and EU support on justice reform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Providing internal document to better understand the developments in Justice sector for EU staff working both at the Delegation and at Headquarters, as well as selected development partners active in the justice sector in Azerbaijan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert 3 – Policy Analysis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound understanding of public policy processes and its actors in Azerbaijan and/or other Eastern Partnership countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Masters-level degree in Political Science, Law, Development Studies, Economics Social Sciences or another relevant areas, or equivalent 15 years of relevant professional experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Russian and/or Azeri orally and in writing an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 10 years of relevant professional experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Experience in public policy analyses in Azerbaijan and/or other Eastern Partnership countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Excellent English report writing and editing skills as attested by the publication of articles, books and/or reports (the list of publications to be provided with the CV).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; At least 5 years of project management experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert 2- Public Sector Reform</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-2-public-sector-reform</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2015 15:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-2-public-sector-reform</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To enhance the process of identification and formulation of EU support to the justice sector, the following specific objectives have been identified:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establishing a comprehensive an informed analysis of the distribution and operation of power and of key aspects of political, social and economic practice, vision, organisation and interactions in the justice sector in Azerbaijan.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributing to the future EU programming and policy dialogue in the justice sector, by identifying the scope, obstacles, opportunities and entry points for productive policy dialogue and EU support on justice reform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Providing internal document to better understand the developments in Justice sector for EU staff working both at the Delegation and at Headquarters, as well as selected development partners active in the justice sector in Azerbaijan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert 2 - Public Sector Reform&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Masters-level degree in Political Science, Law, Development Studies, Economics SocialSciences or another relevant areas, or equivalent 15 years of relevant professionalexperience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English, orally and in writing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in Russian and/or Azeri orally and in writing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 10 years relevant professional experience in the sectors of justice and rule of law and/ or public sector reform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Experience in assessment of Justice Sector Reform programmes and similar/related tools in developing countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Participation to at least one Justice Reform project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Experience in working with international organizations, including preferably the EU&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Sound knowledge of the Public Administration in Azerbaijan and/or other Eastern Partnership countries an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert 1- Justice Sector Reform</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-1-justice-sector-reform</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2015 15:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-1-justice-sector-reform</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To enhance the process of identification and formulation of EU support to the justice sector, the following specific objectives have been identified:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establishing a comprehensive an informed analysis of the distribution and operation of power and of key aspects of political, social and economic practice, vision, organisation and interactions in the justice sector in Azerbaijan.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributing to the future EU programming and policy dialogue in the justice sector, by identifying the scope, obstacles, opportunities and entry points for productive policy dialogue and EU support on justice reform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Providing internal document to better understand the developments in Justice sector for EU staff working both at the Delegation and at Headquarters, as well as selected development partners active in the justice sector in Azerbaijan.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert 1- Justice Sector Reform&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Masters-level degree in Political Science, Law, Development Studies, Economics Social Sciences or another relevant areas, or equivalent 15 years of relevant professional experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Fluent in English, orally and in writing. Command of Russian or Azeri will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A minimum of 10 years relevant professional experience in the sectors of justice and rule of law .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; A minimum of 5 years of experience in Justice Sector Reform in developing or transition countries, preferably in the Eastern Neighbourhood region and/or current or past EU
candidate countries.* A minimum of 3 years of experience in policy analysis and planning;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Previous experience in designing, implementing, monitoring and/or evaluating Justice Reform programs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Expertise in drafting programming documents for EU or other donors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Electoral Expert </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-electoral-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 15:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-electoral-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Election Follow-up Mission to Cambodia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Electoral Expert (Category I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Law, Political Science, International Relations or any other discipline relevant to the assignment, or equivalent professional experience of over 12 years in the area related to Lot 7. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 12 years in the field of electoral assistance and in the sector(s) directly related to the Lot 7. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;at least 5 years in the specific field of the electoral assistance, preferably as part of an EU Election Observation Mission and/or an EU Election Technical Assistance project;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proficiency in electoral issues in developing countries;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellent knowledge of all issues related to the evaluation of electoral assistance projects; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous experience in the country and/or the region is an asset; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adaptability to a multicultural working environment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellent written and spoken skills in English. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further requirements: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience and deep knowledge of Cambodia political and electoral situation, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very good knowledge and understanding of voter registration processes and * Very good knowledge and understanding of legal framework for the election process will be considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Timing&lt;/strong&gt;: for around 21 working days (18 days in country including briefing, debriefing in Brussels and travel days and followed by 3 home-based days for the finalization and editing of the Final Report, including travels) - focusing on programming and planning issues connected to electoral assistance projects, assessing the strengths and limitations of projects to promote and implement reform, providing guidance on the design of future projects based on EU EOM recommendations, including targeted recommendations for short term EU support to forthcoming elections. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:francesca_giordano@dai.com&quot;&gt;francesca_giordano@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
