<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 13:41:25 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experto Categoría III – Informático</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-categoria-iii-informatico</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 08:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-categoria-iii-informatico</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ATI MMAyA 2016-17&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;El contrato tiene como objetivo general apoyar al MMAYA en la implementación de los programas actuales así como en la fase de preparación de un Nuevo Convenio de Financiación (CF) Sectorial y el Programas de Asistencia Técnica al MMAyA. El asesoramiento se producirá a través de la provisión de estudios, metodologías, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project location&lt;/strong&gt;: La Paz, misiones a las potenciales zonas de intervención: Santa Cruz, Tarija, Cochabamba, Beni, Pando y Oruro&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experto Categoría III – Informático&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preparación y calificaciones&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formación académica en los rubros de informática, ingeniería, geografía o cualquier otro tipo de diploma científico;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competencia en manejo de bases de datos Postgres/PostGIS, relacional y sistemas de información distribuidos: manejo de los usuarios, configuración y adaptación de la base de datos, desarrollo de funciones y de consultas, carga y exportación de datos, back-ups;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competencia en operaciones básicas de redes informáticas (TCP / IP , VPN, FTP &amp;hellip;);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competencia en manejo y mantenimiento del servidor, versionamiento Git, SO LINUX, Windows;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competencia en programación/desarrollo de interfaces web para bases de datos (digitalización de datos y consultas);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competencia deseable en lenguajes de programación y herramientas informáticas (SQL y PHP, HTML. Manejo de Drupal, Javascript, Python)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conocimiento en SIG y datos geoespaciales deseable;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debe hablar y escribir fluidamente en español. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experiencia profesional&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mínimo 3 años de experiencia en programación y /o gestión de sistemas, con la aplicación de las competencias arriba mencionadas;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mínimo 3 años de experiencia laboral en Bolivia, que permita un conocimiento de las condiciones de sistemas informáticos en el país;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia en apoyo a sistemas gubernamentales, y del Ministerio de Medioambiente y Agua en particular, deseable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experto Categoría III - Coordinador</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-categoria-iii-coordinador</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-categoria-iii-coordinador</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ATI MMAyA 2016-17&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;El contrato tiene como objetivo general apoyar al MMAYA en la implementación de los programas actuales así como en la fase de preparación de un Nuevo Convenio de Financiación (CF) Sectorial y el Programas de Asistencia Técnica al MMAyA. El asesoramiento se producirá a través de la provisión de estudios, metodologías, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project location&lt;/strong&gt;: La Paz, misiones a las potenciales zonas de intervención: Santa Cruz, Tarija, Cochabamba, Beni, Pando y Oruro&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experto Categoría III - Coordinador:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preparación y calificaciones&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formación académica en los rubros de economía, ciencias sociales o biología. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formación complementaria (postgrado o maestría) es deseable, particularmente en temáticas de desarrollo y/o relacionadas al sector de agua y medioambiente.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debe hablar y escribir fluidamente en español. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debe tener facilidad de comunicación y negociación para relacionarse con autoridades nacionales, subnacionales y organizaciones sociales, competencia intercultural y la predisposición de adaptarse a cambios del entorno institucional con creatividad. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experiencia profesional general&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mínimo de 5 años de experiencia en el sector de agua y medioambiente. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mínimo de 5 años de experiencia laboral en países en vías de desarrollo.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mínimo de 3 años de experiencia laboral con organismos de cooperación (donantes, agencias técnicas, ONGs) en Bolivia.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia demostrada en el desarrollo y/o implementaciones de programas sectoriales, en coordinación con instancias gubernamentales y/o sociales.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experiencia profesional específica deseable&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia en el diseño y/o la implementación de programas de apoyo sectorial, idealmente con la modalidad de apoyo presupuestario de la Unión Europea.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia específica relacionada con políticas de agua, manejo de cuencas, biodiversidad y/o sector forestal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia en el diseño y/o implementación de programas de fortalecimiento de capacidades. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia en trabajo dentro de o en apoyo a instituciones gubernamentales a nivel central o sub-nacional. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert I - Technical Adviser with Experience in a NAO Office</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-i-technical-adviser-with-experience-in-a-nao-office</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 19:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-i-technical-adviser-with-experience-in-a-nao-office</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Short Term Technical Assistance to Support the NAO Office&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of this assignment is to improve the efficiency and effectiveness with which the EU Assistance to Kenya is implemented &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective is to provide technical assistance to the National Treasury primarily to support coordination of the financial management of EU Grants to County Governments, but also to ensure that the National Treasury performs its role with regards to the administration of Grants as outlined in the PFM Act and PFM Regulations and the Cotonou Partnership Agreement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert I - Technical Adviser with Experience in a NAO Office&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Master’s degree in either of the following disciplines: Economics, Finance, Business Administration, Social Sciences or Public Administration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of spoken and written English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 12 years professional experience in an advisory role either in the public or private sector and/or development financing of which at least 5 years must be in an NAO office &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive and demonstrated understanding of funding modalities of the European Union&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent understanding of the current aid architecture (trends in aid policy management, coordination and modes of aid delivery)  such as budget support and use of country systems &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of development cooperation and the various instruments of the EU&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated understanding of project cycle management, developing and implementing monitoring framework for donor funded programmes and the respective challenges for Aid Management
Specific professional experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years work experience in ACP region preferably relevant work experience in a developing country&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with public financial programming and decentralised budgeting/financing system&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated Knowledge of EDF procedures particularly financial and procurement procedures , reporting requirements and programming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;Aurelie_Durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category II Expertise in Sociology</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-expertise-in-sociology</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 19:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-expertise-in-sociology</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation of the Sector Policy Support Programme &amp;lsquo;Promoting mutual trade by removing technical barriers to trade between Ukraine and the European Union&amp;rsquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific purpose for undertaking this evaluation is to evaluate the Technical Barriers to Trade in Sector Budget Support according to the standard OECD criteria and finally study the effects of EU-funded cooperation in the area of technical barriers to trade on the business climate in Ukraine and of the perceptions by the business community of the reforms supported by the TBT SBS and other EU-funded programmes on the subject.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a matter of fact, systematic and timely evaluation of its programmes, activities, instruments, legislation and non-spending activities is a priority of the European Commission in order to demonstrate accountability and to promote lesson learning to improve policy and practice. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The generic purpose of the evaluation is to identify key lessons and to produce recommendations to improve current and inform future choices on the sector reform contracts in Ukraine and on the cooperation between the EU in Ukraine in the sphere of the removal of technical barriers in the trade in industrial goods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 130 days (until May 2017)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category II Expertise in Sociology – 45 working days&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in a field related to the assignment – economic, social or legal sciences - or at least extra 5 years of experience additional to that described below under the general professional experience; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent English communication skills, both spoken and written. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Ukrainian (or Russian) would be a very strong asset;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least 6 years of relevant professional experience in sociology;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;professional experience in development cooperation will be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years of practical experience in designing, implementation and analysis of sociological polls;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical experience in application of the focus groups tool.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category I Expertise  in Technical Barriers to Trade </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-expertise-in-technical-barriers-to-trade</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 19:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-expertise-in-technical-barriers-to-trade</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation of the Sector Policy Support Programme &amp;lsquo;Promoting mutual trade by removing technical barriers to trade between Ukraine and the European Union&amp;rsquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific purpose for undertaking this evaluation is to evaluate the Technical Barriers to Trade in Sector Budget Support according to the standard OECD criteria and finally study the effects of EU-funded cooperation in the area of technical barriers to trade on the business climate in Ukraine and of the perceptions by the business community of the reforms supported by the TBT SBS and other EU-funded programmes on the subject.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a matter of fact, systematic and timely evaluation of its programmes, activities, instruments, legislation and non-spending activities is a priority of the European Commission in order to demonstrate accountability and to promote lesson learning to improve policy and practice. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The generic purpose of the evaluation is to identify key lessons and to produce recommendations to improve current and inform future choices on the sector reform contracts in Ukraine and on the cooperation between the EU in Ukraine in the sphere of the removal of technical barriers in the trade in industrial goods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 130 days (until May 2017)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category I Expertise  in Technical Barriers to Trade – 50 working days&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in a field related to the assignment – economic, legal, financial, international relations, engineering etc. or at least extra 5 years of experience additional to that described below under the general professional experience; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;be proficient in English (level C1 in reading, speaking and writing);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;have excellent communication and analytical skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;be capable using modern IT technologies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;excellent writing skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The working knowledge of Ukrainian or Russian (at least level B2) will be an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least 12 years of relevant professional experience in the areas of technical regulation and quality infrastructure (non-food products), including standardisation, metrology, conformity assessment, market surveillance or accreditation institutions,;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least 1 year of professional experience in development cooperation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience in budget support implementation or evaluation would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the ENP countries, including Ukraine, will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category I Expertise in Evaluation</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-expertise-in-evaluation</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 19:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-expertise-in-evaluation</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation of the Sector Policy Support Programme &amp;lsquo;Promoting mutual trade by removing technical barriers to trade between Ukraine and the European Union&amp;rsquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific purpose for undertaking this evaluation is to evaluate the Technical Barriers to Trade in Sector Budget Support according to the standard OECD criteria and finally study the effects of EU-funded cooperation in the area of technical barriers to trade on the business climate in Ukraine and of the perceptions by the business community of the reforms supported by the TBT SBS and other EU-funded programmes on the subject.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a matter of fact, systematic and timely evaluation of its programmes, activities, instruments, legislation and non-spending activities is a priority of the European Commission in order to demonstrate accountability and to promote lesson learning to improve policy and practice. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The generic purpose of the evaluation is to identify key lessons and to produce recommendations to improve current and inform future choices on the sector reform contracts in Ukraine and on the cooperation between the EU in Ukraine in the sphere of the removal of technical barriers in the trade in industrial goods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 130 days (until May 2017)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category I Expertise in Evaluation – 50 working days&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in a field related to the assignment – economic, legal, financial, international relations, engineering etc. or at least extra 5 years of experience additional to that described below under the general professional experience; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;be proficient in English (level C1 in reading, speaking and writing);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;have excellent communication and analytical skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;be capable using modern IT technologies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;excellent writing skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Ukrainian or Russian (at least level B2) will be an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least 12 years of professional experience gained after obtaining the higher education diploma;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least seven years of experience in development cooperation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;proven experience in at least three evaluations; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in budget support implementation or evaluation will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert Spécialiste des Filières Agricoles 
CAT II 
</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-specialiste-des-filieres-agricoles-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-specialiste-des-filieres-agricoles-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mission d&amp;#39;assistance technique aupres du Ministere de l&amp;#39;Agriculture de l&amp;#39;Elevage (Phase transitoire)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général de l&amp;#39;intervention est de contribuer à la mise en place d&amp;#39;un partenariat efficace et pertinent entre la République du Bénin et l&amp;#39;Union Européenne pour le développement du secteur agricole et la sécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle du Bénin. L’objectif particulier consiste à appuyer le Ministère de l’Agriculture, de l’Elevage et de la Pêche (MAEP), dans la conception de la nouvelle stratégie de développement du secteur agricole et de ses modalités de mise en oeuvre et de pilotage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert Spécialiste des Filières Agricoles 
CAT II – 100 j/h&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;expert doit être titulaire d&amp;#39;un BAC+5 minimum en agronomie, économie rurale ou agricole, sociologie rurale, ou équivalent. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Il doit disposer d&amp;#39;au moins 6 ans d&amp;#39;expérience dans le diagnostic de filières agricoles et les stratégies de développement des filières et la mise en place d&amp;#39;interprofession. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La connaissance de la législation sur les interprofessions en Afrique de l&amp;#39;Ouest est souhaitée. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Il doit disposer d&amp;#39;une bonne connaissance du secteur agricole au Bénin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert Spécialiste du Financement du Secteur Agricole, CAT I</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-specialiste-du-financement-du-secteur-agricole-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 15:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-specialiste-du-financement-du-secteur-agricole-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mission d&amp;#39;assistance technique aupres du Ministere de l&amp;#39;Agriculture de l&amp;#39;Elevage (Phase transitoire)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général de l&amp;#39;intervention est de contribuer à la mise en place d&amp;#39;un partenariat efficace et pertinent entre la République du Bénin et l&amp;#39;Union Européenne pour le développement du secteur agricole et la sécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle du Bénin. L’objectif particulier consiste à appuyer le Ministère de l’Agriculture, de l’Elevage et de la Pêche (MAEP), dans la conception de la nouvelle stratégie de développement du secteur agricole et de ses modalités de mise en oeuvre et de pilotage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Expert Spécialiste du Financement du Secteur Agricole, CAT I – 100 j/h
*&lt;/em&gt;
BAC+5 minimum en agronomie, agroéconomie ou équivalent &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Le consultant doit disposer d’au moins 12 ans d&amp;#39;expérience dans le développement rural. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Il disposera d&amp;#39;au moins 6 ans d&amp;#39;expérience dans le financement du secteur agricole, avec au moins une expérience réussi d&amp;#39;octroi de subventions publiques et de (micro) crédit dans le monde agricole, au moins une expérience réussie en matière d’ingénierie de formation et l&amp;#39;élaboration de plan de formation basé sur l&amp;#39;analyse des besoins et des profils. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Il doit avoir une très bonne connaissance des institutions de financement du secteur agricole et du secteur agricole au Bénin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef de Mission, Expert des Politiques et Stratégies de Développement Agricole, CAT I </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-expert-des-politiques-et-strategies-de-developpement-agricole-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 15:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-expert-des-politiques-et-strategies-de-developpement-agricole-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mission d&amp;#39;assistance technique aupres du Ministere de l&amp;#39;Agriculture de l&amp;#39;Elevage (Phase transitoire)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général de l&amp;#39;intervention est de contribuer à la mise en place d&amp;#39;un partenariat efficace et pertinent entre la République du Bénin et l&amp;#39;Union Européenne pour le développement du secteur agricole et la sécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle du Bénin. L’objectif particulier consiste à appuyer le Ministère de l’Agriculture, de l’Elevage et de la Pêche (MAEP), dans la conception de la nouvelle stratégie de développement du secteur agricole et de ses modalités de mise en oeuvre et de pilotage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chef de Mission, Expert des Politiques et Stratégies de Développement Agricole, CAT I – 120 j/h&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Le chef de mission aura une formation BAC+5 minimum en agronomie, agroéconomie, économie rurale, sociologie rurale ou équivalent avec une expérience générale d’au moins 12 ans dans le développement rural.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Il doit disposer d&amp;#39;au moins 5 ans dans les pays en voie de développement. Il aura une expérience spécifique dans l&amp;#39;élaboration, le suivi et l’évaluation de politiques et de stratégie de développement agricole ainsi que la mise en œuvre de réformes sectorielles dans le secteur agricole. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Une expertise pratique dans les domaines du conseil agricole, de développement des services à l’exploitation agricole, de l’installation des jeunes dans l’agriculture dans des pays en développement sera appréciée. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Il doit disposer d’au moins 6 ans d&amp;#39;expérience dans le domaine des finances rurales et agricoles avec au moins une expérience dans la budgétisation axée sur les résultats ainsi qu&amp;#39;une bonne connaissance de l’ECOWAP/PDDAA, des orientations stratégiques de la CEDEAO et exigences juridiques relatives à l&amp;#39;élaboration de stratégie agricole et mobilisation de ressource. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Une connaissance des procédures de la Commission Européenne constituera un avantage comparatif. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Une connaissance de la problématique du développement rural ou de pays de la sous-région au Bénin est souhaitée.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Value Chain Specialist (Category II) </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/value-chain-specialist-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 15:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/value-chain-specialist-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formulation of the ARISE+ Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On November 3, 2016, the draft Action Document of ARISE+ will be presented to the Quality Support Group of the European Commission Directorate for Development and Cooperation. Comments received during this consultation will be incorporated in a revised draft Action Document that will be made available to and finalised by the experts. A second Quality Support Group will take place tentatively on March 7, 2017 before a final decision on ARISE+ is reached by Q3 of 2017.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mission&amp;rsquo;s main objective is to assist the EU Delegation to Vietnam formulate the ARISE+ Programme in Vietnam with a focus on its support to private sector component.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mission will identify the list of priorities where the programme&amp;rsquo;s scarce resources should be allocated. This includes the list of sectors most likely to benefit from support to access markets in the EU, with maximum impact on job creation and poverty reduction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Value Chain Specialist (Category II) (25 working days)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Masters Degree in Economics, Business, Trade or another relevant discipline. In its absence, 10 years professional experience working on private sector support and export promotion in developing countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; At least 6 years experience on Trade, Standards and/or
Private sector support;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Experience working with business organisations or producers organisations in Vietnam.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; In-depth knowledge of at least three value chains in Vietnam.  - Strong references on export promotion in Vietnam. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Previous experience on EU market access is an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills and ability to work in a multicultural environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent level of English. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of Vietnamese.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Export Promotion Specialist (Category II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/export-promotion-specialist-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/export-promotion-specialist-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formulation of the ARISE+ Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On November 3, 2016, the draft Action Document of ARISE+ will be presented to the Quality Support Group of the European Commission Directorate for Development and Cooperation. Comments received during this consultation will be incorporated in a revised draft Action Document that will be made available to and finalised by the experts. A second Quality Support Group will take place tentatively on March 7, 2017 before a final decision on ARISE+ is reached by Q3 of 2017.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mission&amp;rsquo;s main objective is to assist the EU Delegation to Vietnam formulate the ARISE+ Programme in Vietnam with a focus on its support to private sector component.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mission will identify the list of priorities where the programme&amp;rsquo;s scarce resources should be allocated. This includes the list of sectors most likely to benefit from support to access markets in the EU, with maximum impact on job creation and poverty reduction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Export Promotion Specialist (Category II) (29 working days)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Masters Degree in Economics, Business, Trade or another relevant discipline. In its absence, 10 years professional experience working on private sector support and export promotion in developing countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; At least 6 years experience on Trade, Standards and/or Private sector support;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong references on export promotion projects and support to producers. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of value chain management. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good understanding of the European market and market access issues for developing countries. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with business organisations or producers organisations. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in South East Asia is an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills and ability to work in a multicultural environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent level of English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Trade, Standards and/or Private Sector Support (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-trade-standards-and-or-private-sector-support-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 15:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-trade-standards-and-or-private-sector-support-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formulation of the ARISE+ Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On November 3, 2016, the draft Action Document of ARISE+ will be presented to the Quality Support Group of the European Commission Directorate for Development and Cooperation. Comments received during this consultation will be incorporated in a revised draft Action Document that will be made available to and finalised by the experts. A second Quality Support Group will take place tentatively on March 7, 2017 before a final decision on ARISE+ is reached by Q3 of 2017.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mission&amp;rsquo;s main objective is to assist the EU Delegation to Vietnam formulate the ARISE+ Programme in Vietnam with a focus on its support to private sector component.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mission will identify the list of priorities where the programme&amp;rsquo;s scarce resources should be allocated. This includes the list of sectors most likely to benefit from support to access markets in the EU, with maximum impact on job creation and poverty reduction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Trade, Standards and/or Private Sector Support (TL)&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;(Category I)&lt;/strong&gt; (28 working days)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Masters Degree in Economics, Business, Trade or another relevant discipline. In its absence, 15 years professional experience working on trade policy in developing countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years’ experience on Trade, Standards and/or Private sector support.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong references advising policy makers on trade policy in developing countries. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of sanitary and phytosanitary issues, trade facilitation and quality infrastructure. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good understanding of Free Trade Agreements and Market Access related issues. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 references as Team Leader. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of EU procedures is an advantage. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of formulation of programmes is an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in South East Asia is an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills and ability to work in a multicultural environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent level of English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef de mission (expert de catégorie 1) – 2eme mission</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-expert-de-categorie-1-2eme-mission</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 13:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-expert-de-categorie-1-2eme-mission</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Realisation de deux (02) etudes relatives au diagnostic des capacities de la CPS/SDR et de l&amp;#39;interprofession riz du Mali et l&amp;#39;elaboration de plans de renforcement de leurs capacities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of the Project:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les objectifs de la présente mission portent sur la réalisation des deux études suivantes :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Étude 1 : Élaboration, sur la base d’un diagnostic approfondi, d’un plan d’action pour le développement des capacités institutionnelles de la CPS/SDR;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Étude 2 : Élaboration, sur la base d’un diagnostic approfondi, d’un plan d’action de renforcement des capacités techniques et organisationnelles de l’Interprofession Riz du Mali.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications Required:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Niveau universitaire équivalent au moins au Master en économie, agroéconomie, en science sociale ou dans un autre domaine équivalent et disposant des expériences et connaissances suivantes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir au moins 12 ans d’expériences professionnelles dans le renforcement des capacités des organisations faîtières des filières agricoles dont au moins trois ans d’expériences professionnelles spécifiques dans le renforcement des capacités des organisations faîtières des filières agricoles dans les pays de l’Afrique francophones ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir réalisé en tant que chef de mission au moins trois missions similaires c&amp;#39;est-àdire des missions portant sur le diagnostic des capacités des interprofessions agricoles assorties de l’élaboration de stratégies pour le développement des capacités de ces interprofessions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir des expériences professionnelles ayant des liens avec les filières agricoles au Mali sera un avantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir de solides capacités à communiquer en langue française.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Juriste (expert de catégorie 2) – 2eme mission</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/juriste-expert-de-categorie-2-2eme-mission</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 12:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/juriste-expert-de-categorie-2-2eme-mission</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of the Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les objectifs de la présente mission portent sur la réalisation des deux études suivantes :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Étude 1 : Élaboration, sur la base d’un diagnostic approfondi, d’un plan d’action pour le
développement des capacités institutionnelles de la CPS/SDR ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Étude 2 : Élaboration, sur la base d’un diagnostic approfondi, d’un plan d’action de
renforcement des capacités techniques et organisationnelles de l’Interprofession Riz du
Mali.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications Required:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir un niveau universitaire équivalent au moins au Master en science juridique;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir au moins 6 ans d’expériences professionnelles dans le domaine juridique dont
au moins deux ans dans les pays de l’Afrique francophones ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir réalisé au moins deux missions similaires c&amp;#39;est-à-dire des missions portant sur
l’analyse des cadres juridiques des organisations des filières agricoles et/ou en matière
de conseils juridiques aux organisations des filières agricoles;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir des expériences professionnelles dans le domaine juridique et ayant des liens avec
les filières agricoles au Mali sera un avantage ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir de solides capacités à communiquer en langue française.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spécialise en gestion des Ressources humaines (expert de catégorie 1)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/specialise-en-gestion-des-ressources-humaines-expert-de-categorie-1</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 12:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/specialise-en-gestion-des-ressources-humaines-expert-de-categorie-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of the Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les objectifs de la présente mission portent sur la réalisation des deux études suivantes :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Étude 1 : Élaboration, sur la base d’un diagnostic approfondi, d’un plan d’action pour le
développement des capacités institutionnelles de la CPS/SDR ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Étude 2 : Élaboration, sur la base d’un diagnostic approfondi, d’un plan d’action de
renforcement des capacités techniques et organisationnelles de l’Interprofession Riz du
Mali.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications Required:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Niveau universitaire équivaut au moins au Master en management des organisations, en gestion
des ressources humaines ou dans un autre domaine équivalent et disposant des expériences et
connaissances suivantes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir au moins 12 ans d’expériences professionnelles en matière de Gestion des
Ressources Humaines des Administrations publiques dont au moins trois ans
d’expériences professionnelles spécifiques dans les Administrations publiques des pays
de l’Afrique francophones ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir réalisé, au moins trois missions similaires, c&amp;#39;est-à-dire des missions portant sur
le diagnostic du management (dont la gestion des ressources humaines) des services de
la fonction publique assortie de la formulation de stratégies pour le développement des
capacités de ces services ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir des expériences professionnelles avec l’Administration publique malienne sera un
avantage ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir de solides capacités à communiquer en langue française.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef de mission (expert de catégorie 1)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-expert-de-categorie-1</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-expert-de-categorie-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of the Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les objectifs de la présente mission portent sur la réalisation des deux études suivantes :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Étude 1 : Élaboration, sur la base d’un diagnostic approfondi, d’un plan d’action pour le
développement des capacités institutionnelles de la CPS/SDR ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Étude 2 : Élaboration, sur la base d’un diagnostic approfondi, d’un plan d’action de
renforcement des capacités techniques et organisationnelles de l’Interprofession Riz du
Mali.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Niveau universitaire équivalent au
moins au Master en statistiques ou en planification ou en Agronomie, ou en Agroéconomie ou
dans un autre domaine équivalent et disposant des expériences et connaissances suivantes :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir au moins 12 ans d’expériences professionnelles dans des systèmes de
statistiques (nationaux et/ou Agricoles) couvrant les domaines suivants : planification,
suivi-évaluation des politiques et programmes agricoles, production et diffusion de
statistiques Agricoles dont au moins trois ans d’expériences professionnelles
spécifiques avec les services des statistiques Agricoles dans les pays de l’Afrique
francophone ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir coordonné, en tant que chef de mission, au moins trois missions similaires, c&amp;#39;està-
dire des missions d’évaluation des capacités des services de statistiques agricoles et
d’élaboration de stratégies de développement des capacités de ces services ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir une expérience d’appui dans l’organisation des concertations sectorielles (multiacteurs)
;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir des expériences professionnelles avec l’Administration publique malienne sera un
avantage ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir de solides capacités à communiquer en langue française.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category III Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-iii-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-iii-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Global Objective of this evaluation is to provide the project stakeholders, primarily the EU Delegation to Laos, with sufficient information about the project performance of the Pool Fund
(its relevancy, efficiency, effectiveness, impacts and sustainability), document lessons learned and provide practical recommendations for future programmes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Specific Objectives&lt;/strong&gt; are built on five key parameters for the evaluator to study; and these are:relevance, efficiency, effectives, impact and sustainability as described below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the relevance of the project design (its activities and objectives) in addressing the priority issues in the target communities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess to what extent the available resources have been used economically in delivering the project outputs/results, in terms of quantity, quality and timeliness (efficiency).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the major achievements of the project to date in relation to its stated objectives and intended results based on the logframe (effectiveness);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess to what extent the project is contributing to a long-term positive effect on the entire society in the uplands (impact);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess whether the positive outcomes of the project are likely to continue after the project (sustainability).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications Required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;S/he will have at least a Bachelor degree in Agriculture/Rural Development or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;S/he has at least 3 years of professional experience relevant to the Agriculture/Rural Development sectors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;S/he will have past training delivery experience at the subnational level proven by at least one assignment;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;S/he has at least one past experience in project/programme evaluation, particularly in a rural development project/programme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;English Proficiency&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Communication skills in Lao would be an asset.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category I Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 09:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of the Project:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Global Objective of this evaluation is to provide the project stakeholders, primarily the EU Delegation to Laos, with sufficient information about the project performance of the Pool Fund
(its relevancy, efficiency, effectiveness, impacts and sustainability), document lessons learned and provide practical recommendations for future programmes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Specific Objectives are built on five key parameters for the evaluator to study; and these are: relevance, efficiency, effectives, impact and sustainability as described below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the relevance of the project design (its activities and objectives) in addressing the priority issues in the target communities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess to what extent the available resources have been used economically in delivering the project outputs/results, in terms of quantity, quality and timeliness (efficiency).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the major achievements of the project to date in relation to its stated objectives and intended results based on the logframe (effectiveness);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Asses to what extent the project is contributing to a long-term positive effect on the entire society in the uplands (impact);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess whether the positive outcomes of the project are likely to continue after the project
(sustainability).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications Required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;•S/he has an advanced university degree (minimum Master) in Agriculture/Rural Development studies or relevant International Development Studies or equivalent professional experience of
at least 153 years if candidate does not possess an advance university degree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;•S/he has at least 12 years of professional experience relevant to the Agriculture/Rural Development sectors&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;•S/he has minimum 3 years&amp;#39; experience in the implementation and management of development projects or programmes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;•S/he has least one relevant experience with Programme Based approaches,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;•S/he has at least two relevant past experiences with EU Project Cycle Management and, in particular with evaluation procedures,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;•S/he will also have team leader experience proven by at least two missions as head of mission/team leader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;•English Proficiency&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;•Communication skills in Lao would be an asset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Banking Regulation and Supervision</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-banking-regulation-and-supervision</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 01:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-banking-regulation-and-supervision</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to the preparation of the twinning fiches for the National Bank of the Republic of Belarus&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The assignment will consist of supporting the preparation of the twinning fiche for the National Bank of the Republic of Belarus (NBRB) as the beneficiary and project partner of the first twinning project in Belarus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in Banking Regulation and Supervision (Category I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of general professional experience in the sector related to the Lot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master’s Degree, preferably in macroeconomics, financial management, banking regulation or other relevant field or, in its absence, at least 5 additional years of professional experience on top of the 12 required under general professional experience above&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of professional experience in the area of banking regulation and/or supervision in the EU countries or countries covered by the Enlargement Policy;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in drafting project proposals for technical assistance projects (at least one reference);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good prior knowledge of the banking sector regulatory and supervision situation of the Republic of Belarus would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Background in Twinning matters would be asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in both written and spoken English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Russian would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;em&gt;[Lina&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;](mailto:&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;lina_forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Economic and Monetary Policy </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-economic-and-monetary-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 01:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-economic-and-monetary-policy</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to the preparation of the twinning fiches for the National Bank of the Republic of Belarus&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The assignment will consist of supporting the preparation of the twinning fiche for the National Bank of the Republic of Belarus (NBRB) as the beneficiary and project partner of the first twinning project in Belarus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader, Expert in Economic and Monetary Policy (Category I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of general professional experience in the sector related to the Lot; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master’s Degree, preferably in macroeconomics, financial management, banking regulation or other relevant field or, in its absence, at least 5 additional years of professional experience on top of the 12 required under general professional experience above;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of professional experience in area of monetary and/or macroeconomic policy, targeting inflation, Central bank regulation in the EU countries or countries covered by the Enlargement Policy;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of the EU Acquis in a banking field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in drafting project proposals for technical assistance projects in macroeconomic or banking area (at least one reference);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good prior knowledge of the macroeconomic policy, banking sector, regulatory and supervision situation of the Republic of Belarus would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Background in Twinning matters would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in both written and spoken English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Russian would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
