<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 11:27:57 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deputy Team Leader, Justice Services and Stability for Development (JSS4D), Papua New Guinea </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/deputy-team-leader-justice-services-and-stability-for-development-jss4d-papua-new-guinea</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 11:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/deputy-team-leader-justice-services-and-stability-for-development-jss4d-papua-new-guinea</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Please note that there are &lt;strong&gt;four deputy team leader positions&lt;/strong&gt; relating to Community Safety, Family and Sexual Violence, Law and Justice Services and Anti-Corruption. These positions may be shared where possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Position Description&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Deputy Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; shall support the Team Leader to achieve the outcomes of the Program. They will primarily be responsible for managing activities in their component areas. They may also be required to provide technical input into other aspects of the program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ARF Level&lt;/strong&gt;: C3&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support in the management and coordination in the achievement of the Program objectives. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working in a collaborative and coordinated manner with relevant agency-advisers, support sector agencies, coordinating bodies and other partners, including at the sub-national and community level, to build capacity to implement the JSS4D program; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Encourage and support efforts to improve coordination, coherence and partnerships among sector stakeholders, and to build mutual understanding and engagement with central agencies, at sub-national levels and within communities; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support mechanisms to address service delivery challenges and overarching policy issues such as community and subnational engagement, gender equality and restorative justice; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support law and justice sector managers and staff to participate effectively in sector coordination mechanisms and other forums; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work proactively, in a collaborative manner with other GoA-funded programs, as well as other donors, to enable cross-program learning and coordination, and to ensure effective harmonisation of assistance to the law and justice sector; and &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integrate principles of gender equality and gender mainstreaming into capacity building approaches. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure quality assurance principles guide the timely preparation and submission of required briefings and reports. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skills and experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tertiary qualifications in a relevant field and / or significant experience. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated understanding of the role and functions of the justice system and its agencies in a modern democracy. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated understanding of the range of capacity building approaches and their applicability to different contexts and needs, and commitment to principles of gender equality and gender mainstreaming. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Substantial knowledge, skills and experience in the adviser’s designated area of expertise and an understanding of its importance in effecting sustainable organisational change. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in a dynamic public sector or other major organisational environment, in particular politically sensitive environment. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to develop constructive working relationships with a range of government, private sector and community stakeholders. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High level policy and analytical skills. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High level interpersonal and communication skills. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in working successfully in a cross-cultural, multi-lingual environment, particularly in the Pacific would be an advantage. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to apply&lt;/strong&gt;: Please send your CV by email to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;Sarah_Owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please note that due to high volumes of applications, we cannot guarantee to respond to each applicant.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline for Application&lt;/strong&gt;: 27th April 2015 (Recruitment will close once suitable candidates have been identified) &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader, Law &amp; Justice Sector, Papua New Guinea</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-law-justice-sector-papua-new-guinea-1</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 11:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-law-justice-sector-papua-new-guinea-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectives of the role&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; will have overall responsibility for ensuring all the Services are delivered to good-practice standards, in accordance with requirements and terms of the Contract, and for managing day-to-day activities of the management team and other personnel. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; shall be responsible for all administration, management and quality of all services provided by the Contractor to achieve the outcomes of the Program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ARF Level&lt;/strong&gt;: C4&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the team in the management and coordination in the achievement of the Program objectives; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead and coordinate the provision of technical and policy advisory support for the Program; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide support to the different Ministries on policy and planning as required, including appropriate inputs to relevant associated Development Plan activities and reviews. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the development of an overall work plan and budget for the team, ensuring alignment to GoPNG sub-sector priorities. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establishing and maintaining supportive and cooperative relationships with relevant Partner Government organisations; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure contracted programs and personnel work consultatively with stakeholders and each other and encourage a culture of high performance and collaboration. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regular review of technical and advisory personnel performance, focusing on achievement of outcomes, provision of feedback and management of all performance issues. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage the program office, supervising the work and performance of any support staff and preparing regular financial reports and technical reports/briefings as required. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skills and experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tertiary qualifications in a relevant field and / or significant experience. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated understanding of the role and functions of the justice system and its agencies in developing countries. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated understanding of the role and functions of traditional, customary or informal justice systems in a developing country context would be an advantage. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in managing and implementing complex institutional strengthening initiatives in a developing country, with experience working in Pacific region highly desirable. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated understanding and commitment to principles of gender equality and gender mainstreaming, including how these can be integrated into capacity building approaches. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in a dynamic public sector or other major organisational environment, in particular politically sensitive environment. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High level of interpersonal, communication and leadership skills. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in working successfully in a cross-cultural, multi-lingual environment, particularly in the Pacific would be an advantage. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to apply&lt;/strong&gt;: Please send your CV by email to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;Sarah_Owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please note that due to high volumes of applications, we cannot guarantee to respond to each applicant&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deadline for Application&lt;/strong&gt;: 27th April 2015 (Recruitment will close once a suitable candidate has been identified)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Administration Reform/Legal Sector Reform Expert (Cat.I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/public-administration-reform-legal-sector-reform-expert-cati</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2015 12:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/public-administration-reform-legal-sector-reform-expert-cati</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To draft terms of reference for an EU financed technical assistance project which would reinforce the capacities of the Ministries of Justice in BiH, Brčko District&amp;rsquo;s Judicial Commission, and the HJPC for strategic and budgetary planning, and also strengthen their mutual coordination mechanism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Administration Reform/Legal Sector Reform Expert (Cat.I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;S/he combines both technical competence and practical experience in the reform of public administration,and/or technical competence and practical experience in the justice sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Education at least at Master&amp;rsquo;s degree academic level in the area of law/political science/public administration/economics/social sciences or any other appropriate discipline for this assignment or equivalent professional experience of 4 years above the general professional experience demanded below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not less than 12 years general professional experience relevant for the assignment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have direct experience in providing technical guidance and support in designing, implementing or monitoring of public administration reform or justice sector reform projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in carrying out strategic planning would be considered an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of supporting the implementation of public and justice sector reform measures in the Western Balkan region would be an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of written and verbal English language.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the national languages of BIH would be considered an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 2: Expert en Cartographie – Cat. II</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-expert-en-cartographie-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 16:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-expert-en-cartographie-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;évaluation a pour principaux objectifs de présenter aux services de coopération extérieure concernés de l’Union européenne, au PNUD et au gouvernement partenaire :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une appréciation globale, en toute indépendance, des résultats de l’intervention du PAPDFGC, en s’attachant plus particulièrement aux résultats du projet par rapport à ses objectifs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;les principaux enseignements de l&amp;#39;intervention et des recommandations afin d’améliorer les mesures en cours et les futures actions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2: Expert en Cartographie – Cat. II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formation&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au minimum Master (Bac +5) en géographie, Systèmes d&amp;#39;Information Géographique (SIG) ou toute autre discipline équivalente&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une formation complémentaire en suivi/évaluation sera considérée comme un avantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 6 ans d&amp;#39;expérience professionnelle générale dans le domaine des Systèmes d&amp;#39;Information Géographique et/ou de l&amp;#39;environnement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience d&amp;#39;au moins 4 ans en gestion de projets de production d&amp;#39;infrastructure géographique (base de données, cartographie, topographie, etc…) similaires (secteur privé et/ou assistance à des institutions publiques)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience spécifique sur au moins deux projets de prises de vues aériennes de très haute résolution, ortho-images, modèle numérique de terrain, stéréo préparation et production de cartes topographiques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience d&amp;#39;assistance à au moins une institution publique dans les pays en développement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en Afrique de l&amp;#39;Ouest considérée comme un avantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans le secteur privée considérée comme un avantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans le suivi/évaluation de projets de développement sur financement bilatéraux ou multilatéraux sera considérée comme un avantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Langue&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Français courant obligatoire&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef d’Equipe: Expert Environnement et Evaluation – Cat. I</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-dequipe-expert-environnement-et-evaluation-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-dequipe-expert-environnement-et-evaluation-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;évaluation a pour principaux objectifs de présenter aux services de coopération extérieure concernés de l’Union européenne, au PNUD et au gouvernement partenaire :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;une appréciation globale, en toute indépendance, des résultats de l’intervention du PAPDFGC, en s’attachant plus particulièrement aux résultats du projet par rapport à ses objectifs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;les principaux enseignements de l&amp;#39;intervention et des recommandations afin d’améliorer les mesures en cours et les futures actions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chef d’Equipe: Expert Environnement et Evaluation – Cat. I&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formation&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme supérieur (minimum Master ; Bac +5) en Ecologie ou Environnement, ou géographie physique environnementale, Génie rural, Agroforesterie, Gestion des Ressources Naturelles ou équivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une formation complémentaire en suivi/évaluation sera considérée comme un avantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une formation complémentaire en cartographie et Systèmes d&amp;#39;Information Géographique sera considérée comme un avantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 12 ans d&amp;#39;expérience professionnelle générale dans les domaines de l&amp;#39;environnement et/ou des changements climatiques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience spécifique en gestion de projets de développement sur financement internationaux d&amp;#39;au moins 10 ans dans une ou plusieurs des thématiques suivantes : gestion durable et participative des ressources naturelles, foresterie, agroforesterie, adaptation aux changements climatiques, cartographie environnementale réduction des risques de catastrophe (inondations)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience sur au moins 2 projets de l&amp;#39;approche participative (bottom up) encourageant l&amp;#39;appropriation des activités et des résultats par les populations bénéficiaires&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience de suivi/évaluation d&amp;#39;au moins 4 projets similaires (thématique / budget)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise des procédures PNUD obligatoire (au moins une expérience de gestion de projet PNUD), procédures UE souhaitables&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience préalable en Afrique de l&amp;#39;Ouest et/ou au Bénin dans le secteur de l&amp;#39;environnement et/ou des changements climatiques sera considérée comme un avantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en SIG et cartographie souhaitée&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capacités relationnelles, sens de l&amp;#39;organisation, facultés d&amp;#39;analyse, qualités rédactionnelles (ces qualités pourront être démontrées dans le document Organisation &amp;amp; Méthodologie à soumettre dans les offres&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Langue&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Français courant obligatoire&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Junior Experts in Communications/Journalism/Media </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/three-junior-experts-in-communications-journalism-media</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2015 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/three-junior-experts-in-communications-journalism-media</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guidelines for EU support to media freedom and media integrity in the enlargement countries 2014-20&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To assess the baseline values for each objective and result of the Guidelines against relevant indicators/ benchmarks in all the seven countries providing reliable aggregate data for the reference year 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location Visits&lt;/strong&gt;: Albania, BiH, FYROM, Kosovo, Montenegro, Serbia and Turkey&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Three Junior Experts in Communications/Journalism/Media&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum requirements&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;University Degree in the field of social sciences, communications and journalism or in its absence, minimum 5 years of professional experience in the same fields. Excellent oral and writing skills in English (at least level 2 in a scale from 1 to 5, where 1 is &amp;ldquo;excellent&amp;rdquo; and 5 is &amp;ldquo;basic&amp;rdquo; (template of CV). Knowledge of one or more local languages (at least level 3 in a scale from 1 to 5, where 1 is &amp;ldquo;excellent&amp;rdquo; and 5 is &amp;ldquo;basic&amp;rdquo; (template of CV). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 2 years post-degree relevant professional experience in evaluation, monitoring of programme and policies or academic research. Proven knowledge of local media contexts in the Western Balkans and Turkey (e.g. publications, professional or academic experience). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Contractor will make sure that the experts work in cooperation with each other. All experts will be independent and free of conflicts of interest. The team as a whole should have good command of the following languages &lt;strong&gt;Albanian, Serbo-Croat-Bosnian, Macedonian and Turkish&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please do not apply unless you speak at least one of the above languages&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert: Media </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-media</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2015 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-media</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guidelines for EU support to media freedom and media integrity in the enlargement countries 2014-20&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To assess the baseline values for each objective and result of the Guidelines against relevant indicators/ benchmarks in all the seven countries providing reliable aggregate data for the reference year 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert: Media&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;: 
Minimum Master Degree Academic level or equivalent Diploma. Very good oral and writing skills in English (at least level 2 in a scale from 1 to 5, where 1 is &amp;ldquo;excellent&amp;rdquo; and 5 is &amp;ldquo;basic&amp;rdquo; (template of CV). Knowledge of local language(s) is an asset. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 10 years post-degree relevant professional experience in communication or journalism.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 3 years’ professional experience on assessing/ monitoring media related programmes or policies. Proven knowledge of international and EU standards for media freedom and integrity of media (e.g. publications, professional or academic experience) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One of the two senior experts will be proposed by the Contractor as Team Leader.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert: Monitoring and Evaluation </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-monitoring-and-evaluation</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2015 16:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-monitoring-and-evaluation</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Guidelines for EU support to media freedom and media integrity in the enlargement countries 2014-20&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To assess the baseline values for each objective and result of the Guidelines against relevant indicators/ benchmarks in all the seven countries providing reliable aggregate data for the reference year 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location visits&lt;/strong&gt;: Albania, BiH, FYROM, Kosovo, Montenegro, Serbia and Turkey&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert: Monitoring and Evaluation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;: Minimum Master Degree Academic level or equivalent Diploma. Excellent oral and writing skills in English (level 1 in a scale from 1 to 5, where 1 is &amp;ldquo;excellent&amp;rdquo; and 5 is &amp;ldquo;basic&amp;rdquo; (template of CV). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: 
Minimum 10 years post-degree relevant professional experience in evaluation, monitoring, project management or academic research. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: 
The above experience should also include a minimum of 5 years in monitoring/evaluating policies and programmes in international environments. Experience in qualitative and quantitative research and report drafting&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spécialiste en Suivi-évaluation de programme et projet&quot; (Catégorie I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/specialiste-en-suivi-evaluation-de-programme-et-projet-categorie-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2015 08:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/specialiste-en-suivi-evaluation-de-programme-et-projet-categorie-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Evaluation à mi-parcours du Programme de sécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle au Burkina Faso (PSANBF).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Le Programme de sécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle au Burkina Faso (PSANBF) a été initié suite à la revue à mi-parcours du Programme Indicatif National (PIN) du 10è FED du Burkina Faso. Il s&amp;#39;insère dans le cadre de l&amp;#39;initiative OMD de l&amp;#39;Union européenne en vue de répondre aux problèmes récurrents et structurels d&amp;#39;insécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle au Burkina Faso.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spécialiste en Suivi-évaluation de programme et projet&amp;quot; (Catégorie I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins un Master (ou expérience équivalente de 12 ans) en Economie, en Statistique, en Socio-économie ou équivalent ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 10 ans d’expérience professionnelle dans le  domaine du suivi-évaluation de politiques, de programmes et projets de développement, notamment en Afrique.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;De façon spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir une expérience confirmée en matière de planification, de suivi-évaluation de programmes et projets de développement, avec au moins 5 évaluations de programmes ou projets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir au moins 3 références dans les domaines des techniques de traitement et d’analyse des données d’enquêtes agropastorales, alimentaires et nutritionnelles et des systèmes de statistiques agricoles et d’alerte, d&amp;#39;information sur la sécurité alimentaire et d’analyse des marchés agricoles et des prix seront un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir des connaissances avérées en Gestion Axée sur les Résultats et une bonne maîtrise des approches de gestion de cycle de vie de projet et de cadre logique, notamment l&amp;#39;approche de l&amp;#39;UE en la matière.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir une excellente maîtrise du français (lu, parlé, écrit).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir d’excellentes aptitudes rédactionnelles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne maîtrise de l’utilisation d’outil informatique, en  particulier des logiciels Word, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicolas_fichers@dai.com&quot;&gt;Nicolas_fichers@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert en Sécurité alimentaire, Chef d’équipe (Catégorie I</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-securite-alimentaire-chef-dequipe-categorie-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2015 07:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-securite-alimentaire-chef-dequipe-categorie-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Evaluation à mi-parcours du Programme de sécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle au Burkina Faso (PSANBF).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Le Programme de sécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle au Burkina Faso (PSANBF) a été initié suite à la revue à mi-parcours du Programme Indicatif National (PIN) du 10è FED du Burkina Faso. Il s&amp;#39;insère dans le cadre de l&amp;#39;initiative OMD de l&amp;#39;Union européenne en vue de répondre aux problèmes récurrents et structurels d&amp;#39;insécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle au Burkina Faso.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert en Sécurité alimentaire, Chef d’équipe (Catégorie I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins un Master (ou expérience équivalente de 12 ans en Economie, Agroéconomie, en Agronomie, Socio-économie.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 10 ans d’expérience professionnelle dans le domaine de la sécurité alimentaire, avec une référence dans la gestion des programmes et projets dans le secteur agricole ou de sécurité alimentaire notamment en Afrique.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;De façon spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience confirmée dans l&amp;#39;évaluation de programmes et projets suivant les procédures de l&amp;#39;Union européenne avec au moins 5 évaluations dont au moins 3 comme chef de mission.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience d’au moins 3 cas d&amp;#39;analyses de la sécurité alimentaire et des politiques agricoles et de sécurité alimentaire. Les références dans ce domaine en Afrique de l’Ouest seront un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonnes connaissances des approches de cycle de vie et de cadre logique des projets financés par l&amp;#39;Union européenne.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir une bonne connaissance des concepts et outils, des politiques, de la gouvernance et des dispositions internationales en matière de sécurité alimentaire.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir une bonne connaissance des procédures applicables aux aides extérieures au développement de l&amp;#39;Union européenne, notamment du Fonds Européen de  Développement (FED) sera un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir une bonne capacité d&amp;#39;animation et une aptitude à travailler en équipe.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir été au moins 3 fois chef d&amp;#39;équipe d&amp;#39;évaluation d&amp;#39;un projet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Etre capable de présenter des rapports de grande qualité professionnelle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir une excellente maîtrise du français (lu, parlé, écrit).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir d’excellentes aptitudes rédactionnelles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne maîtrise de l’utilisation d’outil informatique, en particulier des logiciels Word, Excel et Powerpoint.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicolas_fichers@dai.com&quot;&gt;Nicolas_fichers@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Management and Planning Expert (Category III)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/public-management-and-planning-expert-category-iii</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2015 08:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/public-management-and-planning-expert-category-iii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inception Technical Assistance to support Bangladesh Small and Cottage Industries Corporation (BSCIC)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technical Assistance to BSCIC during the programme Inception Phase in order to support and to facilitate the operational start-up of the PRISM project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public Management and Planning Expert (Category III)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master degree in public administration and/or management, public financial management, social sciences or/and professional experience in related field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least three years professional experience in development cooperation planning, management and/or implementation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience with preparation of public procurement documentation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience in procurement in government institutions or development projects in Bangladesh would be considered a strong asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;knowledge of national institutions in Bangladesh and solid understanding of the local context, especially regarding the SME and SMCI (Small an Cottages Industries) sectors is considered an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;managerial and communication skills, including the ability to work effectively with officials from government;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;any experience in training/coaching is considered an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a fluent working knowledge of written and spoken English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;knowledge of Bangla language is considered an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent working knowledge of written and spoken English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:francesca_giordano@dai.com&quot;&gt;Francesca_Giordano@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader / Public Management and Planning (Category II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-public-management-and-planning-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2015 08:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-public-management-and-planning-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inception Technical Assistance to support Bangladesh Small and Cottage Industries Corporation (BSCIC)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technical Assistance to BSCIC during the programme Inception Phase in order to support and to facilitate the operational start-up of the PRISM project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader / Public Management and Planning (Category II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master degree in public administration and/or management, public financial management, social sciences or/and professional experience in related field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least 6 years of professional experience in development cooperation planning, management and implementation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;managerial and leadership skills including the ability to work effectively with officials from government in third countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience as team leader in at least 2 assignments of similar nature and scope;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;be fully familiar with the EU financial and contractual procurement rules; experience in preparation and management of Programme Estimate (PE) in line with EU rules and procedures is mandatory;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience as Imprest Administrator or Imprest Accounting Officer in the context of private indirect decentralised operations is considered an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience in the preparation of ToR, global and annual work plans and budgets for public sector in third countries in the context of donor funded development programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience of training/ coaching officials from government on EU financial and contractual procurement rules: especially preparation and management of PE as well as preparation of global and annual work plans and budgets; ,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;having country specific experience in Bangladesh, previous work experience with officials from government of Bangladesh is considered an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;have good drafting and communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent working knowledge of written and spoken English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:francesca_giordano@dai.com&quot;&gt;Francesca_Giordano@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader – SEED Pacific</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-seed-pacific</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 20:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-seed-pacific</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objective of the Programme&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Australian Government recently established the &lt;strong&gt;innovationXchange&lt;/strong&gt; to drive innovation throughout Australia’s aid program so that it becomes an intrinsic way of thinking and acting. The &lt;strong&gt;innovationXchange&lt;/strong&gt; will create and test development innovations, source new ideas for the wider aid program, and work with the private sector to find more creative and clever ways to achieve better results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Australian Department of Foreign Affairs and Trade (DFAT) works constructively with the private sector in the Pacific in many ways, seeing both successes and opportunities for learning. DFAT has therefore developed &lt;strong&gt;SEED Pacific&lt;/strong&gt;, an innovative initiative that seeks to harness the collective power of business and society to solve development challenges in the Pacific. &lt;strong&gt;SEED Pacific&lt;/strong&gt; will target businesses that are prepared to show leadership and innovation in the Pacific and will broker and support the most promising partnerships between global businesses and local organisations to develop new business solutions that have a development impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organisations&lt;/strong&gt; will receive:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support to tailor their business solutions to the Pacific&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Networking opportunities and links to strategic partners&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunities to develop business solutions in collaboration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Match funding for the best business solutions identified through a competitive process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;objectives&lt;/strong&gt; of SEED Pacific are to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Source, test and scale new business ideas that solve development challenges in the Pacific&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work in an innovative way with partners to create and implement the Initiative and the business solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Forge new multi-sector partnerships with Pacific-based organisations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leverage private sector finance for development outcomes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn from failures as much as successes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scope of Work&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; will be responsible for the technical leadership and overall management of the project.  S/he will oversee the long-term expatriate, short term experts and local staff in achieving project results. S/he will undertake regular assessments of the broader political environment within which the project operates to ensure flexibility and rapid reprioritization of activities when necessary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duties and Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serve as principal liaison with DFAT, government counterparts across the Pacific and community stakeholders on programme communications and technical implementation activities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and manage relationships with key actors including government, the private sector, and CSOs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage and provide oversight of project finances.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage staff and recruitment practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work directly with DAI Head Office on programme planning, implementation, personnel, and budget. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversee contractual and financial matters with donors and key partners, and play a key role in the preparation of budget.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regularly draft and compile monthly, quarterly and annual reports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide timely and accurate reporting to DFAT on all programme areas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversee all technical aspects of the project and participate, as required, in assessment, analysis, and training.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage, lead and oversee long and short term staff and subcontractors in achieving project results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversee the participatory planning process and produce a strategic plan for project deliverables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oversee the development and implementation of the M&amp;amp;E framework.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Present programme findings to stakeholders and clients; both written and oral.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate programme activities with other donors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure good relations with donor agencies and local implementing partners.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure good, frequent, and direct communications with the Head Office.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;More than 10 years of experience in managing multi-cultural teams and complex projects in developing countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;More than 5 years of experience in the design and implementation of challenge or enterprise funds, or innovation initiatives.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated programme implementation capability, particularly in building capacity of counterparts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An advanced Degree in Political Science, International Development, Public/ Business Administration or related area is required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent networking experience and relationship management skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferable experience of working in Australia or the Pacific region.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated knowledge of latest good governance practices in international development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience working with senior host-country counterparts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous management experience of DFAT-funded programmes, ideally in a TL role, or other donor projects including familiarity with donor management tools, mechanisms and procedures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English is required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to Apply&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;br&gt;
If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV in DFAT format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting DFAT/SEEDS in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please note that all profiles are indicative only and therefore subject to change.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior EU Joint Programming Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-eu-joint-programming-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2015 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-eu-joint-programming-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior EU Joint Programming Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master degree academic level in social sciences, political sciences, development management, governance or any other relevant filed or equivalent professional experience of 13 years &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 10 years of professional experience in international development cooperation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5 years in the field of donor coordination, development effectiveness&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 1 year working with the EU Development Partners (either the European Commission and/or EU Member states)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in EU Joint Programming or EU coordination will be considered an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Laos and/or other South East Asian countries will be considered a strong advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Public Finance Management Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-public-finance-management-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 11:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-public-finance-management-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the FWC is to assist the EUD to prepare documentation necessary for the efficient programming of a Sector budget support intervention in the IPA 2015
Programming year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support preparation of the Annexes to the Sector Reform Contract/Action document, in line with the Sector budget support Guidelines from DG ELARG 2014 (the Guidelines will be provided to the contractor at the inception meeting);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support the elaboration of the first and second draft version of the Sector Reform Contract / Action Document (including the identification and negotiation of the relevant targets and tranche disbursement indicators).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organise training sessions on SBS preparation and implementation with local stakeholders (line ministries, oversight bodies, NGOs, academia, etc.);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide assessment on the quality of the SBS selected sector policy and the performance management systems at the national and selected sector levels (PAR and PFM sector).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Public Finance Management Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in Economy/Finance, Management or related area (in the absence of diploma, minimum eight (8) years of relevant professional experience in addition to the minimum number of years of general experience specified below)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum 10 (ten) preferably 12 (twelve) years of experience of working on PFM issues, such as budget planning, preparation and execution; public investment programme and revenue management including taxation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least two (2), preferably three (3) projects during the last six years in design, development or implementation of PFM reform programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in implementation, monitoring, evaluation or assessment of sector budget support projects would be an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:adeline_vanhoutte@dai.com&quot;&gt;Adeline_VanHoutte@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Public administration Reform Expert (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-public-administration-reform-expert-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-public-administration-reform-expert-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the FWC is to assist the EUD to prepare documentation necessary for the efficient programming of a Sector budget support intervention in the IPA 2015
Programming year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support preparation of the Annexes to the Sector Reform Contract/Action document, in line with the Sector budget support Guidelines from DG ELARG 2014 (the Guidelines will be provided to the contractor at the inception meeting);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support the elaboration of the first and second draft version of the Sector Reform Contract / Action Document (including the identification and negotiation of the relevant targets and tranche disbursement indicators).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organise training sessions on SBS preparation and implementation with local stakeholders (line ministries, oversight bodies, NGOs, academia, etc.);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide assessment on the quality of the SBS selected sector policy and the performance management systems at the national and selected sector levels (PAR and PFM sector).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Public Administration Reform Expert (TL)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in Economy, Law, Political science or other relevant field (in the absence of diploma, minimum eight (8) years of relevant professional experience in addition to the minimum number of years of general experience specified below).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum 10 (ten) preferably 12 (twelve) years of postgraduate experience in the area of programming, management or monitoring in the field of public administration reform processes at national or local level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the implementation of at least two (2), preferably three (3) projects during the last six years in the field of implementation of service delivery improvement, decentralization or governance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the preparing at least one (1), preferably two (2) sector budget support projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the EU accession process would be an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:adeline_vanhoutte@dai.com&quot;&gt;Adeline_VanHoutte@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Voter Registration Expert (Cat. I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-voter-registration-expert-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2015 17:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-voter-registration-expert-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The European Union intends to send an expert mission to assess the upcoming Constitutional Referendum in Tanzania, currently foreseen to take place on 30 April 2015, although delay cannot be excluded, with a possible re-run within either thirty or sixty days since the publication of final results depending whether these tie or cast a &amp;ldquo;YES&amp;rdquo; vote in one constituent part and &amp;ldquo;NO&amp;rdquo; in the other. The mission will also assess to the extent possible the efficiency and credibility of the Voter Registration operations managed by NEC. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The purpose of the Expert Mission is to collect factual information concerning this electoral process, in line with the criteria contained in the Commission Communication on Electoral Assistance and Observation [COM(2000)191] Moreover the experts will produce strategic analysis and reporting on the ongoing electoral processes and will provide essential analysis for the possible EU EOM to be deployed for the General elections tentatively foreseen for 25 October 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Voter Registration Expert (Cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Advanced University degree in law, political science, international relations, public administration, statistics, computer science or any other discipline relevant to the assignment, or equivalent professional experience of approximately 12 years in the area related to Lot 7. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience:&lt;/strong&gt;
At least 12 years in the field of voter registration or related to Lot 7. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years in the specific field of voter registration and elections, preferably as part of an EU Election Observation Mission or an EU Election Technical Assistance project; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of electoral issues in developing countries, possibly in Africa, in regards to voter registration. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of electronic registration issues, including in regards to data capture and consolidation, data management, card distribution, the challenge of maintaining a list in a difficult environment, transparency and stakeholder confidence. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in the country and/or the region, and good networks within the different sectors of society in order to be immediately operational is an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adaptability to a multicultural working environment. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to clearly summarize findings and present them in a manner compatible with requested EEM reports. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and spoken skills in English. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Electoral/Legal Expert / Team Leader (Cat. I) </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-electoral-legal-expert-team-leader-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2015 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-electoral-legal-expert-team-leader-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The European Union intends to send an expert mission to assess the upcoming Constitutional Referendum in Tanzania, currently foreseen to take place on 30 April 2015, although delay cannot be excluded, with a possible re-run within either thirty or sixty days since the publication of final results depending whether these tie or cast a &amp;ldquo;YES&amp;rdquo; vote in one constituent part and &amp;ldquo;NO&amp;rdquo; in the other. The mission will also assess to the extent possible the efficiency and credibility of the Voter Registration operations managed by NEC. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The purpose of the Expert Mission is to collect factual information concerning this electoral process, in line with the criteria contained in the Commission Communication on Electoral Assistance and Observation [COM(2000)191]1. Moreover the experts will produce strategic analysis and reporting on the ongoing electoral processes and will provide essential analysis for the possible EU EOM to be deployed for the General elections tentatively foreseen for 25 October 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Electoral/Legal Expert / Team Leader (Cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced University degree in Law, Political Science, International Relations or any other discipline relevant to the assignment, or equivalent professional experience of at least 12 years in the area related to Lot 7. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in Law will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least 12 years of experience in the area related to Lot 7. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years’ work experience in the field of electoral assistance and electoral observation and analysis, preferably as part of an EU Election Observation Mission or an Election Technical Assistance project of the EU or of other international organisations, possibly including managing an electoral observation mission, drafting statements and reports; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with the legal and regulatory framework for the elections as well as international and regional standards for elections. In this context the “Compendium of International Standards for Elections” is an important background document; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent understanding of the functioning of election management bodies; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in political analysis. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in representing and providing briefings. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven work experience with analysis of legal framework for elections will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in assessing the media landscape and media framework, according to international and regional standards, particularly as regards to elections, will be an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in the country and/or the region and good networks within the different sectors of society in order to be immediately operational will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and spoken English. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Knowledge of Kiswahili (even if only passive)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In addition&lt;/strong&gt;, the Electoral/Legal Expert / Team Leader will present the following profile: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and inter-personal skills; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent report drafting skills; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coordination and management skills and past experience of management in a similar assignment; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proven knowledge and field experience of EU policies and programmes in the area of human rights, democratization and good governance; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proven work experience in project implementation and budget management of international civilian missions, preferably as part of an EU Election Observation Mission or an EU Election Technical Assistance project; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proven work experience of managing mission budgets and contracts of local staff is an asset. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adaptability to a multicultural working environment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert in M&amp;E and Education (Category II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-me-and-education-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2015 14:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-me-and-education-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overall objectives of the mid-term review (MTR) are to offer an overview of the activities carried out in the first phase of the implementation of the two Programmes : &amp;ldquo;Support to the
Community Courts of Eritrea&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Capacity Building for the Public Administration of Eritrea&amp;rdquo; and to provide recommendations for the successful implementation during the remainder of the implementation periods. The MTR shall provide recommendations for the way forward and confirm one of the two scenarios:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Scenario: no major changes in the programme’s orientation and objectives but with suggestions for revisions that may be necessary to adapt the programme to emerging needs.
• Scenario: major changes in the programme’s orientation, objectives and implementation modalities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in M&amp;amp;E and Education (Category II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in social sciences or a related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven communication and reporting skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum of six years&amp;#39; experience of the LFA and PCM&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Proven experience in Monitoring and Evaluation of donor funded programmes
• Experience in programme in the higher education sector
• Knowledge of the &lt;strong&gt;Eritrean context&lt;/strong&gt; will be an advantage
• Knowledge of the &lt;strong&gt;Eritrean education system&lt;/strong&gt; will be an advantage&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fluency in English is required. &lt;strong&gt;Knowledge of other languages used in Eritrea&lt;/strong&gt; will be an advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring and Evaluation Expert (Category II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/monitoring-and-evaluation-expert-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2015 14:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/monitoring-and-evaluation-expert-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The overall objectives of the mid-term review (MTR) are to offer an overview of the activities carried out in the first phase of the implementation of the two Programmes : &amp;ldquo;Support to the
Community Courts of Eritrea&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Capacity Building for the Public Administration of Eritrea&amp;rdquo; and to provide recommendations for the successful implementation during the remainder of the implementation periods. The MTR shall provide recommendations for the way forward and confirm one of the two scenarios:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Scenario: no major changes in the programme’s orientation and objectives but with suggestions for revisions that may be necessary to adapt the programme to emerging needs.
• Scenario: major changes in the programme’s orientation, objectives and implementation modalities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring and Evaluation Expert (Category II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in social sciences or a related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven communication and reporting skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum of six years&amp;#39; experience of the LFA and PCM&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in Monitoring and Evaluation of donor funded programmes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in programme in the justice sector&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Eritrean context will be an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Eritrean legal context will be an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fluency in English is required. Knowledge of other languages used in Eritrea will be an advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
