<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2014 12:42:50 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in EU Development Policy/External Relations</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-eu-development-policy-external-relations</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2014 10:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-eu-development-policy-external-relations</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The objective of the project is to reinforce the Permanent Representation of the Ministry of Foreign affairs of Latvia in Brussels and the Ministry of Foreign Affairs in Riga for the duration of the Latvian EU Presidency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 9 months&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in EU Development Policy/External Relations )&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent Level of English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good Level of French&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Latvian is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent drafting, communication and organisational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least 10 years’ experience in the area of development policy/ external relations &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent interpersonal skills and ability to work under pressure and with short deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of EU institutions and their working procedures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience in previous EU council presidencies, including in preparing the EU foreign affairs council/ Development segment will be considered as an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent knowledge of and prior experience in the following: post - 2015 agenda for poverty eradication and sustainable development, including development related to gender issues, financing for development, ACP and CODEV Council working group-related matters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;send%20to:%20nicolas_fichers@dai.com&quot;&gt;Nicolas_fichers@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Tertiary Education Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/global-tertiary-education-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2014 10:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/global-tertiary-education-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Australia has established the Regional Advisory Service (RAS) to provide regional organisations, their island members and the DFAT Pacific regional program with timely and efficient access to a small pool of experts to support.  Beyond the use of individual advisers, this integrated approach to structuring their use of such expertise will improve coordination and networking amongst regional organisations, and with national priorities in member states. It will also more readily enable common themes, challenges and synergies to be identified and addressed in a coherent and efficient way. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The RAS will offer the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A vehicle for joint analysis and learning on the major issues and challenges identified through regional organisation governing bodies, policy dialogue and elsewhere. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Access to a pool of experts (or other inputs and activities) that can be mobilised to work with one or across a number of regional organisations, with member states and with the Australian government or jointly in the following areas: strategic planning, governance, monitoring and evaluation, audit and risk management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A help desk function, where technical staff are available remotely throughout the year for up to 20 days per year.  Typical tasks include specific technical advice, reviewing technical documents produced and joint-assessment of technical issues.  This function should only be used where the staff of regional organisations cannot address a problem themselves and would be moderated through the joint focal points in DFAT and the regional organisations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DFAT will manage the RAS Team through the Suva hub as part of an enhanced engagement on Pacific Islands Regionalism.  DFAT will work jointly with regional organisations and member states to determine their priorities for support including through High Level Consultations and regular discussions between focal points. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Tertiary Education Specialist&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Essential Requirement:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Relevant qualification in international development, international relations or related discipline, and over 20 years’ experience in public sector policy, strategy and program management in development contexts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Essential Occupational Experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of and a minimum of 20 years’ experience in international development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive knowledge of and experience with DFAT’s programming and corporate policies and operations; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience working in development in the Pacific region;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of benchmarking, strategic planning and capacity building for establishing and improving tertiary education institutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highly desirable:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experience of working with Pacific regional educational institutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specialist is required for approximately  60 days’ input over two years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this role please email your CV in DFAT format with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;send%20to:%20sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting reference no. 7014046 in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spécialiste en Sciences et Techniques de Gestion Administrative (Cat. II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/specialiste-en-sciences-et-techniques-de-gestion-administrative-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 15:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/specialiste-en-sciences-et-techniques-de-gestion-administrative-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général&lt;/strong&gt; de cette étude est de faire une analyse institutionnelle du MEDD et de proposer des options concrètes de restructuration et de renforcement des capacités en vue de repositionner le
MEDD et ses structures au regard des évolutions du secteur pour mieux assumer ses missions et faire
face aux enjeux internationaux relatifs à la restructuration de la gouvernance de l&amp;#39;environnement et du développement durable en cours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spécialiste en Sciences et Techniques de Gestion Administrative (Cat. II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formation Diplôme&lt;/strong&gt;: master en droit public, option administration publique, ou management des administrations publiques, ou équivalent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience d&amp;#39;au moins six (6) ans dans le domaine de l&amp;#39;administration publique, la gestion et la comptabilité publique.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en audit/conseil d&amp;#39;administration et de gestion dans des pays en développement notamment en Afrique francophone acquise au cours de trois études au moins (à justifier par des fiches de projets en annexe au CV).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience de réorganisation institutionnelle à démontrer dans au moins cinq projets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience comme formateur dans au moins trois projets/études.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pratique du français avérée par la conduite et la rédaction de rapports acquise au cours de cinq études au moins.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20francesca_giordano@dai.com&quot;&gt;Francesca_Giordano@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spécialiste en Environnement et Développement Durable (Cat. II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/specialiste-en-environnement-et-developpement-durable-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 15:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/specialiste-en-environnement-et-developpement-durable-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général&lt;/strong&gt; de cette étude est de faire une analyse institutionnelle du MEDD et de proposer des options concrètes de restructuration et de renforcement des capacités en vue de repositionner le
MEDD et ses structures au regard des évolutions du secteur pour mieux assumer ses missions et faire
face aux enjeux internationaux relatifs à la restructuration de la gouvernance de l&amp;#39;environnement et du développement durable en cours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spécialiste en Environnement et Développement Durable (Cat. II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formation Diplôme&lt;/strong&gt;: master en environnement, agronomie, géographie ou équivalent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience d&amp;#39;au moins six (6) ans dans le domaine de la conception et gestion de politiques environnementales justifiées en nombre d&amp;#39;années.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expériences d&amp;#39;appui/conseil à des administrations publiques dans le domaine de l&amp;#39;environnement dans au moins cinq projets (à justifier par des fiches projets en annexe au CV).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans le secteur de l&amp;#39;environnement dans des pays en développement notamment en Afrique acquise au cours de trois études au moins (à justifier par des fiches de projets en annexe au CV);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en aide budgétaire dans le secteur de l&amp;#39;environnement acquise au cours au moins d&amp;#39;une étude.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une bonne connaissance des conventions internationales dans le domaine de l’environnement est à démontrer par une note de projet spécifique.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pratique du français avérée par la conduite et la rédaction de rapports acquise au cours de cinq études au moins ou de cinq ans en poste en pays francophone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20francesca_giordano@dai.com&quot;&gt;Francesca_Giordano@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spécialiste des Etudes Diagnostiques Institutionnelles et Organisationnelles (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/specialiste-des-etudes-diagnostiques-institutionnelles-et-organisationnelles-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 15:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/specialiste-des-etudes-diagnostiques-institutionnelles-et-organisationnelles-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général&lt;/strong&gt; de cette étude est de faire une analyse institutionnelle du MEDD et de proposer des options concrètes de restructuration et de renforcement des capacités en vue de repositionner le
MEDD et ses structures au regard des évolutions du secteur pour mieux assumer ses missions et faire
face aux enjeux internationaux relatifs à la restructuration de la gouvernance de l&amp;#39;environnement et du développement durable en cours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spécialiste des Etudes Diagnostiques Institutionnelles et Organisationnelles (TL)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formation Diplôme&lt;/strong&gt;: master en ressources humaines, administration et gestion des organisations, audit de gestion et audits systèmes, développement institutionnel, sciences sociales ou équivalent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience d&amp;#39;au moins douze (12) ans dans le domaine des études diagnostiques institutionnelles et organisationnelles;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en audit/conseil organisationnel dans le secteur public dans des pays en développement notamment en Afrique francophone acquise au cours de trois études au moins (à justifier par des fiches de projets en annexe au CV);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en études diagnostiques institutionnelles ou organisationnelles dans le domaine du développement durable ou l&amp;#39;environnement acquis au moins au cours de deux études au moins (à justifier par des fiches projets en annexe au CV);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience comme Chef de mission dans au moins trois études.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience comme formateur dans au moins un projet/étude.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pratique du français avérée par la conduite et la rédaction de rapports acquise au cours de cinq études au moins.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20francesca_giordano@dai.com&quot;&gt;Francesca_Giordano@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Social Services Delivery specifically in Armenia or Eastern Partnership Countries</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/analysis-of-social-services-delivery-1</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 14:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/analysis-of-social-services-delivery-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To contribute to the analytical work of the sector of social services delivery in Armenia, and to contribute to a new EU intervention in this field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objectives:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To produce an analysis of the state of the social services delivery in Armenia (strategy, actors, funding, decision-making, coverage, statistical data, active donors);&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To support the Ministry of Labour and Social Affairs with the strategic policy direction in this sector, and the EU Delegation with the identification of a new EU-funded action in this area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Location visits: Yerevan + missions all over the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Social Services Delivery specifically in Armenia or Eastern Partnership Countries&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant University Degree in the field of social sciences, political science, public administration, economics, or relevant field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent English, oral and written;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in Armenian would be a strong asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years of experience in the field of social services delivery;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific knowledge of the state of the sector in Armenia would be a strong asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the sector in other Eastern Partnership countries would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Social Services Delivery (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/analysis-of-social-services-delivery</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 13:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/analysis-of-social-services-delivery</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To contribute to the analytical work of the sector of social services delivery in Armenia, and to contribute to a new EU intervention in this field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objectives:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To produce an analysis of the state of the social services delivery in Armenia (strategy, actors, funding, decision-making, coverage, statistical data, active donors);&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To support the Ministry of Labour and Social Affairs with the strategic policy direction in this sector, and the EU Delegation with the identification of a new EU-funded action in this area&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Social Services Delivery (TL)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant University Degree in the field of social sciences, political science, public administration, economics, or relevant field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent English, oral and written.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least 10 years of a wide international experience in the field of social services delivery. Previous experience with EU-funded projects is not required. Previous experience in the region is also not required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experience  in  formulating  developmental  programs in  the  field  of  social  services  delivery would be an asset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
