<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 14:12:38 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior African Peace and Security Architecture (APSA) Specialist (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-african-peace-and-security-architecture-apsa-specialist-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 14:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-african-peace-and-security-architecture-apsa-specialist-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identification/Formulation of support to ECOWAS APSA mandate and ECOWAS mechanism to promote and maintain peace, stability and post crisis operations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overall objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This assignment will provide a coherent proposal to ECOWAS and EU for the strengthening of coordination and cooperation in security in West Africa within the framework of African Union&amp;rsquo;s Africa Peace and Security Architecture and the implementation of a project dealing with specific areas as defined in section 1.1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It will give sufficient background information and justifications to enable the ECOWAS and EU to make an informed decision on specific objectives and of the project&amp;rsquo;s implementation modalities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt;
The specific objective of this assignment is to prepare all the necessary elements of an Action Documents to implement a project covering areas A and B.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is required to proceed to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an identification of issues, strategical  orientations and priority intervention areas (Phase I)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a formulation of the project under 11th EDF  (Phase II).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Location&lt;/strong&gt;: Nigeria, Ethiopia, West African country TBD&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;African Peace and Security Architecture (APSA) Specialist + Identification/Formulation Specialist (Logframe and Technical and Administrative provisions) (Category I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master Degree (Academic level) in Defence or Security Affairs, Project and Programme Management, Public Administration, International relations, Political Science, Engineering, Law or relevant, directly related discipline, or equivalent professional qualification.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 10 years of professional experience which must include 6 years professional experience in peace and security sector in developing countries. In-depth knowledge of the African peace and Security Architecture (APSA) of the African Union. Work experience with regards to the African Union or the ECOWAS programmes will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in monitoring the identification/formulation of large development projects in complex political environments (at least 2 significant identifications/formulations).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Related experience in developing countries or with regards to APSA will be an asset. Experience with EU-funded projects/programmes and familiarity with the methodological approach set by the European Commission will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 2 references as programme manager/expert in delivering project logical frameworks, Identification/formulation Action Documents. Experience in EU European Development Fund financial and procurement procedures considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in problem analysis, stakeholders&amp;#39; analysis, assessment and communication of best practices demonstrated by having been team leader in two relevant assignments, particularly in the security field.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full working knowledge of English and at least very good command of French (or vice versa), as well as excellent report writing and communication skills in both languages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert in Metrology - (Category 1) </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-metrology-category-1</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 21:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-metrology-category-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drafting of a framework for the National Quality Infrastructure of Suriname&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objective of this assignment is to draft a framework for Suriname’s NQI and an implementation plan to strengthen the National Quality Infrastructure (NQI) for Suriname. These outcomes should result in facilitation of the competitiveness of Suriname’s products and services on national and international markets. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 161 days&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in Metrology - (Category 1)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Advanced university degree in law with emphasis on Quality control and metrology &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of professional experience in the legal field of quality control and  metrology, preferably working in/with the public sector or an international organization; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of professional experience in development of legal documents, preferably in writing laws related to metrology for countries that have little to no experience in this area and that are comparable to Suriname (size community, social structure);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in carrying out consultative research (using a variety of approaches) and in producing out high quality analytical reports;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in stakeholders analysis and involvement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of national legal frameworks in the area of metrology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of international legislation on metrology; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Surinamese legal system and strengths/weaknesses institutions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication skills and ability to communicate with people at all levels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written command of English &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven access to a network among international practitioners and managing diverse group of experts in a complex environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven leadership skills with international, interdisciplinary teams and within complex institutional and organizational settings;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analytical and computer skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;lina_forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Development of National Quality Infrastructures (TL – Cat.1) </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-development-of-national-quality-infrastructures-tl-cat1</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 21:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-development-of-national-quality-infrastructures-tl-cat1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drafting of a framework for the National Quality Infrastructure of Suriname&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objective of this assignment is to draft a framework for Suriname’s NQI and an implementation plan to strengthen the National Quality Infrastructure (NQI) for Suriname. These outcomes should result in facilitation of the competitiveness of Suriname’s products and services on national and international markets. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 161 days&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 1 – Senior Expert in Development of National Quality Infrastructures (TL – Cat.1)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Advanced university degree (preferably at Master’s level) in Quality Management Systems or related fields such as Engineering and Business or Public Administration, Economics, Private Sector Development&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of professional experience with the development of national quality infrastructures, institutionalizing quality management systems, quality control and quality assurance (standardisation, conformity assessment, accreditation, meteorology, market surveillance, policy, regulations) according to international standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in capacity building, and knowledge transfer in quality related topics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 5 years (within the 12 years ) of the professional experience gained in managing projects involving multiple technical aspects: quality certifications, regulatory reforms, setup standards and parameters, operation and procedures, conformity assessment, testing, standardisation, accreditation, technical regulations, market control&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication skills and ability to communicate with people at all levels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written command of English &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong change management and institution development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven access to a network among international practitioners and managing diverse group of experts in a complex environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven leadership skills with international, interdisciplinary teams and within complex institutional and organizational settings;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong expert leadership and team building capacities are advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analytical and computer skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;lina_forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 3: International Trade Expert (Category 1) </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-3-international-trade-expert-category-1</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 21:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-3-international-trade-expert-category-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enhancing Trade and Business Opportunities in Mozambique in the Framework of the SADC EPA Implementation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 3: International Trade Expert (Category 1)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This expert will focus mainly on the trade facilitation aspects i.e. completing the terms of reference for the category C of the WTO Trade Facilitation Agreement provisions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following eligibility requirements should be met:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant professional qualifications at least Masters Degree or, in its absence equivalent professional experience in economics, international trade, business administration or other relevant topic &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years international expertise in trade issues in developing countries particularly with regard to trade facilitation, at least 4 of those preferably in Southern Africa&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the requested areas is preferred, this refers specifically to the following areas:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creation of Enquiry Points for Trade Facilitation (provision 1.3)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Definition of Structures and Procedures for Consultations between Border Agencies in the Scope of Trade Facilitation (provision 2.2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advance Rulings (provision 3)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review of the Fees and Charges Imposed on the Import and Export of Goods, and Assessment of their Compliance with Provisions 6.1 and 6.2 of the Agreement on Trade Facilitation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expedited Shipments (provision 7.8)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Definition of Options and Institutional Change Plan for Border Agency Cooperation (provision 8)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Single Window (provision 10.4)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pre-shipment Inspection (provision 10.5)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience from similar assignments &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good communicator, excellent drafting and planning skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent English writing skills &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 2: Policy Analyst (Category 2)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-policy-analyst-category-2</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 20:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-policy-analyst-category-2</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enhancing Trade and Business Opportunities in Mozambique in the Framework of the SADC EPA Implementation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mozambique is part of the six Southern African Development Community (SADC) countries that signed an Economic Partnership Agreement (EPA) with the European Union on 10 June 2016. The SADC EPA Group comprises Botswana, Lesotho, Mozambique, Namibia, South Africa and Swaziland.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The purpose of the present assignment is to define a national EPA Implementation Plan that includes relevant actions/measures to be implemented to facilitate the EPA and to facilitate stakeholders to benefit from the EPA. Furthermore, the consultants shall to also identify the most relevant areas where potential technical assistance is required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2: Policy Analyst (Category 2)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant professional qualifications in economics, business administration or other relevant topic, or in its absence, equivalent professional experience &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of in-depth expertise in business, international trade agreements and investment in Southern Africa (business development services, international trade agreements, policy formulation and capacity building)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated knowledge of international trade agreements is required; in addition knowledge of the Economic Partnership Agreement is highly preferred in SADC, or alternatively other region&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven statistical analysis, experience and capacity &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Mozambican legal and regulatory framework would be an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to collect, analyse and synthesize economic data to produce evidence based recommendations to public and private institutions &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effective communication and reporting skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Portuguese would be highly appreciated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Business, Trade and Investment (TL) </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-business-trade-and-investment-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 20:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-business-trade-and-investment-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enhancing Trade and Business Opportunities in Mozambique in the Framework of the SADC EPA Implementation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mozambique is part of the six Southern African Development Community (SADC) countries that signed an Economic Partnership Agreement (EPA) with the European Union on 10 June 2016. The SADC EPA Group comprises Botswana, Lesotho, Mozambique, Namibia, South Africa and Swaziland.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The purpose of the present assignment is to define a national EPA Implementation Plan that includes relevant actions/measures to be implemented to facilitate the EPA and to facilitate stakeholders to benefit from the EPA. Furthermore, the consultants shall to also identify the most relevant areas where potential technical assistance is required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Business, Trade and Investment (TL) (Category 1)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Relevant professional qualifications&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least Master’s Degree or, in its absence equivalent professional experience in economics, international trade, business administration or other relevant topic &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years international expertise in business, trade and investment in developing countries (trade agreements, trade policy, enterprise competitiveness policies, strategies and initiatives). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated knowledge and competency in private sector development such as promoting trade and sustainable economic development, building institutional capacity of business support organizations, promoting business development, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated knowledge of international trade agreements is required; in addition knowledge of the Economic Partnership Agreement is highly preferred in SADC, or alternatively other region&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable research and analytical skills &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience from similar assignments &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good communicator, experienced leader and moderator &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent English writing skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Portuguese would be highly appreciated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junior Expert in Sustainable Energy </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-expert-in-sustainable-energy</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2017 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-expert-in-sustainable-energy</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation of the programme &amp;lsquo;Support to the introduction of Sustainable Development Policies - Rationale use of Natural Resources in the Energy-Environment Sectors in Turkmenistan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overall objective&lt;/strong&gt;: to improve natural resources management and contribute to the sustainable development of Turkmenistan, in line with its long-term economic growth objectives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective&lt;/strong&gt;: to set-up the first steps necessary to understand the overall rationale of sustainable development policies and to support the development and the implementation of policy, regulatory, and institutional frameworks in the energy and environment sectors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Junior Expert in Sustainable Energy&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is expected that an expert of category Junior (Category III) will be appointed to support the Senior Expert with this assignment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Junior Expert&lt;/strong&gt; must possess the following qualifications and skills: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education to at least Master Degree level or alternatively professional experience of minimum 5 years relevant to the energy field; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of professional experience relevant to the legislative and/or institutional and/or policy development of sustainable energy; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written skills in the following language(s): Turkmen and/or Russian, English; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Local expertise i.e. experience in Turkmenistan and/or Central Asia; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with evaluation methods and techniques in general is an advantage. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Environment/Energy (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-environment-energy-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2017 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-environment-energy-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation of the programme &amp;lsquo;Support to the introduction of Sustainable Development Policies - Rationale use of Natural Resources in the Energy-Environment Sectors in Turkmenistan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overall objective&lt;/strong&gt;: to improve natural resources management and contribute to the sustainable development of Turkmenistan, in line with its long-term economic growth objectives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective&lt;/strong&gt;: to set-up the first steps necessary to understand the overall rationale of sustainable development policies and to support the development and the implementation of policy, regulatory, and institutional frameworks in the energy and environment sectors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Environment/Energy (TL)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; must possess the following qualifications and skills: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education to at least Master Degree level, or alternatively relevant professional experience of a minimum 14 years; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of relevant professional experience relevant to the sustainable management and protection of natural resources; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written skills in the following language(s): English. * Working knowledge of Russian is preferred. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, the &lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert&lt;/strong&gt; will be expected to possess expertise in: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluation methods and techniques in general and, if possible, of evaluation in the field of external relations and development cooperation; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of professional experience gained in the environment/energy sector. Knowledge of one or more of the following areas: Energy policy; legislative and institutional development of sustainable energy/renewable sources; technical assistance/international cooperation projects in the area of energy efficiency; demand-side management of energy efficiency. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous relevant experience in Turkmenistan and/or Central Asia is an advantage. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experto en Seguridad</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-en-seguridad</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 16:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-en-seguridad</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluacion Intermedia y Final del 2 proyectos: Prevencion y control del crimen organizado y del trafico de drogas (Nicaragua) y SECOPA (Panama)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;El objeto de la presente misión es la realización de las evaluaciones intermedia y final de los proyectos SECOPA y Crimen Organizado.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;En el caso de la evaluación intermedia, el principal objetivo será la generación de aprendizajes que retroalimenten la gestión del proyecto.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;En el caso de la evaluación final, el principal objetivo será la generación de lecciones de desarrollo, que alimenten futuras acciones en el sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experto en Seguridad&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Profesional con título universitario con nivel mínimo de maestría en ciencias sociales, y/o derecho y/o criminología, o experiencia equivalente (por ejemplo ex funcionario de policía, judicial o de servicios sociales – por lo menos 06 años de carrera) en seguridad pública/seguridad ciudadana, con conocimiento de temas cuales: prevención primaria-segundaria-terciaria, y/o temas carcelarios y de rehabilitación / reinserción de privados de libertad menores y adultos, y/o policía comunitaria, y/o violencia de género, y similar. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experto en el sector de seguridad pública con conocimiento de la realidad y proyectos de seguridad pública en Centroamérica; conocimiento de la realidad de Nicaragua será una ventaja así como poder demostrar conocimiento de políticas relacionadas implementadas en la UE. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contar con un mínimo de 06 años de experiencia relevante. Sería deseable que de dicha experiencia haya sido en América Latina y/o en Centro América, preferiblemente en Nicaragua o Panamá. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia especifica en América Central en prevención primaria-segundaria-terciaria, temas carcelarios y de rehabilitación / reinserción de privados de libertad menores y adultos, policía comunitaria, y reformas de sectores de seguridad (SSR). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conocimiento de políticas y estrategias de SSR. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Será una ventaja tener experiencia previa del que hacer en tema de seguridad ciudadana en Centro América de UNODC y/o BID y/o AECID. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excelente dominio del español e inglés, excelente capacidad de redacción de informes. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jefe de equipo: Experto en Evaluación</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/jefe-de-equipo-experto-en-evaluacion</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/jefe-de-equipo-experto-en-evaluacion</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluacion Intermedia y Final del 2 proyectos: Prevencion y control del crimen organizado y del trafico de drogas (Nicaragua) y SECOPA (Panama)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;El objeto de la presente misión es la realización de las evaluaciones intermedia y final de los proyectos SECOPA y Crimen Organizado.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;En el caso de la evaluación intermedia, el principal objetivo será la generación de aprendizajes que retroalimenten la gestión del proyecto.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;En el caso de la evaluación final, el principal objetivo será la generación de lecciones de desarrollo, que alimenten futuras acciones en el sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jefe de equipo: Experto en Evaluación&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Profesional con título universitario con nivel mínimo de maestría en ciencias sociales, y/o derecho, y/o criminología, y/o cooperación al desarrollo o tema relacionado. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mínimo 12 años de experiencia relativa a ejecución, monitoreo y evaluación de programas y proyectos. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia relevante en ejecución, monitoreo y evaluación de programas y proyectos (mínimo 3 evaluaciones intermedias o finales) de cooperación internacional en particular financiados por la Unión Europea. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conocimiento de la metodología de trabajo de UNODC y/o BID y/o AECID. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experto comprobado (experiencia o títulos académicos) en la metodología de marco lógico e indicadores, así como análisis de impacto. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Será una ventaja haber realizado con anterioridad por lo menos una evaluación o monitoreo de proyectos de seguridad pública. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Será una ventaja haber realizado con anterioridad por lo menos una evaluación o monitoreo de proyectos de seguridad pública en la región latinoamericana. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Será una ventaja haber realizado con anterioridad por lo menos una evaluación o monitoreo de programas de UNODC y/o BID y/o AECID. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Será una ventaja el conocimiento de las políticas de visibilidad de la UE y de su implementación. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Será una ventaja tener el conocimiento del tema género aplicado a proyectos de seguridad pública. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excelente dominio &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Environment Infrastructure Expert (cat. II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/environment-infrastructure-expert-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 21:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/environment-infrastructure-expert-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Self-evaluation of IPA I Environment Infrastructure Projects&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the evaluation is to provide the EUD to BiH with sufficient information to make an informed judgment about the past performance of the selected projects (their efficiency, effectiveness and impact), to document lessons learned and to provide practical recommendations for follow-up action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To assess in particular the efficiency, effectiveness and impact of project implementation, indicating clearly to what extent the results, purposes and overall objectives of the selected projects were achieved.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To provide comparative assessment of efficiency, effectiveness and impact of EUD interventions based on the selected projects, including strengthens and weaknesses of the different implementation methods.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To identify and document lessons learned, focusing on the design, implementation and management of the selected projects for improving of programming and identification of possible future actions under IPA II.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To provide recommendations for practical follow-up action, with the emphasis on actions related to sustainability of project benefits.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation will determine to what extent the projects have collectively succeeded in meeting the objectives of the EU as set out in the relevant country strategy paper and to what extent the projects have increased the Government’s ability to meet its objectives within the agreed framework of cooperation with the EU. It is therefore important that the review will focus not only on the individual projects being evaluated, but also on their overall achievements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Environment Infrastructure Expert (cat. II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As a minimum Master Degree in Engineering disciplines relevant to the fields of this contract, or, in its absence, equivalent professional experience of at least 4 years above the general professional experience duration fixed below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;General profession experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 6 years of general professional experience in the environment sector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As a minimum, this expert must have participated in 3 environment infrastructure programmes/projects funded by EU and/or other donors/IFIs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English, both spoken and written;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the local language (B/H/S) will be considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Evaluation Expert (cat. I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-evaluation-expert-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 21:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-evaluation-expert-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Self-evaluation of IPA I Environment Infrastructure Projects&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the evaluation is to provide the EUD to BiH with sufficient information to make an informed judgment about the past performance of the selected projects (their efficiency, effectiveness and impact), to document lessons learned and to provide practical recommendations for follow-up action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To assess in particular the efficiency, effectiveness and impact of project implementation, indicating clearly to what extent the results, purposes and overall objectives of the selected projects were achieved.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To provide comparative assessment of efficiency, effectiveness and impact of EUD interventions based on the selected projects, including strengthens and weaknesses of the different implementation methods.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To identify and document lessons learned, focusing on the design, implementation and management of the selected projects for improving of programming and identification of possible future actions under IPA II.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To provide recommendations for practical follow-up action, with the emphasis on actions related to sustainability of project benefits.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation will determine to what extent the projects have collectively succeeded in meeting the objectives of the EU as set out in the relevant country strategy paper and to what extent the projects have increased the Government’s ability to meet its objectives within the agreed framework of cooperation with the EU. It is therefore important that the review will focus not only on the individual projects being evaluated, but also on their overall achievements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation Expert (cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As a minimum Master Degree in a discipline relevant to the fields of this assignment or, in its absence, equivalent professional experience of at least 4 years above the general professional experience duration fixed below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 12 years of general professional experience in working with EU and/or donors/IFIs funded projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As a minimum, this expert must have participated in the position of project evaluator and/or project monitor in three evaluations and/or monitoring of projects completed in the past five years in the environment sector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English, both spoken and written;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the local language (B/H/S) will be considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Un (e) expert (e) spécialiste BSG (cat. II) </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/un-e-expert-e-specialiste-bsg-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 10:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/un-e-expert-e-specialiste-bsg-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mission d&amp;#39;appui au Ministere de la Femme, la Famille et l Enfance, au conseil des pairs et ses partenaires&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectifs généraux&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evaluer et renforcer les capacités du Ministère de la Femme, de la Famille et de l’Enfance et de ses partenaires en intégration de l’approche genre.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif(s) particulier(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les objectifs particuliers sont :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Réaliser le diagnostic organisationnel et fonctionnel de la direction générale des affaires de la femme et la famille a l’échelle nationale et régionale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appuyer les membres du conseil des pairs (décret 2016/626 - du 25 mai 2016) sur la thématique ≪ Genre ≫&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appuyer les cadres de la direction générale des affaires de la femme et la famille au niveau national et régional par des formations générales et spécifiques.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Former les chefs du programme du MFFE et des autres partenaires étatiques sur la thématique ≪ Budgétisation sensible au genre≫.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Un (e) expert (e) spécialiste BSG (cat. II)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire de niveau Master minimum en
économie générale, économie publique, finances publiques,
fiscalité, droit fiscal, droit public, administration publique ou
science politique, ou équivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;En l’absence de ce diplôme, une expérience professionnelle de
3 ans dans le domaine en plus de 6 ans demandes ci-dessous
est indispensable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt; d’au moins 6 ans dans
le domaine du lot couvert par cette demande de prestation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience spécifique&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Critères considérées comme indispensables&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins une expérience pertinente en analyse genre
du budget/budgétisation sensible au genre.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins trois expériences dans la formation/sensibilisation et la préparation des ateliers ou séminaires.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Critères considérées comme atouts&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance des mécanismes institutionnels BSG.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Une expérience en Tunisie ou voisinage du sud&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parfaite connaissance de la langue française.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;La connaissance de l’arabe est considérée comme un atout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;corinamaria_campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Un (e) expert (e) formateur (frice) en gestion de projet (cat. III)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/un-fe-expert-fe-formateur-frice-en-gestion-de-projet-cat-iii</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2017 12:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/un-fe-expert-fe-formateur-frice-en-gestion-de-projet-cat-iii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mission d&amp;#39;appui au Ministere de la Femme, la Famille et l Enfance, au conseil des pairs et ses partenaires&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectifs généraux&lt;/strong&gt;
Evaluer et renforcer les capacités du Ministère de la Femme, de la Famille et de l’Enfance et de ses partenaires en intégration de l’approche genre.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif(s) particulier(s)&lt;/strong&gt;
Les objectifs particuliers sont :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Réaliser le diagnostic organisationnel et fonctionnel de la direction générale des affaires de la femme et la famille a l’échelle nationale et régionale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appuyer les membres du conseil des pairs (décret 2016/626 - du 25 mai 2016) sur la thématique ≪ Genre ≫&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appuyer les cadres de la direction générale des affaires de la femme et la famille au niveau national et régional par des formations générales et spécifiques.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Former les chefs du programme du MFFE et des autres partenaires étatiques sur la thématique ≪ Budgétisation sensible au genre≫.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diplôme universitaire&lt;/strong&gt; équivalent à un master dans des domaines suivants : Gestion, gestion des entreprises, économie, sociologie ou équivalent.
En l’absence de ce diplôme, une expérience professionnelle de 3 ans dans le domaine en plus de 3 ans demandes ci-dessous est indispensable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle&lt;/strong&gt; générale d’au moins 3 ans dans
le domaine du lot couvert par cette demande de prestation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; :
Critères considérées comme indispensables&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 3 expériences de formation, facilitation, conduite d’atelier, session de formation et préparation de module de formation et ce dans les thèmes suivants :&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Les techniques de rédaction des requetés de financement et des fiches projet&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;La GAR et l’approche basée sur les droits humains&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Les techniques de négociation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;La gestion et le suivi des projets : cycle de projet, cadre logique&amp;hellip;etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;La gestion des conflits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Critères considérées comme atouts&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience en Tunisie ou voisinage du sud est considéré comme un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parfaite connaissance de la langue française et de l’arabe.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;corinamaria_campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Un (e) Expert(e) Chef de Mission en Institutionnalisation du Genre et Diagnostic (Cat. I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/un-e-experte-chef-de-mission-en-institutionnalisation-du-genre-et-diagnostic-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2017 12:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/un-e-experte-chef-de-mission-en-institutionnalisation-du-genre-et-diagnostic-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mission d&amp;#39;appui au Ministere de la Femme, la Famille et l Enfance, au conseil des pairs et ses partenaires&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectifs généraux&lt;/strong&gt;
Evaluer et renforcer les capacités du Ministère de la Femme, de la Famille et de l’Enfance et de ses partenaires en intégration de l’approche genre.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif(s) particulier(s)&lt;/strong&gt;
Les objectifs particuliers sont :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Réaliser le diagnostic organisationnel et fonctionnel de la direction générale des affaires de la femme et la famille a l’échelle nationale et régionale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appuyer les membres du conseil des pairs (décret 2016/626 - du 25 mai 2016) sur la thématique ≪ Genre ≫&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appuyer les cadres de la direction générale des affaires de la femme et la famille au niveau national et régional par des formations générales et spécifiques.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Former les chefs du programme du MFFE et des autres partenaires étatiques sur la thématique ≪ Budgétisation sensible au genre≫.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;corinamaria_campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert on Social Cash Transfers (cat II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-social-cash-transfers-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2017 09:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-social-cash-transfers-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;lsquo;Evaluate the Community Score Card methodology and success in 24 communities in Swaziland, to empower grassroot citizen to demand quality basic service&amp;rsquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the assignment is: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;to assess the relevance, efficiency, effectiveness, impact and sustainability of the project &amp;ldquo;Interact with Communities and Health Facilities to implement Community Score Card&amp;rdquo; implemented by World Vision-Swaziland, with technical assistance and capacity development specifically on the CSC methodology, delivered by COSPE-Italy;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;to verify that the activities and results of the project are in line with those outlined in the Financing Agreement, and project documents annexed to the respective contracts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert on Social Cash Transfers (cat II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least 6 years’ experience in a social sector, with some of it related to poverty reduction and/or social transfers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a basic degree in a social sector and a Master Degree in a relevant sector, such as social protection, Social Science, economics, poverty related studies, social work, or related relevant studies. In absence of required diploma, equivalent professional experience with duration above 8 years must be demonstrated in the CV.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;proven experience with poverty reduction programmes, and/or social transfer programmes, social welfare problematics, and/or targeting mechanisms for vulnerable groups, benefit delivery mechanisms, monitoring and database maintenance for social programmes,…&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;knowledgeable about conditionalities in welfare programmes, co-responsibilities of beneficiaries, and how to monitor these.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;proven experience with social cash transfer schemes in developing countries would be an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;proven experience in working with orphans and vulnerable children (OVC) in developing countries would be an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience in monitoring and/or evaluation of development projects, preferable in a developing country setting, would be an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience with EU methodology and regulations, EU monitoring and reporting practices would be an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;computer literacy; excellent analytical, conceptual, communication and reporting skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;good teamwork ability and culturally sensitive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fluent in written and spoken English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;lina_forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Specialist in linking communities to Primary Health Care (cat II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/specialist-in-linking-communities-to-primary-health-care-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2017 08:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/specialist-in-linking-communities-to-primary-health-care-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluate the Community Score Card methodology and success in 24 communities in Swaziland, to empower grassroot citizen to demand quality basic service&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the assignment is: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;to assess the relevance, efficiency, effectiveness, impact and sustainability of the project &amp;ldquo;Interact with Communities and Health Facilities to implement Community Score Card&amp;rdquo; implemented by World Vision-Swaziland, with technical assistance and capacity development specifically on the CSC methodology, delivered by COSPE-Italy;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;to verify that the activities and results of the project are in line with those outlined in the Financing Agreement, and project documents annexed to the respective contracts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specialist in linking communities to Primary Health Care (cat II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years’ experience in the health sector, preferable in basic health services, preferably in developing countries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a basic degree in the health sector and a Master Degree in a relevant sector. In absence of required diploma, equivalent professional experience with duration above 8 years must be demonstrated in the CV.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with health systems in an African setting. Knowledgeable in Primary Health Care strengthening in a development setting (for example: the health pyramid, referral systems, basic health care packages, essential drugs management, hygiene and infection control in health facilities, retention of health care workers, quality of PHC).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledgeable, through experience, of barriers to access to basic services, for disadvantaged communities, due to poverty, distance, cultural obstacles, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in monitoring and/or evaluation of health projects, preferable in a developing country setting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Having knowledge of EU regulations and procedures in external development actions would be an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer literacy; excellent analytical, conceptual, communication and reporting skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good teamwork ability and culturally sensitive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in written and spoken English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;lina_forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community mobilisation specialist; project evaluation specialist (team leader; cat I</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/community-mobilisation-specialist-project-evaluation-specialist-team-leader-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2017 08:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/community-mobilisation-specialist-project-evaluation-specialist-team-leader-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluate the Community Score Card methodology and success in 24 communities in Swaziland, to empower grassroot citizen to demand quality basic service&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the assignment is: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;to assess the relevance, efficiency, effectiveness, impact and sustainability of the project &amp;ldquo;Interact with Communities and Health Facilities to implement Community Score Card&amp;rdquo; implemented by World Vision-Swaziland, with technical assistance and capacity development specifically on the CSC methodology, delivered by COSPE-Italy;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;to verify that the activities and results of the project are in line with those outlined in the Financing Agreement, and project documents annexed to the respective contracts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community mobilisation specialist; project evaluation specialist (team leader; cat I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years&amp;#39; experience in the community mobilization and/or grass-root empowerment and/or participatory governance. The expert must have experience in project evaluation, preferably in developing countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a basic degree in the social sector, or governance and development or economics and a Master Degree in a relevant sector. In absence of required diploma, equivalent professional experience with duration above 14 years must be demonstrated in the CV.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in monitoring and evaluation of development projects, preferably in developing countries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with community mobilization, or participatory approaches, or grass-root empowerment, or linking rural populations with governance and service monitoring, preferably in developing countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with community engagement techniques, such as Focus Group Discussions, Key Informant Interviews, and/or working with Local Authorities in rural settings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Project Cycle Management: from implementation to M&amp;E; the use of Logical Frameworks, the interpretation of indicators to follow progress, the methodology of output/outcome/impact monitoring&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with EU procedures in external actions (PRAG, finance and contracts issues, project cycle, monitoring EU projects preferably having knowledge the EU Results Oriented Monitoring methodology - ROM).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer literacy; excellent analytical, conceptual, communication and reporting skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good teamwork ability and culturally sensitive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in written and spoken English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;lina_forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SME Development Specialist (Cat III)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/sme-development-specialist-cat-iii</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2017 17:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/sme-development-specialist-cat-iii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Evaluation of IPA 2011 Grant Support for Local Economic Development&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;: To provide the Delegation of the European Union with systematic and timely evaluation of its programme to demonstrate accountability and to promote lesson learning to improve policy and practice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective&lt;/strong&gt;: The specific objective of the evaluation is to identify key lessons and to produce recommendations to improve current and inform of future choices on IPA II support to Bosnia and Herzegovina in the field of SME competitiveness and innovation at local level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SME Development Specialist (Cat III)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education at least Master Degree in any field related to economic sciences, or in its absence, at least 3 years of relevant experience in the private sector development are required above the general professional experience required below. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of relevant experience in the private sector development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As a minimum, this expert must have participated in one international aid project in the area of SME or local economy development completed in the past five years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The expert should preferably demonstrate previous relevant expertise in the country/region.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English, both spoken and written.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;lina_forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation Expert (Cat.II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/evaluation-expert-catii</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2017 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/evaluation-expert-catii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Evaluation of IPA 2011 Grant Support for Local Economic Development&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;: To provide the Delegation of the European Union with systematic and timely evaluation of its programme to demonstrate accountability and to promote lesson learning to improve policy and practice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective&lt;/strong&gt;: The specific objective of the evaluation is to identify key lessons and to produce recommendations to improve current and inform of future choices on IPA II support to Bosnia and Herzegovina in the field of SME competitiveness and innovation at local level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation Expert (Cat II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education at least Masters Degree Academic level, or in its absence, at least 6 years of relevant experience in the private sector development are required above the general professional experience required below. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of relevant experience in the private sector development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As a minimum, this expert must have participated in two reviews, and/or assessments, and/or monitoring, and/or evaluations of projects completed in the past five years. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of relevant experience in EU SME policy, preferably gained in implementation of the EU funded projects. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The expert should preferably demonstrate previous relevant expertise in the country/region.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English, both spoken and written.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;lina_forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
