<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2014 11:57:20 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Twinning Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-twinning-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2014 11:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-twinning-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The general objective of this contract is to support the Israeli Ministry of Economy and the European Commission in the preparation of an institutional Twinning project within the framework of the EU-Israel Action Plan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective of this contract is to support the Israeli Ministry of Economy in drafting a clear and concise Twinning Fiche necessary for launching an institutional Twinning. The Twinning Fiche shall be circulated simultaneously to the 28 EU Member States in an invitation to submit proposals for its joint implementation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Senior Twinning Expert&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Relevant University degree;
• Working experience in the public service or assimilated body;
• Fluent English, oral and written&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;General professional experience&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least 10 years working experience in public administration&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 5 years of direct experience in Twinning;
• Proven familiarity with Twinning procedures;
• Experience of working in third countries, ideally under ENPI.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert on Market Surveillance Systems</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-on-market-surveillance-systems</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2014 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-on-market-surveillance-systems</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;general objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this contract is to support the Israeli Ministry of Economy and the European Commission in the preparation of an institutional Twinning project within the framework of the EU-Israel Action Plan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this contract is to support the Israeli Ministry of Economy in drafting a clear and concise Twinning Fiche necessary for launching an institutional Twinning. The Twinning Fiche shall be circulated simultaneously to the 28 EU Member States in an invitation to submit proposals for its joint implementation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert on Market Surveillance Systems&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in field relevant to this project (e.g. Law, Economics, Engineering, Chemistry, etc.);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years working experience in market surveillance in the field of technical products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practical knowledge of European Union market surveillance systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good understanding of EU technical legislation, namely the New and Global Approach Directives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing large-scale cooperation projects in the sector relevant to this project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent English, oral and written&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least 10 years’ experience in the area relevant to the assignment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experience in leading missions for project identification and/or drafting project design documents would be an asset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Sustainable Consumption and Production (specialised in Southeast Asia) </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-sustainable-consumption-and-production-specialised-in-southeast-asia</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2014 15:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-sustainable-consumption-and-production-specialised-in-southeast-asia</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The objective of the final evaluation is to assess the design, implementation and results of &amp;ldquo;the Project&amp;rdquo; and to draw lessons of the experience of projects implementation and give recommendations for the way forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Sustainable Consumption and Production (specialised in Southeast Asia)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced university degree (minimum Master) or equivalent qualification in environmental sciences/policy, international economics or social sciences or equivalent professional experience of 15 years if candidate does not possess post graduate degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of oral and written English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years of experience in the sector(s) of environment and economics (environmental policy and regulatory frameworks, SME development, clean air, pollution, waste management).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years of working experience in Southeast Asia in the area of development cooperation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 assignments in the evaluation of programmes, preferably in the area of environment and SME development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicolas_fichers@dai.com&quot;&gt;Nicolas_fichers@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deputy Team Leader, </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/deputy-team-leader-</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2014 17:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/deputy-team-leader-</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Innovation for Indonesia’s School Children (INOVASI)&lt;/strong&gt; will provide necessary resources to help the Government of Indonesia (GoI) achieve a breakthrough in improving student learning by generating evidence of tailored solutions to locally prevailing challenges and promoting the adaptation and replication of these tested strategies to influence both policy and practice.  The impact of INOVASI will be accelerated progress towards improving learning outcomes for Indonesian students.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;INOVASI is designed to be transformational by investigating what works and what doesn’t work to get teachers teaching better and students learning more, and why, in order to leverage Indonesia’s substantial spend in education.  It is not designed to be a program for directly delivering educational services.  It will be transformational by:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding local challenges and opportunities to improving student learning outcomes by bringing together key government and non-government stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generating evidence of what works and what does not work to improve student learning in Indonesian classrooms by trialing and testing local solutions (tested strategies).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sharing this evidence with stakeholders in target and non-target districts to promote adaptation and replication of tested strategies in target and non-target districts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;INOVASI will work closely with GoI (district, provincial and national) to develop and implement action-oriented research.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deputy Team Leader, Innovation for Indonesia’s School Children (INOVASI)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Role&lt;/strong&gt;: The Deputy Team Leader will oversee all operational functions of the program – ensuring compliance with all DFAT and DAI rules and regulations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responsibilities include (but are not limited to):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All operations including but not limited to administration, logistics, procurement, budgeting, financial, and property. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensuring that program implementation is in accordance with DFAT regulations and procedures and the specifications determined in the project Service Order. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assuring that the most reasonable, fair, expeditious and appropriate procurement choices were made pursuant to DAI’s Procurement Guide.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supervision of DAI’s day‐to‐day field presence in the areas of operations (including the project&amp;rsquo;s facilities such as office space, equipment and project vehicles), administration, logistics, procurement, budgeting and financial accounting and act as the Team Leader when he/she is absent from the program.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supervision of the daily financial operations of the contract, which include cash flow management, time sheet recording, reporting to DAI on the financial aspects of the project, and daily monitoring of obligations, budgets, and expenditures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensuring continuous liquidity for the project, including handling all human resource issues and investigating and identifying new ways of achieving project efficiencies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EDUCATION&lt;/strong&gt;
BA in Political Science, International Development, or related field preferred&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WORK EXPERIENCE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant work experience, including experience with a Contractor or international NGO managing an office or program. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of experience working on donor‐funded projects in a related role and with some demonstrated supervisory experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in developing countries is required, preferably in the Asia-Pacific region. Experience of working in Indonesia will be an advantage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SKILLS &amp;amp; KNOWLEDGE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience and knowledge in establishing systems and overseeing program start‐up under limited time constraints. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Human resources and adviser management, especially in recruitment; logistics and procurement; capacity building and training; financial management, budgeting and reporting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written English skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Bahasa Indonesian an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The program is planned as an eight-year initiative, to be implemented in two four-year phases.  This proposal concerns the first four-year project phase.
The estimated start date would be January 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for this nominated role please email your CV with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements. Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;sarah_owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting &lt;strong&gt;DFAT/AOP/008&lt;/strong&gt; in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Environment and Biology Expert (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/opportunities/senior-environment-and-biology-expert-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 20:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/opportunities/senior-environment-and-biology-expert-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Expert 2 is expected to contribute the implementation of all of the related modules and the preparation of both training materials and Training Evaluation Report in the context of related chapter/s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in Biology, Ecology, Chemistry or other Natural Sciences related to assignment. In the absence of the degree required, at least 17 years of professional experience in the related areas is requested.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good command of both written and spoken English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General professional experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in the sector(s) related to the Lot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience in technical and/or scientific fields required for the implementation of the Water Framework Directive and/or Habitat Directive and/or other related Directives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 river basin management plans experience in terms of setting of environmental objectives and/or setting, design and upgrade of biological monitoring programme and/or execution and assessment of biological monitoring.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in development of measures for water pollution reduction and/or improving ecological status, and/or river basin characterisation/analysis will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in projects related to Integrated Water Resources Management will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
