<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 12:37:44 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for Junior Experts with Experience in Evaluation, Monitoring or Academic Research</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/call-for-junior-experts-com-2016</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 11:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/call-for-junior-experts-com-2016</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Call for Junior Experts, EC COM 2016&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Strategic evaluations analyse EU strategies from conception to implementation, assessing the results of EU funded activities. These evaluations are complex, covering several programmes and instruments over a significant period of time. They are conducted at several levels: country, region or sector; they can also assess the procedures and instruments EuropeAid uses to provide aid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Junior Experts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of post-graduate working experience in evaluation, monitoring or academic research&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of data processing and statistics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience with EU procedures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in EU Evaluations will be an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will be seeking experts with a variety of language skills, but *&lt;em&gt;French *&lt;/em&gt; is always an asset. All experts must be fluent in English.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are particularly interested in hearing from &lt;strong&gt;experts based in Brussels&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category II Expert in Media with Experience in South European Neighbourhood Policy</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-expert-in-media-with-experience-in-south-european-neighbourhood-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-expert-in-media-with-experience-in-south-european-neighbourhood-policy</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation of &amp;lsquo;MedMedia&amp;rsquo; Regional Project
**
**Overall Objective&lt;/strong&gt;
The overall objective of the project is to reinforce the role of media as vector for democratisation and contribute to the development of a more public service-orientated media landscape in the Southern Mediterranean as well as to contribute to the creation and development of a public sphere in the region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Purpose&lt;/strong&gt;
The specific objectives of the project have been reformulated by the inception report and approved by the Commission as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To build public trust by strengthening the media’s role as an independent watchdog and a forum for democratic debate;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To forge closer links between media practitioners across the region, thereby facilitating an ongoing exchange of experience and information;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To develop capacities in the media sector so that key players can rise to new professional challenges and respond to audience needs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To enrich and expand the informational resources available to the institutions and individuals responsible for implementing media reforms in the Southern Mediterranean Region.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One specific objective has been added by the Inception Report to give &amp;lsquo;due prominence to the project’s engagement on a governmental level and its commitment to giving new momentum to reform processes&amp;rsquo;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To strengthen partnerships with media policy makers at ministerial and parliamentary level and with key stakeholders lobbying for media reforms.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category II Expert in Media with Experience in South European Neighbourhood Policy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;University degree. In absence of the University degree, the relevant professional experience will be of a minimum 10 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As such, the experts must demonstrate the following experience: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive and relevant experience (minimum 6 years) in the field of international cooperation, preferably in geographical area of the South European Neighbourhood policy with field experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 4 years of relevant experience in the area of media development, freedom of expression. At least one of the experts should have experience in support for social dialogue, civil society or good governance and democratisation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full working knowledge of English and French and excellent report writing skills. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven Experience (min.2 years) in mid-term and final evaluation preferably of media development projects&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Neighbourhood South region&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good understanding of EU programmes and policies in the field of media development&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full knowledge of the principles and working methods of project cycle management and EC aid delivery methods.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least one of the experts should have a working knowledge in *&lt;em&gt;Arabic *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Media with Experience in South European Neighbourhood Policy (Cat I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-media-with-experience-in-south-european-neighbourhood-policy-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-media-with-experience-in-south-european-neighbourhood-policy-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation of &amp;lsquo;MedMedia&amp;rsquo; Regional Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overall Objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project is to reinforce the role of media as vector for democratisation and contribute to the development of a more public service-orientated media landscape in the Southern Mediterranean as well as to contribute to the creation and development of a public sphere in the region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Purpose&lt;/strong&gt;
The specific objectives of the project have been reformulated by the inception report and approved by the Commission as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To build public trust by strengthening the media’s role as an independent watchdog and a forum for democratic debate;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To forge closer links between media practitioners across the region, thereby facilitating an ongoing exchange of experience and information;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To develop capacities in the media sector so that key players can rise to new professional challenges and respond to audience needs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To enrich and expand the informational resources available to the institutions and individuals responsible for implementing media reforms in the Southern Mediterranean Region.
One specific objective has been added by the Inception Report to give &amp;lsquo;due prominence to the project’s engagement on a governmental level and its commitment to giving new momentum to reform processes&amp;rsquo;:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To strengthen partnerships with media policy makers at ministerial and parliamentary level and with key stakeholders lobbying for media reforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Media with Experience in South European Neighbourhood Policy (Cat I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;University degree. In absence of the University degree, the relevant professional experience will be of a minimum 13 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive and relevant experience (minimum 12 years) in the field of international cooperation, preferably in geographical area of the South European Neighbourhood policy with field experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 8 years of relevant experience in the area of media development, freedom of expression. At least one of the experts should have experience in support for social dialogue, civil society or good governance and democratisation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full working knowledge of English and French and excellent report writing skills. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven Experience (min.3 years) in mid-term and final evaluation preferably of media development projects&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Neighbourhood South region&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good understanding of EU programmes and policies in the field of media development&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full knowledge of the principles and working methods of project cycle management and EC aid delivery methods.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biodiversity/Conservation Expert </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/biodiversity-conservation-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 11:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/biodiversity-conservation-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identification of Biodiversity Action under 11th EDF&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To support the Government of Mozambique, represented by the National Authorizing Office, and the EU Delegation to Mozambique in the identification of opportunities for biodiversity-related interventions contributing to the overall objectives of the agreed 11th EDF NIP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective of this contract is to identify and advice on needs and options for appropriate EU actions addressing biodiversity conservation that could be supported through the 11th EDF to complement other actions in the rural development component and contribute to poverty alleviation in the rural areas of Mozambique (NIP rural development objective).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The consultancy should contribute to identify interventions that will: 1) empower communities to participate and benefit from environmental, social and economic gains from a sustainable management of the natural resources; 2) Strengthening capacity and governance structures for sustainable use and protection of the natural resources and 3) Identify the areas in which the EU can complement other development partners in line with the Government priorities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Biodiversity/Conservation Expert (approx. 70 days)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in natural resource management or other related discipline relevant to the assignment;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in Portuguese with strong ability to write and edit documents is a prerequisite;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of English is an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Country knowledge (previous assignments conducted in Mozambique) is a prerequisite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 8 years of relevant professional experience in natural resource management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The expert must have extensive specific experience in biodiversity/ conservation development interventions with focus on conservation areas and the involvement of communities in natural resources management;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in identification and formulation, consultation processes, review and evaluation of development programmes will be an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Mozambican Biodiversity and Conservation legislation and implementing modalities for conservation areas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in implementation of Natural resource management programmes will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with multi-donor actions, institutional funds and trust-funds will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in NRM/Conservation/Biodiversity - Coordinator/ Team Leader </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-nrm-conservation-biodiversity-coordinator-team-leader</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-nrm-conservation-biodiversity-coordinator-team-leader</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identification of Biodiversity Action under 11th EDF&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To support the Government of Mozambique, represented by the National Authorizing Office, and the EU Delegation to Mozambique in the identification of opportunities for biodiversity-related interventions contributing to the overall objectives of the agreed 11th EDF NIP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective of this contract is to identify and advice on needs and options for appropriate EU actions addressing biodiversity conservation that could be supported through the 11th EDF to complement other actions in the rural development component and contribute to poverty alleviation in the rural areas of Mozambique (NIP rural development objective).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The consultancy should contribute to identify interventions that will: 1) empower communities to participate and benefit from environmental, social and economic gains from a sustainable management of the natural resources; 2) Strengthening capacity and governance structures for sustainable use and protection of the natural resources and 3) Identify the areas in which the EU can complement other development partners in line with the Government priorities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in NRM/Conservation/Biodiversity - Coordinator/ Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; (approx. 80 days)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in Environmental studies, Natural resources, or other related discipline relevant to the assignment;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English with strong ability to communicate with a variety of stakeholders, to write and edit documents is a prerequisite;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Country knowledge (previous assignments conducted in Mozambique) will be a strong asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ability to read and speak Portuguese&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least 10 years of relevant professional experience in Environmental conservation, Biodiversity, protected areas, Natural resource management and Forestry/Forestry governance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must possess proven experience as a team leader, facilitator and coordinator of comparable assignments;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must possess proven experience in identification and formulation, review and evaluation of Natural resource management development programmes and Biodiversity/conservation actions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the involvement of the private/public partnerships in Natural resource management activities will be an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with innovative actions like Ecosystem payment services will be an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in implementation of Natural resource management programmes will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with multi-donor actions, institutional funds and trust-funds will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gender Expert with Development Cooperation Background (fluent in Siswati)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/development-cooperation-background-fluent-in-siswati</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2016 17:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/development-cooperation-background-fluent-in-siswati</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Development of a Gender Analysis Report for EU Delegation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt; of the assignment are to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide an overview and analysis of the factors like legal and human policy framework, political, socio-economic, cultural, religious, etc. hat impede on the gender equality and empowerment of women in the country;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide a brief overview and analysis of the EU and key partner’s strengths and shortcomings to date on mainstreaming gender in their development cooperation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide proposals on how to adapt current programmes for gender equality outcomes; on how to integrate gender into future programmes and projects especially on Agriculture and Social Protection; on relevant and feasible new actions; and on which GAP II objectives of the EU can contribute;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify realistic objectives and opportunities on gender issues for policy discussion with a view to contribute to EU engagement with Government and other key stakeholders in the political dialogue.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gender Expert with a Development Cooperation Background (fluent in Siswati)– Cat. 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s Degree in social sciences, gender studies, development studies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6 years’ experience in development cooperation, especially in EU funded projects;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience and relevant expertise dealing with issues of gender mainstreaming, gender profiling and gender analysis;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated knowledge of key international agreements and instruments on human rights especially women’s rights;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience of EU development policies, instruments and guidelines;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good communication and presentation skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;English and Siswati fluency (written and oral).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Gender Expert with Development Cooperation Background (TL) </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-gender-expert-with-development-cooperation-background-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2016 17:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-gender-expert-with-development-cooperation-background-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Development of a Gender Analysis Report for EU Delegation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt; of the assignment are to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide an overview and analysis of the factors like legal and human policy framework, political, socio-economic, cultural, religious, etc. hat impede on the gender equality and empowerment of women in the country;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide a brief overview and analysis of the EU and key partner’s strengths and shortcomings to date on mainstreaming gender in their development cooperation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide proposals on how to adapt current programmes for gender equality outcomes; on how to integrate gender into future programmes and projects especially on Agriculture and Social Protection; on relevant and feasible new actions; and on which GAP II objectives of the EU can contribute;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify realistic objectives and opportunities on gender issues for policy discussion with a view to contribute to EU engagement with Government and other key stakeholders in the political dialogue.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Gender Expert with Development Cooperation Background (TL) (Cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s Degree in social sciences, gender studies, development studies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10 years’ experience in development cooperation (agriculture, social protection, health, education, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8 years’ experience in national policies on gender/women participation and empowerment in developing countries, especially in the SADC region;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience and relevant expertise dealing with issues of gender mainstreaming, gender profiling and gender analysis;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated knowledge of key international agreements and instruments on human rights especially women’s rights;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience of EU development policies, instruments and guidelines;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good communication and presentation skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;English fluency (written and oral.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Assistant – Experience in Environment/Biodiversity Projects (Cat. II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/project-assistant-experience-in-environment-biodiversity-projects-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2016 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/project-assistant-experience-in-environment-biodiversity-projects-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PSF - Legal and illegal trade in wildlife species between the EU and Mexico&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project aims to provide a comprehensive analysis of the trade of CITES listed species between Mexico and the EU (whether legally or illegally traded), in order to pave the way towards the development and implementation of actions to ensure their conversation, and guarantee that their trade is legal, sustainable and traceable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Assistant – Experience in Environment/Biodiversity Projects (Cat. II)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University Degree in wildlife monitoring, conservation and trade, environmental science and policy, or related fields;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience (at least 3 years) in international cooperation projects in the field of environment and biodiversity;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven research and writing skills as well as strong analytical skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and presentation skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English and Spanish&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Wildlife Trade (TL) </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-wildlife-trade-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2016 09:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-wildlife-trade-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PSF - Legal and illegal trade in wildlife species between the EU and Mexico&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project aims to provide a comprehensive analysis of the trade of CITES listed species between Mexico and the EU (whether legally or illegally traded), in order to pave the way towards the development and implementation of actions to ensure their conversation, and guarantee that their trade is legal, sustainable and traceable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Wildlife Trade (TL) (Cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master Degree in wildlife monitoring, conservation and trade, environmental science and policy or related fields;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience (at least 5 years) in monitoring legal and illegal wildlife trade, and contributing to wildlife trade analysis and policies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of the CITES Convention and related wildlife trade policies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven research and writing skills as well as strong analytical skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven previous experience as team leader coordinating a pool of experts in research projects;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Strong management skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Excellent communication and presentation skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Fluency in English and Spanish&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert en Matière de Pêche et de Mareyage </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-matiere-de-peche-et-de-mareyage</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 07:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-matiere-de-peche-et-de-mareyage</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appui sectoriel a la Formulation des Interventions de l&amp;#39;UE dans les domaines Agroalimentaire et des Produits de la Pêche&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif spécifique du projet est l’appui sectoriel a la formulation des interventions de l’UE dans les domaines agroalimentaire et des produits de la pêche, au bénéfice de l’Office National de Sécurité Sanitaire des Produits Alimentaires (ONSSA), du Ministère de l’Agriculture et de la Pêche Maritime (MAPM) et de l’Agence pour le Développement Agricole (ADA).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2 - Expert en Matière de Pêche et de Mareyage (Cat. I, 19w/d)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme d&amp;#39;ingénieur agronome ou tout autre domaine pertinent, ou en cas d&amp;#39;absence de diplôme une expérience professionnelle de minimum 17 années dans le domaine de la pêche et du mareyage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 12 années d&amp;#39;expérience en conception (planification stratégique, monitoring, évaluation et gestion des risques) et/ou mise en œuvre opérationnelle (pilotage, management et gestion) de politiques publiques dans le domaine de la pêche et du mareyage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 5 années de pratique des politiques publiques de l’UE dans le domaine de la pêche et du mareyage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonne maitrise de la langue française parlée et écrite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Atouts&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience au sein d&amp;#39;un organisme national en Europe (Ministère, Agence…) et/ou d’une organisation internationale dans le domaine de la pêche et du mareyage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en conseil / assistance technique au secteur public&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans un pays présentant un contexte de développement similaire à celui du Maroc (selon le référentiel IDH)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance de la législation et de l’administration marocaines dans le domaine concerné&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance des procédures UE pour les instruments de jumelage institutionnel et assistance technique&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert Agroalimentaire Senior et Chef de Mission </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-agroalimentaire-senior-et-chef-de-mission</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 07:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-agroalimentaire-senior-et-chef-de-mission</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appui sectoriel a la Formulation des Interventions de l&amp;#39;UE dans les domaines Agroalimentaire et des Produits de la Pêche&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif spécifique du projet est l’appui sectoriel a la formulation des interventions de l’UE dans les domaines agroalimentaire et des produits de la pêche, au bénéfice de l’Office National de Sécurité Sanitaire des Produits Alimentaires (ONSSA), du Ministère de l’Agriculture et de la Pêche Maritime (MAPM) et de l’Agence pour le Développement Agricole (ADA).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert Agroalimentaire Senior et Chef de Mission (Cat. I, 36 w/d)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme d&amp;#39;ingénieur agronome ou tout autre domaine pertinent, ou en cas d&amp;#39;absence de diplôme une expérience professionnelle de minimum 17 années&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 12 années d&amp;#39;expérience en conception (planification stratégique, monitoring, évaluation et gestion des risques) et/ou mise en œuvre opérationnelle (pilotage, management et gestion) de politiques publiques dans le domaine de l’agroalimentaire.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 5 années de pratique des politiques publiques de l’UE dans les domaines de : (i) de la sécurité sanitaire des produits agroalimentaires, (ii) des systèmes d’indications géographiques.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins deux expériences pertinentes en matière de management et de coordination de mission.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonne maitrise de la langue française parlée et écrite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Atouts&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience au sein d&amp;#39;un organisme national en Europe (Ministère, Agence…) et/ou d’une organisation internationale dans au moins un des domaines suivants: (i) la sécurité sanitaire des produits agroalimentaires, (ii) les systèmes d’indications géographiques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en conseil / assistance technique au secteur public&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans un pays présentant un contexte de développement similaire à celui du Maroc (selon le référentiel IDH)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance de la législation et de l’administration marocaines dans le domaine concerné&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance des procédures UE pour les instruments de jumelage institutionnel et assistance technique&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Environnementaliste Senior</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/environnementaliste-senior</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 07:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/environnementaliste-senior</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation a mi par cours du Pagos au Gabon&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les principaux objectifs de cette évaluation sont de présenter:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une appréciation globale des résultats du PAGOS en s’attachant plus particulièrement aux résultats du projet par rapport à ses objectifs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Souligner les principaux enseignements de l’intervention et des recommandations afin d’améliorer les mesures en cours et les futures actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 4 : Environnementaliste Senior (Cat. I, 22 jours)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Un diplôme universitaire en ingénierie des ressources naturelles, spécialiste des questions environnementales, agronomie, forestières ou de thématiques apparentées&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle de 12 ans pertinente dans le secteur – Catégorie I&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une bonne connaissance des problématiques de gouvernance des ressources naturelles en général, des ressources forestières et l&amp;#39;environnement en en particulier.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une bonne connaissance des principales des cadres légaux et règlementaires qui régissent les diverses sous-composantes du PAGOS environnement (dont APV-FLEGT, EIES ; instruments de financement carbone et de crédits développement durable, …)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une bonne connaissance de la réglementation internationale en la matière.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to Nicte Garcia-soria &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spécialiste Senior Minier </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/specialiste-senior-minier</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 07:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/specialiste-senior-minier</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation a mi par cours du Pagos au Gabon&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les principaux objectifs de cette évaluation sont de présenter:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une appréciation globale des résultats du PAGOS en s’attachant plus particulièrement aux résultats du projet par rapport à ses objectifs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Souligner les principaux enseignements de l’intervention et des recommandations afin d’améliorer les mesures en cours et les futures actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 3 : Spécialiste Senior Minier (22 jours, Cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Qualifications et compétences
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formation supérieure universitaire d’ingénieur minier ou similaire&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle de 12 ans pertinente dans le secteur minier – Catégorie I&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une bonne connaissance des problématiques des Mines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une bonne connaissance des principales règles de régulation, de gouvernance du secteur et des processus ITIE, KIMBERLEY, … et des SIG&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une bonne connaissance de la réglementation internationale en la matière.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to Nicte Garcia-soria &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Economiste Senior des Transports </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/economiste-senior-des-transports</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 07:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/economiste-senior-des-transports</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation a mi par cours du Pagos au Gabon&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les principaux objectifs de cette évaluation sont de présenter:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une appréciation globale des résultats du PAGOS en s’attachant plus particulièrement aux résultats du projet par rapport à ses objectifs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Souligner les principaux enseignements de l’intervention et des recommandations afin d’améliorer les mesures en cours et les futures actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Economiste Senior des Transports (Cat. I, 22 jours)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Un diplôme universitaire en économie ou ingénierie civile, complété par une spécialisation dans le secteur des transports (routiers).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience professionnelle d&amp;#39;au moins 12 ans dans le secteur des transports est demandée – Catégorie I.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une bonne connaissance de l&amp;#39;économie des transports (mécanismes de financements de l&amp;#39;entretien, fonds d&amp;#39;entretien routier et agences routières, relations institutionnelles ministères de tutelle et agences, gouvernance sectorielle).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une bonne connaissance des principales institutions et agences de régulation du secteur.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une bonne connaissance du montage institutionnel de la collecte des taxes et des redevances destinées à l&amp;#39;entretien routier.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to Nicte Garcia-soria &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef de mission, Spécialiste des Finances Publiques et en Gouvernance (Cat. I, 25 j)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-specialiste-des-finances-publiques-et-en-gouvernance-cat-i-25-j</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 07:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-specialiste-des-finances-publiques-et-en-gouvernance-cat-i-25-j</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Evaluation a mi par cours du Pagos au Gabon
*&lt;/em&gt;
Les principaux objectifs de cette évaluation sont de présenter:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une appréciation globale des résultats du PAGOS en s’attachant plus particulièrement aux résultats du projet par rapport à ses objectifs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Souligner les principaux enseignements de l’intervention et des recommandations afin d’améliorer les mesures en cours et les futures actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chef de mission, Spécialiste des Finances Publiques et en Gouvernance (Cat. I, 25 j)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Un diplôme universitaire en économie, complété par une spécialisation dans la gouvernance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale :
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience professionnelle d&amp;#39;au moins 12 ans dans le domaine des finances publiques – Catégorie I&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une bonne connaissance de l&amp;#39;économie des pays en voie de développement en Afrique subsaharienne,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une bonne connaissance des principales institutions et agences de régulation sectorielle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to Nicte Garcia-soria &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experto 2, Evaluacion Intermedia del PADH</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-2-</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 20:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-2-</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluacion Intermedia del PADH&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;El objetivo del Proyecto es evaluar el Programa de Apoyo a los Derechos Humanos y en particular analizar si el planeamiento y ejecución del programa hasta la fecha es capaz de lograr los objetivos previstos en el Convenio de Financiamiento y en los diferentes planes operativos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experto 2 (Cat. I, 18 w/d)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mínimo 12 años de experiencia en su campo profesional &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Título universitario reconocido en ciencias económicas, financieras, o equivalentes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Título universitario reconocido de nivel de Maestría en el área de gestión de proyectos, finanzas, o áreas equivalentes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Al menos 5 años de experiencia en  el monitoreo y evaluación de programas de fortalecimiento institucional&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Al menos 5 años de experiencia en análisis financiero y evaluación coste-eficiencia de programas  de fortalecimiento institucional&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Al menos 5 años de experiencia efectiva en países en vías de desarrollo de los cuales algunos en América Latina.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Se apreciará el haber participado en evaluaciones de proyectos similares.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jefe de Misión, Evaluacion Intermedia del PADH</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/jefe-de-mision</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 20:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/jefe-de-mision</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Evaluacion Intermedia del PADH
*&lt;/em&gt;
El objetivo del Proyecto es evaluar el Programa de Apoyo a los Derechos Humanos y en particular analizar si el planeamiento y ejecución del programa hasta la fecha es capaz de lograr los objetivos previstos en el Convenio de Financiamiento y en los diferentes planes operativos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jefe de Misión (Cat. I, 18w/d)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mínimo 12 años de experiencia en su campo profesional&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formación universitaria en ciencias económicas, políticas, jurídicas o equivalentes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Título universitario reconocido de nivel de Maestría en las áreas económicas, políticas, jurídicas o equivalentes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Al menos 10 años de experiencia directamente relacionados con programas de cooperación de apoyo al fortalecimiento de los  Derechos Humanos. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferiblemente, 5 años de experiencia en programas/proyectos de apoyo a políticas públicas en la materia &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferiblemente, 5 años de experiencia en gestión, seguimiento y evaluación de proyectos con algunos de monto superior a 5.000.000 euros.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia previa en dirección de equipo de evaluación.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Con un mínimo 5 años de experiencia efectiva en países en vías de desarrollo de preferencia en América Latina.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Buenos conocimientos de los procedimientos para la cooperación exterior de la Comisión Europea, ciclo de proyecto y marco lógico.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert in Judicial Reform and Rule of Law </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-judicial-reform-and-rule-of-law</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 19:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-judicial-reform-and-rule-of-law</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term External Evaluation of the EU funded programme &amp;lsquo;Promotion of the respect of Rule of Law in Kyrgyzstan with particular emphasis on Transparency and Accountability&amp;rsquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To assist in strengthening the respect of the Rule of Law in the Kyrgyz Republic by promoting transparency, accountability and anti-corruption measures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in Judicial reform and Rule of Law (Cat. III, 35 w/d):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in social sciences at least at Bachelor level;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience working in the sector of judicial reform and rule of law;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 1 year of specific experience working in an international project in the areas of rule of law;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Soft skills&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills (both oral and written communication skills);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English, Russian and Kyrgyz languages both oral and written is an absolute requirement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to Nicte Garcia-soria &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert in Justice, Home Affairs and Criminal Legislation (Category II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-justice-home-affairs-and-criminal-legislation-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-justice-home-affairs-and-criminal-legislation-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term External Evaluation of the EU funded programme &amp;lsquo;Promotion of the respect of Rule of Law in Kyrgyzstan with particular emphasis on Transparency and Accountability&amp;rsquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To assist in strengthening the respect of the Rule of Law in the Kyrgyz Republic by promoting transparency, accountability and anti-corruption measures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in Justice, Home Affairs and Criminal Legislation (Category II, 45 w/d)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education at least Masters&amp;#39; Degree law or, in its absence, Bachelor or Specialist degree in law plus 5 years of equivalent professional experience in the judicial sector as lawyer, judge or prosecutor (the equivalent experience must be above the general professional experience duration fixed below);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of experience in the sector Justice and Home Affairs as lawyer looking after administrative, civil and/or criminal legislation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of specific experience working on judicial
reform abroad preferably within the framework of a programme of technical assistance funded by the EU or by another international donor;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Soft skills&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills (both oral and written communication skills)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English and in Russian both oral and written is an absolute requirement. Knowledge of Kyrgyz language will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to Nicte Garcia-soria &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader, Senior Expert in Justice, Home Affairs and Criminal Legislation </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-expert-in-justice-home-affairs-and-criminal-legislation</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 15:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-expert-in-justice-home-affairs-and-criminal-legislation</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term External Evaluation of the EU funded programme &amp;lsquo;Promotion of the respect of Rule of Law in Kyrgyzstan with particular emphasis on Transparency and Accountability&amp;rsquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To assist in strengthening the respect of the Rule of Law in the Kyrgyz Republic by promoting transparency, accountability and anti-corruption measures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader, Senior Expert in Justice, Home Affairs and Criminal Legislation&lt;/strong&gt; (Cat. I, 55w/d):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education in law at least Masters&amp;#39; Degree or, in its absence, Bachelor or Specialist degree in law plus 5 years of equivalent professional experience in the judicial sector as lawyer, judge or prosecutor (the equivalent experience must be above the general professional experience duration fixed below);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in the sector Justice and Home Affairs as lawyer looking after administrative, civil and/or criminal legislation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of specific experience working on judicial reform abroad preferably within the framework of a programme of technical assistance funded by the EU or by another international donor; at least 3 years professional experience at managerial level.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Soft skills&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent facilitation and communication skills (both oral and written communication skills) as the Expert is expected to act as Team leader;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English both oral and written is an absolute requirement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Russian language will be an asset. Knowledge of Kyrgyz will be an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to Nicte Garcia-soria &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
