<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 12:51:21 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef de mission (expert de catégorie 1)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-expert-de-categorie-1</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-expert-de-categorie-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of the Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les objectifs de la présente mission portent sur la réalisation des deux études suivantes :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Étude 1 : Élaboration, sur la base d’un diagnostic approfondi, d’un plan d’action pour le
développement des capacités institutionnelles de la CPS/SDR ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Étude 2 : Élaboration, sur la base d’un diagnostic approfondi, d’un plan d’action de
renforcement des capacités techniques et organisationnelles de l’Interprofession Riz du
Mali.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Niveau universitaire équivalent au
moins au Master en statistiques ou en planification ou en Agronomie, ou en Agroéconomie ou
dans un autre domaine équivalent et disposant des expériences et connaissances suivantes :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir au moins 12 ans d’expériences professionnelles dans des systèmes de
statistiques (nationaux et/ou Agricoles) couvrant les domaines suivants : planification,
suivi-évaluation des politiques et programmes agricoles, production et diffusion de
statistiques Agricoles dont au moins trois ans d’expériences professionnelles
spécifiques avec les services des statistiques Agricoles dans les pays de l’Afrique
francophone ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir coordonné, en tant que chef de mission, au moins trois missions similaires, c&amp;#39;està-
dire des missions d’évaluation des capacités des services de statistiques agricoles et
d’élaboration de stratégies de développement des capacités de ces services ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir une expérience d’appui dans l’organisation des concertations sectorielles (multiacteurs)
;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir des expériences professionnelles avec l’Administration publique malienne sera un
avantage ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir de solides capacités à communiquer en langue française.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category III Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-iii-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-iii-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Global Objective of this evaluation is to provide the project stakeholders, primarily the EU Delegation to Laos, with sufficient information about the project performance of the Pool Fund
(its relevancy, efficiency, effectiveness, impacts and sustainability), document lessons learned and provide practical recommendations for future programmes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Specific Objectives&lt;/strong&gt; are built on five key parameters for the evaluator to study; and these are:relevance, efficiency, effectives, impact and sustainability as described below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the relevance of the project design (its activities and objectives) in addressing the priority issues in the target communities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess to what extent the available resources have been used economically in delivering the project outputs/results, in terms of quantity, quality and timeliness (efficiency).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the major achievements of the project to date in relation to its stated objectives and intended results based on the logframe (effectiveness);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess to what extent the project is contributing to a long-term positive effect on the entire society in the uplands (impact);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess whether the positive outcomes of the project are likely to continue after the project (sustainability).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications Required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;S/he will have at least a Bachelor degree in Agriculture/Rural Development or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;S/he has at least 3 years of professional experience relevant to the Agriculture/Rural Development sectors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;S/he will have past training delivery experience at the subnational level proven by at least one assignment;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;S/he has at least one past experience in project/programme evaluation, particularly in a rural development project/programme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;English Proficiency&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Communication skills in Lao would be an asset.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category I Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 09:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of the Project:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Global Objective of this evaluation is to provide the project stakeholders, primarily the EU Delegation to Laos, with sufficient information about the project performance of the Pool Fund
(its relevancy, efficiency, effectiveness, impacts and sustainability), document lessons learned and provide practical recommendations for future programmes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Specific Objectives are built on five key parameters for the evaluator to study; and these are: relevance, efficiency, effectives, impact and sustainability as described below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the relevance of the project design (its activities and objectives) in addressing the priority issues in the target communities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess to what extent the available resources have been used economically in delivering the project outputs/results, in terms of quantity, quality and timeliness (efficiency).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the major achievements of the project to date in relation to its stated objectives and intended results based on the logframe (effectiveness);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Asses to what extent the project is contributing to a long-term positive effect on the entire society in the uplands (impact);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess whether the positive outcomes of the project are likely to continue after the project
(sustainability).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications Required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;•S/he has an advanced university degree (minimum Master) in Agriculture/Rural Development studies or relevant International Development Studies or equivalent professional experience of
at least 153 years if candidate does not possess an advance university degree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;•S/he has at least 12 years of professional experience relevant to the Agriculture/Rural Development sectors&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;•S/he has minimum 3 years&amp;#39; experience in the implementation and management of development projects or programmes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;•S/he has least one relevant experience with Programme Based approaches,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;•S/he has at least two relevant past experiences with EU Project Cycle Management and, in particular with evaluation procedures,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;•S/he will also have team leader experience proven by at least two missions as head of mission/team leader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;•English Proficiency&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;•Communication skills in Lao would be an asset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail%20to:%20nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Banking Regulation and Supervision</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-banking-regulation-and-supervision</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 01:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-banking-regulation-and-supervision</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to the preparation of the twinning fiches for the National Bank of the Republic of Belarus&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The assignment will consist of supporting the preparation of the twinning fiche for the National Bank of the Republic of Belarus (NBRB) as the beneficiary and project partner of the first twinning project in Belarus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in Banking Regulation and Supervision (Category I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of general professional experience in the sector related to the Lot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master’s Degree, preferably in macroeconomics, financial management, banking regulation or other relevant field or, in its absence, at least 5 additional years of professional experience on top of the 12 required under general professional experience above&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of professional experience in the area of banking regulation and/or supervision in the EU countries or countries covered by the Enlargement Policy;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in drafting project proposals for technical assistance projects (at least one reference);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good prior knowledge of the banking sector regulatory and supervision situation of the Republic of Belarus would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Background in Twinning matters would be asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in both written and spoken English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Russian would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;em&gt;[Lina&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;](mailto:&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;lina_forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Economic and Monetary Policy </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-economic-and-monetary-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 01:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-economic-and-monetary-policy</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to the preparation of the twinning fiches for the National Bank of the Republic of Belarus&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The assignment will consist of supporting the preparation of the twinning fiche for the National Bank of the Republic of Belarus (NBRB) as the beneficiary and project partner of the first twinning project in Belarus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader, Expert in Economic and Monetary Policy (Category I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of general professional experience in the sector related to the Lot; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master’s Degree, preferably in macroeconomics, financial management, banking regulation or other relevant field or, in its absence, at least 5 additional years of professional experience on top of the 12 required under general professional experience above;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of professional experience in area of monetary and/or macroeconomic policy, targeting inflation, Central bank regulation in the EU countries or countries covered by the Enlargement Policy;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of the EU Acquis in a banking field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in drafting project proposals for technical assistance projects in macroeconomic or banking area (at least one reference);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good prior knowledge of the macroeconomic policy, banking sector, regulatory and supervision situation of the Republic of Belarus would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Background in Twinning matters would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in both written and spoken English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Russian would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Environment Specialist - (Cat. II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/environment-specialist-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 02:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/environment-specialist-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KE4 -  Environment Specialist - (Cat. II, minim um of 22 working  days)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification &amp;amp; Skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MSc. in Environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;General   experience:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6 years of experience in Environmental Impact Assessment studies with a particular focus on small infrastructure and agriculture projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of rural development in developing countries
Specific experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A good knowledge of the Philippines and/or Asian environment will be an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to  &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Economist, SME Specialist (Cat. II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/economist-sme-specialist-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 02:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/economist-sme-specialist-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KE3 - Economist, SME Specialist (Cat. II, minimum of 66 working days)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification &amp;amp; Skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MSc. in Business, Economics and Social sciences and Development studies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The expert should have a minimum of 6 years of professional experience in economics and Development, conducting studies for the development of SME and/or business associations; private sector capacity building (including experience as trainer) and expert promotion in developing countries to hire and manage external consultants with a view to achieving high quality outputs and results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A specific expertise is required in gender issues and social dimension of development and job creation (Social Corporate Responsibility, child labour) as well  as  the  integration  of Indigenous  Populations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of South East Asia would be an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perfect command of English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to  &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rural Engineer/Civil Engineer (Cat. I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/rural-engineer-civil-engineer-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 02:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/rural-engineer-civil-engineer-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KE2 -  Rural Engineer/Civil Engineer (Cat. I, minimum of 66 working   days)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification &amp;amp; Skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MSc. in civil engineering in rural context&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The expert should have at least 12 years of professional experience in conducting engineering and feasibility studies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth knowledge of designing and building feeder roads, bridges, building construction, irrigation schemes and drainage works&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in civil engineering works and rural roads construction involving communities and cash for works procedures as well as roads maintenance issues and practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perfect command of English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to  &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader/Agro-Economist Specialist of Cooperatives/Famers groups (Cat.I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-agro-economist-specialist-of-cooperatives-famers-groups-cati</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 02:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-agro-economist-specialist-of-cooperatives-famers-groups-cati</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formulation of a Job Creation Programme in Mindanao&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader/Agro-Economist Specialist of Cooperatives/Famers groups (Cat. I, minimum of 68 Working days)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification &amp;amp; Skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The expert must be an agro-economist with a university degree in these fields (minimum MSc.) or equivalent professional experience of at least 20 years in agro-economics and rural development  fields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He must have at least 12 years of experience in conducting agricultural feasibility studies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong  experience  in  capacity  building  and  support  to  farmers  groups  and  cooperatives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in conducting workshops (participatory project appraisal, objective oriented planning, logframe)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in  extension   services delivery,  marketing and   post-harvest technologies   of agricultural crops&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of agro-business projects, preferably in South East Asia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with communities involvement in developing countries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the EU procedures would be an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perfect command of English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to  &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perito Cat. II – perito em avaliação de projectos de desenvolvimento institucional</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/perito-cat-ii-perito-em-avaliaco-de-projectos-de-desenvolvimento-institucional</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/perito-cat-ii-perito-em-avaliaco-de-projectos-de-desenvolvimento-institucional</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Avaliação Final do PAANE II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;O Objectivo Global deste projeto è a avaliação final do Programa de Apoio aos Actores Não Estatais (PAANE II) . Especificamente, após consulta e análise da documentação disponível, das visitas as províncias do projecto e contactos/entrevistas com os diferentes interlocutores, os consultores deverão: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avaliar em que medida os resultados esperados do projecto foram alcançados;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elaborar uma lista exaustiva de lições aprendidas e boas práticas adquiridas com o projecto; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elaborar um estudo de viabilidade e análise sectorial que analise a pertinência do apoio da União Europeia à articulação das OSC com as autoridades locais, bem como, de que maneira como o Governo de Angola encara este apoio; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identificar novas áreas para apoiar; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identificar as limitações e restrições à implementação do projecto, susceptíveis de terem afectado a sua performance; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avaliar o gau de sustentabilidade do projecto; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recomendar medidas correctivas, para maximizar os resultados e a sustentabilidade do projecto; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Na base das constatações retiradas do terreno, recomendar eixos e metodologias de intervenção numa perspectiva de um próximo apoio às organizações da sociedade civil e autoridades locais previsto no âmbito do 11º FED.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Perito Cat. II – perito em avaliação de projectos de desenvolvimento institucional&lt;/strong&gt;  -  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pelo menos 6 anos de experiência de trabalho no desenvolvimento, implementação e avaliação de programas/políticas relativas a projectos de mobilização social/apoio ao desenvolvimento da sociedade civil&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiência em desenvolvimento local (desenvolvimento e capacitação institucional, descentralização e desconcentração, participação da sociedade civil nas políticas públicas, etc) - Bons conhecimentos e experiência em gestão, administração e implementação de procedimentos de monitoria processual e financeira de projetos de cooperação UE–ACP. - Conhecimento do contexto institucional e da sociedade civil em Angola especialmente nas províncias &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiência em avaliação de programas institucionais&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Domínio da língua portuguesa e inglesa (falada e escrita)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Outras competências&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiência relevante em avaliação de projectos de apoio institucional às OSC &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiência profissional relevante em monitoria e avaliação de projectos de desenvolvimento e apoio institucional (em particular no eixo de governação) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assessoria técnica para o desenvolvimento institucional de organizações da sociedade civil,&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conhecimento do contexto institucional e da sociedade civil em Angola &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conhecimentos e experiência comprovada dos procedimentos FED&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bom conhecimento da abordagem da Gestão de Ciclo de projecto (Quadro Logico) da União Europeia &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Domínio do português e inglês falado he escrito&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capacidade de trabalhar de forma eficiente com as autoridades governamentais a nível nacional, provincial e local, bem como com as OSC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chefe de equipa (perito Cat. I) </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chefe-de-equipa-perito-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chefe-de-equipa-perito-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Avaliação Final do PAANE II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;O Objectivo Global deste projeto è a avaliação final do Programa de Apoio aos Actores Não Estatais (PAANE II) . Especificamente, após consulta e análise da documentação disponível, das visitas as províncias do projecto e contactos/entrevistas com os diferentes interlocutores, os consultores deverão: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avaliar em que medida os resultados esperados do projecto foram alcançados;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elaborar uma lista exaustiva de lições aprendidas e boas práticas adquiridas com o projecto; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elaborar um estudo de viabilidade e análise sectorial que analise a pertinência do apoio da União Europeia à articulação das OSC com as autoridades locais, bem como, de que maneira como o Governo de Angola encara este apoio; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identificar novas áreas para apoiar; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identificar as limitações e restrições à implementação do projecto, susceptíveis de terem afectado a sua performance; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avaliar o gau de sustentabilidade do projecto; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recomendar medidas correctivas, para maximizar os resultados e a sustentabilidade do projecto; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Na base das constatações retiradas do terreno, recomendar eixos e metodologias de intervenção numa perspectiva de um próximo apoio às organizações da sociedade civil e autoridades locais previsto no âmbito do 11º FED.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chefe de equipa (perito Cat. I) – perito em gestão e avaliação de projectos de desenvolvimento institucional&lt;/strong&gt; – 40 dias de trabalho &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formação universitária ao nível de Mestrado num ramo das Ciências sociais bem como formação complementar numa área relevante para a missão &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pelo menos 12 anos de experiência de trabalho em áreas relevantes para a missão: apoio institucional, apoio à sociedade civil, políticas de descentralização, experiência em redes de OSC em países em desenvolvimento, projectos de mobilização social/desenvolvimento da sociedade civil (de preferência nos PALOP)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiência como avaliador e coordenador de avaliação de pelo menos 3 programas de apoio ao desenvolvimento da sociedade civil (de preferência nos PALOP e no âmbito do FED) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conhecimento do contexto institucional e da sociedade civil em Angola &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Domínio da língua portuguesa e inglesa (falado e escrito)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Outras competências&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiência relevante em avaliação de projectos de apoio institucional às OSC &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiência profissional relevante em monitoria e avaliação de projectos de desenvolvimento e apoio institucional (em particular no eixo de governação) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assessoria técnica para o desenvolvimento institucional de organizações da sociedade civil,&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conhecimento do contexto institucional e da sociedade civil em Angola &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conhecimentos e experiência comprovada dos procedimentos FED&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bom conhecimento da abordagem da Gestão de Ciclo de projecto (Quadro Logico) da União Europeia &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Domínio do português e inglês falado e escrito&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capacidade de trabalhar de forma eficiente com as autoridades governamentais a nível nacional, provincial e local, bem como com as OSC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Electoral/Political Expert (Cat. I - Senior) and Senior Legal Expert (Cat.I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/electoral-political-expert-cat-i-senior</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 18:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/electoral-political-expert-cat-i-senior</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EEM The Gambia 2016&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of this assignment is to contribute to support democracy in the context of the Gambian Presidential Election scheduled for December the 1st, 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective of the assignment is to provide reporting to the European External Action Service, Democracy and Election Observation Division (hereafter referred to as EEAS) and the European Commission, Foreign Policy Instruments (here after referred to as EC FPI) on the ongoing electoral process during and after the Gambian presidential election. The experts will also provide the EEAS and EC with an analysis relating to recommendations with a view to further aligning all elements of the electoral process to international standards, in line with the criteria contained in the EC Communication on Electoral Assistance and Observation [COM(2000)191]. Elements of this report may eventually be shared with Electoral Authorities and the Government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One Team Leader – Electoral/Political Expert (Cat. I - Senior) for 49 working days&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*** One Legal Expert (Cat. I - Senior) for 48 working days **&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Education at least Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree Academic level in Political Science, International Relations, Law or any other discipline relevant to the assignment. In its absence, equivalent professional experience (more than 12 years). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;: At least 12 years of experience in the area related to Lot 7. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Significant work experience in the field of electoral assistance and/or electoral observation and analysis, preferably as part of an EU Election Observation Mission or an Election Technical Assistance project of the EU or of other international organisations, in position of managing the mission or drafting statements and reports. This work experience will include the participation as Core Team member or independent expert in at least four (4) election observation missions by international or domestic organizations such as: Election Observation Missions, Election Assessment Teams, Election Expert Mission, Follow-up Mission, Exploratory Missions, Needs Assessment Missions. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with the legal and regulatory framework for the elections as well as international and regional standards for elections. In this context the “Compendium of International Standards for Elections” is an important background document; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven work experience on electoral legislation and good understanding of election dispute resolution systems; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent understanding of the functioning of election management bodies; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in assessing the media landscape and media framework, according to international and regional standards, particularly as regards to elections, will be an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in the country and/or the region and good networks within the different sectors of society in order to be immediately operational will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and spoken English. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reporting will be done in English. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific to Team Leader&amp;rsquo;s profile&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition , the Team Leader will present the following profile: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and inter-personal skills; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent report drafting skills; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordination and management skills and past experience of management in a similar assignment, preferably as Deputy Chief Observer in an Election observation mission or as Chief Technical Adviser in a technical assistance project; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven knowledge and field experience of EU policies and programmes in the area of human rights, democratisation and good governance; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven work experience in project implementation and budget management of international civilian missions, preferably as part of an EU Election Observation Mission or an EU Election Technical Assistance project is an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven work experience of contractual and budgetary procedures of EU external action and related mechanisms is an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Governance and Anti-Corruption Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/governance-and-anti-corruption-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 07:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/governance-and-anti-corruption-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support for coordination and implementation of the Anti-corruption Road Map&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To support the development partners in Nepal in the refinement and implementation of the Road Map for Anti-Corruption and associated DPs coordination mechanisms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To work in collaboration with a local team with relevant competence, in order to jointly develop baseline and indicators on corruption and anti-corruption in Nepal, and to contribute to the development of an adequate local framework for data management and evidence based analysis related to
corruption/anti-corruption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Governance and Anti-Corruption Specialist&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The expert will have an advanced university degree in law, criminal justice, economics, political and social sciences, Public Financial Management or the equivalent combination of experience in related areas;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least twelve years of experience of anti-corruption work in the Development Cooperation sector;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least five years of experience in working on national anti-corruption policies, strategies, including the development of &amp;ldquo;home-grown indicators&amp;rdquo; and result-based frameworks for programming, and public campaigns;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least two years of operational experience working with an anti-corruption authority or law enforcement agencies, or prosecuting authority or international organizations as technical advisor on anti-corruption or a non-governmental organization working on anticorruption activities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in promoting innovative approaches, youth involvement, ICT tools etc.;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in Nepal and/or other South Asian countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good methodological skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good interpersonal skills and ability to establish and maintain effective partnership and working relationships in a multicultural environment;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to take initiative, and work independently as well as in a team;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in both oral and written English is required;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Nepali is an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantity Surveyor – Category II</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/quantity-surveyor-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 15:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/quantity-surveyor-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assessment of the rehabilitation and maintenance needs of the National Strategic Grain Reserves Infrastructure&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The purpose of this contract is to provide support to the National Food Reserve Agency to improve the condition of multiple national grain storage facilities by assessing their rehabilitation and maintenance needs in order to ensure their sustainable management.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The requested services entail a detailed assessment of the status of each of the grain silos/warehouses which includes but is not limited to: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A thorough assessment of each silo and warehouse with details of the extent of damage to each of the grain storage facilities and proposed remedial measures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare initial cost estimates for the remedial works and corresponding supervision services. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make recommendations for further detailed technical investigations and prepare Terms of Reference for the study.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Expert 2: Quantity Surveyor – Category II  - 100 working days&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master’s Degree in Quantity Surveying. In its absence, a Bachelor’s Degree in Quantity Surveying with at least 10 years professional experience or a Diploma in quantity surveying with at least 13 years professional experience. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Membership of a recognized professional institution(s) is required. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Those with understanding of Chichewa will have an added advantage. 
General professional experience &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of relevant practical and professional experience in quantity surveying.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in preparation of BOQs. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in taking measurements for construction and rehabilitation works.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Civil/Structural Engineer (Team Leader)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-civil-structural-engineer-team-leader</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 15:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-civil-structural-engineer-team-leader</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assessment of the rehabilitation and maintenance needs of the National Strategic Grain Reserves Infrastructure&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The purpose of this contract is to provide support to the National Food Reserve Agency to improve the condition of multiple national grain storage facilities by assessing their rehabilitation and maintenance needs in order to ensure their sustainable management.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The requested services entail a detailed assessment of the status of each of the grain silos/warehouses which includes but is not limited to: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A thorough assessment of each silo and warehouse with details of the extent of damage to each of the grain storage facilities and proposed remedial measures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare initial cost estimates for the remedial works and corresponding supervision services. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make recommendations for further detailed technical investigations and prepare Terms of Reference for the study.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Civil/Structural Engineer (Team Leader): Category I – 100 working days&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master Degree in Civil Engineering or equivalent engineering discipline. In its absence, a Bachelor’s Degree in Civil Engineering with at least 13 years professional experience. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Membership of a recognized professional institution(s) is required. 
General professional experience &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of relevant practical and professional experience and a proven record in the civil and structural works. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years professional experience in the design and supervision of structural works for which at least 3 years should be in developing countries in Sub Saharan Africa. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Specific professional experience *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong track record in project management skills for works contracts. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In depth understanding of structural works design and supervision. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in assessment of buildings for rehabilitation and maintenance. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ASiST Programme</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/asist-programme-1</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 14:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/asist-programme-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Not a BENEF 1 opportunity but the ASiST programme concerns similar areas of expertise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Purpose of role&lt;/strong&gt;
DAI’s ASiST programme is an advisory service for the European Commission rural development, food security and nutrition directorate (unit C1) within the Directorate General for Development and Cooperation (DEVCO). ASiST aims at providing support to identify and fine-tune tools to achieve the strategic objectives of food and nutrition security and sustainable agriculture in developing countries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ASiST Coordinator will provide direct hands-on support to the Team Leader and C1 Programme Manager to coordinate efficient delivery across the repertoire of ASiST technical and operational tasks. The role will add further value to ASiST by supporting a number of new or expanded functions, including: (i) coordinating a new technical help desk service; (ii) servicing ASiST’s knowledge management systems; and (iii) strengthening coordination and communications with internal and external stakeholders. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key tasks and responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;General operational support&lt;/em&gt;
• Routine support to the full complement of programme activities under the supervision of the Team Leader and DEVCO C1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Regular liaison with the DEVCO C1 Programme Manager and core team to ensure efficient and effective activity coordination, including through attending in-person meetings at DEVCO headquarters on a flexible basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Service and participate in ASiST’s frequent meetings and events, including organising venues, attendance lists, agendas, minute taking, circulating and monitoring agreed follow-up actions. These events include regular strategy meetings with DEVCO and the ASiST team as well as a range of conferences, presentations, roundtables, etc involving other DEVCO units, services and partners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Direct support to delivery of ASiST technical services. These include quality assurance of reports, research, studies, etc relating to ASiST’s core technical themes as well as an often significant volume of demand-driven requests from DEVCO and EU Delegations. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Play an active role in programme process planning and improvement initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Communication and collaboration&lt;/strong&gt;
• Serve as the coordination point to facilitate ongoing technical and thematic collaboration with other relevant DEVCO units and services (such as NAS and FANSSA) around key topics and activities of mutual relevance;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Support the team to continually promote ASiST, EU and thematic visibility, including through developing and disseminating communications materials, maintaining newsletters, etc;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Manage ASiST’s knowledge management systems, including: coordinating and disseminating regular knowledge products; helping DEVCO C1 in organising EU InfoPoint debriefings; taking the lead role in managing ASiST content on the Capacity4Dev portal. With the latter, the junior expert will be in charge of collecting contributions from ASiST experts after each mission and updating Capacity4Dev by writing blog posts on specific insights and writing briefs to illustrate social transfer instruments and issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Responsible for helping the Team Leader to explore and develop innovative ways of exchanging information and learning with C1 and EUDs around key themes and services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ASiST Helpdesk coordination&lt;/strong&gt;
• Work with the team to set up and manage the ASiST helpdesk, including receiving, fielding and coordinating enquiries and responses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications, knowledge, skills and experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/em&gt;
• Minimum Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in a relevant field or equivalent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience in coordinating projects and activities operating across multiple locations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience with project communications and knowledge management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience in providing quality assurance to reports and proofing reports or written products for development agencies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Excellent written and verbal communication skills in both English and French.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Strong organisational skills with excellent attention to detail.
• Proactive, resourceful, team player and able to independently manage complex tasks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Excellent interpersonal skills – able to establish and maintain positive working relationships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• A strong client-service delivery approach to delivering tasks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Ability to work under pressure and to tight deadlines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• MS Office expertise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;
• Minimum 5 years of professional experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Previous experience working with European Union Delegations and DEVCO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;
• Minimum 5 years of professional experience in one of the following thematic areas: food security, nutrition, resilience, sustainable agriculture, rural development, social transfers. Field experience would be an advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Demonstrable understanding of DEVCO, EUD processes and PRAG rules.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience working with EU-funded projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience working in international development cooperation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV to &lt;a href=&quot;mail:%20penny_buckle@dai.com&quot;&gt;penny_buckle@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWP 2 Projects Review</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Beyond WTO Program (B-WTO) was developed in response to a request from the Government of Vietnam (GoV) for donor support to help with managing economic integration and the transition to a market economy following WTO accession. The B-WTO goal is “to strengthen government’s capacity to manage the integration of Vietnam into the global economy and the transition of Vietnam to a socialist market economy”. The immediate objective is “implementation of priority policy actions from the GoV’s Action Plan to enhance Vietnam’s capacity to sustain pro-poor growth (GAP)”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The remit of this project was a review of the 2nd annual work plan’s implementation (AWP2) of Phase 2 of the B-WTO in May 2013. The objectives of the review were to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the project implementation performance and project results relative to the logical framework targets and evaluation criteria. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the results achieved at the Component and Program’s level according to the Monitoring and Evaluation (M&amp;amp;E) framework of the Program.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify lessons learned from implementation, make recommendations for the remaining duration of the program and the Independent Completion Report process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program 2013 Performance and Quality Mapping Exercise</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID’s PNG Program is looking to improve its performance and quality (P&amp;amp;Q) standards and systems. The purpose of this project was to map the PNG Program’s current P&amp;amp;Q capacity and systems, to address the risk of AusAID being unable to demonstrate results for its increased investments in PNG over the next four years. Over the last several years, the PNG Program has undertaken a number of M&amp;amp;E assessments and reviews which have identified key strengths and challenges within the program. This project was intended to pick up where these assessments left off. Through a desk review and consultations with sector teams, the Review Team were to distil key P&amp;amp;Q risks and issues for the PNG Program. The Review Team’s brief included the provision of recommendations on priority activities to support sector approaches to M&amp;amp;E, strengthen the Program’s ability to collect evidence, provide critical analysis and report on results.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID required a consultant to assist with the development and finalisation of its Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework. Development of a humanitarian monitoring and evaluation framework is a key commitment outlined in AusAID’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy (HAP) and its associated Implementation Plan. In line with the agency focus on results reporting, the HAP and HAP Implementation Plan commit AusAID to develop a monitoring and evaluation framework to support the initial performance assessment framework contained within the HAP and AusAID annual reporting under the Comprehensive Aid Policy Framework.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key objective of this assignment was to build the Humanitarian program’s capacity for monitoring and reporting results by:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In consultation with AusAID’s Humanitarian team, redraft and finalise the Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework, to ensure it provides a platform to:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track implementation of key commitments in Australia’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy; and,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish a set of measurable humanitarian performance indicators (in addition to the two CAPF indicators) to enable AusAID to track achievements, lessons learned and to report on the results achieved from AusAID’s humanitarian work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
