<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 11:23:16 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader/WTO Compliance/Trade Facilitation Advisor (Cat. I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-wto-compliance-trade-facilitation-advisor-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 11:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-wto-compliance-trade-facilitation-advisor-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this assignment is to contribute to the fulfilment of Tajikistan’s commitments taken during the WTO accession.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the assignment is to provide support for the implementation of the post-WTO accession Action Plan approved by the Government of Tajikistan, most notably the action items related to the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Obtaining the GSP Plus status;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Becoming signatory of the WTO Agreement on Trade in Civil aircraft;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Submitting ITA Schedule to the WTO ITA Committee;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Negotiations for the accession to WTO Agreement on Government Procurement;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Technical support to and capacity building of SUE staff in operating the SWIS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader/WTO Compliance/Trade Facilitation Advisor (Cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Masters&amp;#39;  Degree of Academic level in law, economics, international trade or political science from a recognized university or more than 15
years of equivalent professional experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English, oral and written;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;S/he should have at least 12 years&amp;#39; of professional experience related to international trade and/or international law;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid experience in trade related technical assistance, demonstrated by at least five years of experience in implementing trade assistance programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth knowledge and expertise of the multilateral trading
system, most notably WTO, demonstrated by his/her participation in at least two long term (of at least one year each) assignments in support to trade negotiations within the WTO framework;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven leadership and people management skills, including the ability to establish and maintain effective working relationships with others in an international multi-cultural working environment, as demonstrated through the participation in at least one long-term assignment (of minimum one year) as Team Leader;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with rural Tajikistan, or a similar transitional context, is considered as an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Russian and/or Tajik language is considered to be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in EU-funded programmes and projects would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert on Agriculture Subsidies </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-agriculture-subsidies</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 07:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-agriculture-subsidies</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert on Agriculture Subsidies&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DAI is looking for an Expert on Agriculture Subsidies for a possible assignment within the Framework of the EC-funded ASiST III programme that DAI is managing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Expert *&lt;/em&gt;will be required to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;review ongoing EUD interventions in the field of agricultural subsidies, and &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;present options, methodology for developing interventions in this field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in the field of agricultural subsidies, preferably in Eastern and Southern Africa&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working on EC projects will be an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be proficient in drafting report in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and analytical skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Project location: home-based plus possible missions in Southern African countries&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Engineering, Environment and/or Development with Policy Development Experience </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-engineering-environment-and-or-development-with-policy-development-experience</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2015 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-engineering-environment-and-or-development-with-policy-development-experience</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the assignment is to provide policy and contractual support to the Nexus Dialogues project on behalf of DG DEVCO. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;overall objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the Nexus Dialogues project is to support the transformation required to meet increasing water, energy and food security (including land) demand (without further environment degradation), through the development of a truly integrated nexus approach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project location&lt;/strong&gt;: Europe and ad-hoc missions to Africa, LA, Asia and Neighbourhood countries&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Senior Expert in Engineering, Environment and/or Development with Policy Development Experience (Cat. I) *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Masters’ degree relevant to engineering, the environment and/or development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;15 years working experience in international political processes related to development cooperation and/or the environment, and/or engineering;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10 years working experience in programmes related to water or energy or food security or environmental policy development and specific experience in facilitating participative multi-stakeholder processes and institutional development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge and understanding of the EuropeAid and EU Development cooperation work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in knowledge management and communication;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work as a team member in collaboration with other experts;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills, oral and written, in English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific knowledge of EU development cooperation in the nexus and/or water and or energy and/or food security will be an &lt;strong&gt;asset&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of preparing proposals for funding will be an &lt;strong&gt;asset&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the development of monitoring frameworks for programmes oriented towards policy development will be an &lt;strong&gt;asset&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good communication skills, oral and written, in French and Spanish will be an &lt;strong&gt;asset&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader/Agronomist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-agronomist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2015 07:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-agronomist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectives of the role&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall goal of this activity is to reduce the burden of childhood malnutrition through the production, promotion and uptake of nutritious, locally-produced complementary foods for children of 6-23 months, and nutritional supplements for pregnant and lactating women (PLW).  The activity is implemented by Clinton Health Access Initiative (CHAI) who work closely with local governments, international investors and donors.  The activity is initially being implemented in Rwanda and Ethiopia and will potentially be expanded to two further African countries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MFAT are contributing to component three of the activity which aims to ensure a reliable supply of local crop inputs for the factory that will produce the complementary foods.  To achieve this, CHAI are working with smallholder farmers, cooperatives and unions to increase the quantity and quality of maize and soya produced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These services will supply technical assistance to CHAI, local trainers and government extension providers to strengthen farmer training programmes and provide technical information to farmers unions and cooperatives to inform investments in harvest and post-harvest technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The outcomes of these services will be:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Extension service providers can sustainably deliver practical and effective farmer-oriented training to increase the quantity and quality of soya and maize yields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Farmers cooperatives and unions are able to make informed decisions about the costs and benefits of investing in agricultural technology to assist with planting, harvest and post-harvest.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; will:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Ensure all team members are briefed on their roles and responsibilities in the project, and ensure all team inputs are well coordinated and delivered to a high quality standard;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Liaise with CHAI and key stakeholders in Rwanda; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support the New Zealand Aid Programme to actively engage in the agriculture components of the initiative, including through attendance at the annual steering committee meetings; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare work plans and budget; coordinate  inputs; and consolidate reports;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define monitoring and evaluation system in conjunction with CHAI and the government;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist with preparation of extension manual and farmer training packages for maize and soy production;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support delivery of training to extension officers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Length of the project: It is anticipated that approximately 120 days of technical assistance per year will be provided by a team of advisors over a three year period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to apply&lt;/strong&gt;: Please send a recent version of your CV to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;Sarah_Owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Please note that all profiles are indicative only and therefore subject to change once the ToR is made available.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader for the Investment Design Process for Peace though Education</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-for-the-investment-design-process-for-peace-though-education</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 14:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-for-the-investment-design-process-for-peace-though-education</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectives of the role&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objective of the assignment is to assist DFAT in drafting an investment concept for an Australian Government investment in peace though education and lead the drafting of an investment design for six-year Australian Government aid investment program   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Length of the project&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Team Leader will be engaged for an initial nine month period with an option to extend up to a total of 12 months. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 10-year experience working in education programs, preferably conflict-sensitive education programs &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of the nature and history of conflicts in Muslim Mindanao &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of key players in Muslim Mindanao, along with a demonstrated network of contacts in ARMM, will be viewed positively &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have been substantially involved in an education or peace program design process; or service delivery in conflict zones &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have led or managed a team responsible for the design and/or implementation of a conflict-sensitive education program &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with and understanding of designs of donor supported conflict sensitive education programs in the Philippines or overseas &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in conducting analytical work and high quality technical writing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced degree in Education, Development, Economics, Political Science, Asian Studies, Peace and Conflict Studies or a field related to conflict sensitive development/education; University degree in above fields, combined with substantial relevant experience, may be considered in lieu of an advanced degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferably Filipino national and based in the Philippines, an international advisor may be considered&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deadline for Application: Please apply to: &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:katarzyna_rybak@dai.com&quot;&gt;katarzyna_rybak@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;strong&gt;4 August 2015&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Please note that all profiles are indicative only and therefore subject to change once the ToR is made available.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experts in SME Access to Finance, PSD, Public Private Partnerships, Macro Economic Analysis &amp; Financial Sector Policies</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-in-sme-access-to-finance-psd-public-private-partnerships-macro-economic-analysis-financial-sector-policies</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2015 14:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-in-sme-access-to-finance-psd-public-private-partnerships-macro-economic-analysis-financial-sector-policies</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;DAI Europe is a leading international developing consulting firm working throughout the developing world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due to our expanding portfolio we are looking to supplement our database of independent consultants for project work (not permanent posts).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We seek experienced independent consultants who specialise in the following areas: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SME access to finance &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Private sector development &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Public private partnerships (PPP)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Macroeconomic analysis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Financial sector policies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An excellent command of English is required and a good working knowledge of French, Spanish and/or Arabic would be an advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Work experience with the &lt;strong&gt;European Commission (EC)&lt;/strong&gt;, the &lt;strong&gt;European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD)&lt;/strong&gt; and the &lt;strong&gt;European Investment Bank (EIB)&lt;/strong&gt; is an advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like to be considered for inclusion in our Consultants’ Database please email your CV (preferably in EC format) to Nicolas Fichers (&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicolas_fichers@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicolas_fichers@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;) quoting reference: CV – Finance, PSD, PPP and Macroeconomy&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further information on &lt;strong&gt;DAI can be found at &lt;a href=&quot;http://dai.com/&quot;&gt;http://dai.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWP 2 Projects Review</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Beyond WTO Program (B-WTO) was developed in response to a request from the Government of Vietnam (GoV) for donor support to help with managing economic integration and the transition to a market economy following WTO accession. The B-WTO goal is “to strengthen government’s capacity to manage the integration of Vietnam into the global economy and the transition of Vietnam to a socialist market economy”. The immediate objective is “implementation of priority policy actions from the GoV’s Action Plan to enhance Vietnam’s capacity to sustain pro-poor growth (GAP)”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The remit of this project was a review of the 2nd annual work plan’s implementation (AWP2) of Phase 2 of the B-WTO in May 2013. The objectives of the review were to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the project implementation performance and project results relative to the logical framework targets and evaluation criteria. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the results achieved at the Component and Program’s level according to the Monitoring and Evaluation (M&amp;amp;E) framework of the Program.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify lessons learned from implementation, make recommendations for the remaining duration of the program and the Independent Completion Report process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program 2013 Performance and Quality Mapping Exercise</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID’s PNG Program is looking to improve its performance and quality (P&amp;amp;Q) standards and systems. The purpose of this project was to map the PNG Program’s current P&amp;amp;Q capacity and systems, to address the risk of AusAID being unable to demonstrate results for its increased investments in PNG over the next four years. Over the last several years, the PNG Program has undertaken a number of M&amp;amp;E assessments and reviews which have identified key strengths and challenges within the program. This project was intended to pick up where these assessments left off. Through a desk review and consultations with sector teams, the Review Team were to distil key P&amp;amp;Q risks and issues for the PNG Program. The Review Team’s brief included the provision of recommendations on priority activities to support sector approaches to M&amp;amp;E, strengthen the Program’s ability to collect evidence, provide critical analysis and report on results.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID required a consultant to assist with the development and finalisation of its Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework. Development of a humanitarian monitoring and evaluation framework is a key commitment outlined in AusAID’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy (HAP) and its associated Implementation Plan. In line with the agency focus on results reporting, the HAP and HAP Implementation Plan commit AusAID to develop a monitoring and evaluation framework to support the initial performance assessment framework contained within the HAP and AusAID annual reporting under the Comprehensive Aid Policy Framework.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key objective of this assignment was to build the Humanitarian program’s capacity for monitoring and reporting results by:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In consultation with AusAID’s Humanitarian team, redraft and finalise the Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework, to ensure it provides a platform to:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track implementation of key commitments in Australia’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy; and,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish a set of measurable humanitarian performance indicators (in addition to the two CAPF indicators) to enable AusAID to track achievements, lessons learned and to report on the results achieved from AusAID’s humanitarian work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of Pacific Forum Compact Reporting</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The purpose of the assignment was to examine country views of aid effectiveness and regional organisations expressed through Forum Compact reporting, particularly peer review of Forum Island Countries’ national development plan processes. The services provided included the preparation of a think piece which outlines key aid effectiveness issues arising from country reporting under the Compact reporting and discusses options for addressing these issues.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study on Community-based Social Protection</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/study-on-community-based-social-protection</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/study-on-community-based-social-protection</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Poverty and Social Analysis is the process of using and generating evidence on poverty throughout the aid management cycle. Most poverty and social analysis focuses on economic and human capital, but there are two oft neglected elements: voice and influence, and social capital. Yet more and more development practitioners are recognizing the importance of social capital, particularly informal social capital, in preventing and addressing poverty and vulnerability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This project supported AusAID to explore:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the role of informal social capital in the Fijian context and whether it lends itself to fair redistribution of resources and, if so, the ways in which AusAID can engage with local communities to strengthen existing social capital structures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;how such structures can enable the disempowered and poor to claim their entitlements in the three domains discussed in the PSA framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the potential challenges that can arise from such efforts. For instance, the poorest are often included on less favorable terms within social networks, and have access to fewer and lower-quality networks. Further, we need to better understand how poverty and disempowerment intersect with an absence of informal social capital, the repercussions this has, and the options available for tackling this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Provision of a Child Protection Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/provision-of-a-child-protection-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/provision-of-a-child-protection-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For this project HTSPE was contracted to provide a child protection specialist and handle all the associated management and administrative work. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The child protection specialist provided by HTSPE was required to work on an assignment designed to assist the Pacific Division (PACD) to improve its approach to child protection and managing risks to children. AusAID has a number of partners in the Pacific who work with children or come into contact with children through their activities. The AusAID-wide child protection stocktake, conducted in May 2013 found that there are a number of organisations funded by AusAID in the Pacific with a high or very high inherent child protection risk. Consistent with the stocktake report PACD proposes to escalate efforts to ensure partner organisations policies, procedures and practices are in accordance with AusAID’s Child Protection Policy 2013 and to make child protection a more explicit focus of PACD’s risk management system.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Environment and Biology Expert (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/opportunities/senior-environment-and-biology-expert-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 20:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/opportunities/senior-environment-and-biology-expert-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Expert 2 is expected to contribute the implementation of all of the related modules and the preparation of both training materials and Training Evaluation Report in the context of related chapter/s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in Biology, Ecology, Chemistry or other Natural Sciences related to assignment. In the absence of the degree required, at least 17 years of professional experience in the related areas is requested.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good command of both written and spoken English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General professional experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in the sector(s) related to the Lot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience in technical and/or scientific fields required for the implementation of the Water Framework Directive and/or Habitat Directive and/or other related Directives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 river basin management plans experience in terms of setting of environmental objectives and/or setting, design and upgrade of biological monitoring programme and/or execution and assessment of biological monitoring.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in development of measures for water pollution reduction and/or improving ecological status, and/or river basin characterisation/analysis will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in projects related to Integrated Water Resources Management will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
