<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 09:57:18 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert on Mediation</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-on-mediation</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-on-mediation</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final evaluation of th IfS/IcSO support under Articles 3 and 4 Mediation in beneficiary countries (2007-2018)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Context&lt;/strong&gt;
The Instrument contributing to Stability and Peace foresees &amp;lsquo;support, through the provision of technical and logistical assistance, for the efforts undertaken by international and regional organisations and by State and civil society actors in promoting confidence-building, mediation, dialogue and reconciliation.&amp;rsquo; (Art 3, 2 (a)), and &amp;lsquo;facilitating and building capacity in confidence-building, mediation, dialogue and reconciliation, with particular regard to emerging inter-community tensions&amp;rsquo; (Art 4, 1 (b)).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of the assignment&lt;/strong&gt;
This evaluation consists of a sector evaluation. The sector evaluation shall assess IfS/IcSP support to mediation, strictly within the scope of “mediation” as defined in the EU Concept of 2009. This evaluation will not assess the efficiency, effectiveness and impact of individual projects. The main objectives of this evaluation are to provide the relevant services of the European Union, the interested stakeholders and the wider public with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an overall independent assessment of the past performance of the IfS/IcSP support to mediation related projects and programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;key lessons and recommendations in order to improve current (if relevant) and future actions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In particular, this evaluation will serve the European Commission, the European External Action Service, and other relevant stakeholders with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an independent assessment of the overall IfS/IcSP support to mediation (2007-2018);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;key lessons and recommendations to FPI.2 in order to improve current and future support for mediation related interventions financed under the IcSP;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;recommendations to the European Commission on the best way to approach and improve its support to mediation overall.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main users of this evaluation will be the European Commission and the European External Action Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category I expert: Expert on Mediation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;:
At least a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Development, International Relations, Diplomacy, Social sciences, Law or other relevant field related to this assignment; or, in its absence, equivalent professional experience of 5 years (above the general professional experience duration fixed below) in a relevant area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years professional experience in the management and / or evaluation of projects in the fields of peacebuilding, dialogue and reconciliation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 8 years of professional experience in evaluation of or management of projects/programmes in the area of international peace processes, mediation, facilitation and dialogue in developing and/or fragile countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience monitoring/observing cease-fire/peace accords and agreements;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of experience of project cycle management (PCM) application, monitoring and evaluation of projects preferably in the field of crisis, post-crisis assistance or development, notably in fragile states and/or countries prone to political instability, man-made disasters, and in particular those funded by IfS/IcSP;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience conducting evaluation / reviews / assessment of large-scale donor funded projects or programmes in a conflict or conflict prone context.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communicating skills, in particular, liaising with different stakeholders (including diplomatic corps, Governmental officials, security agencies and civil society) as evidenced by previous assignments;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong capacity to quickly understand complex and changing circumstances as evidenced by previous assignments.
The following knowledge and experience will be an asset:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in evaluation of mediation support projects and/or other IfS or IcSP funded programmes or interventions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English (written and spoken), proved by at least a level CT2 in the Common European Framework of Reference for Languages, or equivalent system.
** Good command of French and Spanish (one or the other for each expert).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3776&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3776&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Peace-building Dialogue and Reconciliation (Team Leader)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-peace-building-dialogue</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 09:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-peace-building-dialogue</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final evaluation of th IfS/IcSO support under Articles 3 and 4 Mediation in beneficiary countries (2007-2018)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Context&lt;/strong&gt;
The Instrument contributing to Stability and Peace foresees &amp;lsquo;support, through the provision of technical and logistical assistance, for the efforts undertaken by international and regional organisations and by State and civil society actors in promoting confidence-building, mediation, dialogue and reconciliation.&amp;rsquo; (Art 3, 2 (a)), and &amp;lsquo;facilitating and building capacity in confidence-building, mediation, dialogue and reconciliation, with particular regard to emerging inter-community tensions&amp;rsquo; (Art 4, 1 (b)).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of the assignment&lt;/strong&gt;
This evaluation consists of a sector evaluation. The sector evaluation shall assess IfS/IcSP support to mediation, strictly within the scope of “mediation” as defined in the EU Concept of 2009. This evaluation will not assess the efficiency, effectiveness and impact of individual projects. The main objectives of this evaluation are to provide the relevant services of the European Union, the interested stakeholders and the wider public with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an overall independent assessment of the past performance of the IfS/IcSP support to mediation related projects and programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;key lessons and recommendations in order to improve current (if relevant) and future actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In particular, this evaluation will serve the European Commission, the European External Action Service, and other relevant stakeholders with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an independent assessment of the overall IfS/IcSP support to mediation (2007-2018);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;key lessons and recommendations to FPI.2 in order to improve current and future support for mediation related interventions financed under the IcSP;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;recommendations to the European Commission on the best way to approach and improve its support to mediation overall.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main users of this evaluation will be the European Commission and the European External Action Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category I expert: Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;: 
At least a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Development, International Relations, Diplomacy, Social sciences, Law or other relevant field related to this assignment; or, in its absence, equivalent professional experience of 5 years (above the general professional experience duration fixed below) in a relevant area. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: 
At least 12 years professional experience in the management and / or evaluation of projects in the fields of peacebuilding, dialogue and reconciliation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 8 years of professional experience in evaluation of or management of projects/programmes in the area of international peace processes, mediation, facilitation and dialogue in developing and/or fragile countries; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience monitoring/observing/mediating cease-fire/peace accords and agreements; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of experience of project cycle management (PCM) application, monitoring and evaluation of projects preferably in the field of crisis, conflict prevention and crisis preparedness, notably in fragile states and/or countries prone to political instability, and in particular those related to peace mediation; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience conducting evaluation / reviews / assessment of large-scale donor funded projects or programmes in a conflict or conflict prone context.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Soft skills&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communicating skills, in particular, liaising with different stakeholders (including diplomatic corps, Governmental officials, security agencies and civil society) as evidenced by previous assignments; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the management of complex and politically sensitive projects in a conflict or conflict prone context as well as a track-record of successful coordination and team management. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong capacity to quickly understand complex and changing circumstances as evidenced by previous assignments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following knowledge and experience will be an asset: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in evaluation of mediation support projects and/or IfS or IcSP funded programmes or interventions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English (written and spoken), proved by at least a level CT2 in the Common European Framework of Reference for Languages, or equivalent system. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good command of French and Spanish (one or the other for each expert).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3776&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3776&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Economics Experts</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/economics-experts</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 13:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/economics-experts</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to the Ministry of Economy of the Republic of Belarus on Analysis of the Potential GDP and Output Gap Estimations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To support the Ministry of Economy of the Republic of Belarus on analysis of the potential GDP and Output Gap Estimations, the experts are expected to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide lecture and workshop exercises on practical application of econometric models of GDP growth decomposition and output gap calculations among governmental authorities involved in policymaking. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Examine various methods of output gap estimation and forecasting to justify most balanced socio-economic development scenario.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elaborate guidelines for selection of preferred method based on assigned tasks knowing strengths and weaknesses of different univariate and multivariate methods.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practice applications of non-structural univariate methods for the estimation of potential output to Belarusian data (The Hodrick and Prescott filter, the Baxter and King filter, the Beveridge-Nelson decomposition, the unobserved components decomposition, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practice application of multivariate methods for the estimation of potential output and cycle extraction techniques to Belarusian data (the multivariate Hodrick-Prescott filter, the multivariate Kalman filter, etc.), namely expansion of univariate methods with Okun’s law, Phillips curve, NAIRU, and business-cycle indicators.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practice application of structural approaches (methods based on an aggregate production function)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To prepare guidelines for Belarusian policymakers for application of output gap estimation and forecasting, economic growth decomposition.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experts should have a background in principles, methods and interpretations of economic fluctuations in order to make correct assumptions and build efficient model corresponding to the current political and economic targets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree, preferably in economics or other relevant field or, in its absence, at least 5 additional years of professional experience on top of the 12 required under general professional experience above;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of specific professional experience in area of macroeconomic policy, macroeconomic analysis and modelling, econometrics;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the use of univariative and multivarative methods;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in working in EViews 9.0/10.0&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in working with other econometric software would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;One *&lt;/em&gt; candidate should have the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the research or publications on the concepts of potential GDP, output gap and business cycle fluctuations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The *&lt;em&gt;second *&lt;/em&gt; should have:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in applied econometrics in forecasting GDP, trade, inflation, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fluency in both written and spoken English;
Knowledge of Russian would be an asset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link and attach your CV in EC format &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3769&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3769&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert Senior dans les domaines de l’enseignement fondamental / primaire, de l’éducation, la coopération et du développement</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-senior-dans-les-domaines-de-lenseignement-fondamental-primaire-de-leducation-la-cooperation-et-du-developpement</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-senior-dans-les-domaines-de-lenseignement-fondamental-primaire-de-leducation-la-cooperation-et-du-developpement</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Programme d&amp;#39;appui a l&amp;#39;enseignement fondamental au Mali (PROF)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif général&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif général de la prestation est celui du PROF à savoir &amp;ldquo;contribuer au renforcement du système éducatif malien dans l&amp;#39;enseignement fondamental&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif particulier&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif particulier de la prestation est de fournir aux différentes parties prenantes du PROF les éléments leur permettant de se situer quant à l’état d’avancement du programme vers les résultats attendus et de prendre les mesures nécessaires pour l’atteinte des objectifs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Services demandés&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Le programme sera apprécié sur la base des cinq critères types du CAD de l&amp;#39;OCDE, à savoir : pertinence, efficacité, efficience, viabilité et impact. En outre, deux critères d’évaluation spécifiques à l’Union européenne seront examinés :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;La valeur ajoutée européenne du programme, sous l&amp;#39;angle de sa conception comme de sa mise en œuvre;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;La cohérence du programme lui-même, par rapport à la stratégie poursuivie par l’Union européenne au Mali et à celle des États membres.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;expert en charge de l&amp;#39;évaluation à mi-parcours devra répondre aux questions d’évaluation spécifiques formulées ci-après. Ces questions à étudier sont indicatives au stade de la signature du contrat. Elles peuvent faire l’objet de discussions avec l’expert au cours de la phase documentaire et seront alors arrêtées. Une fois arrêtées, elles ont valeur contractuelle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KE1 (Cat 1) dans les domaines de l’enseignement fondamental / primaire, de l’éducation, la coopération et du développement&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Profil par expert ou expertise demandée: catégorie et durée de l&amp;#39;expérience équivalente: Catégorie I soit au moins 12 années d&amp;#39;expérience dans les secteurs concernés par le lot 4.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formation&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Condition minimum&lt;/strong&gt; 
Un niveau d’enseignement correspondant à un cycle complet d’études post baccalauréat de quatre années ou plus, sanctionné par un diplôme de fin d’études. Une expérience professionnelle générale pertinente de 5 ans supplémentaires devra être justifiée en cas de diplôme de niveau inférieur.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Condition minimum&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;12 ans d’expérience pertinente dans les secteurs concernés par le lot 4.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conditions préférables&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience dans le secteur de l&amp;#39;éducation, en particulier dans l&amp;#39;enseignement fondamental/primaire au sein d’un service/d&amp;#39;une organisation en charge de ce domaine en tant qu’assistant technique, en tant que contractuel ou en tant que cadre national ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience dans le secteur de l&amp;#39;éducation, en particulier dans l&amp;#39;enseignement fondamental/primaire au sein d&amp;#39;un projet de coopération/développement en tant que chef de projet ou responsable d&amp;#39;une composante ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience dans l&amp;#39;identification et la formulation de projets de coopération et de développement, en particulier dans le domaine de l&amp;#39;éducation ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience dans l’évaluation de projets, en particulier dans le domaine de l&amp;#39;éducation ;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;La connaissance des principes et des méthodes de la Commission européenne.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;La connaissance du contexte malien serait un atout&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissances linguistiques&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parfaite maîtrise du français à l’écrit et à l’oral.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, attaching your CV in EC format &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3768&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3768&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Communication Strategies and Implementation Plans, Public Relations or Journalism</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-communication-strategies-and-implementation-plans-public-relations-or-journalism</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 10:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-communication-strategies-and-implementation-plans-public-relations-or-journalism</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preparation of the service tender dossier &amp;lsquo;Support to Communication and Visibility Actions for the Ghana Employment and Social Protection (GESP) Programme&amp;rsquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;overall objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the assignment is to support the European Union Delegation to Ghana (EUD) with the preparation of the Terms of Reference for the tender dossier to award the service contract “Support to Communication and Visibility actions for the Ghana Employment and Social Protection Programme (GESP)”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives are to: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyse the needs of the GESP Programme, in terms of communication and visibility;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Propose possible areas of support and actions to be covered under the above-mentioned service contract.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KE1 (Cat 1) in communication strategies and implementation plans, public relations, journalism or other relevant fields&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent English language skills both oral and written are required. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in design and implementation of communication and visibility actions in the context of EU funded aid modalities (preparation of tender and grants projects, ToR etc.);&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in social projects communication;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Experience in the area of communication in developing countries; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Experience in design and implementation of awareness campaigns.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please apply via the following link, attaching your CV in EC format
&lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/requisitions/RequisitionView.jsp?act=show&amp;amp;id=3764&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/requisitions/RequisitionView.jsp?act=show&amp;amp;id=3764&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KE 1 (cat. 1) - Spécialiste en sécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle (SAN), transferts sociaux, lien urgence/développement</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/ke-1-cat-1-specialiste-en-securite-alimentaire-et-nutritionnelle-san-transferts-sociaux-lien-urgence-developpement</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 08:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/ke-1-cat-1-specialiste-en-securite-alimentaire-et-nutritionnelle-san-transferts-sociaux-lien-urgence-developpement</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assistance technique au Haut-commissariat à l&amp;#39;initiative 3N dans le domaine de la sécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle – Appui complémentaire au Contrat de réforme sectorielle Sécurité alimentaire, nutritionnelle et développement agricole durable&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général&lt;/strong&gt; de la prestation est d&amp;#39;appuyer les efforts du gouvernement de la République du Niger à éradiquer la pauvreté, à promouvoir une croissance durable et inclusive et à consolider et améliorer la gouvernance démocratique et économique. Les objectifs spécifiques de la présente prestation sont les suivants :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Soutenir le Haut-Commissariat dans son mandat de pilotage stratégique du secteur de la Sécurité Alimentaire et Nutritionnelle et du développement Agricole Durable et de coordination et suivi de la mise en oeuvre du Plan d’Action 2016-2020 de l’I3N, en particulier des programmes stratégiques 9,10, 11;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Appuyer le HC3N dans le suivi des engagements dans le cadre du CRS SANAD en particulier ceux relevant des institutions de mise en oeuvre des Programmes stratégiques 9, 10, 11, dans le domaine de la réponse à l’insécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle conjoncturelle et chronique;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Renforcer la réflexion et la veille stratégique et technique dans le secteur SANAD en lien avec la prévention et gestion des crises (résultant de chocs climatiques et sécuritaires) et la protection sociale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KE 1 (cat. 1) - Spécialiste en sécurité alimentaire et nutritionnelle (SAN), transferts sociaux, lien urgence/développement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master en agronomie, économie agricole/rurale, sécurité alimentaire ou autre discipline équivalente&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 10 ans d&amp;#39;expérience en Afrique sub-Saharienne;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 12 ans d&amp;#39;expérience comme appui technique, institutionel et de renforcement de capacité dans le domaine de la sécurité alimentaire et nutritionelle et dans le domaine des transferts sociaux;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10 ans d&amp;#39;expérience en tant qu&amp;#39;appui institutionelle pour la gouvernance et le renforcement des capacités d&amp;#39;acteurs nationaux dans le secteur SAN;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 ans d&amp;#39;expérience en analyse et système d&amp;#39;information sur la SAN, l&amp;#39;économies des ménages et moyes d&amp;#39;existence;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 ans d&amp;#39;expérience dans les transferts sociaux contre la vulnérabilité alimentaire et nutritionelle;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 ans d&amp;#39;expérience en réponse d&amp;#39;urgence aux crises et nexus humanitaire-développement;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 ans d&amp;#39;expérience dans la conception stratégique et programmatique pour l&amp;#39;appui au développement et pour la prévention et gestion de crises humanitaires;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarité avec les modalités de l&amp;#39;Union Européenne en matière d&amp;#39;appui budgétaire sectoriel;
*Connaissance du contexte institutionelle SAN du Niger, des structures et des acteurs impliqués dans les actions concernées.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellente maÎtrise de la langue francaise; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bon niveau en anglais (B2).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please upload your CV in EC format at &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3762&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3762&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KE2 Civil Works/Infrastructure Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/ke2-civil-works-infrastructure-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 08:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/ke2-civil-works-infrastructure-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance II to the Department of Projects of the Planning and Cooperation Directorate of the Ministry of Health&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project&amp;rsquo;s objective is to contribute to the improvement of the population health status by increased access to health care by the population, with special attention to the poorest and to gender specific needs, in line with the Government&amp;rsquo;s 2015-2020 Five-Year Plan priorities. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specifically, it involves:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fully upgrading Manhica District Hospital and Gilé Rural Hospital infrastructure&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stabilization of qualified health staff through increase of number of critical staff housing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reinforced capacity of the Department of Projects within the Ministry of Health in sector planing and management of investments&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The services will be carried out in the fields of financial and technical management, communication and quality insurance of the construction processes related to the Manhica and Gilé Project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KE2 Civil Works/Infrastructure Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master or equivalent experience in engineering or architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5 years in the field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 years proven experience in coordination and/or management of civil works or infrastructure projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in management of contracts or project under international procedures (EU or FIDIC, World Bank, ADB, other) is mandatory&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portuguese (fluent), English (good knowledge)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please upload your CV in EC format at &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3761&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3761&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KE2 Expert in Sustainable Development, NRM or Environment (Cat 2)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/ke2-expert-in-sustainable-development-nrm-or-environment-cat-2</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 13:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/ke2-expert-in-sustainable-development-nrm-or-environment-cat-2</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ex-post Evaluation of the project &amp;lsquo;Support for the Implementation of Mauritius Strategy for Small Islands Developing States in the ESA-IO Region&amp;rsquo; project (also known as ISLANDS Phase I &amp;amp; II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective of the evaluation&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of the ex-post evaluation of the ISLANDS Programme is to provide the IOC and the European Union, with necessary information on the performance of the project, both under Phase I and Phase II.  These results will be used in the formulation and implementation of an 11 the EDF project under the Eastern and South African and Indian ocean region Regional Indicative Programme for island developing states.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This evaluation will serve to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Make an overall independent assessment about the past performance of the project, paying particular attention to the efficiency and effectiveness of the project actions against its objectives, as well as indications of impacts and outcomes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify key lessons learnt and propose practical recommendations for followup actions that can be included in the new 11th EDF regional project on SIDS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Validate the final findings of the ex-post evaluation with relevant stakeholders (National Focal Points of countries covered, IOC Secretariat and EU)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific aspects to be evaluated&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The consultants are requested to verify, analyse and assess the integration and impact of cross cutting issue in the project, in particular gender equality and protection of the environment.  The consultants are required to use their professional judgement and experience to review all relevant factors and to bring these to the attention of the IOC and European Union.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KE2 Expert in Sustainable Development, NRM or Environment (Cat 2)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum requirements of the team&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Educational qualifications at Masters’ level in environment, or sustainable development, or natural resource management &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience in evaluation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience in climate change and sustainable development &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least one member of the team should have working experience in Sustainable Development Goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least one member of the team should have working experience in Small Island State issues &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least one member of the team should have good knowledge of the Eastern and Southern African and Indian Ocean region&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills of the team&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in written and spoken English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in written and spoken French&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please apply via the following link, sumbitting your CV in EC format &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3760&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3760&lt;/a&gt;)    &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KE1 Team Leader (Cat 1)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/ke1-team-leader-cat-1</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 13:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/ke1-team-leader-cat-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ex-post Evaluation of the project &amp;lsquo;Support for the Implementation of Mauritius Strategy for Small Islands Developing States in the ESA-IO Region&amp;rsquo; project (also known as ISLANDS Phase I &amp;amp; II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective of the evaluation&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of the ex-post evaluation of the ISLANDS Programme is to provide the IOC and the European Union, with necessary information on the performance of the project, both under Phase I and Phase II.  These results will be used in the formulation and implementation of an 11 the EDF project under the Eastern and South African and Indian ocean region Regional Indicative Programme for island developing states.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This evaluation will serve to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make an overall independent assessment about the past performance of the project, paying particular attention to the efficiency and effectiveness of the project actions against its objectives, as well as indications of impacts and outcomes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify key lessons learnt and propose practical recommendations for followup actions that can be included in the new 11th EDF regional project on SIDS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Validate the final findings of the ex-post evaluation with relevant stakeholders (National Focal Points of countries covered, IOC Secretariat and EU)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific aspects to be evaluated&lt;/strong&gt; 
The consultants are requested to verify, analyse and assess the integration and impact of cross cutting issue in the project, in particular gender equality and protection of the environment.  The consultants are required to use their professional judgement and experience to review all relevant factors and to bring these to the attention of the IOC and European Union&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KE1 Team Leader (Cat 1)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum requirements of the team  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Educational qualifications at masters level in environment, or sustainable development,or natural resource management &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience in evaluation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience in climate change and sustainable development &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least one member of the team should have working experience in Sustainable Development Goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least one member of the team should have working experience in Small Island State issues &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least one member of the team should have good knowledge of the Eastern and Southern African and Indian Ocean region&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills of the team&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in written and spoken English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in written and spoken French&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please apply via the following link, submitting your CV in EC format &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3760&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3760&lt;/a&gt;)   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 2 – Catégorie II, Evaluation Finale de la Decision AO/FED/2009/21 - 626</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-categorie-ii-evaluation-finale-de-la-decision-ao-fed-2009-21-626</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 13:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-categorie-ii-evaluation-finale-de-la-decision-ao-fed-2009-21-626</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation Finale de la Decision AO/FED/2009/21 - 626&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cette évaluation est principalement vouée à fournir aux services compétents de l’Union Européenne et aux parties prenantes intéressées:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une analyse globale et indépendante de la performance de la décision AO/FED/2009/21-626 “Développement des capacités institutionnelles dans le cadre de la modernisation de la fonction publique en matière de planification en Angola”, en prêtant une attention particulière a ses résultats en comparaison avec les objectifs fixes ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Des leçons et des recommandations de manière à améliorer, le cas échéant, les actions futures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;En particulier, cette évaluation servira à comprendre la performance de l’action, ses facteurs déterminants et ceux qui ont freiné l’obtention des résultats aussi bien que les perspectives de durabilité de ses résultats, de manière ont server de base à la planification des actions et des interventions futures de l’UE dans le même secteur.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les principaux utilisateurs de cette évaluation seront la délégation de l’UE en Angola, les services compétents de l’UE a Bruxelles, le Ministère de l’Economie et du Plan de la République d’Angola &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2 – Catégorie II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formation académique de niveau universitaire, de préférence en sciences sociales, économie, science politique, ou autre discipline pertinente ou équivalente. Une spécialisation dans le domaine de l’évaluation et gestion de projets sera considérée un avantage ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle en gestion et/ou évaluation de projets de développement de minimum 5 ans. Une expérience dans les pays ACP sera considérée un avantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle en tant qu’évaluateur de projets de développement (minimum 5 évaluations) ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience et connaissances des politiques, règles et procédures de gestion des financements du FED ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience préalable en Angola en tant qu’expert en évaluations sera considérée un avantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellente maitrise du portugais, lu, parlé, écrit (le rapport final devra être rédigé en portugais)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne connaissance de l’anglais et/ou du français lus, écrits, parlés.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef de mission, Evaluation Finale de la Decision AO/FED/2009/21 - 626</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 13:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation Finale de la Decision AO/FED/2009/21 - 626&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cette évaluation est principalement vouée à fournir aux services compétents de l’Union Européenne et aux parties prenantes intéressées:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une analyse globale et indépendante de la performance de la décision AO/FED/2009/21-626 “Développement des capacités institutionnelles dans le cadre de la modernisation de la fonction publique en matière de planification en Angola”, en prêtant une attention particulière a ses résultats en comparaison avec les objectifs fixes ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Des leçons et des recommandations de manière à améliorer, le cas échéant, les actions futures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;En particulier, cette évaluation servira à comprendre la performance de l’action, ses facteurs déterminants et ceux qui ont freiné l’obtention des résultats aussi bien que les perspectives de durabilité de ses résultats, de manière ont server de base à la planification des actions et des interventions futures de l’UE dans le même secteur.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les principaux utilisateurs de cette évaluation seront la délégation de l’UE en Angola, les services compétents de l’UE a Bruxelles, le Ministère de l’Economie et du Plan de la République d’Angola &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chef de mission – Catégorie I&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formation académique de niveau universitaire, de préférence en sciences sociales, économie, science politique, ou autre discipline pertinente ou équivalente ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle en gestion et/ou évaluation de projets de développement de minimum 10 ans, dont 3 ans dans des pays ACP ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle en tant qu’évaluateur et coordinateur de minimum 10 évaluations de projets. L’évaluation de projets dans le domaine de la réforme institutionnelle et d’appui aux services de l’ON du FED sera considérée un avantage ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance approfondie des politiques, règles et procédures de gestion des financements du FED ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Forte capacité analytique et de synthèse ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience préalable en Angola en tant qu’expert en évaluations sera considérée un avantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellente maitrise du portugais, lu, parlé, écrit (le rapport final devra être rédigé en portugais)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne connaissance de l’anglais et/ou du français lus, écrits, parlés.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert in Public Health, Monitoring and Evaluation</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-public-health-monitoring-and-evaluation</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 12:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-public-health-monitoring-and-evaluation</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation of the Programme in support for the Health Sector II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The consultants will provide clear advice on the Program´s outcomes and the sustainability of the actions and tools developed as part of PASS II. He will conduct a sound analysis of the Program within the health sector in Angola in order to assess key factors influencing sustainability issues and produce recommendations to reinforce the sustainability and the ownership by MINSA.  They will assess the effectiveness of the Program´s interventions in achieving the goal and objectives set in the original Financing Agreement, which are: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Overall objective: to contribute to improved health conditions of the population, especially women and children, with a focus in the provinces of Huambo, Bié, Benguela, Huíla e Luanda. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific objectives: 1: To strengthen MOH capacity, at central level, in strategic and operational planning, budgeting, organization of the health system, training and management of Human Resources for Health, coordination, advocacy and monitoring and evaluation; 2: To strengthen Provincial Health Directorates capacity and leadership in planning, budgeting, development of the health system (including training and management of HRH) and management of activities, in accordance with the ongoing administrative decentralization and the Revitalization of the Municipal Health System processes; 3: To improve the accessibility and quality of the basic package of health services provided to the population at municipal level, by reinforcing the availability of good quality essential maternal, newborn and children health services, with a specific focus in the provinces of Huambo, Bie, Benguela, Huíla and Luanda.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in Public Health, Monitoring and Evaluation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6-year experience in Public Health, Monitoring and Evaluation. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MSc in Public Health, Public Administration, or equivalent from a recognized University.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience of at least 6 years as Monitoring and Evaluation consultant in the public health sector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with at least 2 different organizations in conducting evaluations and assessments of public health interventions. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Background working in post conflict environments and fragile states in the health sector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with EU funded programs: EDF, Global Budget, etc. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity and experience with EU programs of support to the health sector. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong interpersonal communications and writing skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical and synthesis skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Negotiation skills to develop consensus around policy strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in Portuguese &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent Portuguese written skills / English written skills desirable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:almudena_salmeron@dai.com&quot;&gt;Almudena_Salmeron@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:fwcsieaLot4@dai.com&quot;&gt;FWCSIEALot4@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; in cc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Public Health, Health Policy and Planning</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-public-health-health-policy-and-planning</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 11:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-public-health-health-policy-and-planning</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation of the Programme in support for the Health Sector II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The consultants will provide clear advice on the Program´s outcomes and the sustainability of the actions and tools developed as part of PASS II. He will conduct a sound analysis of the Program within the health sector in Angola in order to assess key factors influencing sustainability issues and produce recommendations to reinforce the sustainability and the ownership by MINSA.  They will assess the effectiveness of the Program´s interventions in achieving the goal and objectives set in the original Financing Agreement, which are: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Overall objective: to contribute to improved health conditions of the population, especially women and children, with a focus in the provinces of Huambo, Bié, Benguela, Huíla e Luanda. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific objectives: 1: To strengthen MOH capacity, at central level, in strategic and operational planning, budgeting, organization of the health system, training and management of Human Resources for Health, coordination, advocacy and monitoring and evaluation; 2: To strengthen Provincial Health Directorates capacity and leadership in planning, budgeting, development of the health system (including training and management of HRH) and management of activities, in accordance with the ongoing administrative decentralization and the Revitalization of the Municipal Health System processes; 3: To improve the accessibility and quality of the basic package of health services provided to the population at municipal level, by reinforcing the availability of good quality essential maternal, newborn and children health services, with a specific focus in the provinces of Huambo, Bie, Benguela, Huíla and Luanda.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Public Health, Health Policy and Planning&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12-year experience in Public Health.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MSc in Public Health, Health Policy and Planning, Health Services Management, or equivalent from a recognized University.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience of at least 12 years as public health expert / consultant in developing countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with at least 3 different organizations in conducting health systems reviews, health sector reforms, strategic planning and health services evaluations. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Background working in post conflict environments and fragile states in the health sector.Experience working with EU funded programs: EDF, Global Budget, etc. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience in Angola. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity and experience with EU programs of support to the health sector in Angola and other countries. Strong analytical and synthesis skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Negotiation skills to develop consensus around policy strategies. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent leadership skills, ability to exercise a significant degree of initiative and to work effectively with stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work with individuals and teams in completing tasks that are urgent, high priority and sensitive, and ability to deliver high quality work on tight timelines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong interpersonal communications and writing skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in Portuguese.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent Portuguese written skills / English written skills desirable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:almudena_salmeron@dai.com&quot;&gt;Almudena_Salmeron@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:fwciealot4@dai.com&quot;&gt;FWCSIEALot4@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; in cc.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert technique en services d&#39;appui à l&#39;industrie</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-technique-en-services-dappui-a-lindustrie</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 08:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-technique-en-services-dappui-a-lindustrie</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assistance technique pour la mise en oeuvre de la reforme des centres techniques sectoriels en Tunisie&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contribuer au développement des performances des centres techniques sectoriels en les rendant à même d’assumer convenablement leur rôle de soutien et de développement du secteur industriel et d’être des contributeurs efficaces et reconnus au renforcement de l’industrie tunisienne.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert technique en services d&amp;#39;appui à l&amp;#39;industrie&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire dans un domaine pertinent (ingénieur, gestion ou équivalent), ou expérience équivalente (minimum 2 ans en plus des 12 ans demandés ci-dessous).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle d&amp;#39;au moins 12 ans au sein de structures publiques ou privées d&amp;#39;appui technologique à l’industrie avec un degré croissant de responsabilité technique (Management, organisation, planification et contrôle des activités d&amp;#39;une équipe d&amp;#39;expert).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;incluant une expérience pratique dans l’élaboration et la production des documents de planification et de budget d&amp;#39;investissements;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir des aptitudes à communiquer et à animer des réunions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ayant une expérience d&amp;#39;au moins 3 ans dans des postes de chef de département technique au sein de centres techniques ou des institutions similaires.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ayant animé au moins un séminaire/atelier pour un auditoire non spécialisé.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience de travail en Tunisie ou dans un pays du voisinage sud.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonne connaissance de la langue française parlée et écrite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:almudena_salmeron@dai.com&quot;&gt;Almudena_Salmeron@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef de mission, expert en management d&#39;institutions d&#39;appui technologique à l&#39;industrie</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-expert-en-management-dinstitutions-dappui-technologique-a-lindustrie</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 07:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-expert-en-management-dinstitutions-dappui-technologique-a-lindustrie</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assistance technique pour la mise en oeuvre de la reforme des centres techniques sectoriels en Tunisie&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contribuer au développement des performances des centres techniques sectoriels en les rendant à même d’assumer convenablement leur rôle de soutien et de développement du secteur industriel et d’être des contributeurs efficaces et reconnus au renforcement de l’industrie tunisienne.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chef de mission, expert en management d&amp;#39;institutions d&amp;#39;appui technologique à l&amp;#39;industrie&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire de niveau Master dans un domaine pertinent (ingénieur, gestion ou équivalent), ou expérience équivalente (minimum 2 ans en plus des 12 ans demandés ci-dessous).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle d&amp;#39;au moins 12 ans au sein de structures publiques ou privées d&amp;#39;appui technologique à l’industrie avec un degré croissant de responsabilité, démontrant des connaissances en planification stratégique, management financier et de ressources humaines;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ayant une expérience pratique avérée dans l’élaboration et la production des documents de planification.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ayant une expérience d&amp;#39;au moins 3 ans dans des postes de management senior au sein de centres techniques ou des institutions similaires1;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ayant mené au moins une mission d’expertise en tant que chef de mission;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ayant participé à un projet d’appui à une structure type centre technique;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ayant une expérience de travail en Tunisie ou dans un pays du voisinage sud;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonne connaissance de la langue anglaise parlée et écrite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonne connaissance de la langue française parlée et écrite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to [Almudena Salmeron (mailto:&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:almudena_salmeron@dai.com&quot;&gt;almudena_salmeron@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;)]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PFM Expert (Category III)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/pfm-expert-category-iii</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 07:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/pfm-expert-category-iii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of the project are to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve framework for corruption prevention, in particular through increasing transparency and detection of corruption, improving handling and follow up of corruption reports, and strengthening the controlling regime for political parties&amp;#39; financing.
Improve framework for corruption repression, in particular through improving efficiency and effectiveness of criminal investigations against corruption; and supporting a good track record of investigated cases submitted to the prosecution services.
Improve framework for awareness of corruption, in particular through encouraging civil society and the general public to report corruption cases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master’s degree at University Level in economics or related, or, in its absence, at least 5 years&amp;#39; equivalent professional experience in the sectors related to PFM;
At least 3 years&amp;#39; general experience in public finance management;
Major contribution under at least one EU budget support programmes reviews, preferably in relation to financial management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3644&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3644&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rule of Law Expert (Category III)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/rule-of-law-expert-category-iii</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 07:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/rule-of-law-expert-category-iii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of the project are to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve framework for corruption prevention, in particular through increasing transparency and detection of corruption, improving handling and follow up of corruption reports, and strengthening the controlling regime for political parties&amp;#39; financing.
Improve framework for corruption repression, in particular through improving efficiency and effectiveness of criminal investigations against corruption; and supporting a good track record of investigated cases submitted to the prosecution services.
Improve framework for awareness of corruption, in particular through encouraging civil society and the general public to report corruption cases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master’s degree at University Level in political or social sciences/law/another relevant discipline, or, in its absence, at least 5 years&amp;#39; equivalent professional experience in the sectors related to the reinforcement of the rule of law and administration of justice;
At least 3 years&amp;#39; general experience in the rule of law, administration of justice or the public sector;
Major contribution under at least one EU budget support programmes reviews, preferably in relation to rule of law.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3644&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3644&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader (Category II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-category-ii-1</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 07:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-category-ii-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of the project are to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve framework for corruption prevention, in particular through increasing transparency and detection of corruption, improving handling and follow up of corruption reports, and strengthening the controlling regime for political parties&amp;#39; financing.
Improve framework for corruption repression, in particular through improving efficiency and effectiveness of criminal investigations against corruption; and supporting a good track record of investigated cases submitted to the prosecution services.
Improve framework for awareness of corruption, in particular through encouraging civil society and the general public to report corruption cases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications Required:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master’s degree at University Level in political or social sciences/law/another relevant discipline, or, in its absence, at least 8 years&amp;#39; equivalent professional experience in the sectors related to the reinforcement of the rule of law and administration of justice;
At least 6 years&amp;#39; general experience in the rule of law sector;
Major contribution under at least three EU budget support programmes reviews, preferably in relation to rule of law;
Knowledge of prevention, repression, awareness of corruption will be considered as an asset;
Very good knowledge of English language, including effective spoken presentation and written reporting abilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3644&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3644&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experts in Human Rights, Migration, Justice, Decentralization and Civil Society</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-in-human-rights-migration-justice-decentralization-and-civil-society</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2018 16:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-in-human-rights-migration-justice-decentralization-and-civil-society</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In readiness for projects announced under FWC SIEA 1018 Lot 3 &lt;strong&gt;DAI Europe&lt;/strong&gt; would like to invite potential candidates to apply for future short and long-term assignments in the following technical areas:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Human rights, Democracy &amp;amp; Rule of Law (minorities inclusion, elections, democratisation, media, justice/penitentiary/police reform, public administration etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Civil Society (trainings, needs diagnostic of CSOs etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Decentralization (community-based development, local authority etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Migration (legal migration, mobility, human trafficking, asylum etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conflict Resolution, Peace &amp;amp; Security (DDR, SALW, SSR, land mines, rehabilitation and demobilisation etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kindly note that this is a general call for experts with expertise relevant to &lt;strong&gt;FWC SIEA 2018 Lot 3&lt;/strong&gt; and not a call for a specific mission or project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Requirements for Category I (Senior) Experts&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in areas related to the above, including Human Rights, Politics, Economics, Law, Rule of Law, Conflict Studies or similar. In its absence, must have at least 18 years of professional work experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years&amp;#39; experience related to policy development, public administration and institutional reform, capacity building of civil society and government or similar;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience with at least 1 assignment funded by the European Union (EC, EIB, EBRD etc);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Requirements for Category II (Mid-level) Experts&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in in areas related to the above, including Human Rights, Politics, Economics, Law, Rule of Law, Conflict Studies or similar. In its absence, must have at least 12 years of professional work experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years&amp;#39; experience related to policy development, public administration and institutional reform, capacity building of civil society and government or similar;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Requirements for Category III (Junior) Experts&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in in areas related to the above, including Human Rights, Politics, Economics, Law, Rule of Law, Conflict Studies or similar. In its absence, must have at least 6 years of professional work experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years&amp;#39; experience related to policy development, public administration and institutional reform, capacity building of civil society and government or similar;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in being considered for these opportunities please apply via &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3642&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3642&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experts in Infrastructure, Energy, Private Sector Development and Sustainable Growth</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-in-infrastructure-energy-private-sector-development-and-sustainable-growth</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2018 15:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-in-infrastructure-energy-private-sector-development-and-sustainable-growth</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In readiness for projects announced under FWC SIEA 1018 Lot 2 &lt;strong&gt;DAI Europe&lt;/strong&gt; would like to invite potential candidates to apply for future short and long-term assignments in the following technical areas:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transport &amp;amp; Infrastructure (roads, railways, harbours, airports, buildings, inter-modal infrastructure etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Digital Technologies (cybersecurity, data protection, broadband, surveillance etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Earth Observation (satellite data, policy and analysis)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Urban Development &amp;amp; Cities (smart cities, social housing, mobility, urban resilience etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sustainable Energy (renewable energies, power grids, energy efficiency etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nuclear Safety (Safety, decommissioning, waste disposal etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sustainable Waste Management &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Private Sector (SMEs, commercial banking, PPPs etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trade (customs, integration, SPS, Barriers to trade, metrology, intellectual property, competition etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employment Creation (labour market analysis, wage policy, trade unions, job creation etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kindly note that this is a general call for experts with expertise relevant to &lt;strong&gt;FWC SIEA 2018 Lot 2&lt;/strong&gt; and not a call for a specific mission or project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Requirements for Category I (Senior) Experts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in areas related to the above, including Engineering, Banking and Finance, Business Administration, Data management or similar. In its absence, must have at least 18 years of professional work experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years&amp;#39; experience related to infrastructure, energy, private sector development or sustainable growth;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience with at least 1 assignment funded by the European Union (EC, EIB, EBRD etc).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Requirements for Category II (Mid-level) Experts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in in areas related to the above, including Engineering, Banking and Finance, Business Administration, Data management or similar. In its absence, must have at least 12 years of professional work experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years&amp;#39; experience related to infrastructure, energy, private sector development or sustainable growth.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Requirements for Category III (Junior) Experts&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in in areas related to the above, including Engineering, Banking and Finance, Business Administration, Data management or similar. In its absence, must have at least 6 years of professional work experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years&amp;#39; experience related to infrastructure, energy, private sector development or sustainable growth.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in being considered for these opportunities please apply via &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3641&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3641&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
