<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 16:26:59 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security Expert (CAT I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/security-expert-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 16:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/security-expert-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Study to identify areas of beneficial cooperation between CARIFORM and Latin America in the area of Crime and Security&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To undertake a study to identify possible areas of beneficial cooperation between CARIFORUM and Latin America, including concrete entry points for Caribbean participation in existing EU continental cooperation programmes with Latin America in the area of Crime and Security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KE1: Security Expert (CAT I)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post graduate qualifications (at least a Master’s degree) or equivalent (or, in its absence,equivalent professional experience – see also below) in Security Studies, Law, Political Sciences, or related fields;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid analytical skills, particularly the ability to conduct research and prepare appropriate findings and conclusions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent interpersonal and communication skills (both oral and written), including demonstrated tact in intercultural communication;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to build trust across cultural lines;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent report writing skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong planning and organisation skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency/mastery in oral and written English and at least effective operational proficiency in Spanish;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer literacy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least twelve (12) years’ experience in the security sector, but in the absence of postgraduate qualifications at least four more years of relevant professional experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience at a senior or advisory level in either Government, a relevant international or regional organisation would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the security sector reform in an international environment;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct experience in statistical analysis and research in a developing country context;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Up-to-date and comprehensive knowledge and experience of EU development policies and instruments;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of EU practices in development programmes related to the sector would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous consulting and relevant experience of working in Latin America and/or the Caribbean.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&quot;&gt;Gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>International Relations Specialist or Economic Development Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/international-relations-specialist-or-economic-development-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 12:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/international-relations-specialist-or-economic-development-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Consultancy to develop a framework for an effective platform for structured and continuous FCORs/OCTS/CARIFORUM dialogue at the political and technical level&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the Programme is to deepen and strengthen cooperation and contribute to the sustainable social and economic development of the Wider Caribbean Region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; is to design a framework for structured and continuous dialogue to strengthen political, economic and technical cooperation between the Caribbean Forum of the African, Caribbean and Pacific States (CARIFORUM), the FCORs and OCTs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key expert 2: International Relations Specialist or Economic Development Specialist&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master’s Degree in International Relations, International Development Policy, Development Economics, Business/Public Administration or related discipline;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OR in its absence not less than three (3) years&amp;#39; relevant experience in addition to the 12 years professional experience required below&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the economic, social and political development realities in the CARIFORUM/FCOR/OCT context would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English (written and spoken) and good articulation in French is required. Articulation in Spanish and/or Dutch would be a further asset but is not necessary. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 12-years relevant development cooperation and regional integration experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in formulation, organization, planning, and/or implementation of regional economic and political cooperation and collaboration policy and related activities, including knowledge and experience of related EDF procedures and processes; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated professional experience in the fostering of inter-agency and inter-governmental relations, including the formulation of policy for the promotion of regional cooperation, collaboration and integration, at both the technical and political levels;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in relevant institutional strengthening and reform processes; such experience in a general Caribbean regional cooperation context would be a plus. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience as a Team Leader in relevant regional cooperation processes; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Caribbean Regional Integration processes and the EU/CARIFORUM EPA process will be an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader, International Relations Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-international-relations-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 12:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-international-relations-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Consultancy to develop a framework for an effective platform for structured and continous FCORs/OCTS/CARIFORUM dialogue at the political and technical level&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the Programme is to deepen and strengthen cooperation and contribute to the sustainable social and economic development of the Wider Caribbean Region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; is to design a framework for structured and continuous dialogue to strengthen political, economic and technical cooperation between the Caribbean Forum of the African, Caribbean and Pacific States (CARIFORUM), the FCORs and OCTs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key expert 1: Team Leader, International Relations Specialist&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team Leader with at least a Master’s Degree in International Relations, International Development Policy, Development Economics, Business/Public Administration  or related discipline&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OR in its absence not less than three (3) years&amp;#39; relevant experience in addition to the 12 years professional experience required below;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the economic, social and political development realities in the CARIFORUM/FCOR/OCT context will be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Caribbean Regional Integration processes and the EU/CARIFORUM EPA process will be an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid command of English and comfortable articulation in French is required; articulation in Spanish and/or Dutch would be a further asset but is not absolutely necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 12-years relevant development cooperation and regional integration experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in relevant institutional strengthening and reform processes; such experience in a general Caribbean regional cooperation context would be a plus Demonstrated experience in formulation, organization, planning, and/or implementation of regional economic and political cooperation and collaboration policy and related activities, including knowledge and experience of related EDF procedures and processes; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated professional experience in the fostering of inter-agency and inter-governmental relations, including the formulation of policy for the promotion of regional cooperation, collaboration and integration, at both the technical and political levels;
Demonstrated experience as a Team Leader in relevant regional cooperation processes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert in Non-Trade Barriers (NTB), Technical Barriers to Trade (TBT) and Sanitary and Phyto-Sanitary Measures</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-non-trade-barriers-ntb-technical-barriers-to-trade-tbt-and-sanitary-and-phyto-sanitary-measures</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 13:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-non-trade-barriers-ntb-technical-barriers-to-trade-tbt-and-sanitary-and-phyto-sanitary-measures</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to the Ministry of Industrialisation, Trade &amp;amp; SME Development and the Namibia Trade Forum&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The team will work to enhance trade and business opportunities in Namibia that contribute to sustainable and inclusive economic development, in the framework of the ACP-EU Partnership Agreement and the EU-SADC Economic Partnership Agreement (EPA). They will have to assist the Ministry of Industrialisation, Trade &amp;amp; SME Development through the Namibia Trade Forum in liaison with other stakeholders – such as the ministries of Agriculture, Fisheries, the Statistic Agency and the Namibia Standard Institute, as well as other relevant Government and non-governmental Agencies and institutions – in defining an EPA Implementation Plan for Namibia. Additionally, they will also have to define a trade and business agenda and an all-inclusive institutional set-up that aims at improving the ease of doing business and incentivising investments for local, regional and European companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KE2 – Non-trade Barriers (NTB), Technical Barriers to Trade (TBT) and Snaitary and Phyto-Sanitary Measures (SPS) Expert&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Master’s degree or equivalent qualification in economics, business administration, trade or another relevant field is required, or in its absence, a relevant Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree or equivalent plus an additional 2 years of professional experience over and above what is requested below (second bullet);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years’ experience in developing countries1 in providing advice on trade related issues, in particular on non-trade barriers, technical barriers to trade and sanitary and phyto-sanitary measures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in undertaking a capacity needs assessment or institutional assessment in NTB, TBT and SPS issues, as well as the delivery of capacity building is preferred. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience of EPA / regional trade agreements implementation is preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and writing skills in English is required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&quot;&gt;gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TL – Trade Agreement Specialist </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/tl-trade-agreement-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 13:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/tl-trade-agreement-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to the Ministry of Industrialisation, Trade &amp;amp; SME Development and the Namibia Trade Forum&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The team will work to enhance trade and business opportunities in Namibia that contribute to sustainable and inclusive economic development, in the framework of the ACP-EU Partnership Agreement and the EU-SADC Economic Partnership Agreement (EPA). They will have to assist the Ministry of Industrialisation, Trade &amp;amp; SME Development through the Namibia Trade Forum in liaison with other stakeholders – such as the ministries of Agriculture, Fisheries, the Statistic Agency and the Namibia Standard Institute, as well as other relevant Government and non-governmental Agencies and institutions – in defining an EPA Implementation Plan for Namibia. Additionally, they will also have to define a trade and business agenda and an all-inclusive institutional set-up that aims at improving the ease of doing business and incentivising investments for local, regional and European companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KE1/TL – Trade Agreement Specialist&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Master’s degree or equivalent qualification in economics, business administration, trade or another relevant field is required, or in its absence, a relevant Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree or equivalent plus an additional 2 years of professional experience over and above what is requested below (second bullet);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years’ experience in developing countries  in policy analysis and/or formulation related to private sector and business development, as well as trade and investment promotion is required. This experience should preferably be in Africa. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in capacity building is preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience of EPA / regional trade agreements implementation is preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and writing skills in English is required. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&quot;&gt;gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Legal Harmonisation</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-legal-harmonisation</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-legal-harmonisation</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance for Development of Consumer Protection Policy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the project is to set-up environment for efficient and effective protection of consumer rights. The team will be expected to complete the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Achieve further harmonisation of the national legislation in the consumer protection area with the relevant EU acquis;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop a Consumer Protection Strategy (covering 5-year period);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strengthen the institutional capacity of the various stakeholders responsible for developing and implementing laws and policies in the area of consumer protection;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2/Category 1: Senior Expert in Legal Harmonisation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education at least master&amp;rsquo;s degree in law, or in its absence, general professional experience of at least 5 years above the required general professional experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English both- oral and writing; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent computer literacy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 12 years of general professional experience in the area of EU internal market.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least three (3) years of experience as legal expert in consumer protection field, such as: acting as a legal practitioner/lawyer on subjects in the area, providing counselling for legal gap analyses, law assessment, legal harmonisation with EU acquis, and similar; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the area of consumer protection in EU member countries or candidate countries shall be considered an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@com&quot;&gt;gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Consumer Protection Policy (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-consumer-protection-policy-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-consumer-protection-policy-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance for Development of Consumer Protection Policy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the project is to set-up environment for efficient and effective protection of consumer rights. The team will be expected to complete the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Achieve further harmonisation of the national legislation in the consumer protection area with the relevant EU acquis;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Develop a Consumer Protection Strategy (covering 5-year period);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Strengthen the institutional capacity of the various stakeholders responsible for developing and implementing laws and policies in the area of consumer protection.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 1/Category 1: Senior Expert in Consumer Protection Policy, (also will act as a Team leader)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education at least master&amp;rsquo;s degree in law, or economics, or in its absence, general professional experience of at least 5 years above the required general professional experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English both- oral and writing; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent computer literacy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 12 years of general professional experience in the area of EU internal market.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of experience in management or implementation of consumer programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in drafting of at least 2strategies/plans related to consumer protection/rights policy; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the area of consumer protection in EU member countries or candidate countries shall be considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&quot;&gt;gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATION&lt;/strong&gt;S&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expertise 2: junior, de catégorie II, en cartographie et systèmes d’information géographique </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expertise-2-junior-de-categorie-ii-en-cartographie-et-systemes-dinformation-geographique</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expertise-2-junior-de-categorie-ii-en-cartographie-et-systemes-dinformation-geographique</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Renforcement des capacités techniques et juridiques en matière de protection des ressources en eau en soutenant le processus de rapprochement vers les exigences de l’Acquis et des bonnes pratiques européennes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et competences:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire supérieur, de niveau Master (Bac +5), en cartographie ou systèmes d’information géographiques, ou diplôme équivalent et pertinent par rapport aux objectifs du contrat ;&lt;br&gt;
Une expérience professionnelle de 6 ans en cartographie ou systèmes d’information géographiques appliquée et modélisation numérique en plus de celle indiquée comme expérience professionnelle générale, pourra compenser l’absence de Master ; Expérience professionnelle générale : 
Critère minimum : 6 ans d’expérience minimum en cartographie ou systèmes d’information géographiques ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique :&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Critère minimum : expérience professionnelle d’au moins 6 ans en gestion de projets de cartographie ou de systèmes d’information géographiques ;&lt;br&gt;
Atout : expérience professionnelle d’au moins 1 an en tant que formateur en projets de cartographie ou de systèmes d’information géographiques. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissance linguistique :&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne maîtrise de la langue française parlée et écrite. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:Nicte_Garcia-Soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;Nicte_Garcia-Soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expertise senior, de catégorieI, en Hydrogéologie /Chef de mission</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expertise-senior-de-categorie-i-en-hydrogeologie-chef-de-mission</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 10:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expertise-senior-de-categorie-i-en-hydrogeologie-chef-de-mission</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Renforcement des capacités techniques et juridiques en matière de protection des ressources en eau en soutenant le processus de rapprochement vers les exigences de l’Acquis et des bonnes pratiques européennes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire supérieur, niveau Master, en hydrogéologie ou diplôme équivalent et pertinent par rapport aux objectifs du contrat ou justifier une expérience professionnelle de 5 ans minimum en conseil réglementaire en hydrogéologie en plus de celle indiquée comme expérience professionnelle générale, pourra compenser l’absence de diplôme universitaire supérieur ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional Experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Critère minimum : une expérience professionnelle de 12 ans en conseil hydrogéologique&lt;br&gt;
Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;br&gt;
Critère minimum : expérience professionnelle d’au moins 10 ans en études et projets relatifs à la connaissance et la modélisation des aquifères ; 
Atout : Expérience au Maroc ou expérience internationale dans des pays présentant un contexte géographique et hydrogéologique proche de celui du Maroc ; 
Atout : Connaissance de la réglementation et des institutions marocaines dans le domaine hydrogéologique ; 
Connaissance linguistique : 
Bonne maîtrise de la langue française parlée et écrite. 
Atout : Connaissances ou pratique de la langue arabe parlée. 
Le/la chef(e) de mission devra répondre, en plus des compétences ci-dessus, aux critères suivants :&lt;br&gt;
Exigence minimale : Au moins deux expériences pertinentes en matière de management et de coordination de mission.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:Nicte_Garcia-Soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;Nicte_Garcia-Soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legal Expert (Cat. II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/legal-expert-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/legal-expert-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Policy Advice to the Government of Kyrgyzstan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To assist the Government of the Kyrgyz Republic and other actors to improve their capacity to implement strategic and economic reforms towards efficient and equitable delivery of high quality, cost effective services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of this assignment are to provide advisory services and to strengthen capacity of the Government staff to (i) take an active role in the policy dialogue between the EU and KR and demonstrate commitment to the fundamental values of human rights, democracy and the rule of law; (ii) take an active role in EU aid programming and implementation as well as cooperation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Legal Expert (Cat. II)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in the field of law or minimum of 7 years of professional experience in legal area.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of relevant professional experience in the sectors related to Lot 7&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of working experience in legal issues in the Kyrgyz Republic;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years of working experience in the legal analysis and/or development of the Country Strategy and/or the Sector Development Strategy;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience in projects funded by the Development Partners;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience in at least two EU-funded projects;
• Knowledge of the EU budget support and EU programming exercise will be a strong asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in Russian&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working level of English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Kyrgyz language is a strong asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:anju_english@dai.com&quot;&gt;anju_english@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader - Adviser (Cat. I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-adviser-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 14:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-adviser-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Policy Advice to the Government of Kyrgyzstan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To assist the Government of the Kyrgyz Republic and other actors to improve their capacity to implement strategic and economic reforms towards efficient and equitable delivery of high quality, cost effective services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of this assignment are to provide advisory services and to strengthen capacity of the Government staff to (i) take an active role in the policy dialogue between the EU and KR and demonstrate commitment to the fundamental values of human rights, democracy and the rule of law; (ii) take an active role in EU aid programming and implementation as well as cooperation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader - Adviser (Cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in the field of economics or law or minimum of 14 years of professional experience in economic or legal area.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years professional experience at team leader&amp;rsquo;s level.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years&amp;#39; experience in the sectors related to Lot 7&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of working experience in the EU legal framework, incl. EU trade regulations;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience in GSP+ issues;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of working experience in post-Soviet countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience in Kyrgyzstan will be a strong asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience in at least two EU-funded projects;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Partnership and Cooperation Agreements between the EU and partner countries will be a strong asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in Russian&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:anju_english@dai.com&quot;&gt;anju_english@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert dans le Domaine de la Filière d’Elevage (Catégorie III)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-dans-le-domaine-de-la-filiere-delevage-categorie-iii</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 13:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-dans-le-domaine-de-la-filiere-delevage-categorie-iii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lecons Tirees de Deux Projets du Secteur De L&amp;#39;Elevage et Propositions pour Poursuivre L&amp;#39;appui dans Le 11eme FED&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général&lt;/strong&gt; de la prestation est de renforcer l’efficacité et augmenter l&amp;#39;impact de l&amp;#39;appui de l’Union Européenne dans la filière d’élevage (cycle court) en République de la Guinée-Bissau. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Les objectifs spécifiques&lt;/strong&gt; de la prestation sont :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;tirer les leçons des deux projets mis en oeuvre par IMVF et par Mani Tese;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;formuler des propositions pour renforcer la filière d&amp;#39;élevage et les stratégies d&amp;#39;appui à suivre dans le cadre du 11ème FED.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert dans le Domaine de la Filière d’Elevage (Catégorie III)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire ou un master de niveau universitaire ou équivalent en sciences sociales, agronomie, économie agricole ou équivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle en matière de coopération au développement en général et dans le domaine spécifique de la filière d’élevage, en particulier.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle internationale, en particulier dans les pays de l&amp;#39;Afrique de l&amp;#39;Ouest et/ou dans des Pays Moins Avancés (PMA); expérience en Guinée-Bissau serait un plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience avérée en matière d&amp;#39;évaluation et maîtrise démontrée des principes et des méthodes de travail de la gestion du cycle de projet (identification, formulation, mise en oeuvre, suivi, évaluation); la maîtrise des méthodes de l&amp;#39;aide communautaire, notamment dans le cadre du FED, serait un plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise du portugais (B1 ou B2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;La connaissance du français (B1 minimum) sera considérée comme un atout important&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef d’équipe et Expert dans le Domaine de la Filière d’Elevage</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-dequipe-et-expert-dans-le-domaine-de-la-filiere-delevage</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 13:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-dequipe-et-expert-dans-le-domaine-de-la-filiere-delevage</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lecons Tirees de Deux Projets du Secteur De L&amp;#39;Elevage et Propositions pour Poursuivre L&amp;#39;appui dans Le 11eme FED&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général&lt;/strong&gt; de la prestation est de renforcer l’efficacité et augmenter l&amp;#39;impact de l&amp;#39;appui de l’Union Européenne dans la filière d’élevage (cycle court) en République de la Guinée-Bissau. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les &lt;strong&gt;objectifs spécifiques&lt;/strong&gt; de la prestation sont :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;tirer les leçons des deux projets mis en oeuvre par IMVF et par Mani Tese;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;formuler des propositions pour renforcer la filière d&amp;#39;élevage et les stratégies d&amp;#39;appui à suivre dans le cadre du 11ème FED.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chef d’équipe et Expert dans le Domaine de la Filière d’Elevage (catégorie II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire ou un master de niveau universitaire ou équivalent en sciences sociales, agronomie, économie agricole ou équivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle en matière de coopération au développement en général et dans le domaine spécifique de la filière d’élevage, en particulier.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle internationale, en particulier dans les pays de l&amp;#39;Afrique de l&amp;#39;Ouest et/ou dans des Pays Moins Avancés (PMA); expérience en Guinée-Bissau serait un plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience avérée en matière d&amp;#39;évaluation et maîtrise démontrée des principes et des méthodes de travail de la gestion du cycle de projet (identification, formulation, mise en oeuvre, suivi, évaluation); la maîtrise des méthodes de l&amp;#39;aide communautaire, notamment dans le cadre du FED, serait un plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise du portugais (B1 ou B2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;La connaissance du français (B1 minimum) sera considérée comme un atout important&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IT Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/it-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 19:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/it-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term evaluation decision ENPI/2008/019622 &amp;lsquo;Modernisation of the Lebanese Justice&amp;rsquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation shall focus on the following results / activities of the technical and administrative provisions (TAPs) of the related Financing Agreement:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;C1. Automation of Beirut Courts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;C2. Access to Justice: activities related to (i) the development of the capacities of the MoJ (i.e. assistance provided to the MoJ for the implementation of the Master Plan) and (ii) the access to information (i.e. support the establishment of a help desk at the Beirut Court, support the establishment of a help desk unit at the General Prosecutor&amp;rsquo;s office and development of the legal database and provision of technical training for its use).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2: IT expert, category II&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education at least Master’s degree in legal informatics or, in its absence, 9 years of relevant general professional experience as specified below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills, both oral and written.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least six (6) years of experience in legal informatics/courts automation operations/projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous similar work experiences in EU or non EU countries required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience in enhancement and development of public institutions systems through the establishment of comprehensive information and communication technologies (ICT) framework.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience in similar assignments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English (spoken and written) is compulsory.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Arabic and French (spoken and written) would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&quot;&gt;gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Law expert and Team Leader </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/law-expert-and-team-leader</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 19:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/law-expert-and-team-leader</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term evaluation decision ENPI/2008/019622 &amp;lsquo;Modernisation of the Lebanese Justice&amp;rsquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation shall focus on the following results / activities of the technical and administrative provisions (TAPs) of the related Financing Agreement:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;C1. Automation of Beirut Courts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;C2. Access to Justice: activities related to (i) the development of the capacities of the MoJ (i.e. assistance provided to the MoJ for the implementation of the Master Plan) and (ii) the access to information (i.e. support the establishment of a help desk at the Beirut Court, support the establishment of a help desk unit at the General Prosecutor&amp;rsquo;s office and development of the legal database and provision of technical training for its use).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 1: Law expert and Team Leader, category II&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education at least Master’s degree in law or, in its absence, 9 years of relevant general professional experience as specified below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills, both oral and written.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facilitation capacities to work effectively with government counterparts in complex environments and coordinate positively with various stakeholders, including Ministries, donors and NGOs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least six (6) years of experience in the expertise common to all lots and in the following technical area(s) related to lot 7, area A.3.7 with focus on legal IT.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous similar work experiences in EU or non EU countries required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experiences in enhancement and development of the judiciary sector through the utilization of a comprehensive information and communication technologies (ICT) framework.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experiences of judicial dossier / document management, archiving, decision making and final rulings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience in leading a team under similar assignments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English (spoken and written) is compulsory.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of Arabic (spoken and written) is compulsory.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of French (spoken and written) would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&quot;&gt;gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert de catégorie II, en hydrologie </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-de-categorie-ii-en-hydrologie</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 12:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-de-categorie-ii-en-hydrologie</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appui en matiere de gestion des risques naturels lles a l&amp;#39;eau, et en particulier celui des inondations part l&amp;#39;amelioration des outils de prevision des crues&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Renforcement des capacités techniques et règlementaires en matière de gestion des risques liés à l’eau et plus particulièrement la prévention et la protection des risques d’inondation en s’appuyant sur les exigences et les bonnes pratiques européennes et environnementales durables. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les présents termes de référence envisagent la mise en place d’une assistance technique ayant pour but le renforcement des capacités techniques et juridiques en matière de prévention et de protection contre les risques d’inondation, plus particulièrement à travers le développement de systèmes de prévision et d’annonce des crues, par la mise en œuvre de modèles hydrométéorologiques et hydrauliques, intégrant notamment les données et prévisions météorologiques (radars, données satellitaires). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;En particulier, il s’agit ici de réaliser une prévision des crues en temps réel en s’appuyant sur des modèles hydrométéorologiques et hydrauliques, intégrant d’une part l’ensemble des données et prévisions météorologiques disponibles en temps réel, d’autre part la transformation, sous bassins par sous bassin, des données pluviométriques en données hydrométriques (hauteurs d’eau et débits), de la propagation des hydrogrammes vers l’aval en tenant compte des conditions topographiques et hydrauliques des biefs concernés, des réalimentations successives par les affluents rencontrés et du rôle primordial des barrages dans le processus de laminage des crues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expertise 2 : Expert de catégorie II, en hydrologie&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire supérieur, de niveau Master (Bac +5), en hydraulique ou diplôme équivalent et pertinent par rapport aux objectifs du contrat ou justifier une expérience professionnelle de 5 ans minimum en conseil réglementaire en hydraulique en plus de celle indiquée comme expérience professionnelle générale, pourra compenser l’absence de diplôme universitaire supérieur ;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt; : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Critère minimum : 5 ans d’expérience minimum en tant que hydrologue ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Critère minimum : expérience professionnelle d’au moins 3 ans en modélisation informatique des crues ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Atout : expérience professionnelle d’au moins 1 an en tant que formateur du secteur public ou privé. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissance linguistique&lt;/strong&gt; : Maîtrise de la langue française parlée et écrite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior, de catégorie I, en gestion de risques hydrauliques/Chef de mission</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-de-categorie-i-en-gestion-de-risques-hydrauliques-chef-de-mission</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 12:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-de-categorie-i-en-gestion-de-risques-hydrauliques-chef-de-mission</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appui en matiere de gestion des risques naturels lles a l&amp;#39;eau, et en particulier celui des inondations part l&amp;#39;amelioration des outils de prevision des crues&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Renforcement des capacités techniques et règlementaires en matière de gestion des risques liés à l’eau et plus particulièrement la prévention et la protection des risques d’inondation en s’appuyant sur les exigences et les bonnes pratiques européennes et environnementales durables. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les présents termes de référence envisagent la mise en place d’une assistance technique ayant pour but le renforcement des capacités techniques et juridiques en matière de prévention et de protection contre les risques d’inondation, plus particulièrement à travers le développement de systèmes de prévision et d’annonce des crues, par la mise en œuvre de modèles hydrométéorologiques et hydrauliques, intégrant notamment les données et prévisions météorologiques (radars, données satellitaires). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;En particulier, il s’agit ici de réaliser une prévision des crues en temps réel en s’appuyant sur des modèles hydrométéorologiques et hydrauliques, intégrant d’une part l’ensemble des données et prévisions météorologiques disponibles en temps réel, d’autre part la transformation, sous bassins par sous bassin, des données pluviométriques en données hydrométriques (hauteurs d’eau et débits), de la propagation des hydrogrammes vers l’aval en tenant compte des conditions topographiques et hydrauliques des biefs concernés, des réalimentations successives par les affluents rencontrés et du rôle primordial des barrages dans le processus de laminage des crues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expertise 1 : Senior, de catégorie I, en gestion de risques hydrauliques/Chef de mission&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; :  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme d’enseignement supérieur, de niveau Master (Bac + 5), en hydraulique ou diplôme équivalent et pertinent par rapport aux objectifs du contrat ou justifier une expérience professionnelle de 5 ans minimum en conseil réglementaire en hydraulique en plus de celle indiquée comme expérience professionnelle générale, pourra compenser l’absence de diplôme universitaire supérieur ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Critère minimum : 15 ans d’expérience en tant que conseil stratégique en hydraulique ou  hydrologie. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Critère minimum : expérience professionnelle d’au moins 10 ans en études stratégiques et mise en œuvre de projets de modélisation dans le cadre de systèmes de prévision et d’annonce des crues; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Critère minimum : expérience professionnelle d’au moins 3 ans en conseil réglementaire hydraulique &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Atout: expérience professionnelle d’au moins 2 ans en tant que formateur auprès d’un établissement universitaire ou en tant que conseil/assistance technique auprès de cadres du secteur public ou privé ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Atout : Connaissance de l’organisation relative à la prévision et à l’annonce des crues dans un ou plusieurs pays de l’UE ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Atout : Expérience au Maroc ou dans un pays présentant un contexte hydro-climatologique proche de celui du Maroc ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissance linguistique&lt;/strong&gt; : maîtrise de la langue française parlée et écrite ; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Le/la chef(e) de mission&lt;/strong&gt; devra répondre, en plus des compétences ci-dessus, aux critères suivants:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale : Au moins deux expériences pertinentes en matière de management et de coordination de missions. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Le/la chef(e) de mission sera responsable de la préparation de la mission ainsi que des différents livrables et rapports. Ces documents seront préparés avec le concours du deuxième expert.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Le/la chef(e) de mission devra s&amp;#39;assurer de la bonne organisation de la mission, du respect des termes de références et des instructions reçues de la Délégation. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;La présence du chef de mission est requise pour les réunions de démarrage et de restitution du projet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert senior, de catégorie I, en météorologie</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-senior-de-categorie-i-en-meteorologie</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-senior-de-categorie-i-en-meteorologie</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appui en matiere d&amp;#39;adaptation des modalites de gestion des ressources en eau face au changement climatique&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif général&lt;/strong&gt;
Promouvoir une bonne gouvernance environnementale face aux changements climatiques.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif spécifique&lt;/strong&gt;
Renforcement des capacités techniques et institutionnelles de gestion de la pénurie d’eau, en matière, notamment, de gestion des ressources en eau face au changement climatique en s’appuyant sur les exigences de l’Acquis et des bonnes pratiques européennes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert senior, de catégorie I, en météorologie&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire supérieur, de niveau Master en études météorologiques, en hydrologie hydraulique, ou diplôme équivalent et pertinent par rapport aux objectifs du contrat ; une expérience professionnelle de 5 ans en météorologie, en plus de celle indiquée comme expérience professionnelle générale, pourra compenser l’absence de Master ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Critère minimum : expérience professionnelle d’au moins 10 ans en ingénierie hydrologique ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifiqu&lt;/strong&gt;e :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Critère minimum :  Expérience  professionnelle  d’au moins 5  ans  en  modélisation  météorologique prévisionnelle;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Atout : expérience professionnelle d’au moins 1 an en tant que formateur auprès d’un établissement universitaire ou auprès de cadres du secteur public ou privé.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissance linguistique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise parfaite de la langue française parlée et écrite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;lina_forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert senior, de catégorie I, en Hydrologie/Chef(e) de mission</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-senior-de-categorie-i-en-hydrologie-chefe-de-mission</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 12:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-senior-de-categorie-i-en-hydrologie-chefe-de-mission</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appui en matiere d&amp;#39;adaptation des modalites de gestion des ressources en eau face au changement climatique&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif général&lt;/strong&gt;
Promouvoir une bonne gouvernance environnementale face aux changements climatiques.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif spécifique&lt;/strong&gt;
Renforcement des capacités techniques et institutionnelles de gestion de la pénurie d’eau, en matière, notamment, de gestion des ressources en eau face au changement climatique en s’appuyant sur les exigences de l’Acquis et des bonnes pratiques européennes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert senior, de catégorie I, en Hydrologie/Chef(e) de mission&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire supérieur, de niveau Master en hydrologie ou diplôme équivalent et pertinent par rapport aux objectifs du contrat ou justifier une expérience professionnelle de 5 ans minimum en conseil en hydrologie, en plus de celle indiquée comme expérience professionnelle générale, pourra compenser l’absence de diplôme universitaire supérieur ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Critère minimum : 15 ans d’expérience en conseil stratégique en hydraulique ou hydrologie.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Critère minimum : expérience professionnelle d’au moins 10 ans en études et projets relatifs à la connaissance et la modélisation hydrologique, en particulier aux changements climatiques;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Critère minimum : expérience professionnelle d’au moins 3 ans en études d’impact hydrologique à la suite de changements climatiques ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Atout : Expérience au Maroc ou dans un pays présentant un contexte hydro-climatologique proche de celui du Maroc ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Atout : Connaissance de la normative  de l’organisation marocaine dans le domaine concerné.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissance linguistique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise parfaite de la langue française parlée et écrite ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Le/la &lt;strong&gt;chef(e) de mission&lt;/strong&gt; devra répondre, en plus des compétences ci-dessus, aux critères suivants:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exigence  minimale&lt;/strong&gt;  :  Au  moins  deux  expériences  pertinentes  en  matière  de  management  et  de coordination de mission.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;lina_forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert en Communication </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-communication</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-communication</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appui a l&amp;#39;elaboration du plan d&amp;#39;actions pour le renforcement des capacites du dispositif de suivi evaluation du PNDES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif global de cette consultation est de mettre à la disposition du SP/PNDES et des différents acteurs impliqués un plan d’actions pour le renforcement du suivi-évaluation pour PNDES. Ce plan d&amp;#39;action devra veiller à définir des actions permettant le suivi des Objectifs de développement durable (ODD) et de renforcer les liens entre le suivi de la politique et le processus budgétaire.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert en Communication&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Être titulaire d&amp;#39;un master ou équivalent en communication ou matières équivalentes ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir une expérience en matière de conception de stratégies de communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir une bonne connaissance des logiciels Word, Excel et Powerpoint&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir une parfaite maîtrise du français, à l&amp;#39;oral comme à l&amp;#39;écrit. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience avec l&amp;#39;administration du Burkina Faso sera un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Être capable de travailler en équipe, de communiquer et d&amp;#39;assurer un leadership. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Faire preuve d&amp;#39;initiative, de réactivité, d&amp;#39;objectivité, d&amp;#39;organisation et avoir une bonne méthodologie dans l&amp;#39;exécution du travail et le management d’équipes. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir au minimum dix (10) ans d&amp;#39;expérience en matière de communication. Une expérience Afrique subsaharienne serait un atout. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Posséder une expérience de communication en matière de politiques de développement et de résultats serait un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
