<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 15:49:29 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Director, Provision of Expertise for the Election Observation Missions</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/project-director-provision-of-expertise-for-the-election-observation-missions</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 15:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/project-director-provision-of-expertise-for-the-election-observation-missions</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This contract does not form part of the BENEF or COM 1 Frameworks but is Lot 1 of the &lt;strong&gt;EIDHR Election Framework Contract&lt;/strong&gt;.  However, the expertise required most closely aligns to BENEF Lot 7 expertise, hence we have placed these &amp;lsquo;calls for experts&amp;rsquo; on the Lot 7 page of the DAI Framework Contracts website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EIDHR Election Framework Contract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The scope of Lot 1 of the Framework Contract (FWC) is to provide expertise for the &lt;strong&gt;Election Observation Missions (EOMs)&lt;/strong&gt; in order to provide support to genuine elections in partner countries. As far as the partner countries are concerned, they are in the regions of Africa, Pacific region, Asia, Latin America, North Africa and Middle East countries. The EU normally does not observe in the OSCE area but exceptions to this rule could be considered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Election observation is a fundamental component of an election process. It is a crucial transparency check that promotes accountability and can therefore deter fraud and irregularities. This in turn can reduce violence and encourage participation. Election observation also provides wider information on a country&amp;rsquo;s human rights situation and promotes immediate and long-term democratic development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since 2000 the European Union (EU) has been committed to undertaking comprehensive, long-term election observation, in accordance with international standards, through the deployment of EOMs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a variety of actors involved in the process:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;EU Member States (MS) and the European Parliament (EP) are consulted on the selection of election priorities; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the Chief Observer is an Member of the European Parliament;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;EU Member States identify the long and short-term observers; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the European Commission is responsible for the budgetary, security and logistical aspects;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;EU Delegations on the ground are fully involved during the various steps;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the European External Action Service (EEAS) is in charge of the programming and political aspects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EU EOMs are independent (from the EU Member States, the European Commission, the European Parliament) in their political judgements regarding their findings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On average approximately 10 EU EOMs are deployed yearly to countries all over the world to the destinations mentioned in section 1.1. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EU EOMs are projects financed by the European Commission and implemented through contracting the selected Framework Contract contractor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EU EOMs are composed of:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Chief Observer (CO), Member of European Parliament designated by the High Representative/Vice-President of the European Commission (HR/VP);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deputy Chief Observer (DCO) contracted by the European Commission as a Special Adviser to the HR/VP;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Core Team (CT) of experts in electoral matters, selected by the European Commission and the EEAS;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Long and Short-term Election Observers (LTOs and STOs), volunteers proposed by the Member States (Focal Points) and selected by the European Commission and the EEAS;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;EP Delegations;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Locally recruited Short-term Observers (LSTOs), EU MS diplomats posted in the partner country.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Director&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of the global offer, the tenderer has to identify a Project Director and one substitute, who shall at least be available and formally take over each time the Project Director is temporarily absent. It should be noted that several assignments can run in parallel. The Project Director will have an overall responsibility for the performance of the contract. In particular, the Project Director shall ensure the provision of high-quality services throughout the assignment. The Project Director will also be responsible for the day-to-day management of the contract and act as the central point of contact for each individual assignment. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Framework Contract Project Director must have the following skills and experience:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University level education in Management, Business Administration, Public Administration, Finance, Economics, International Relations or a related field. Adequate training in a related field and equivalent professional experience in project management may be accepted in lieu of a university degree. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent proven command (level C1of English or French, a working knowledge (level B2 of the other language).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of EU institutions and policies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organisational skills; planning, evaluating and problem-solving skills;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to work in a multi-cultural environment;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Financial and budget management skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to meet tight deadlines and operate under stress situations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years of work experience of management, implementation and administration of large-scale international operations in a multi-cultural environment in a similar position, 5 of which in a senior management position.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Management of large scale international operations or programmes (including with teams in the field);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team management experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in one or several regions where EU EOMs take place;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Management responsibility (contractual, financial, operational) of projects for international organisations, and in particular for EU-funded projects, would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Project Director&lt;/strong&gt; will have at least the following tasks:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;responsibility for the day-to-day management of the FWC and each individual assignment;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;monitoring of the services rendered and of the performance of the experts implementing the individual assignments; ensuring that quality control of the Specific Contract outputs is carried out, either by the Project Director him/herself or through an identified consortium member and its staff.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please apply via the following link &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=2513&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=2513&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior International Trade Expert </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-international-trade-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 13:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-international-trade-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identification of the EU Support for Trade Related Assistance in Bhutan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;overall objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the mission is to provide the EU Delegation for Bhutan with technical assistance for the design of the EU Trade Related Assistance in Bhutan under the regional programming for Asia multiannual indicative programme (MIP) 2014 – 2020 adopted by the EU in September 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the mission is to prepare a report giving an overview of state of play of Bhutan trade policy initiatives as well as detailing the different actors involved; identifying opportunities and needs for EU to strengthen Bhutan trade competitiveness; analysing sectorial opportunities for EU trade assistance specifically in RNR, Tourism, Handicrafts and SMEs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;International Trade Expert (Cat.I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University Degree in the field of Trade, Law, Business Administration, Economics or other relevant field,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;12 years of experience in the field of international trade cooperation/relations or private sector development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identification and/or formulation of trade related assistance programmes/projects;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience dealing with WTO issues;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Action Document drafting under EU procedures;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience in Bhutan and familiarity with the Department of Trade.in Bhutan.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Natural Resource/Climate Change/Biodiversity Experts </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/natural-resource-climate-change-biodiversity-experts</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/natural-resource-climate-change-biodiversity-experts</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Climate Change Documentary of Malawi
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Global objective *&lt;/em&gt;
To produce a documentary on the challenges and successes of climate change adaptation/resilience in Malawi at district/village level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt;
A finished, edited documentary, duration 20 minutes (plus a 2 minute teaser/trailer) telling the story of village people&amp;rsquo;s lives affected by climate change. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Natural Resource/Climate Change/Biodiversity Experts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Teams of suitably qualified Film Journalist/Media Production Experts and Natural Resource/Climate Change/Biodiversity Experts are required in order to fulfil the objectives of the assignment.  At least one member of the media team must have worked in central and southern Africa within the last three years on work of a similar nature.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;: English and Chichewa&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project is of one year&amp;rsquo;s duration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com
&lt;/a&gt;
WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Film Journalist/Media Production Experts</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/film-journalist-media-production-experts</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 10:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/film-journalist-media-production-experts</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Climate Change Documentary of Malawi
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt; 
To produce a documentary on the challenges and successes of climate change adaptation/resilience in Malawi at district/village level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt;
A finished, edited documentary, duration 20 minutes (plus a 2 minute teaser/trailer) telling the story of village people&amp;rsquo;s lives affected by climate change. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Film Journalist/Media Production Experts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Teams of suitably qualified Film Journalist/Media Production Experts and Natural Resource/Climate Change/Biodiversity Experts are required in order to fulfil the objectives of the assignment.  At least one member of the media team must have worked in central and southern Africa within the last three years on work of a similar nature.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will be an assignment of one-year&amp;rsquo;s duration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;: English and Chichewa&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATION&lt;/strong&gt;S&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ingénieur Halieute, Biologiste des Pêches ou Equivalent (catégorie I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/ingenieur-halieute-biologiste-des-peches-ou-equivalent-categorie-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 09:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/ingenieur-halieute-biologiste-des-peches-ou-equivalent-categorie-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation à mi-parcours du projet d’Aménagement Durable des Pêcheries&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contribuer à améliorer l&amp;#39;efficacité, l&amp;#39;efficience et l&amp;#39;impact de la mise en œuvre des plans d&amp;#39;aménagement de la crevette profonde et du poulpe. Et, en particulier,  que le projet est sur la voie de la réalisation des résultats prédéfinis et de fournir des recommandations sur les tendances à maintenir et les ajustements nécessaires à y apporter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert II: Ingénieur Halieute, Biologiste des Pêches ou Equivalent (catégorie I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formation : formation universitaire (Maîtrise / Master 1) en matière de gestion des pêches. Un PHD serait un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale de au moins de 12 années d’expérience dans les domaines de l&amp;#39;aménagement de pêcheries africaines. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience d&amp;#39;au moins 3 ans dans l&amp;#39;évaluation des projets et programmes. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capacité rédactionnelle et maitrise des logiciels usuels de traitement de texte, tableur et base de données.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance et expérience dans le domaine de la formulation et/ou la mise en œuvre/ évaluation de plans de gestion et d&amp;#39;aménagement des pêches (au minimum deux expériences). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans le fonctionnement d’un observatoire économique de pêches (au moins une expérience).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en amélioration des connaissances et en modélisation biologique en accompagnement des plans d&amp;#39;aménagement (au moins une expérience).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance des pêcheries ouest-africaines et/ou celles du Sénégal et de la problématique de l&amp;#39;aménagement des pêcheries au Sénégal serait un atout. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne connaissance des acteurs professionnels de la pêche et des organisations professionnelles au Sénégal serait un atout. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans la conduite d’études et/ou de l&amp;#39;évaluation des projets et programmes de pêche notamment ceux financés par l’Union Européenne serait un atout. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise du français (lu, écrit et parlé)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef de mission, Expert Economiste ou Gestionnaire de Projets de Développement et Praticien de la Gestion des Pêches (Catégorie I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-expert-economiste-ou-gestionnaire-de-projets-de-developpement-et-praticien-de-la-gestion-des-peches-categorie-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-expert-economiste-ou-gestionnaire-de-projets-de-developpement-et-praticien-de-la-gestion-des-peches-categorie-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation à mi-parcours du Projet d’Aménagement Durable des Pêcheries&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contribuer à améliorer l&amp;#39;efficacité, l&amp;#39;efficience et l&amp;#39;impact de la mise en œuvre des plans d&amp;#39;aménagement de la crevette profonde et du poulpe. Et, en particulier,  que le projet est sur la voie de la réalisation des résultats prédéfinis et de fournir des recommandations sur les tendances à maintenir et les ajustements nécessaires à y apporter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chef de mission, Expert Economiste ou Gestionnaire de Projets de Développement et Praticien de la Gestion des Pêches (Catégorie I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formation universitaire (Maîtrise / Master 1) en Economie, Gestion ou Analyse de projets. Un PhD serait un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins de 12 années d’expérience dans les domaines de l’évaluation des politiques publiques de gestion des pêches. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience d&amp;#39;au moins 5 ans dans l&amp;#39;élaboration et l&amp;#39;évaluation des projets et programmes et dans l’appui institutionnel pour la gestion des pêches. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance des pêcheries ouest-africaines et/ou celles du Sénégal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans une position technique opérationnelle de responsabilité. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capacité rédactionnelle et maitrise des logiciels usuels de traitement de texte, tableur et base de données.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance et expérience dans le domaine de la formulation et/ou la mise en œuvre/ évaluation de plans de gestion et d&amp;#39;aménagement des pêches (au moins 3 expériences). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience avérée dans le fonctionnement d’un observatoire économique de pêches et/ou des systèmes d&amp;#39;information des pêcheries (au moins 2 expériences). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience sur les questions relatives à l&amp;#39;allocation de droit d&amp;#39;usages exclusif dans la pêche (au moins une expérience).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellente connaissance des questions relatives à la gouvernance des pêches au Sénégal serait un atout. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne connaissance des acteurs et des organisations professionnelles de pêche au Sénégal serait un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance de la problématique de l’aménagement des pêches au Sénégal serait un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans la conduite d&amp;#39;évaluation des projets et programmes de pêche notamment ceux financés par l’Union Européenne serait un atout&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise du français (lu, écrit et parlé)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castailla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Senior Experts in Agro-economy, Agriculture Production Systems, Value Chains, Irrigation Development and Agricultural Finance </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/5-senior-experts-in-agro-economy-agriculture-production-systems-value-chains-irrigation-development-and-agricultural-finance</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 16:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/5-senior-experts-in-agro-economy-agriculture-production-systems-value-chains-irrigation-development-and-agricultural-finance</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this assignment is to formulate a result and impact oriented sustainable agriculture programme that will support the Government of Malawi (GoM) to enhance food, nutrition and income security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;objective&lt;/strong&gt;of this consultancy assignment is to provide decision makers in the Government of Malawi and European Commission with sufficient information and analysis to justify the choice of areas and implementation modalities for the KULIMA as a sustainable agriculture programme of the 11th European Development Fund (EDF) for Malawi. In this frame, the overall outcome of the consultancy will be: to provide adequate information which will constitute the basis for concluding a financing agreement between the EU Commission and the GoM to undertake the ambitious transformative sustainable agriculture programme. This will involve the appraisal and strengthening of the design, coherence, relevance, feasibility and potential for effectiveness of a draft action document, along with the elaboration of implementation modalities and the necessary stakeholder collaboration and accountability and coordination arrangements for the implementation of the programme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt; of the assignment are to provide advise so that:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The choice of areas and implementing modalities proposed in the programme will have a broadbased impact in transforming smallholder homestead diversified farming, increases agriculture production and productivity, contributes to overall improving the nutritional status of Malawians and strengthens value chain development and promotes value addition, ensures easy access to markets and generation of increased incomes for rural households, promotes skills to adapt/mitigate climate change effects, and sustainable management of natural resources in the agriculture sector;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adequate conditions under which EU Aid will have a structural impact in transforming multisector policy and planning, interaction, collaboration and joint operations in addressing food, nutrition and income security in Malawi;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The programme design will provide the possibility for EU Member States to join and/or cooperate within an agreed programme, as well as to integrate continental and regional recommendations and country-level concerns and considerations;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The programme design will define means and strategies for effective diversification of agriculture production in Malawi;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The programme design will ensure that the county / district dimension is taken into consideration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5 Senior Experts in Agro-economy, Agriculture Production Systems, Value Chains, Irrigation Development and Agricultural Finance&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A formulation team of indicatively 5 experts of &lt;strong&gt;category I&lt;/strong&gt; is expected for a total of approximately &lt;strong&gt;210 working days&lt;/strong&gt; (for both phase 1 and 2). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;proposed Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;key experts&lt;/strong&gt; covering agroeconomy, agriculture production systems, agriculture value chain development, irrigation development and agricultural finance are preferably to be covered by a category I expert. A combination of expertise can be covered by one expert.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The team is required to have the following general expertise:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team leader with strong ability to lead, coordinate and manage a team to provide high-quality inputs. This requires proven managerial, project management and team coordination skills. (S)He must have been team leader of at least one previous EDF formulation mission for the EU;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Up to date knowledge of latest developments in the fields related to the programme, including innovative approaches;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All members of the team must have excellent inter-personal and communication skills, including the ability to work with and adjust to diverse audiences (such as politicians, Government technical staff, development partners, civil society, private sector, local chiefs, and smallholder farmers);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Within the team there should be knowledge and expertise in organisational capacity development, governance and change management in low-income countries, particularly in relation to agricultural transformation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one team member should have experience of working with multi-sectoral programmes, with Governments (at national and sub-national levels, urban and rural), Non-State Actors (e.g. academia, research institutes, private sector including micro-enterprises, farmer organisations, CBOs/CSOs/NGOs; financial institutions) and Development Partners;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Within the team there should be expertise in M&amp;amp;E and reporting systems following Project Cycle Management (PCM) logic;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one team member must be familiar with international policies related to the issues covered by the programme, as well as with EU development policy and EC development cooperation programmes and EU contractual procedures;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of similar assignment(s) in Sub-Saharan Africa is an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;formulation team&lt;/strong&gt; will need the following &lt;strong&gt;KULIMA&lt;/strong&gt; specific expertise:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Senior Agro-economist with familiarity of practical participatory approaches.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in extension systems with specialist knowledge and experience in design and implementation of the Farmer Field schools (FFS) approach and farmer Business School (FBS) approach and with experience in support of farmer-led research;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in development of irrigation systems in sub-saharan Africa;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in practical use of integrated production methods (ICM/IPM practices, agroforestry etc…) under tropical and sub-tropical conditions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise on different types of cooperative and farmers&amp;#39; organization development as well as anchor farms and contract farming modalities, preferably in African countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough knowledge of private sector in agriculture with focused expertise in agriculture value chain development and promotion of micro-, small and medium sized enterprises;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in agriculture related financial service delivery, including formal banking system and other types of financial service providers (e.g. micro-finance, warehouse receipt systems, credit schemes, Village Savings and Loans etc.);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise on cross-cutting issues, most particularly nutrition, gender, human rights, social protection and governance must be present in the team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise on trade related issues (domestic and regional) is an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise on food safety and food technology, quality assurance, standardization, accreditation and metrology requirements is an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language and IT skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• All team members must have excellent skills in spoken and written English;
• All team members must be fully computer-literate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Experts (Team Leader and key experts)&lt;/strong&gt; should have at least a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree or equivalent in a discipline relevant to the required expertise of this ToR and to their assignment in the team and 12 years of general professional experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Extra years of experience would be acceptable as an alternative to a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree. A senior expert (category I) without a Master’s Degree would require relevant professional experience of at least 15 years;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Member - Agricultural Specialist or Land &amp; Water management / Irrigation specialist (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-member-agricultural-specialist-or-land-water-management-irrigation-specialist-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 08:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-member-agricultural-specialist-or-land-water-management-irrigation-specialist-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Review of the Accompanying Measures Sugar Protocol (AMSP) 2011-2013&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective is to elaborate an independent mid-term evaluation which will provide the decision-makers in the Government of Mozambique, the relevant external co-operation services of the European Commission and the wider public with sufficient information to: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make an overall independent assessment of the performance, so far of the programme, paying particularly attention to the results already achieved or expected to be achieved, and potential impact of the project against its objectives; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Draw key lessons and propose practical recommendations in order to improve current and future action and for addressing challenges faced by the programme. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Member - Agricultural Specialist or Land &amp;amp; Water management / Irrigation specialist (Category I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Master degree in agronomy, land &amp;amp; water management or irrigation or related field; 
•  At least 10 years professional experience in development cooperation in management, evaluation and monitoring of rural/community development and/or poverty alleviation programmes; 
• Experience with design and management of irrigation and drainage schemes; 
• Good knowledge of hydrological and environmental aspects of irrigation/drainage schemes in flood-prone areas; 
• Good knowledge of the sugarcane cultivation. 
• Fluency in English (oral, written and comprehension); 
• Minimum good knowledge of the Portuguese language; 
• Experience and knowledge of the socio-political context of Mozambique would be an asset 
• A good knowledge of the sugar industry or of comparable out grower programmes will be an asset&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &amp;lsquo;Nicte Garcia-soria&amp;rsquo; &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert with TL &amp; M&amp;E Experience in Rural Community/Poverty Alleviation Programmes (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-with-tl-me-experience-in-rural-community-poverty-alleviation-programmes-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 08:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-with-tl-me-experience-in-rural-community-poverty-alleviation-programmes-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Review of the Accompanying Measures Sugar Protocol (AMSP) 2011-2013&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective is to elaborate an independent mid-term evaluation which will provide the decision-makers in the Government of Mozambique, the relevant external co-operation services of the European Commission and the wider public with sufficient information to: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make an overall independent assessment of the performance, so far of the programme, paying particularly attention to the results already achieved or expected to be achieved, and potential impact of the project against its objectives; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Draw key lessons and propose practical recommendations in order to improve current and future action and for addressing challenges faced by the programme. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert with TL &amp;amp; M&amp;amp;E Experience in Rural Community/Poverty Alleviation Programmes (Category I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master degree in rural development, rural economics, social sciences or related field; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years professional experience in development cooperation in management, evaluation and monitoring of rural/community development and/or poverty alleviation programmes; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years&amp;#39; experience as team-leader in project evaluations/monitoring/implementation; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth knowledge of, and experience with, participatory evaluation methods; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully familiar and proven working experience with the EC&amp;rsquo;s Project Cycle Management and Logical Framework approach; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with the EC procedures and rules and regulations; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with assessing gender aspects and other cross-cutting issues; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience in Sub-Saharan Africa is required; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant experience in Mozambique is an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English (oral, written and comprehension); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum good knowledge of the Portuguese language; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience and knowledge of the socio-political context of Mozambique would be an asset &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A good knowledge of the sugar industry or of comparable out grower programmes will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &amp;lsquo;Nicte Garcia-soria&amp;rsquo; &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert Spécialiste du Processus Electoral (Catégorie I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-specialiste-du-processus-electoral</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 16:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-specialiste-du-processus-electoral</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation finale du Programme d&amp;#39;appui au Processus Electoral&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif général du projet est réaliser l’évaluation finale du programme afin de dégager des recommandations concrètes à destination de la delegation de l’UE pour ses interventions dans le domaine du processus électoral au Cameroun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert Spécialiste du Processus Electoral (Catégorie I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formation universitaire en sciences social, politique, humaine ou économique (BAC+5 ou équivalent);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle d’au moins 12 ans dans la coopération et le développement;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans la formulation, la mise en œuvre et/ou le suivi ou l’évaluation de projets dans le domaine électoral;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience pratique d’évaluation d’au moins deux projets financés par le FED;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance du secteur électoral dans divers pays en Afrique francophone;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spécialisation en suivi ou observation des élections;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne connaissance de l’environnement économique et institutionnel africain;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance du domaine électoral au Cameroun;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jouit d’une excellente capacité d’analyse, de synthèse et de rédaction des rapports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent français (écrit et parlé) ; Bonnes connaissances d’anglais (écrit et parlé).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICAT&lt;/strong&gt;IONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior M&amp;E and Extension Development Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-me-and-extension-development-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 13:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-me-and-extension-development-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Evaluation of the PEP and Operationalisation of PEP II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The assignment will pursue two objectives and will, thus, develop into two separate, although interlinked, phases, to be carried-out by the same team of consultants, consisting of 1) the final evaluation of PEP; and 2) the development of recommendations for PEP II. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) To provide the relevant external co-operation services of the European Union and the Zambian government with: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an independent assessment of the performance and impact of the &amp;ldquo;Support to the Agricultural Sector Performance Enhancement Programme&amp;rdquo; (PEP), paying particular attention to the project&amp;rsquo;s achievements against its expected results and purpose; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a re-assessment of the strategic objectives and implementation mechanisms of PEP as well as of the extent to which these have been effective in delivering results; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;key lessons learned from PEP and recommendations to improve the future implementation of the follow up &amp;ldquo;Performance Enhancement Programme for the Ministry of Agriculture and the Ministry of Fisheries and Livestock for Better Service Delivery to Farmers&amp;rdquo; (PEP II).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) To assist the Ministry of Agriculture and the Ministry of Fisheries and Livestock, the National Authorising Officer and the European Union Delegation in the operationalisation of PEP II through the provision of strategic recommendations for the development of the related multiannual programme estimate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior M&amp;amp;E and Extension Development Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree (or, in its absence, 12 years of equivalent professional experience) in statistics, economics, agriculture, agricultural economics, Business studies, social science or any relevant field related to the sector of this assignment. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in both written and spoken English. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Initiative, good interpersonal skills and demonstrated ability to work in multicultural environments. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of professional experience with designing, implementing and/or evaluating donor-funded projects supporting the strengthening of extension and research capacities and services for agriculture and/or rural development; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of experience with M&amp;amp;E systems design, implementation and/or evaluation in public service institutions. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with developing and using the logical framework approach and other results-based strategic planning approaches for donor-funded programme/project monitoring and evaluation. Similar experience under EU-funded programmes in sub-Saharan Africa will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of and experience with EDF rules and procedures will be seen as an advantage; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 years relevant experience of working in developing countries. Experience in sub-Saharan Africa will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Institutional Capacity Development and Human Resources Management Expert (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-institutional-capacity-development-and-human-resources-management-expert-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 12:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-institutional-capacity-development-and-human-resources-management-expert-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Evaluation of the PEP and Operationalisation of PEP II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The assignment will pursue two objectives and will, thus, develop into two separate, although interlinked, phases, to be carried-out by the same team of consultants, consisting of 1) the final evaluation of PEP; and 2) the development of recommendations for PEP II. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) To provide the relevant external co-operation services of the European Union and the Zambian government with: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• an independent assessment of the performance and impact of the &amp;ldquo;Support to the Agricultural Sector Performance Enhancement Programme&amp;rdquo; (PEP), paying particular attention to the project&amp;rsquo;s achievements against its expected results and purpose; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a re-assessment of the strategic objectives and implementation mechanisms of PEP as well as of the extent to which these have been effective in delivering results; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;key lessons learned from PEP and recommendations to improve the future implementation of the follow up &amp;ldquo;Performance Enhancement Programme for the Ministry of Agriculture and the Ministry of Fisheries and Livestock for Better Service Delivery to Farmers&amp;rdquo; (PEP II).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) To assist the Ministry of Agriculture and the Ministry of Fisheries and Livestock, the National Authorising Officer and the European Union Delegation in the operationalisation of PEP II through the provision of strategic recommendations for the development of the related multiannual programme estimate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Institutional Capacity Development and Human Resources Management Expert (TL)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Team Leader will be the liaison person for the EU Delegation for all matters related to the implementation of the assignment and of the delivery of expected outputs. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree (or, in its absence, 12 years of equivalent professional experience) in public policy, public administration, human resources management, economics, business management or any relevant field related to the sector of this assignment. Certification of Registration with Human Resources professional bodies will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in both written and spoken English; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Initiative, tact and ability to maintain harmonious working relationships in a multicultural setting; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of professional experience with designing, implementing and/or evaluating donor-funded institutional support projects addressing public service reforms, capacity development and change management in the public sector; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience working as a Team Leader of civil service reform and/or agricultural projects. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 years of experience with designing, implementing and/or evaluating donor-funded projects focusing on policy development and implementation in the public sector. Similar experience in the agricultural sector will be seen as an advantage; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of professional experience with designing, implementing and/or evaluating donor-funded projects supporting the strengthening of human resources management and human resource development capacity and training in government organisations; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 years of experience with developing and/or evaluating policies, strategies, approaches, and tools for effective HIV &amp;amp; AIDS and gender mainstreaming in donor-funded programs and projects; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of and experience with EDF rules and procedures will be seen as an advantage; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 years of relevant experience of working in developing countries. Experience in sub-Saharan Africa will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWP 2 Projects Review</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Beyond WTO Program (B-WTO) was developed in response to a request from the Government of Vietnam (GoV) for donor support to help with managing economic integration and the transition to a market economy following WTO accession. The B-WTO goal is “to strengthen government’s capacity to manage the integration of Vietnam into the global economy and the transition of Vietnam to a socialist market economy”. The immediate objective is “implementation of priority policy actions from the GoV’s Action Plan to enhance Vietnam’s capacity to sustain pro-poor growth (GAP)”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The remit of this project was a review of the 2nd annual work plan’s implementation (AWP2) of Phase 2 of the B-WTO in May 2013. The objectives of the review were to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the project implementation performance and project results relative to the logical framework targets and evaluation criteria. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the results achieved at the Component and Program’s level according to the Monitoring and Evaluation (M&amp;amp;E) framework of the Program.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify lessons learned from implementation, make recommendations for the remaining duration of the program and the Independent Completion Report process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program 2013 Performance and Quality Mapping Exercise</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID’s PNG Program is looking to improve its performance and quality (P&amp;amp;Q) standards and systems. The purpose of this project was to map the PNG Program’s current P&amp;amp;Q capacity and systems, to address the risk of AusAID being unable to demonstrate results for its increased investments in PNG over the next four years. Over the last several years, the PNG Program has undertaken a number of M&amp;amp;E assessments and reviews which have identified key strengths and challenges within the program. This project was intended to pick up where these assessments left off. Through a desk review and consultations with sector teams, the Review Team were to distil key P&amp;amp;Q risks and issues for the PNG Program. The Review Team’s brief included the provision of recommendations on priority activities to support sector approaches to M&amp;amp;E, strengthen the Program’s ability to collect evidence, provide critical analysis and report on results.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID required a consultant to assist with the development and finalisation of its Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework. Development of a humanitarian monitoring and evaluation framework is a key commitment outlined in AusAID’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy (HAP) and its associated Implementation Plan. In line with the agency focus on results reporting, the HAP and HAP Implementation Plan commit AusAID to develop a monitoring and evaluation framework to support the initial performance assessment framework contained within the HAP and AusAID annual reporting under the Comprehensive Aid Policy Framework.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key objective of this assignment was to build the Humanitarian program’s capacity for monitoring and reporting results by:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In consultation with AusAID’s Humanitarian team, redraft and finalise the Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework, to ensure it provides a platform to:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track implementation of key commitments in Australia’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy; and,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish a set of measurable humanitarian performance indicators (in addition to the two CAPF indicators) to enable AusAID to track achievements, lessons learned and to report on the results achieved from AusAID’s humanitarian work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of Pacific Forum Compact Reporting</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The purpose of the assignment was to examine country views of aid effectiveness and regional organisations expressed through Forum Compact reporting, particularly peer review of Forum Island Countries’ national development plan processes. The services provided included the preparation of a think piece which outlines key aid effectiveness issues arising from country reporting under the Compact reporting and discusses options for addressing these issues.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study on Community-based Social Protection</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/study-on-community-based-social-protection</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/study-on-community-based-social-protection</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Poverty and Social Analysis is the process of using and generating evidence on poverty throughout the aid management cycle. Most poverty and social analysis focuses on economic and human capital, but there are two oft neglected elements: voice and influence, and social capital. Yet more and more development practitioners are recognizing the importance of social capital, particularly informal social capital, in preventing and addressing poverty and vulnerability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This project supported AusAID to explore:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the role of informal social capital in the Fijian context and whether it lends itself to fair redistribution of resources and, if so, the ways in which AusAID can engage with local communities to strengthen existing social capital structures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;how such structures can enable the disempowered and poor to claim their entitlements in the three domains discussed in the PSA framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the potential challenges that can arise from such efforts. For instance, the poorest are often included on less favorable terms within social networks, and have access to fewer and lower-quality networks. Further, we need to better understand how poverty and disempowerment intersect with an absence of informal social capital, the repercussions this has, and the options available for tackling this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Provision of a Child Protection Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/provision-of-a-child-protection-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/provision-of-a-child-protection-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For this project HTSPE was contracted to provide a child protection specialist and handle all the associated management and administrative work. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The child protection specialist provided by HTSPE was required to work on an assignment designed to assist the Pacific Division (PACD) to improve its approach to child protection and managing risks to children. AusAID has a number of partners in the Pacific who work with children or come into contact with children through their activities. The AusAID-wide child protection stocktake, conducted in May 2013 found that there are a number of organisations funded by AusAID in the Pacific with a high or very high inherent child protection risk. Consistent with the stocktake report PACD proposes to escalate efforts to ensure partner organisations policies, procedures and practices are in accordance with AusAID’s Child Protection Policy 2013 and to make child protection a more explicit focus of PACD’s risk management system.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
