<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 21:00:47 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social and Economic Analyst with Experience in the Pacific Islands</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/social-and-economic-analyst-with-experience-in-the-pacific-islands</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2014 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/social-and-economic-analyst-with-experience-in-the-pacific-islands</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2&gt;Project Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Impact Assessment of the Small Business Enterprise Centre (SBEC) and the Private Sector Support Facility (PSSF)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HTSPE requires consultants with experience of undertaking Impact Assessments to assist with the upcoming evaluation of the Small Business Enterprise Centre (SBEC) and the Private Sector Support Facility (PSSF) in Samoa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;objectives of the study&lt;/strong&gt; are to assess:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the role and contribution of SBEC Samoa to the economic    livelihoods of small and medium size businesses in Samoa&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the quality of services provided by SBEC Samoa to their clients and stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the operations of SBEC and costs associated with the operations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the sustainability of SBEC operations in the future&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the role and contribution of the PSSF to the economic livelihoods of businesses in Samoa&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the quality of services provided by PSSF Secretariat to their clients and stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the operations of PSSF and costs associated with the operations. The assessment should take into account the impact that the redesigned framework has had on the operations of the facility in delivering its mandate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the sustainability of PSSF operations in the future&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the results from exploration/promotional visits and trade shows overseas attended by applicants through PSSF funding.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scope:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An economic analysis of the impact of SBEC services to small businesses and the contribution of small businesses to the economy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A social analysis of the benefits and costs derived to the families and communities from small businesses supported through SBEC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An assessment of the role of small businesses in the development of Samoan economy in terms of employment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An analysis of the issues faced by small businesses in Samoa and the need for SBEC’s services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing baseline information to assist SBEC in developing targets for the next 5 years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An assessment of SBEC’s role and services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An economic analysis of the impact of PSSF services to the growth of business in Samoa&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A social analysis of the benefits and costs derived to the families and communities from small businesses supported through PSSF&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing baseline information to assist PSSF in developing targets for the next 5 years.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An economic analysis of the results from overseas trips funded by PSSF for applicants to attend exploration /promotional visits and trade shows in relation to the economic benefit derived from local marketing and promotion. An assessment of impact of PSSF activity on other private sector stakeholders in Samoa (e.g government, private sector organizations)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An assessment of PSSF’s role and services in the next five to 10 years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An assessment of the achievement or otherwise of an enabling environment for the private sector through the PSSF&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location: Home-based and Samoa&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Experience &amp;amp; Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Social and Economic Analyst with experience in the Pacific Islands (2-3 positions)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in a relevant field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be an economic and/or business analyst with at least 5 years’ experience in this field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social analyst with experience and understanding of the Samoan social and cultural contexts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Background and experience in assessing organisations and seeking funding options for organisations in the future&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the Samoan business environment and understanding government policies on trade, commerce and industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oral and written communication skills in Samoan would be an advantage, but not required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The assignment will start in July 2014, for an estimated  40 days (20 days’ field work plus 15 days for the report preparations, with an additional 5 days for comments).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Application Procedure&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for these nominated roles please email your CV  with a covering note outlining how you fit the requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please email your application to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarah.owen@htspe.com&quot;&gt;sarah.owen@htspe.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting SBEC/PSSF in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regional Development Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/regional-development-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2014 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/regional-development-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2&gt;Project Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Verification of the Rural Development Support Programme (RDSP, AAP 2011) Compliance in Azerbaijan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this assignment is to assist the Government of Azerbaijan (GoA) in the implementation of reforms in rural development in line with the State Program on poverty reduction and sustainable development in the Azerbaijan Republic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this assignment is to conduct two detailed reviews of GoA compliance to conditions laid out in the EU funded Rural Development Support Programme (RDSP, AAP 2011), on the basis of which the European Commission will decide on disbursements of the first and second variable tranches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requested services, including suggested methodology&lt;/strong&gt;
The The consultant team will conduct two three-week missions to Azerbaijan, one in November 2014 and one in October 2015 to verify GoA compliance with the provisions of the RDSP Technical and Administrative Provisions (TAPs). The review will be conducted on the basis of a disbursement request and materials prepared in advance and translated by the GoA, and on-site visits where relevant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Experience &amp;amp; Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Regional Development Expert: (36 work days)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in rural/regional development, economics or equivalent, or, in its absence equivalent professional experience of at least 15 years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in written and spoken English (competence at least 2 on a scale of 1 to 5 (1 - excellent; 5 – basic)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Azerbaijani, Turkish or Russian would be asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 10 years of professional working experience on regional and rural development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 5 years&amp;#39; experience programming and/or implementing economic development and diversification initiatives in developing countries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work experience in the Neighbourhood Region of the EU would be an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in budget support programmes would be an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Application Procedure&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe.messenger@htspe.com&quot;&gt;chloe.messenger@htspe.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We are only able to respond to candidates who meet the specifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Legal and Economic Research of EU Environmental Legislation Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-legal-and-economic-research-of-eu-environmental-legislation-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2014 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author> </author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-legal-and-economic-research-of-eu-environmental-legislation-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2&gt;Project Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Development of National Climate Change Strategy by 2030&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The broader Global Objective of the assignment is to ensure an economically, environmentally and socially sound and viable development of Montenegro in a long-term perspective with special focus on climate change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Specific Objectives&lt;/strong&gt; of the assignment are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analysis of relevant national plans, programmes, strategies and legal framework in order to identify the current state of play, in particular the gaps to be addressed by the final strategic document. Identification and preparation of emission scenarios and analysis of GHG emissions and projections by sector;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Programme the strategic approach to climate change using three scenarios model – comprising different combination of assumptions: without measures, with measures and with additional measures in different timeframe (2020-2025-2030) in accordance with IPPC and EMEP/EEA Emission Inventory Guidebook and other relevant methodologies as necessary. Identification of the sensitivity and the level of uncertainty of projections in order to enable flexible planning of specific measures for achievement of planned results;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preparation of final draft National Climate Change Strategy, taking into account SEA procedure and public discussion process, ready for approval by all stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Experience &amp;amp; Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Legal and Economic Research of EU Environmental Legislation Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Excellent &lt;strong&gt;English&lt;/strong&gt; language&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Education of at least Master degree in the &lt;strong&gt;field of Law&lt;/strong&gt; or equivalent professional experience of at least &lt;strong&gt;15 years in the field of EU and international environmental and climate legislation&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum &lt;strong&gt;12 years’ experience&lt;/strong&gt; in the field of:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Legal analysis of strategic documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support to national authorities in the implementation of environmental policies in line with EU acquis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To have at least &lt;strong&gt;5 years work experience&lt;/strong&gt; in the following fields relevant for this assignment:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;EU environnemental and climat acquis. Drafting of legal acts and transposition of EU environmental acquis into national legislative frameworks;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assessing of environmental compliance through comparison of national, international and EU environmental and climate legislation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Economy of environmental measures in the climate change development strategies cost-benefit of environmentally conscious development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Application Procedure&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe.messenger@htspe.com&quot;&gt;chloe.messenger@htspe.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We are only able to respond to candidates who meet the specifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agricultural Experts with Experience of Working with MFAT</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/agricultural-experts-mfat-experience</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2014 13:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/agricultural-experts-mfat-experience</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2&gt;Project Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;New Zealand Aid Programme&lt;/strong&gt;, acting for and on behalf of the Ministry of Foreign Affairs and Trade &lt;strong&gt;(MFAT)&lt;/strong&gt;, has appointed a Panel of specialist advisers and organisations with a wide range of skills, capabilities and areas of expertise across the &lt;strong&gt;Agriculture&lt;/strong&gt; sector. This range reflects the diverse and international nature of New Zealand Aid Programme work that is often conducted in niche areas of specific regions and countries. MFAT will use the Panel as its preferred sourcing method for &lt;strong&gt;agriculture sector specialists&lt;/strong&gt; to support the delivery of international development activities, and will open for a two year term with the option to extend for an additional two years at MFAT’s discretion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HTSPE&lt;/strong&gt;, with their partner &lt;strong&gt;AgFirst New Zealand&lt;/strong&gt;, is one of the contractors on a pre-approved list of suppliers who are available to provide MFAT with the specified services outlined in the Deed of Standing Offer. Over time, MFAT may expand the panel to meet evolving business needs or if they require additional specialisms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 16 agriculture specialisms provided across the Panel are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agribusiness&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. attracting investors to the agricultural industry; preparing a range of policy options for agribusiness development; designing and implementing livelihood projects;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agricultural economics&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. monitoring and evaluation of agricultural programs; carrying out financial and cost-benefit analyses; leading financial surveys;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agricultural extension services and technology transfer&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. carrying out training; agricultural extension; rural advisory services; technology transfer programs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Applied agricultural research&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. design and implementation of applied research trials;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Market access&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. development of efficient and effective rural markets; value chain approaches; conducting reviews and surveys to identify new market opportunities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tropical cash crop and food production&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. knowledge of tropical cultivation, including annual and perennial crops; agro-production and marketing;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Temperate cash crop and food production&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. advising on production methods for temperate crops;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food safety&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. phytosanitary standards; animal welfare and health; food safety regulations;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tropical and/or Dryland Livestock production&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. research on the challenges facing livestock production in these areas; livestock production evaluations;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Temperate Livestock production&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. identifying and reviewing animal health issues, designing and implementing methods for improved production;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organic production and/or ethical certification systems&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. providing knowledge and advice on farm management, productivity and best practice around organic production; conducting a review on the applicability of ethical certification systems, such as Fair Trade;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Post-harvest operations&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. advising on the storage of crops post-harvest; methods of crop mechanisation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agro-processing&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. assess and review food processing techniques; advise on the potential to expand into new markets;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food security&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. knowledge of food security information systems and early warning systems; familiarity with the availability of various subsidies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agriculture education and curriculum development&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. understanding of agriculture issues in New Zealand; experience in delivering training courses and workshops;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trade and market analysis&lt;/strong&gt; e.g. capable of undertaking evidence-based analyses; establishing contact with key partners and stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**Duration of overall Panel contract: March 2014 - May 2016 (may be extended)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Experience &amp;amp; Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agricultural Experts with experience of working with MFAT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to enhance our Consultants&amp;#39; Database, HTSPE would like to hear from consultants with expertise in the above agriculture specialisms, and with experience of working with MFAT, who would be interested in assignments within this Panel Agreement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**Experience and Qualifications required&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum bachelor level degree;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly skilled agricultural professionals with experience in any of the aforementioned 16 specialisms;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A good understanding of agricultural practices in New Zealand;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong stakeholder management skills, with proven ability to identify stakeholder needs and achieve desired results;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working on donor-funded development programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of project management and the project life cycle;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working in the Asia-Pacific region;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in spoken and written English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Application Procedure&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the criteria and would like to be considered for Panel assignments please email your CV to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:hr@htspe.com&quot;&gt;hr@htspe.com&lt;/a&gt; quoting &lt;strong&gt;2013127/AA/MFAT&lt;/strong&gt; in the subject line of your email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We are only able to respond to candidates who meet the specifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
