<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 08:29:47 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert with TL &amp; M&amp;E Experience in Rural Community/Poverty Alleviation Programmes (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-with-tl-me-experience-in-rural-community-poverty-alleviation-programmes-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 08:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-with-tl-me-experience-in-rural-community-poverty-alleviation-programmes-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Review of the Accompanying Measures Sugar Protocol (AMSP) 2011-2013&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective is to elaborate an independent mid-term evaluation which will provide the decision-makers in the Government of Mozambique, the relevant external co-operation services of the European Commission and the wider public with sufficient information to: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make an overall independent assessment of the performance, so far of the programme, paying particularly attention to the results already achieved or expected to be achieved, and potential impact of the project against its objectives; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Draw key lessons and propose practical recommendations in order to improve current and future action and for addressing challenges faced by the programme. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert with TL &amp;amp; M&amp;amp;E Experience in Rural Community/Poverty Alleviation Programmes (Category I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master degree in rural development, rural economics, social sciences or related field; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years professional experience in development cooperation in management, evaluation and monitoring of rural/community development and/or poverty alleviation programmes; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years&amp;#39; experience as team-leader in project evaluations/monitoring/implementation; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth knowledge of, and experience with, participatory evaluation methods; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully familiar and proven working experience with the EC&amp;rsquo;s Project Cycle Management and Logical Framework approach; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with the EC procedures and rules and regulations; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with assessing gender aspects and other cross-cutting issues; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience in Sub-Saharan Africa is required; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant experience in Mozambique is an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English (oral, written and comprehension); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum good knowledge of the Portuguese language; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience and knowledge of the socio-political context of Mozambique would be an asset &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A good knowledge of the sugar industry or of comparable out grower programmes will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &amp;lsquo;Nicte Garcia-soria&amp;rsquo; &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert Spécialiste du Processus Electoral (Catégorie I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-specialiste-du-processus-electoral</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 16:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-specialiste-du-processus-electoral</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation finale du Programme d&amp;#39;appui au Processus Electoral&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif général du projet est réaliser l’évaluation finale du programme afin de dégager des recommandations concrètes à destination de la delegation de l’UE pour ses interventions dans le domaine du processus électoral au Cameroun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert Spécialiste du Processus Electoral (Catégorie I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formation universitaire en sciences social, politique, humaine ou économique (BAC+5 ou équivalent);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle d’au moins 12 ans dans la coopération et le développement;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans la formulation, la mise en œuvre et/ou le suivi ou l’évaluation de projets dans le domaine électoral;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience pratique d’évaluation d’au moins deux projets financés par le FED;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance du secteur électoral dans divers pays en Afrique francophone;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spécialisation en suivi ou observation des élections;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne connaissance de l’environnement économique et institutionnel africain;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance du domaine électoral au Cameroun;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jouit d’une excellente capacité d’analyse, de synthèse et de rédaction des rapports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent français (écrit et parlé) ; Bonnes connaissances d’anglais (écrit et parlé).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICAT&lt;/strong&gt;IONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior M&amp;E and Extension Development Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-me-and-extension-development-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 13:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-me-and-extension-development-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Evaluation of the PEP and Operationalisation of PEP II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The assignment will pursue two objectives and will, thus, develop into two separate, although interlinked, phases, to be carried-out by the same team of consultants, consisting of 1) the final evaluation of PEP; and 2) the development of recommendations for PEP II. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) To provide the relevant external co-operation services of the European Union and the Zambian government with: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an independent assessment of the performance and impact of the &amp;ldquo;Support to the Agricultural Sector Performance Enhancement Programme&amp;rdquo; (PEP), paying particular attention to the project&amp;rsquo;s achievements against its expected results and purpose; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a re-assessment of the strategic objectives and implementation mechanisms of PEP as well as of the extent to which these have been effective in delivering results; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;key lessons learned from PEP and recommendations to improve the future implementation of the follow up &amp;ldquo;Performance Enhancement Programme for the Ministry of Agriculture and the Ministry of Fisheries and Livestock for Better Service Delivery to Farmers&amp;rdquo; (PEP II).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) To assist the Ministry of Agriculture and the Ministry of Fisheries and Livestock, the National Authorising Officer and the European Union Delegation in the operationalisation of PEP II through the provision of strategic recommendations for the development of the related multiannual programme estimate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior M&amp;amp;E and Extension Development Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree (or, in its absence, 12 years of equivalent professional experience) in statistics, economics, agriculture, agricultural economics, Business studies, social science or any relevant field related to the sector of this assignment. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in both written and spoken English. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Initiative, good interpersonal skills and demonstrated ability to work in multicultural environments. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of professional experience with designing, implementing and/or evaluating donor-funded projects supporting the strengthening of extension and research capacities and services for agriculture and/or rural development; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of experience with M&amp;amp;E systems design, implementation and/or evaluation in public service institutions. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with developing and using the logical framework approach and other results-based strategic planning approaches for donor-funded programme/project monitoring and evaluation. Similar experience under EU-funded programmes in sub-Saharan Africa will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of and experience with EDF rules and procedures will be seen as an advantage; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 years relevant experience of working in developing countries. Experience in sub-Saharan Africa will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Institutional Capacity Development and Human Resources Management Expert (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-institutional-capacity-development-and-human-resources-management-expert-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 12:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-institutional-capacity-development-and-human-resources-management-expert-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Evaluation of the PEP and Operationalisation of PEP II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The assignment will pursue two objectives and will, thus, develop into two separate, although interlinked, phases, to be carried-out by the same team of consultants, consisting of 1) the final evaluation of PEP; and 2) the development of recommendations for PEP II. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) To provide the relevant external co-operation services of the European Union and the Zambian government with: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• an independent assessment of the performance and impact of the &amp;ldquo;Support to the Agricultural Sector Performance Enhancement Programme&amp;rdquo; (PEP), paying particular attention to the project&amp;rsquo;s achievements against its expected results and purpose; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a re-assessment of the strategic objectives and implementation mechanisms of PEP as well as of the extent to which these have been effective in delivering results; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;key lessons learned from PEP and recommendations to improve the future implementation of the follow up &amp;ldquo;Performance Enhancement Programme for the Ministry of Agriculture and the Ministry of Fisheries and Livestock for Better Service Delivery to Farmers&amp;rdquo; (PEP II).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) To assist the Ministry of Agriculture and the Ministry of Fisheries and Livestock, the National Authorising Officer and the European Union Delegation in the operationalisation of PEP II through the provision of strategic recommendations for the development of the related multiannual programme estimate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Institutional Capacity Development and Human Resources Management Expert (TL)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Team Leader will be the liaison person for the EU Delegation for all matters related to the implementation of the assignment and of the delivery of expected outputs. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree (or, in its absence, 12 years of equivalent professional experience) in public policy, public administration, human resources management, economics, business management or any relevant field related to the sector of this assignment. Certification of Registration with Human Resources professional bodies will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in both written and spoken English; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Initiative, tact and ability to maintain harmonious working relationships in a multicultural setting; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of professional experience with designing, implementing and/or evaluating donor-funded institutional support projects addressing public service reforms, capacity development and change management in the public sector; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience working as a Team Leader of civil service reform and/or agricultural projects. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 years of experience with designing, implementing and/or evaluating donor-funded projects focusing on policy development and implementation in the public sector. Similar experience in the agricultural sector will be seen as an advantage; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of professional experience with designing, implementing and/or evaluating donor-funded projects supporting the strengthening of human resources management and human resource development capacity and training in government organisations; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 years of experience with developing and/or evaluating policies, strategies, approaches, and tools for effective HIV &amp;amp; AIDS and gender mainstreaming in donor-funded programs and projects; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of and experience with EDF rules and procedures will be seen as an advantage; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 years of relevant experience of working in developing countries. Experience in sub-Saharan Africa will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert(e), de Catégorie I, en Renforcement des Capacités des Collectivités Territoriales</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-de-categorie-i-en-renforcement-des-capacites-des-collectivites-territoriales</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 12:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-de-categorie-i-en-renforcement-des-capacites-des-collectivites-territoriales</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appui a la Delegation de l&amp;#39;Union europeenne pour I&amp;#39;Identification et la formulation d&amp;#39;un &amp;lsquo;programme de developpement territorial&amp;rsquo; au Maroc&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif général&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contribuer à la mise en oeuvre de la stratégie de coopération de l&amp;#39;Union européenne avec le Royaume du Maroc, notamment en matière de promotion d&amp;#39;une croissance durable et inclusive en faveur du développement humain et de renforcement de la démocratie et la gouvernance locale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif particulier&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Procéder à l&amp;#39;identification et la formulation du programme d&amp;#39;appui sectoriel de l&amp;#39;Union européenne au développement territorial intégré des zones rurales et enclavées.Cette identification/formulation devra répondre à certains principes directeurs, à savoir :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Le programme d’appui devrait promouvoir une approche territoriale centrée sur une plus grande responsabilisation de la commune, tout en s’inscrivant dans le dispositif de la « régionalisation avancée » ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ce faisant le programme contribuera à faire émerger « par le bas » des procédures appropriées d’identification, de financement, de mise en oeuvre et de gestion du développement local tout en s’inscrivant dans le système de gouvernance territoriale multiacteurs et multi-niveaux constitué par la « régionalisation avancée » ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;L’appui envisagé pourrait offrir une opportunité de tester, dans une région pilote, les dispositifs envisagés dans la législation nationale et capitaliser les leçons apprises.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location&lt;/strong&gt;: La mission se déroulera essentiellement à Rabat. Des déplacements dans d&amp;#39;autres provinces pourraient être nécessaires.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert(e), de Catégorie I, en Renforcement des Capacités des Collectivités Territoriales&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale : niveau d’enseignement correspondant à un cycle complet d’études universitaires de 4 années ou plus sanctionné par un diplôme dans le domaine de l&amp;#39;administration publique, des sciences politiques ou juridiques ou d&amp;#39;un domaine équivalent est requis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale : très bonne maîtrise de la langue française parlée et écrite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale : au moins 12 années d&amp;#39;expérience dans la conception, la mise en œuvre ou l&amp;#39;évaluation de politiques publiques menées par des collectivités locales.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Atout : au moins 2 expériences (2 projets ou programmes) acquises à l’international dans ce domaine.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Atout : au moins 2 ans d’expérience en matière d&amp;#39;animation de processus multi-acteurs et processus de développement participatif au niveau local.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale : au moins 5 ans d&amp;#39;expérience dans le domaine du renforcement des capacités des collectivités locales ou des services déconcentrés de l&amp;#39;Etat en milieu rural.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale : au moins 3 ans d&amp;#39;expérience dans le domaine de la gestion du développement local dans un contexte de décentralisation (planification, élaboration et mise en oeuvre de stratégies locales de développement, de développement de maîtrise d&amp;#39;ouvrage communale, de gestion partenariale, …).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Atout : connaissance (acquise dans le cadre des études, de recherches, ou de l’expérience professionnelle) des modalités d&amp;#39;intervention de l&amp;#39;aide extérieure européenne notamment de l&amp;#39;appui budgétaire sectoriel, de l&amp;#39;approche projet, des contrats d&amp;#39;assistance technique et de jumelage).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert(e), de Catégorie I, en Développement Social</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-de-categorie-i-en-developpement-social</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 12:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-de-categorie-i-en-developpement-social</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appui a la Delegation de l&amp;#39;Union europeenne pour I&amp;#39;Identification et la formulation d&amp;#39;un &amp;lsquo;programme de developpement territorial&amp;rsquo; au Maroc&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif général&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contribuer à la mise en oeuvre de la stratégie de coopération de l&amp;#39;Union européenne avec le Royaume du Maroc, notamment en matière de promotion d&amp;#39;une croissance durable et inclusive en faveur du développement humain et de renforcement de la démocratie et la gouvernance locale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif particulier&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Procéder à l&amp;#39;identification et la formulation du programme d&amp;#39;appui sectoriel de l&amp;#39;Union européenne au développement territorial intégré des zones rurales et enclavées. Cette identification/formulation devra répondre à certains principes directeurs, à savoir :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Le programme d’appui devrait promouvoir une approche territoriale centrée sur une plus grande responsabilisation de la commune, tout en s’inscrivant dans le dispositif de la « régionalisation avancée » ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ce faisant le programme contribuera à faire émerger « par le bas » des procédures appropriées d’identification, de financement, de mise en oeuvre et de gestion du développement local tout en s’inscrivant dans le système de gouvernance territoriale multiacteurs et multi-niveaux constitué par la « régionalisation avancée » ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;L’appui envisagé pourrait offrir une opportunité de tester, dans une région pilote, les dispositifs envisagés dans la législation nationale et capitaliser les leçons apprises.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert(e), de Catégorie I, en Développement Social&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale : niveau d’enseignement correspondant à un cycle complet d’études universitaires de 4 années ou plus sanctionné par un diplôme dans le domaine des sciences sociales ou dans un domaine équivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale : très bonne maîtrise de la langue française parlée et écrite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale : au moins 12 années d&amp;#39;expérience dans le domaine du développement social (développement et gestion de services sociaux de type santé, éducation, alphabétisation, insertion des groupes vulnérables…) dont au moins 3 années acquises à l’international dans ce domaine.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale : au moins 3 expériences (3 projets ou programmes) dans le cadre de projets ou programmes ciblant le milieu rural.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale : au moins 5 années d&amp;#39;expérience dans la coordination, la gestion et la mise en oeuvre de politiques ou programmes de développement social ou de lutte contre la
pauvreté à grande échelle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale : au moins 2 expériences en matière d&amp;#39;élaboration, de suivi ou d&amp;#39;évaluation de programmes, stratégies ou politiques sociales.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Atout : au moins 3 années d&amp;#39;expérience en matière d&amp;#39;appui aux processus multi-acteurs et processus de développement participatif au niveau local.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Atout : au moins 2 expériences dans le domaine du renforcement des capacités (diagnostic des besoins, conception de plan de formations, animation de formations).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Atout : au moins 3 années d&amp;#39;expérience dans des pays figurant dans la liste de pays bénéficiaires de l&amp;#39;aide établie par le Comité d&amp;#39;Aide au Développement (CAD) de l&amp;#39;OCDE.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Atout : connaissance (acquise dans le cadre des études, de recherches, ou de l’expérience professionnelle) des modalités d&amp;#39;intervention de l&amp;#39;aide extérieure européenne notamment de l&amp;#39;appui budgétaire sectoriel, de l&amp;#39;approche projet, des contrats d&amp;#39;assistance technique et de jumelage).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert(e), de Catégorie I, Agroéconomiste</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-de-categorie-i-agroeconomiste</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-de-categorie-i-agroeconomiste</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appui a la Delegation de l&amp;#39;Union europeenne pour I&amp;#39;Identification et la formulation d&amp;#39;un &amp;lsquo;programme de developpement territorial&amp;rsquo; au Maroc&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif général :&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contribuer à la mise en oeuvre de la stratégie de coopération de l&amp;#39;Union européenne avec le Royaume du Maroc, notamment en matière de promotion d&amp;#39;une croissance durable et inclusive en faveur du développement humain et de renforcement de la démocratie et la gouvernance locale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif particulier:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Procéder à l&amp;#39;identification et la formulation du programme d&amp;#39;appui sectoriel de l&amp;#39;Union européenne au développement territorial intégré des zones rurales et enclavées. Cette identification/formulation devra répondre à certains principes directeurs, à savoir :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Le programme d’appui devrait promouvoir une approche territoriale centrée sur une plus grande responsabilisation de la commune, tout en s’inscrivant dans le dispositif de la « régionalisation avancée » ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ce faisant le programme contribuera à faire émerger « par le bas » des procédures appropriées d’identification, de financement, de mise en oeuvre et de gestion du développement local tout en s’inscrivant dans le système de gouvernance territoriale multiacteurs et multi-niveaux constitué par la « régionalisation avancée » ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;L’appui envisagé pourrait offrir une opportunité de tester, dans une région pilote, les dispositifs envisagés dans la législation nationale et capitaliser les leçons apprises.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location&lt;/strong&gt;: La mission se déroulera essentiellement à Rabat. Des déplacements dans d&amp;#39;autres provinces pourraient être nécessaires.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert(e), de Catégorie I, Agroéconomiste&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences :&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale : niveau d’enseignement correspondant à un cycle complet d’études universitaires de 4 années ou plus sanctionné par un diplôme dans le domaine de l&amp;#39;agroéconomie, des sciences économiques / de gestion, ou d&amp;#39;un domaine équivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale : très bonne maîtrise de la langue française parlée et écrite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale :&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale : au moins 12 années d&amp;#39;expérience dans l&amp;#39;appui aux politiques/stratégies publiques de développement agricole, dont au moins 3 années acquises à l’international dans ce domaine.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale : au moins 2 expériences (2 projets ou programmes) d&amp;#39;appui à la structuration et au développement de filières agricoles (études de marché, études filières,structuration des filières, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale : au moins 5 ans d&amp;#39;expérience dans l&amp;#39;analyse et l&amp;#39;évaluation des politiques d&amp;#39;appui aux coopératives et groupements de petits producteurs en milieu rural.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Atout : au moins 2 expériences (2 projets ou programmes) en matière d’appui à la commercialisation des productions agricoles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Atout : connaissance (acquise dans le cadre des études, de recherches, ou de l’expérience professionnelle) des modalités d&amp;#39;intervention de l&amp;#39;aide extérieure européenne notamment de l&amp;#39;appui budgétaire sectoriel, de l&amp;#39;approche projet, des contrats d&amp;#39;assistance technique et de
jumelage).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert(e), de Catégorie I en Développement Rural Intégré - Chef de Mission</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-de-categorie-i-en-developpement-rural-integre-chef-de-mission</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-de-categorie-i-en-developpement-rural-integre-chef-de-mission</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appui a la Delegation de l&amp;#39;Union europeenne pour I&amp;#39;Identification et la formulation d&amp;#39;un &amp;lsquo;programme de developpement territorial&amp;rsquo; au Maroc&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif général&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contribuer à la mise en oeuvre de la stratégie de coopération de l&amp;#39;Union européenne avec le Royaume du Maroc, notamment en matière de promotion d&amp;#39;une croissance durable et inclusive en faveur du développement humain et de renforcement de la démocratie et la gouvernance locale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif particulier:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Procéder à l&amp;#39;identification et la formulation du programme d&amp;#39;appui sectoriel de l&amp;#39;Union européenne au développement territorial intégré des zones rurales et enclavées. Cette identification/formulation devra répondre à certains principes directeurs, à savoir :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Le programme d’appui devrait promouvoir une approche territoriale centrée sur une plus grande responsabilisation de la commune, tout en s’inscrivant dans le dispositif de la « régionalisation avancée » ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ce faisant le programme contribuera à faire émerger « par le bas » des procédures appropriées d’identification, de financement, de mise en oeuvre et de gestion du développement local tout en s’inscrivant dans le système de gouvernance territoriale multiacteurs et multi-niveaux constitué par la « régionalisation avancée » ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;L’appui envisagé pourrait offrir une opportunité de tester, dans une région pilote, les dispositifs envisagés dans la législation nationale et capitaliser les leçons apprises.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location visits&lt;/strong&gt;: La mission se déroulera essentiellement à Rabat. Des déplacements dans d&amp;#39;autres provinces pourraient être nécessaires.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert(e), de Catégorie I en Développement Rural Intégré - Chef de Mission&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale : niveau d’enseignement correspondant à un cycle complet d’études universitaires de 4 années ou plus sanctionné par un diplôme dans le domaine du développement local ou rural ou autre domaine équivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale : très bonne maîtrise de la langue française parlée et écrite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale :&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale : au moins 12 années d&amp;#39;expérience dans la conception, la mise en œuvre ou l&amp;#39;évaluation de politiques de développement rural / local dont au moins 3 années acquises
à l’international dans ce domaine.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale : au moins 3 ans d’expérience d’assistance technique en tant que chef de mission en charge de la gestion d&amp;#39;équipes d&amp;#39;experts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Atout : au moins 2 expériences (2 projets ou programmes) dans l’identification et le suivi d&amp;#39;indicateurs de politiques et/ou de mécanismes institutionnels d&amp;#39;appui aux politiques
sectorielles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale : au moins 5 ans d&amp;#39;expérience dans la coordination, la gestion ou la mise en oeuvre de programmes ou projets de développement local ou rural intégrés à caractère multisectoriel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale : au moins 3 ans d&amp;#39;expérience dans le domaine de la gestion durable des ressources environnementales.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Atout : au moins 2 expériences (2 projets ou programmes) en matière de développement participatif au niveau local.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Atout : connaissance (acquise dans le cadre des études, de recherches, ou de l’expérience professionnelle) des modalités d&amp;#39;intervention de l&amp;#39;aide extérieure européenne notamment de l&amp;#39;appui budgétaire sectoriel, de l&amp;#39;approche projet, des contrats d&amp;#39;assistance technique et de jumelage).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microfinance/Financial Inclusion Expert (Cat. II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/microfinance-financial-inclusion-expert-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 11:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/microfinance-financial-inclusion-expert-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Review of 2nd Disbursement Tranche&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;overall objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the assessment is to assist the Government of Jordan in eradicating poverty, promoting sustainable and inclusive growth, and consolidating and improving economic governance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; is to develop a clear assessment of Jordan&amp;rsquo;s achievement for the 2nd tranche specific reform benchmarks. The experts shall have the following main objectives: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Collect all compliance documents concerning the achievement of the 2nd tranche specific reform benchmarks; and &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To analyse factually the conformity of the compliance documentation obtained with the specifications and requirements defined in the TAPs, and establish whether the benchmark was met/achieved/partially achieved; and &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To contribute to maintain a high level of clarity, and a shared understanding by all stakeholders (the main stakeholders are those mentioned in section 1 of the present terms of reference), regarding the steps required to ensure that the benchmarks are met. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Microfinance/Financial Inclusion Expert (Cat. II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree or, in its absence, equivalent professional experience in: microfinance, access to credit, financial inclusion or other relevant subject is required;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant professional experience of at least 6 years;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 4 years of recent professional experience directly related to microfinance/financial inclusion;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Governments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in developing countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in the region;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the microfinance industry in Jordan (desirable);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and spoken English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in speaking, writing and reading Arabic (desirable).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Microfinance/Financial Inclusion Experts (Cat. I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/microfinance-financial-inclusion-experts-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/microfinance-financial-inclusion-experts-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Review of 2nd Disbursement Tranche&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;overall objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the assessment is to assist the Government of Jordan in eradicating poverty, promoting sustainable and inclusive growth, and consolidating and improving economic governance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; is to develop a clear assessment of Jordan&amp;rsquo;s achievement for the 2nd tranche specific reform benchmarks. The experts shall have the following main objectives: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Collect all compliance documents concerning the achievement of the 2nd tranche specific reform benchmarks; and &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To analyse factually the conformity of the compliance documentation obtained with the specifications and requirements defined in the TAPs, and establish whether the benchmark was met/achieved/partially achieved; and &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To contribute to maintain a high level of clarity, and a shared understanding by all stakeholders (the main stakeholders are those mentioned in section 1 of the present terms of reference), regarding the steps required to ensure that the benchmarks are met. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Microfinance/Financial Inclusion Experts (Cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree or, in its absence, equivalent professional experience in: microfinance, access to credit, financial inclusion or other relevant subject is required;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant professional experience of at least 12 years;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 8 years of recent professional experience directly related to microfinance/financial inclusion;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Governments;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in developing countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of, and experience in, direct budget support programmes, particularly EU-funded programmes, including experience in monitoring and evaluation of such programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in th region and the finance industry; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in the region;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the microfinance industry in Jordan (desirable);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and spoken English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in speaking, writing and reading Arabic (desirable).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWP 2 Projects Review</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Beyond WTO Program (B-WTO) was developed in response to a request from the Government of Vietnam (GoV) for donor support to help with managing economic integration and the transition to a market economy following WTO accession. The B-WTO goal is “to strengthen government’s capacity to manage the integration of Vietnam into the global economy and the transition of Vietnam to a socialist market economy”. The immediate objective is “implementation of priority policy actions from the GoV’s Action Plan to enhance Vietnam’s capacity to sustain pro-poor growth (GAP)”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The remit of this project was a review of the 2nd annual work plan’s implementation (AWP2) of Phase 2 of the B-WTO in May 2013. The objectives of the review were to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the project implementation performance and project results relative to the logical framework targets and evaluation criteria. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the results achieved at the Component and Program’s level according to the Monitoring and Evaluation (M&amp;amp;E) framework of the Program.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify lessons learned from implementation, make recommendations for the remaining duration of the program and the Independent Completion Report process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program 2013 Performance and Quality Mapping Exercise</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID’s PNG Program is looking to improve its performance and quality (P&amp;amp;Q) standards and systems. The purpose of this project was to map the PNG Program’s current P&amp;amp;Q capacity and systems, to address the risk of AusAID being unable to demonstrate results for its increased investments in PNG over the next four years. Over the last several years, the PNG Program has undertaken a number of M&amp;amp;E assessments and reviews which have identified key strengths and challenges within the program. This project was intended to pick up where these assessments left off. Through a desk review and consultations with sector teams, the Review Team were to distil key P&amp;amp;Q risks and issues for the PNG Program. The Review Team’s brief included the provision of recommendations on priority activities to support sector approaches to M&amp;amp;E, strengthen the Program’s ability to collect evidence, provide critical analysis and report on results.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID required a consultant to assist with the development and finalisation of its Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework. Development of a humanitarian monitoring and evaluation framework is a key commitment outlined in AusAID’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy (HAP) and its associated Implementation Plan. In line with the agency focus on results reporting, the HAP and HAP Implementation Plan commit AusAID to develop a monitoring and evaluation framework to support the initial performance assessment framework contained within the HAP and AusAID annual reporting under the Comprehensive Aid Policy Framework.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key objective of this assignment was to build the Humanitarian program’s capacity for monitoring and reporting results by:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In consultation with AusAID’s Humanitarian team, redraft and finalise the Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework, to ensure it provides a platform to:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track implementation of key commitments in Australia’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy; and,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish a set of measurable humanitarian performance indicators (in addition to the two CAPF indicators) to enable AusAID to track achievements, lessons learned and to report on the results achieved from AusAID’s humanitarian work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of Pacific Forum Compact Reporting</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The purpose of the assignment was to examine country views of aid effectiveness and regional organisations expressed through Forum Compact reporting, particularly peer review of Forum Island Countries’ national development plan processes. The services provided included the preparation of a think piece which outlines key aid effectiveness issues arising from country reporting under the Compact reporting and discusses options for addressing these issues.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study on Community-based Social Protection</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/study-on-community-based-social-protection</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/study-on-community-based-social-protection</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Poverty and Social Analysis is the process of using and generating evidence on poverty throughout the aid management cycle. Most poverty and social analysis focuses on economic and human capital, but there are two oft neglected elements: voice and influence, and social capital. Yet more and more development practitioners are recognizing the importance of social capital, particularly informal social capital, in preventing and addressing poverty and vulnerability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This project supported AusAID to explore:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the role of informal social capital in the Fijian context and whether it lends itself to fair redistribution of resources and, if so, the ways in which AusAID can engage with local communities to strengthen existing social capital structures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;how such structures can enable the disempowered and poor to claim their entitlements in the three domains discussed in the PSA framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the potential challenges that can arise from such efforts. For instance, the poorest are often included on less favorable terms within social networks, and have access to fewer and lower-quality networks. Further, we need to better understand how poverty and disempowerment intersect with an absence of informal social capital, the repercussions this has, and the options available for tackling this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Provision of a Child Protection Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/provision-of-a-child-protection-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/provision-of-a-child-protection-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For this project HTSPE was contracted to provide a child protection specialist and handle all the associated management and administrative work. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The child protection specialist provided by HTSPE was required to work on an assignment designed to assist the Pacific Division (PACD) to improve its approach to child protection and managing risks to children. AusAID has a number of partners in the Pacific who work with children or come into contact with children through their activities. The AusAID-wide child protection stocktake, conducted in May 2013 found that there are a number of organisations funded by AusAID in the Pacific with a high or very high inherent child protection risk. Consistent with the stocktake report PACD proposes to escalate efforts to ensure partner organisations policies, procedures and practices are in accordance with AusAID’s Child Protection Policy 2013 and to make child protection a more explicit focus of PACD’s risk management system.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Environment and Biology Expert (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/opportunities/senior-environment-and-biology-expert-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 20:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/opportunities/senior-environment-and-biology-expert-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Expert 2 is expected to contribute the implementation of all of the related modules and the preparation of both training materials and Training Evaluation Report in the context of related chapter/s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in Biology, Ecology, Chemistry or other Natural Sciences related to assignment. In the absence of the degree required, at least 17 years of professional experience in the related areas is requested.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good command of both written and spoken English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General professional experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in the sector(s) related to the Lot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience in technical and/or scientific fields required for the implementation of the Water Framework Directive and/or Habitat Directive and/or other related Directives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 river basin management plans experience in terms of setting of environmental objectives and/or setting, design and upgrade of biological monitoring programme and/or execution and assessment of biological monitoring.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in development of measures for water pollution reduction and/or improving ecological status, and/or river basin characterisation/analysis will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in projects related to Integrated Water Resources Management will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
