<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2015 08:05:59 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluator / Senior Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/evaluator-senior-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2015 07:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/evaluator-senior-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objectives:&lt;/strong&gt; 
To contribute to the improvement of EU-funded assistance to the Republic of Belarus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objectives:&lt;/strong&gt; 
To help the Delegation of the EU to the Republic of Belarus and its headquarters fine tune future assistance, implementation and coordination mechanisms of assistance provided to Belarus from 2016 onwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Location visits: Brussels, Brest (Belarus), Hrodna, Minsk, Rostock, Hamburg, Wismar, Vilnius, Biała Podlaska, Warsaw and home office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluator / Senior Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;: at least master degree (academic level); &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Or&lt;/strong&gt;, in the absence of a university degree, minimum of three additional years of professional experience on top of the ten years mentioned under general professional experience (see next criteria). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum of ten years of professional experience in the sector of development policies. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Having carried out a minimum of two mid-term/final and/or sector evaluations; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Result-Oriented Monitoring exercises would be an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in designing EU-funded assistance programmes would be an asset (drafting of Terms of Reference, Action Fiches/Documents, etc.); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in a country of the former Soviet Union5 would be an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in working in, or on, a CBC programme/project would be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in spoken and written English; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Russian and/or Belarusian and/or Polish &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key Expert 2 – EU Procedures Project Manager (Category II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-expert-2-eu-procedures-project-manager-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 15:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-expert-2-eu-procedures-project-manager-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The global objective is to contribute to a more enabling environment for civil society in Lebanon. To this end, the team should identify actions which contribute to the promotion of an increased engagement of civil society organisation in Lebanon both at policy and local development levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Expert 2 – EU Procedures Project Manager (Category II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advance University degree in humanities, law, social science, public administration or equivalent;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to work in close cooperation with international and local stake-holders;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English (spoken and written);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate in French is compulsory;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Arabic would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 10 years of experience in identifying/managing/evaluating development projects in support to civil society is compulsory;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated knowledge of EU project cycle management and EU external aid procedures is compulsory;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 1 experience in identifying/managing EU project modalities of implementation is required, such as:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Grant;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribution agreement;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Service contracts;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience in the ENI region. Experience in Lebanon would be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader – Civil Society Expert (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-civil-society-expert-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-civil-society-expert-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The global objective is to contribute to a more enabling environment for civil society in Lebanon. To this end, the team should identify actions which contribute to the promotion of an increased engagement of civil society organisation in Lebanon both at policy and local development levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader – Civil Society Expert (Category I)&lt;/strong&gt;
37 working days:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master Degree in humanities, law, social science or equivalent;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to work in close cooperation with international and local stake-holders;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven analytical, organisational, team leadership and writing skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English (spoken and written);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate in French is an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 12 years of experience in working with civil society, government institutions, international organisations and in carrying out analysis on institutional strengthening and training needs, as well as of project design for projects supporting civil society;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of relevant work experience in the specific area of local development projects implemented by Civil Society;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong abilities in needs assessment, data collection and analysis;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one (1) work experience related to the current assignment in an ENI country is compulsory. Experience in Lebanon would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experto Junior, Categoría III</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-junior-categoria-iii</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 12:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-junior-categoria-iii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;La Evaluación de Medio Término ofrecerá a los tomadores de decisiones en el gobierno de Bolivia y en la Comisión Europea información de calidad suficiente que les permita hacerse una opinión fundada sobre el desempeño del PROEX.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La misión es finalizada a producir una Evaluación de Medio Término que analice el contexto sectorial y la lógica de intervención del CF, identifique las dificultades experimentadas y valore los avances logrados para concluir en recomendaciones de mejoramiento y ajuste, tanto para la Unidad de Gestión del PROEX como para el Ministerio de Desarrollo Productivo y Economía Plural y la DUE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experto Junior, Categoría III&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Título de estudio universitario en economía, comercio, ciencias sociales, ciencias humanas o equivalente; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Al menos 3 años de experiencia en la administración y en programas de cooperación, preferentemente en modalidad de presupuestos programa de la CE; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conocimientos del ordenamiento jurídico de Bolivia y aspectos institucionales públicos en los temas de comercio y apoyo a las exportaciones (niveles de administración pública, legislación para entidades públicas); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia en evaluaciones de programas financiados por la Comisión Europea, posiblemente con componentes de fondos concursables; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excelente conocimiento del idioma español (hablado y escrito). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader, Categoría I</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-categoria-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-categoria-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;La Evaluación de Medio Término ofrecerá a los tomadores de decisiones en el gobierno de Bolivia y en la Comisión Europea información de calidad suficiente que les permita hacerse una opinión fundada sobre el desempeño del PROEX.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La misión es finalizada a producir una Evaluación de Medio Término que analice el contexto sectorial y la lógica de intervención del CF, identifique las dificultades experimentadas y valore los avances logrados para concluir en recomendaciones de mejoramiento y ajuste, tanto para la Unidad de Gestión del PROEX como para el Ministerio de Desarrollo Productivo y Economía Plural y la DUE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader, Categoría I&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Título de estudio universitario y maestría en economía, comercio o equivalente; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Un mínimo de 12 años de experiencia en proyectos de la cooperación internacional, preferentemente en países andinos; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia en la organización y gestión de misiones de evaluación de medio término de proyectos/programas financiados por la UE, de preferencia con al menos una experiencia bajo la modalidad de presupuesto programa; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia en la implementación/ evaluación de programas en los temas de comercio y apoyo a las exportaciones; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excelente conocimiento del idioma español (hablado y escrito). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert en Changement Climatique</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-changement-climatique</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 16:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-en-changement-climatique</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif général&lt;/strong&gt;
L’objectif général est d’appuyer le Togo dans la mise en oeuvre d’une réponse nationale aux défis posés par le changement climatique.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif particulier&lt;/strong&gt;
L’objectif particulier est de contribuer à l&amp;#39;identification puis à la formulation d&amp;#39;un d&amp;#39;appui à l&amp;#39;adaptation et à l&amp;#39;atténuation durable au changement climatique au Togo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Au stade de l&amp;#39;identification&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyser le contexte togolais en ce qui concerne la problématique du changement climatique;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifier les sous-secteurs nécessitant un appui et des idées d&amp;#39;actions conformes aux objectifs de l&amp;#39;AMCC+, du développement de l&amp;#39;Union européenne et du gouvernement togolais;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluer la pertinence et la faisabilité éventuelles de ces idées de projet;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Préparer le document d&amp;#39;actions conforme à la phase d&amp;#39;identification et correspondant aux activités retenues;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Elaborer un plan de travail décrivant les analyses qui devront être faites au stade de la Formulation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Au stade de la formulation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Confirmer la pertinence et la faisabilité de l&amp;#39;idée de projet retenue après la mission d&amp;#39;identification;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Préparer un plan détaillé du projet (y inclus le système de mise en oeuvre et de coordination, les moyens de financement, les conditions de faisabilité et durabilité, les modalités d&amp;#39;évaluation et d&amp;#39;audit);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;(1) Education, recherche, (2) gestion des zones côtières, (3) Eau et assainissement, infrastructure (4) Energie, (5) développement global et réduction de la pauvreté, (6) forêts et ressources naturelles et (7) agriculture;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;(1) l’intégration transversale des questions liées au CC, (2) l’adaptation au CC, (3) la REDD, (4) le renforcement de la participation aux efforts d’atténuation et (5) la réduction des risques de catastrophe;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Préparer le document d&amp;#39;action complet, les Dispositions Techniques et Administratives (DTA) correspondantes et le cadre logique du projet;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Préparer les documents de base permettant le lancement de l&amp;#39;exécution du projet (à savoir notamment les profils d&amp;#39;experts qu&amp;#39;il faudra recruter et les termes de référence correspondants; les dispositions techniques dont il faudra tenir compte au moment de la rédaction d&amp;#39;appels d&amp;#39;offre et de propositions, les équipements à fournir, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert en Changement Climatique&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Etre titulaire d’un diplôme universitaire de niveau au moins Bac + 5 dans les sciences, environnementales ou équivalentes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Il doit posséder au moins douze (12) ans d’expérience générale dans le domaine du changement climatique et bien imprégné des questions politiques et institutionnelles y afférant;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir une expérience spécifique de minimum 10 ans dans la formulation et/ou la mise en oeuvre de programme en lien avec le changement climatique. En particulier :&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Toute expérience dans la formulation et/ou la mise en oeuvre de programmes de l&amp;#39;initiative AMCC+ sera considéré comme un plus ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Toutes expériences dans les disciplines suivantes seront considérées comme des plus:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;REDD, problématique des ressources forestières, de la déforestation, de la filière bois-énergie (efficacité, substitution par le gaz etc.);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intégration du changement climatique dans les politiques publiques;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gestion des zones côtières;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Etre familier avec les mécanismes de gouvernances environnementales internationales ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir une capacité de synthèse, d’analyse et de rédaction en français;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtriser les politiques de coopération de l&amp;#39;Union européenne et le cycle de projet (identification, formulation et gestion);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtriser des procédures de la Commission européenne et une expérience d&amp;#39;au moins 3 projets de ce type en Afrique est obligatoire;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir de solides pratiques des activités d’appui au développement socioéconomique et de bonnes connaissances des réalités socio- politiques et économiques de l’Afrique de l’Ouest.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key Experts -TOMAK-To’os Ba Moris Diak/Farming for Prosperity, Timor-Leste</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-experts-tomak-toos-ba-moris-diak-farming-for-prosperity-timor-leste</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2015 15:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-experts-tomak-toos-ba-moris-diak-farming-for-prosperity-timor-leste</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objective of the Programme&lt;/strong&gt;
The objective of the assignment is to assist in the investment design for TOMAK (To’os Ba Moris Diak / Farming for Prosperity), which is a new 5-year agricultural livelihoods programme funded by the Australian government’s aid programme (DFAT) in Timor-Leste. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The programme’s goal is to ensure its selected rural households live more prosperous and sustainable lives.        &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TOMAK will achieve this through parallel and linked interventions that will:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish a foundation of food security and good nutrition for targeted rural households; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build their capacity to confidently and ably engage in profitable agricultural markets.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a result of this the project will be broken down into two interrelated outcomes:          &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Outcome 1&lt;/strong&gt;: Local commercial producers will be partnering sustainably and profitably with agribusiness and service providers in the selected agricultural value chains.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Outcome 2&lt;/strong&gt;: Locally relevant partners will trigger household demand for year-round production and utilisation of diverse and sufficient food&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Experts&lt;/strong&gt;:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duties and responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Value Chain Experts&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Primary responsibility to ensure local producers are partnering sustainably and profitably with agribusiness and service providers in the selected value chains in line with the objectives of outcome 1.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist with the Livelihood Zone Analysis, Engagement Strategy, identification of target value chains, and development of an Implementation Plan;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure selection of value chains that supports women’s economic empowerment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage implementation of Outcome 1 activities and Partnership agreements;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentoring responsibility for local staff.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nutrition Specialist&lt;/strong&gt;:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Primary responsibility for the management of Outcome 2 with a strong focus on behaviour change communication aspects of nutrition programming (with the support of international short term experts); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist with the Livelihood Zone Analysis, Engagement Strategy, identification of target value chains, and development of an Implementation Plan;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentoring responsibility for local staff.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring and Evaluation Expert&lt;/strong&gt;:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development of the Results Frameworks and M&amp;amp;E Plan for TOMAK;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide Advice and input on the operational research / learning agenda for the programme; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure the methodological rigor of the methods/tools developed;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review of key baseline and annual studies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quality assurance of M&amp;amp;E implementation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsibility for the day to day implementation of the M&amp;amp;E Plan;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentoring responsibility for local staff.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced degree agriculture, agribusiness or related field. Masters degree preferred;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least ten years of professional experience in programme design in the sectors of value chain and/or nutrition and/or gender and/or livelihood zone and/or administration-as applicable to the position;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience and ability to develop monitoring and evaluation frameworks in large, complex donor funded programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communicational skills; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong data analysis and report writing skills; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience working in Timor-Leste/South East Asia;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with DFAT would be desirable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please apply via the following link:
&lt;a href=&quot;http://chc.tbe.taleo.net/chc06/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=2290&quot;&gt;http://chc.tbe.taleo.net/chc06/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=2290&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please note that all profiles are indicative only and subject to change once the RFT is made available.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader – TOMAK –To’os Ba Moris Diak/Farming for Prosperity, Timor-Leste</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-tomak-toos-ba-moris-diak-farming-for-prosperity-timor-leste</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2015 15:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-tomak-toos-ba-moris-diak-farming-for-prosperity-timor-leste</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objective of the Programme&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objective of the assignment is to assist in the investment design for TOMAK (To’os Ba Moris Diak / Farming for Prosperity), which is a new 5-year agricultural livelihoods programme funded by the Australian government’s aid programme (DFAT) in Timor-Leste. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The programme’s goal is to ensure its selected rural households live more prosperous and sustainable lives.        &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TOMAK will achieve this through parallel and linked interventions that will:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish a foundation of food security and good nutrition for targeted rural households; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build their capacity to confidently and ably engage in profitable agricultural markets.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a result of this the project will be broken down into two interrelated outcomes:          &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Outcome 1&lt;/strong&gt;: Local commercial producers will be partnering sustainably and profitably with agribusiness and service providers in the selected agricultural value chains.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Outcome 2&lt;/strong&gt;: Locally relevant partners will trigger household demand for year-round production and utilisation of diverse and sufficient food&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader – TOMAK –To’os Ba Moris Diak/Farming for Prosperity, Timor-Leste&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Duties and Responsibilities *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the TOMAK Team and the implementation of TOMAK based on the design and approved annual plans; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Primary contact point with the Australian Embassy in Dili; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain open and effective links with Government of Timor-Leste (GoTL) and other development partners; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure the quality of all TOMAK reporting;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure compliance with DFAT and GoTL Policy (including gender); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appoint and manage performance of all TOMAK staff; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage performance of all TOMAK sub-agreements with local partners.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skills and Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong track record of successful project team leadership on international donor funded programs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience working in agricultural livelihoods programmes or similar.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced degree in agriculture, rural/development economics, international development or similar;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in Timor-Leste, and language abilities in Portuguese or Tetum would be desirable;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience working with DFAT would be preferable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Programme Start Date&lt;/strong&gt;:
Early 2016 for five years, with an option of an additional five years&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Application Deadline&lt;/strong&gt;:
15 October&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please apply via the following link:
&lt;a href=&quot;http://chc.tbe.taleo.net/chc06/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=2291&quot;&gt;http://chc.tbe.taleo.net/chc06/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=2291&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please note that all profiles are indicative only and subject to change once the RFT is made available.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert in Governance and Home Affairs</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-governance-and-home-affairs-1</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 13:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-governance-and-home-affairs-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The main objective of this assignment is to prepare a draft Law on the Transnistrian settlement process that would provide the legal basis for the existing and future interaction between the representatives of the two banks of the Nistru river. This would include the &amp;ldquo;5+2&amp;rdquo; talks, the expert Working Groups, and other forms of interaction between the officials of the Republic of Moldova and the de facto Transnistrian authorities at all levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in Governance and Home Affairs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Category and duration of equivalent experience:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category III&lt;/strong&gt;: at least 3 years of work experience in or with (for) public administration. Experience in conflict resolution and/ or post conflict management would be an asset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in political science, law or any of the social sciences or a university degree in one of these fields and 3 years of equivalent professional experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in drafting of legislation &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience of working with various levels of government and/or international organization &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in the conflict settlement process would be an advantage. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Excellent written and spoken English and Russian are required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert in Diplomacy, International Relations and Conflict Resolution</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-diplomacy-international-relations-and-conflict-resolution</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 12:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-diplomacy-international-relations-and-conflict-resolution</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The main objective of this assignment is to prepare a draft Law on the Transnistrian settlement process that would provide the legal basis for the existing and future interaction between the representatives of the two banks of the Nistru river. This would include the &amp;ldquo;5+2&amp;rdquo; talks, the expert Working Groups, and other forms of interaction between the officials of the Republic of Moldova and the de facto Transnistrian authorities at all levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in Diplomacy, international relations and conflict resolution&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category and duration of equivalent experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Category I: at least 12 years of experience in public administration, diplomacy, conflict resolution, academics in the sphere of conflict resolution or international relations and/ or post conflict management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;:
Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in political science, law or any of the social sciences or a university degree in one of these fields and 12 years of equivalent professional experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 7 years of experience in conflict resolution and/ or post conflict management or diplomacy or work at international organization; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience of working with various levels of government or international organizations; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferably 5 years of professional experience in the countries of the European Neighbourhood Policy (ENP) - East, Commonwealth of Independent States (CIS) or Enlargement countries; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in Moldova would be an advantage. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Excellent written and spoken English; knowledge of Romanian and Russian would be an asset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert in Governance and Home Affairs</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-governance-and-home-affairs</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-governance-and-home-affairs</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The main objective of this assignment is to prepare a draft Law on the Transnistrian settlement process that would provide the legal basis for the existing and future interaction between the representatives of the two banks of the Nistru river. This would include the &amp;ldquo;5+2&amp;rdquo; talks, the expert Working Groups, and other forms of interaction between the officials of the Republic of Moldova and the de facto Transnistrian authorities at all levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in Governance and Home Affairs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Category and duration of equivalent experience:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Category III: at least 3 years of professional experience. 
Education:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in law or a university degree in law and three years of professional experience. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 12 years of professional experience, including drafting the texts of Constitutional laws and/or laws in the domain of public administration and/or international treaties and/or international conventions. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience of working in or with the government or at international organization; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in conflict resolution and/or post conflict management would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Excellent written and spoken English and Russian and Romanian are required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert Governance and Home Affairs (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-governance-and-home-affairs-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 11:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-governance-and-home-affairs-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The main objective of this assignment is to prepare a draft Law on the Transnistrian settlement process that would provide the legal basis for the existing and future interaction between the representatives of the two banks of the Nistru river. This would include the &amp;ldquo;5+2&amp;rdquo; talks, the expert Working Groups, and other forms of interaction between the officials of the Republic of Moldova and the de facto Transnistrian authorities at all levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert Governance and Home Affairs (TL)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Category and duration of equivalent experience: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Category I: at least 12 years of legal experience. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in law or a university degree in law and 12 years of professional experience. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 12 years of professional experience, including drafting the texts of Constitutional laws and/or laws in the domain of public administration and/or international treaties and/or international conventions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience of working with various levels of government; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferably 5 years of professional experience in or with the countries of the European &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Neighbourhood Policy (ENP) - East, Commonwealth of Independent States (CIS) or Enlargement countries; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in conflict resolution and/or post conflict management would be an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;International legal experience would be an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in Moldova would be an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Excellent written and spoken English; knowledge of Romanian and/or Russian would be an asset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Juvenile Justice, Criminal Law and Penitentiary Administration</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-juvenile-justice-criminal-law-and-penitentiary-administration</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-juvenile-justice-criminal-law-and-penitentiary-administration</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The objective of the mission is to identify and formulate a programme to support, building on previous and ongoing actions and a demand-driven approach, relevant improvements of the justice system in Lebanon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Juvenile Justice, Criminal Law and Penitentiary Administration (category I, 42 w/d):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least University Degree in law or relevant experience of 3 years in addition to the required general professional experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience working in the area of justice sector reform;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years’ experience in carrying out analysis on institutional strengthening, capacity building and training needs, strategic and technical advice as well as project design on criminal justice reform and in particular on juvenile justice reform;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years’ experience on the legal protection of children in conflict with the law, including through the adoption of preventive measures, custodial and non-custodial measures;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience as an expert in at least 1 identification/formulation mission of a minimum duration of  15 days/per mission, including the preparation of the required Action Document/Fiche according to the EC template;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven working experience in Lebanon or other MENA countries would be a strong asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in written and spoken English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in written and spoken Arabic strongly preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader – Senior Justice Sector Reform Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-justice-sector-reform-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 09:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-justice-sector-reform-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The objective of the mission is to identify and formulate a programme to support, building on previous and ongoing actions and a demand-driven approach, relevant improvements of the justice system in Lebanon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader – Senior Justice Sector Reform Expert (Category I, 42 w/d)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least University Degree in law or relevant experience of 3 years in addition to the required general professional experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 15 years of experience in providing strategic and technical advice in the area of justice sector reform, including focus on areas such as juvenile justice and protection of children and other vulnerable groups; access to justice; international criminal law; international human rights law; penitentiary administration;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience as Team Leader in at least 2 identification/formulation missions in the justice sector of a minimum duration of 15 days/per mission&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in preparing the required Action Document/Fiche according to the EC template in at least 1 previous assignment related to the justice sector;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven working experience in Lebanon or other MENA countries would be a strong asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in written and spoken English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in written and spoken Arabic strongly preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;**WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/em&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Un Expert Senior en Evaluation dans le Domaine du Renforcement et de la Structuration de la Société Civile (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/un-expert-senior-en-evaluation-dans-le-domaine-du-renforcement-et-de-la-structuration-de-la-societe-civile</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2015 19:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/un-expert-senior-en-evaluation-dans-le-domaine-du-renforcement-et-de-la-structuration-de-la-societe-civile</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Cette mission d’évaluation finale doit permettre aux parties prenantes i) d’avoir une vision précise des activités réalisées au cours des 45 mois d’opérationnalité du Projet OSCAR et si non de leur impact, du moins de leurs effets sur les processus démocratiques en cours au Burundi ; ii) mais aussi, dans le cas où les conditions de démarrage du futur projet 11ème FED seraient remplies dans les prochains mois, de conforter la prise en compte de certaines des réalisations du Projet OSCAR dans le cadre de ce futur projet et iii) finalement de proposer des pistes de reformulation du futur projet 11ème FED au cas où la situation politique du pays continuerait à se dégrader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Un expert en évaluation dans le domaine du renforcement et de la structuration de la société civile (y compris les médias), ayant de l&amp;#39;expérience dans les thématiques suivantes: renforcement des capacités, ingénierie de la formation, réforme du cadre juridique régulant la société civile, structuration et mise en réseau des acteurs de la société civile, relations société civile – autorités gouvernementales, participation de la société civile aux processus de formulation et suivi-évaluation des politiques publiques. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chef de mission - Expert senior&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Niveau maîtrise en sciences sociales (formation complémentaires en droit et/ou économie souhaitable);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience de 12 ans minimum dans la mise en œuvre et/ou le suivi/évaluation de projets/programmes de développement (FED et autres bailleurs); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience de 5 ans minimum dans le domaine spécifique de la société civile;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience de 3 ans minimum dans le suivi/évaluation de projets FED;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins une expérience avec la société civile en Afrique sub-saharienne (au total 1 an de travail dans ce domaine dans cette aire géographique);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonnes compétences de communication dans différents milieux culturels;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise parfaite du français écrit et parlé.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Carbon Markets and Emissions Trading Systems</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-carbon-markets-and-emissions-trading-systems</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2015 12:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-carbon-markets-and-emissions-trading-systems</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The *&lt;em&gt;**main objective&lt;/em&gt;* of the present mid-term evaluation is to provide the relevant decision makers both in China and the European Union, with an overall independent assessment to make an informed judgment about the past performance of the project. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Particular attention must be paid to the project results in relation to supporting the national and regional institutional framework (policy and decision makers on the national and local DRC levels, as well as supporting institutions and think-tanks) and also to advance the EU-China ETS joint policy agenda, in order to document lessons learned and to provide practical recommendations for follow-up action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;**Project location&lt;/em&gt;*: China (Beijing, Shanghai, Guangdong and Hubei) and Belgium (Brussels)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Carbon Markets and Emissions Trading Systems&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;***&lt;em&gt;Qualifications and skills *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Academic qualification in a sector relevant to the assignment (at least Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree or, in its absence, equivalent professional experience of 5 years) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellent communication, drafting and reporting-writing skills; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven professional experience of at least 12 years in the sector (s) related to the Lot &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven professional experience of at least 7 years in the field of carbon markets and emissions trading systems, MRVA, registry, allocation, cap setting and market oversight. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The expert must have field experience in project management and project evaluation. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Language skills *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proficiency in written and spoken English. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience in the development of operational manuals, guides and training tools related to the ETS sector would be an asset, as well as knowledge of China and the local language (Mandarin) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert with Evaluation and Sector Experience , Cat I - Team Leader</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-with-evaluation-and-sector-experience-cat-i-team-leader</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2015 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-with-evaluation-and-sector-experience-cat-i-team-leader</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The *&lt;em&gt;**main objecti&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;ve&lt;/em&gt;* of the present mid-term evaluation is to provide the relevant decision makers both in China and the European Union, with an overall independent assessment to make an informed judgment about the past performance of the project. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Particular attention must be paid to the project results in relation to supporting the national and regional institutional framework (policy and decision makers on the national and local DRC levels, as well as supporting institutions and think-tanks) and also to advance the EU-China ETS joint policy agenda, in order to document lessons learned and to provide practical recommendations for follow-up action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project location&lt;/strong&gt;: China (Beijing, Shanghai, Guangdong and Hubei) and Belgium (Brussels)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert with Evaluation and Sector Experience , Cat I - Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Academic qualification in a sector relevant to the assignment (at least Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree or, in its absence, equivalent professional experience of 5 years) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication, drafting and reporting-writing skills; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proven professional experience of at least 12 years in the sector(s) related to the Lot at the international level in evaluation procedures and methodologies applied to the various modalities of implementation, instruments and channels of cooperation / aid delivery. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of technical and/or financial programme management as well as of Project Cycle Management (PCM) and Logical Framework Approaches. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of cost-benefit and impact analysis. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience with Governmental officials at senior level and within a team of international and national consultants &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience with EU-funded programmes and with ETS or carbon market-related programmes would be an asset. Working experience in or with China (short or long-term missions) would be also an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proficiency in written and spoken English. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rural Development Expert with specific experience in Needs Assessment in the Livestock Sector and Project Formulation</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/rural-development-expert-with-specific-experience-in-needs-assessment-in-the-livestock-sector-and-project-formulation</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/rural-development-expert-with-specific-experience-in-needs-assessment-in-the-livestock-sector-and-project-formulation</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this assignment is to provide technical support to the on-going process of defining and implementing support measures to fast-track the restructuring of the agricultural sector and establish a competitive and sustainable dairy sector that is able to produce Hellim/Halloumi in compliance with PDO requirements and in conformity with other relevant EU provisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rural Development Expert with specific experience in Needs Assessment in the Livestock Sector and Project Formulation (Category II, 30 w/d)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master’s Degree in Rural development or equivalent disciplines;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years professional experience in rural development, with main focus on livestock development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in livestock development and formulation of supportive measures;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with EU Guidelines on project cycle management and formulation procedures is an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent reporting, presentation and communication skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of participatory techniques and approaches is an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English, both spoken and written;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Turkish is an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Livestock Expert with specific experience in Elaboration of Plans to improve Milk Yields of Sheep and Goat Breeds</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/livestock-expert-with-specific-experience-in-elaboration-of-plans-to-improve-milk-yields-of-sheep-and-goat-breeds</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 07:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/livestock-expert-with-specific-experience-in-elaboration-of-plans-to-improve-milk-yields-of-sheep-and-goat-breeds</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this assignment is to provide technical support to the on-going process of defining and implementing support measures to fast-track the restructuring of the agricultural sector and establish a competitive and sustainable dairy sector that is able to produce Hellim/Halloumi in compliance with PDO requirements and in conformity with other relevant EU provisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Livestock Expert with specific experience in Elaboration of Plans to improve Milk Yields of Sheep and Goat Breeds (Category I, 50 w/d)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master’s Degree in Animal Husbandry, Biology, Animal Genetics or equivalent disciplines;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years professional experience in livestock development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in livestock breeding program;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with developing breeding plans for sheep or goats;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the Southern Mediterranean region is an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent reporting, presentation and communication skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English, both spoken and written;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Turkish is an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agro-economist with specific experience in Policy Formulation and Analysis for the Dairy Sector (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/agro-economist-with-specific-experience-in-policy-formulation-and-analysis-for-the-dairy-sector-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 07:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/agro-economist-with-specific-experience-in-policy-formulation-and-analysis-for-the-dairy-sector-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The *&lt;em&gt;**global objecti&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;ve&lt;/em&gt;* of this assignment is to provide technical support to the on-going process of defining and implementing support measures to fast-track the restructuring of the agricultural sector and establish a competitive and sustainable dairy sector that is able to produce Hellim/Halloumi in compliance with PDO requirements and in conformity with other relevant EU provisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agro-economist with specific experience in Policy Formulation and Analysis for the Dairy Sector (Category I, 120 w/d)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master’s Degree in Economics, Agricultural Economics or equivalent;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of professional experience in agricultural economics;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in livestock development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in policy analysis and formulation for the dairy sector;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in designing &amp;amp; supervising of value chain analysis will be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in data collection and analysis to support evidence based policy development for the dairy sector will be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent reporting, presentation and communication skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English, both spoken and written;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Turkish is an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
