<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 21:41:44 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spécialiste Senior en ingénierie pédagogique: sur les thèmes risques dans les marchés publics et contrôle interne (Cat.I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/specialiste-senior-en-ingenierie-pedagogique-sur-les-themes-risques-dans-les-marches-publics-et-controle-interne-cati</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 21:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/specialiste-senior-en-ingenierie-pedagogique-sur-les-themes-risques-dans-les-marches-publics-et-controle-interne-cati</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appui a l&amp;#39;Organe national de prevention et de lutte contre la corruption (ONPLC) en Algerie&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif général&lt;/strong&gt;
La prestation projetée a pour objectif d’appuyer et de renforcer les activités des services de l’ONPLC dans le cadre de la politique de prévention de la corruption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectifs particuliers&lt;/strong&gt; :
Les objectifs particuliers consistent à :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Un appui au programme national de sensibilisation et de formation anti-corruption destiné aux agents publics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engager une étude d’appui à la modernisation du traitement et du contrôle de ladé claration de patrimoine de tous les élus et hauts fonctionnaires qui y sont soumis avec les administrations concernées.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Réaliser l’étude de la mise en oeuvre de la déclaration d’intérêt avec définition du cadre juridique.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Réaliser une étude d’évaluation des risques permettant de dessiner une cartographie faisant ressortir les vulnérabilités et les disfonctionnements pouvant faciliter la corruption.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fournir une assistance à la rédaction d’une stratégie nationale anti-corruption proposant les voies et moyens pour l’amélioration de l’intégrité publique.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spécialiste Senior en ingénierie pédagogique: sur les thèmes risques dans les marchés publics et contrôle interne (Cat.I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire en droit public, en sciences humaines et sociales ou équivalent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parfaite maîtrise, orale et écrite, de la langue française&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;12 ans minimum d&amp;#39;expérience dans le domaine de l’enseignement et de la conception de documents pédagogiques et d’organisation de programmes de
formation ou de perfectionnement professionnel de préférence sur des thèmes en rapport avec la bonne gouvernance et la prévention et la lutte contre la corruption.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 ans d’expérience en matière en matière de gestion et de contrôle des marchés publics et de parfaite maitrise des outils de contrôle interne et d’évaluation des
performances.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Atouts supplémentaires&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans le domaine de la coopération UE&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir travaillé dans un pays similaire serait un atout&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aptitude à concevoir la transmission de connaissances et de savoir-faire.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef de Mission – Consultant en bonne gouvernance, spécialiste en évaluation des risques de corruption (Cat.I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-consultant-en-bonne-gouvernance-specialiste-en-evaluation-des-risques-de-corruption-cati</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 21:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-consultant-en-bonne-gouvernance-specialiste-en-evaluation-des-risques-de-corruption-cati</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appui a l&amp;#39;Organe national de prevention et de lutte contre la corruption (ONPLC) en Algerie&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif général&lt;/strong&gt;
La prestation projetée a pour objectif d’appuyer et de renforcer les activités des services de l’ONPLC dans le cadre de la politique de prévention de la corruption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectifs particuliers&lt;/strong&gt; :
Les objectifs particuliers consistent à :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Un appui au programme national de sensibilisation et de formation anti-corruption destiné aux agents publics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engager une étude d’appui à la modernisation du traitement et du contrôle de ladé claration de patrimoine de tous les élus et hauts fonctionnaires qui y sont soumis avec les administrations concernées.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Réaliser l’étude de la mise en oeuvre de la déclaration d’intérêt avec définition du cadre juridique.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Réaliser une étude d’évaluation des risques permettant de dessiner une cartographie faisant ressortir les vulnérabilités et les disfonctionnements pouvant faciliter la corruption.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fournir une assistance à la rédaction d’une stratégie nationale anti-corruption proposant les voies et moyens pour l’amélioration de l’intégrité publique.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chef de Mission – Consultant en bonne gouvernance, spécialiste en évaluation des risques de corruption (Cat.I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire (3ième cycle minimum) en droit public, économie ou sociologie d&amp;#39;un niveau de Mastère ou équivalent &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parfaite maîtrise, orale et écrite, de la langue française&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;12 ans minimum d&amp;#39;expérience dans les services de contrôle financiers (y compris et principalement en matière de prévention de la corruption et/ou du crime organisé).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pilotage et/ou réalisation d’études psycho-socio-économiques ayant permis l’élaboration d’une cartographie des risques anti-corruption.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ayant déjà élaboré une stratégie anti-corruption ou une stratégie sur un dispositif similaire.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Atouts supplémentaires&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans le domaine de la coopération UE&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir travaillé dans un pays similaire serait un atout&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance de la langue arabe serait aussi un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aptitude à transmettre des connaissances et un savoir-faire.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sustainable Economic Development and Diversification Expert (Category 1)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/sustainable-economic-development-and-diversification-expert-category-1</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 21:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/sustainable-economic-development-and-diversification-expert-category-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance to the Government of Montserrat for the programming of 11th EDF Territorial Allocation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objective of this assignment is to provide Technical Assistance to Montserrat in the programming of the OCTs 11th EDF territorial allocation in favour of the Montserrat Sustainable Development Plan and economic growth strategy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two specific objectives for this consultancy, as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objective 1&lt;/strong&gt;: To conduct consultations with relevant stakeholders; prepare the required documents described under point 2.4 and ensure their quality in view of the programming of the OCTs 11th EDF territorial allocation as multi-sector reform contract focusing on key sectors for sustainable growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objective 2&lt;/strong&gt;: To provide the assistance required by Montserrat Government throughout the programming exercise of the OCTs 11th EDF territorial allocation and until the signature of the Financing Agreement, including the necessary follow-up to the submitted documents under specific objective 1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2: Sustainable Economic Development and Diversification Expert (Category 1, 42 working days)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Masters’  degree  in  Sustainable  Economic  Development,  Development  Economics,  or Equivalent;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;12 – 15 years of relevant work experience working in economic development and sustainable growth policy and programmes;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sound experience in developmental issues at regional level as well as all at sector level;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience in technical assistance project delivery and/or design; including institutional strengthening at public level either nationally or regionally;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience in providing technical assistance/capacity building and consulting in policy and planning in the key economic sectors, in particular energy, tourism, infrastructure, trade and private sector development, governance;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience in development cooperation with DEVCO will be a significant advantage;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Work experience in the region and Small Island States development issues will be a significant advantage;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A high level of written and spoken English. The working language of this assignment will be English.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team leader and Public Finance Specialist (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-and-public-finance-specialist-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 21:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-and-public-finance-specialist-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance to the Government of Montserrat for the programming of 11th EDF Territorial Allocation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objective of this assignment is to provide Technical Assistance to Montserrat in the programming of the OCTs 11th EDF territorial allocation in favour of the Montserrat Sustainable Development Plan and economic growth strategy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two specific objectives for this consultancy, as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objective 1&lt;/strong&gt;: To conduct consultations with relevant stakeholders; prepare the required documents described under point 2.4 and ensure their quality in view of the programming of the OCTs 11th EDF territorial allocation as multi-sector reform contract focusing on key sectors for sustainable growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objective 2&lt;/strong&gt;: To provide the assistance required by Montserrat Government throughout the programming exercise of the OCTs 11th EDF territorial allocation and until the signature of the Financing Agreement, including the necessary follow-up to the submitted documents under specific objective 1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 1: Team leader and Public Finance Specialist (Category I, 42 working days)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Masters’ degree in public finance, macroeconomics, economic development or equivalent;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Senior macro-economist/public finance specialist with at least 12 years relevant work experience working on public sector finance;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Specific experience or knowledge of establishing a Medium-term Expenditure Framework;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience or knowledge of making assessments on budget support eligibility as regards macro-economic framework, public finance management and transparency and oversight of the budget;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous experience of preparing and formulating budget support operations for beneficiaries of European Union development assistance;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ability to assess the institutional capacity of institutions involved in implementation budget support programmes in small islands administrations;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A high level of written and spoken English. The working language of this assignment will be English.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 4 – IOC Component</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-4-ioc-component</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2016 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-4-ioc-component</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term review of Maritime Security Programme in the Eastern, Southern Africa and Indian Ocean Region (ESA-IO Region)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Under the provisions of the Cotonou agreement, the regional program of EDF 10th for the Eastern, Southern Africa and Indian Ocean Region has had foreseen a support to the focal sector 2 &amp;ldquo;Regional political integration and cooperation&amp;rdquo; and special focus on security issues. In this sector a Maritime and security Programme MASE of EUR 37 500 000 has been developed under the responsibility of Intergovernmental Authority on Development (IGAD) as Regional Authorised Officer which has sub delegate its authority for the implementation of the component/Result 2 to East Africa Community (EAC), of the component/Result 3 to Common Market for Eastern and Southern Africa (COMESA), and of the  components/Results 4 and 5 to Indian Ocean Commission (IOC).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Overall Objective of the programme is to enhance maritime security in the ESA-IO region hence contribute to global security and create a favourable environment for the economic development of the ESA-IO region and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Specific objective of the programme is to strengthen the capacity of the ESA-IO region in the implementation of the Regional Strategy and Action Plan against Piracy and for Maritime Security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 4 – IOC Component&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master degree in maritime studies or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience on maritime domain awareness systems,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience on maritime safety surveillance and control mechanisms,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience on maritime information sharing and information fusion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of maritime security issues in the ESA-IO region&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience on monitoring evaluation of EC and UN programmes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Common Minimum requirement to all experts&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree or equivalent; General experience on monitoring/evaluation EC and UN programmes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid and diversified experience in the specific field of expertise needed;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in evaluation/monitoring of similar projects/programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant experience of at least 5 years in developing countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one of the experts is fully conversant with the principles and working methods of project cycle management and EU aid delivery methods;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one of the experts proposed should have knowledge of gender, environment and governance mainstreaming;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one of the experts proposed should have direct experience on maritime issues maritime criminality, with civil society in conflict prevention and resolution;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one of the experts proposed should have direct experience in law enforcement issues and capacity building activities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full working knowledge in English and excellent writing skills plus working knowledge in French&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent computer skills with at least Microsoft offices usual software (Word, Excel, MSProject, Power Point) or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent writing skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 3 – COMESA/Interpol Component</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-3-comesa-interpol-component</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2016 19:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-3-comesa-interpol-component</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term review of Maritime Security Programme in the Eastern, Southern Africa and Indian Ocean Region (ESA-IO Region)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Under the provisions of the Cotonou agreement, the regional program of EDF 10th for the Eastern, Southern Africa and Indian Ocean Region has had foreseen a support to the focal sector 2 &amp;ldquo;Regional political integration and cooperation&amp;rdquo; and special focus on security issues. In this sector a Maritime and security Programme MASE of EUR 37 500 000 has been developed under the responsibility of Intergovernmental Authority on Development (IGAD) as Regional Authorised Officer which has sub delegate its authority for the implementation of the component/Result 2 to East Africa Community (EAC), of the component/Result 3 to Common Market for Eastern and Southern Africa (COMESA), and of the  components/Results 4 and 5 to Indian Ocean Commission (IOC).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Overall Objective of the programme is to enhance maritime security in the ESA-IO region hence contribute to global security and create a favourable environment for the economic development of the ESA-IO region and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Specific objective of the programme is to strengthen the capacity of the ESA-IO region in the implementation of the Regional Strategy and Action Plan against Piracy and for Maritime Security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 3 – COMESA/Interpol component&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master degree in law or economics/finance and substantial experience/expertise in relevant fields such as money laundering, financial crimes and related investigation/prosecution ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recent experience (last 3 years) in regional related programmes in COMESA region;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of the COMESA region is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience on monitoring evaluation of EC and UN programmes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Common Minimum requirement to all experts&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree or equivalent; General experience on monitoring/evaluation EC and UN programmes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid and diversified experience in the specific field of expertise needed;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in evaluation/monitoring of similar projects/programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant experience of at least 5 years in developing countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one of the experts is fully conversant with the principles and working methods of project cycle management and EU aid delivery methods;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one of the experts proposed should have knowledge of gender, environment and governance mainstreaming;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one of the experts proposed should have direct experience on maritime issues maritime criminality, with civil society in conflict prevention and resolution;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one of the experts proposed should have direct experience in law enforcement issues and capacity building activities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full working knowledge in English and excellent writing skills plus working knowledge in French&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent computer skills with at least Microsoft offices usual software (Word, Excel, MSProject, Power Point) or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent writing skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 2 EAC component – for National /Regional Legal Issues for Arrest, Transfer Detention and Prosecution</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-eac-component-for-national-regional-legal-issues-for-arrest-transfer-detention-and-prosecution</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2016 16:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-eac-component-for-national-regional-legal-issues-for-arrest-transfer-detention-and-prosecution</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term review of Maritime Security Programme in the Eastern, Southern Africa and Indian Ocean Region (ESA-IO Region)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Under the provisions of the Cotonou agreement, the regional program of EDF 10th for the Eastern, Southern Africa and Indian Ocean Region has had foreseen a support to the focal sector 2 &amp;ldquo;Regional political integration and cooperation&amp;rdquo; and special focus on security issues. In this sector a Maritime and security Programme MASE of EUR 37 500 000 has been developed under the responsibility of Intergovernmental Authority on Development (IGAD) as Regional Authorised Officer which has sub delegate its authority for the implementation of the component/Result 2 to East Africa Community (EAC), of the component/Result 3 to Common Market for Eastern and Southern Africa (COMESA), and of the  components/Results 4 and 5 to Indian Ocean Commission (IOC).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Overall Objective of the programme is to enhance maritime security in the ESA-IO region hence contribute to global security and create a favourable environment for the economic development of the ESA-IO region and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Specific objective of the programme is to strengthen the capacity of the ESA-IO region in the implementation of the Regional Strategy and Action Plan against Piracy and for Maritime Security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2 EAC component – for national /regional legal issues for arrest, transfer detention and prosecution&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master degree in law and good knowledge on maritime legal framework;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recent experience in maritime law enforcement institutions ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated recent experience (last 3 years) in procurement processes and EDF procedures at national or regional level;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience on monitoring evaluation of EC and UN programmes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of EAC is an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the region is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in EDF procurement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Common Minimum requirement to all experts&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree or equivalent; General experience on monitoring/evaluation EC and UN programmes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid and diversified experience in the specific field of expertise needed;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in evaluation/monitoring of similar projects/programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant experience of at least 5 years in developing countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one of the experts is fully conversant with the principles and working methods of project cycle management and EU aid delivery methods;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one of the experts proposed should have knowledge of gender, environment and governance mainstreaming;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one of the experts proposed should have direct experience on maritime issues maritime criminality, with civil society in conflict prevention and resolution;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one of the experts proposed should have direct experience in law enforcement issues and capacity building activities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full working knowledge in English and excellent writing skills plus working knowledge in French&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent computer skills with at least Microsoft offices usual software (Word, Excel, MSProject, Power Point) or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent writing skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team leader (IGAD component and overall coordination)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-igad-component-and-overall-coordination</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2016 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-igad-component-and-overall-coordination</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term review of Maritime Security Programme in the Eastern, Southern Africa and Indian Ocean Region (ESA-IO Region)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Under the provisions of the Cotonou agreement, the regional program of EDF 10th for the Eastern, Southern Africa and Indian Ocean Region has had foreseen a support to the focal sector 2 &amp;ldquo;Regional political integration and cooperation&amp;rdquo; and special focus on security issues. In this sector a Maritime and security Programme MASE of EUR 37 500 000 has been developed under the responsibility of Intergovernmental Authority on Development (IGAD) as Regional Authorised Officer which has sub delegate its authority for the implementation of the component/Result 2 to East Africa Community (EAC), of the component/Result 3 to Common Market for Eastern and Southern Africa (COMESA), and of the  components/Results 4 and 5 to Indian Ocean Commission (IOC).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Overall Objective of the programme is to enhance maritime security in the ESA-IO region hence contribute to global security and create a favourable environment for the economic development of the ESA-IO region and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Specific objective of the programme is to strengthen the capacity of the ESA-IO region in the implementation of the Regional Strategy and Action Plan against Piracy and for Maritime Security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 1 – Team leader (IGAD component and overall coordination)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master degree in economics or in Law enforcement and Maritime security knowledge or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Substantial experience in monitoring and evaluation of EC and UN agencies programmes as team leader,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience as a team leader in the last 5 years; (Minimum required skills)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least two experiences in programme evaluation in the last five years in management and maritime security strategies ; (Minimum required skills)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recent experience (last five years) in the region EAC/COMESA/IGAD/IOC region is an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Common Minimum requirement to all experts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree or equivalent; General experience on monitoring/evaluation EC and UN programmes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid and diversified experience in the specific field of expertise needed;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in evaluation/monitoring of similar projects/programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant experience of at least 5 years in developing countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one of the experts is fully conversant with the principles and working methods of project cycle management and EU aid delivery methods;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one of the experts proposed should have knowledge of gender, environment and governance mainstreaming;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one of the experts proposed should have direct experience on maritime issues maritime criminality, with civil society in conflict prevention and resolution;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one of the experts proposed should have direct experience in law enforcement issues and capacity building activities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full working knowledge in English and excellent writing skills plus working knowledge in French&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent computer skills with at least Microsoft offices usual software (Word, Excel, MSProject, Power Point) or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent writing skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation Team with EDF Experience (TL, Senior experts and junior experts) </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/evaluation-team-with-edf-experience-tl-senior-experts-and-junior-experts</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 21:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/evaluation-team-with-edf-experience-tl-senior-experts-and-junior-experts</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation of 11th EDF Performance Review&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This project will evaluate the 11th EDF with the objective of provide an independent assessment of the funds, including complementarities with other External Financing Instruments, as well as to inform the programming and implementation of the current EDF.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experts will conduct evaluations in the ACP region, and carry out this project within the period mid-July 2016 – August 2017.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;evaluation team&lt;/strong&gt; (TL, Senior experts and junior experts) shall have the following experience and expertise:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of EU external action policies, and the implementation modalities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of the international aid and development effectiveness agenda and principles e.g. Global Partnership for effective development co-operation (Busan) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;EU external co-operation policy and development policy of Member States, and their aid modalities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implementation procedures of the EDF;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compliance checking in the area of policy implementation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluation methods and techniques in general and, preferably, of evaluation in the field of external relations and development cooperation; in particular the team needs to demonstrate experience in analytical methods which can evaluate change, and which can evaluate contribution;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quantitative and qualitative data collection and analysis; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The evaluation team should have an excellent command of English – both spoken and written – and the ability to  function at a high level command of French, and also a passive understanding of Spanish and Portuguese&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further to this the &lt;strong&gt;Team leader&lt;/strong&gt; should have excellent communication, team co-ordination, presentation and proven report writing and editing skills in English. As well as previous experience leading complex evaluations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climate Disaster Management Expert </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/climate-disaster-management-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 10:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/climate-disaster-management-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this contract is to minimize the risks of probable disasters that may occur depending on the climate change in Turkey. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s) :&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of this contract are as follows: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To conduct legislative and institutional gap analysis, climate change impacts and climate related disaster vulnerabilities in Turkey analysis &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To prepare/revise the necessary project documents such as project fiche, terms of reference including the budget and technical specifications based on the analysis of existing documentation and stakeholder views for the project “Enhancing the Capacity to Determine and Reduce the Disaster Risks Stemming from the Climate Change in Turkey&amp;quot;. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Climate Disaster Management Expert&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expert 3 will be responsible for the preparation of legislative and institutional gap analysis report, lessons learned and impact analysis report and best examples report. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master’s degree in the field of natural sciences, engineering, earth sciences, environmental sciences, agriculture or equivalent. In the absence of the degree requested, the expert will have an equivalent professional experience of minimum 11 years in the relevant fields, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good command of written and spoken English. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 6 years of working experience in the sector related to the lot. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years of experience on disaster risk reduction and impact analysis of disasters. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Climate Change and Natural Disasters Vulnerability Assessment Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-climate-change-and-natural-disasters-vulnerability-assessment-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 10:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-climate-change-and-natural-disasters-vulnerability-assessment-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this contract is to minimize the risks of probable disasters that may occur depending on the climate change in Turkey. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of this contract are as follows: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To conduct legislative and institutional gap analysis, climate change impacts and climate related disaster vulnerabilities in Turkey analysis &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To prepare/revise the necessary project documents such as project fiche, terms of reference including the budget and technical specifications based on the analysis of existing documentation and stakeholder views for the project “Enhancing the Capacity to Determine and Reduce the Disaster Risks Stemming from the Climate Change in Turkey&amp;quot;. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2: Climate Change and Natural Disasters Vulnerability Assessment Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expert 2 will be responsible for conducting an analysis of existing studies, reports and documentation on climate related disaster risks, together with climate change impacts and climate related disaster vulnerabilities in Turkey to identify the likely changes in risk levels and areas under risk in the future and preparation of a report of changes in risk levels and areas under risk in the future with the findings and also preparation of a GIS map of these vulnerability areas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Qualifications and skills *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master’s degree in the field of natural sciences, engineering, earth sciences, environmental sciences, agriculture or equivalent. In the absence of the degree requested, the expert will have an equivalent professional experience of minimum 17 years in the relevant fields, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good command of written and spoken English. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of professional experience in the sector related to the lot. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 1 experience on climate change disaster vulnerability analyses, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in GIS mapping. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert with Extensive Experience related to Lot 6 Sector + Preparation of Project Fiches, ToRs, Technical Specs </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-with-extensive-experience-related-to-lot-6-sector-preparation-of-project-fiches-tors-technical-specs</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 10:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-with-extensive-experience-related-to-lot-6-sector-preparation-of-project-fiches-tors-technical-specs</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this contract is to minimize the risks of probable disasters that may occur depending on the climate change in Turkey. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of this contract are as follows: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To conduct legislative and institutional gap analysis, climate change impacts and climate related disaster vulnerabilities in Turkey analysis &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To prepare/revise the necessary project documents such as project fiche, terms of reference including the budget and technical specifications based on the analysis of existing documentation and stakeholder views for the project “Enhancing the Capacity to Determine and Reduce the Disaster Risks Stemming from the Climate Change in Turkey&amp;quot;. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert with Extensive Experience related to Lot 6 Sector + Preparation of Project Fiches, ToRs, Technical Specs&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expert 1 will be responsible for overall project management and preparation of the deliverables. Expert 1 will also revise the Project Fiche; prepare the Terms of Reference and Budget document, Technical Specifications and Market Research in accordance with the PRAG Rules. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master’s Degree in the field of natural sciences, environment or equivalent. In the absence of the degree requested, the expert will have an equivalent professional experience of minimum 17 years in the relevant fields. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good command of written and spoken English. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in the sector related to the lot. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 experiences in preparation of Project Fiche, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in preparation of Terms of Reference, Technical Specifications and budget estimation for both Terms of Reference and Technical Specification, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 1 year of experience working as a team leader within a project related to climate change issues. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert in promoting the use of ICT for sustainable agricultural development (Cat.I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-promoting-the-use-of-ict-for-sustainable-agricultural-development-cati</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 15:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-promoting-the-use-of-ict-for-sustainable-agricultural-development-cati</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance in the Mid-term Review of the Strategic Plan for Agricultural Transformation in Rwanda (PSTA III)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The expected global objective is to improve the agriculture sector’s delivery capacity towards the achievement of Rwanda’s growth-, export-, poverty reduction-, food and nutrition security-, and sustainable development targets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in promoting the use of ICT for sustainable agricultural development (Cat.I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University- or Postgraduate Degree closely related to information and communication technology (ICT), management information system or other subjects closely related to enhanced agricultural information and communication systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent English language report writing and communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of successful professional experience with analysing, designing, implementing and evaluating the use of ICT for enhancing agricultural data collection at grass-roots level.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of successful professional experience with analysing, designing, implementing and evaluating the use of ICT for enhancing agricultural extension and communication systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in youth - and gender-sensitive agricultural value chain development ( Cat. I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-youth-and-gender-sensitive-agricultural-value-chain-development-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 14:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-youth-and-gender-sensitive-agricultural-value-chain-development-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance in the Mid-term Review of the Strategic Plan for Agricultural Transformation in Rwanda (PSTA III)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The expected global objective is to improve the agriculture sector’s delivery capacity towards the achievement of Rwanda’s growth-, export-, poverty reduction-, food and nutrition security-, and sustainable development targets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in youth- and gender-sensitive agricultural value chain development (Cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University- or Postgraduate Degree closely related to agricultural sciences, agricultural economy, economy, enterprise development or business administration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of successful professional experience in analysing, designing and implementing agricultural value chain support projects/strategies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent English language report writing and communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 8 years of successful professional experience with analysing, designing, implementing and evaluating employment-creation support measures in agricultural value chains.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 8 years of successful professional experience with analysing, designing, implementing and evaluating strategies for engaging and empowering youth and women through agriculture value chain development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in soil and water conservation (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-soil-and-water-conservation-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 14:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-soil-and-water-conservation-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance in the Mid-term Review of the Strategic Plan for Agricultural Transformation in Rwanda (PSTA III)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The expected global objective is to improve the agriculture sector’s delivery capacity towards the achievement of Rwanda’s growth-, export-, poverty reduction-, food and nutrition security-, and sustainable development targets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in soil and water conservation (Category I)&lt;/strong&gt;
40 working days&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University- or Postgraduate Degree closely related to soil and water conservation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of successful experience in analysing, designing or implementing soil and water conservation strategies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent English language report writing and communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of successful professional experience with analysing, designing, implementing and evaluating investments in soil and water conservation of steeply sloped agricultural land.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of successful professional experience with analysing, designing, implementing and evaluating investments in radical and progressive soil terracing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Analysing Institutional Business Processes of Public Sector Institutions (Cat.I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-analysing-institutional-business-processes-of-public-sector-institutions-cati</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 14:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-analysing-institutional-business-processes-of-public-sector-institutions-cati</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance in the Mid-term Review of the Strategic Plan for Agricultural Transformation in Rwanda (PSTA III)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The expected global objective is to improve the agriculture sector’s delivery capacity towards the achievement of Rwanda’s growth-, export-, poverty reduction-, food and nutrition security-, and sustainable development targets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Analysing Institutional Business Processes of Public Sector Institutions (Cat.I)&lt;/strong&gt;
40 working days&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University- or Postgraduate Degree closely related to Public Sector Management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At  least  12  years  of  experience  in  Public  Sector  Management  Consulting  and  change management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent English language report writing and communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience related to harmonizing institutional goals, strategies and business processes of public and private sector agencies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Profound experience related to analysing defining and strengthening institutional performance of public agencies in the agriculture sector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Agricultural Policy and Economy (TL) (Cat.I – TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-agricultural-policy-and-economy-tl-cati-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 14:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-agricultural-policy-and-economy-tl-cati-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance in the Mid-term Review of the Strategic Plan for Agricultural Transformation in Rwanda (PSTA III)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The expected global objective is to improve the agriculture sector’s delivery capacity towards the achievement of Rwanda’s growth-, export-, poverty reduction-, food and nutrition security-, and sustainable development targets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Agricultural Policy and Economy (TL) (Cat.I – TL) 
60 working days&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University- or Postgraduate Degree in Agricultural Economy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At  least  10  years  of  experience  in  Project  Management  and  using  strategic  planning approaches/tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent English diplomatic language report writing and communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in analysing/advising national agricultural policies and public investments in relation to poverty reduction, food and nutrition security and sustainability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Profound experience with pro-poor and sustainable agricultural growth and agricultural transformation (value addition) strategies in a context of severe land scarcity for small holders in a land locked country.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for Junior Experts with Experience in Evaluation, Monitoring or Academic Research</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/call-for-junior-experts-com-2016</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 11:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/call-for-junior-experts-com-2016</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Call for Junior Experts, EC COM 2016&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Strategic evaluations analyse EU strategies from conception to implementation, assessing the results of EU funded activities. These evaluations are complex, covering several programmes and instruments over a significant period of time. They are conducted at several levels: country, region or sector; they can also assess the procedures and instruments EuropeAid uses to provide aid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Junior Experts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of post-graduate working experience in evaluation, monitoring or academic research&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of data processing and statistics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience with EU procedures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in EU Evaluations will be an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will be seeking experts with a variety of language skills, but *&lt;em&gt;French *&lt;/em&gt; is always an asset. All experts must be fluent in English.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are particularly interested in hearing from &lt;strong&gt;experts based in Brussels&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category II Expert in Media with Experience in South European Neighbourhood Policy</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-expert-in-media-with-experience-in-south-european-neighbourhood-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-expert-in-media-with-experience-in-south-european-neighbourhood-policy</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation of &amp;lsquo;MedMedia&amp;rsquo; Regional Project
**
**Overall Objective&lt;/strong&gt;
The overall objective of the project is to reinforce the role of media as vector for democratisation and contribute to the development of a more public service-orientated media landscape in the Southern Mediterranean as well as to contribute to the creation and development of a public sphere in the region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Purpose&lt;/strong&gt;
The specific objectives of the project have been reformulated by the inception report and approved by the Commission as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To build public trust by strengthening the media’s role as an independent watchdog and a forum for democratic debate;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To forge closer links between media practitioners across the region, thereby facilitating an ongoing exchange of experience and information;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To develop capacities in the media sector so that key players can rise to new professional challenges and respond to audience needs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To enrich and expand the informational resources available to the institutions and individuals responsible for implementing media reforms in the Southern Mediterranean Region.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One specific objective has been added by the Inception Report to give &amp;lsquo;due prominence to the project’s engagement on a governmental level and its commitment to giving new momentum to reform processes&amp;rsquo;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To strengthen partnerships with media policy makers at ministerial and parliamentary level and with key stakeholders lobbying for media reforms.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category II Expert in Media with Experience in South European Neighbourhood Policy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;University degree. In absence of the University degree, the relevant professional experience will be of a minimum 10 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As such, the experts must demonstrate the following experience: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive and relevant experience (minimum 6 years) in the field of international cooperation, preferably in geographical area of the South European Neighbourhood policy with field experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 4 years of relevant experience in the area of media development, freedom of expression. At least one of the experts should have experience in support for social dialogue, civil society or good governance and democratisation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full working knowledge of English and French and excellent report writing skills. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven Experience (min.2 years) in mid-term and final evaluation preferably of media development projects&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Neighbourhood South region&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good understanding of EU programmes and policies in the field of media development&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full knowledge of the principles and working methods of project cycle management and EC aid delivery methods.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least one of the experts should have a working knowledge in *&lt;em&gt;Arabic *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Media with Experience in South European Neighbourhood Policy (Cat I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-media-with-experience-in-south-european-neighbourhood-policy-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-media-with-experience-in-south-european-neighbourhood-policy-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation of &amp;lsquo;MedMedia&amp;rsquo; Regional Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overall Objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project is to reinforce the role of media as vector for democratisation and contribute to the development of a more public service-orientated media landscape in the Southern Mediterranean as well as to contribute to the creation and development of a public sphere in the region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Purpose&lt;/strong&gt;
The specific objectives of the project have been reformulated by the inception report and approved by the Commission as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To build public trust by strengthening the media’s role as an independent watchdog and a forum for democratic debate;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To forge closer links between media practitioners across the region, thereby facilitating an ongoing exchange of experience and information;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To develop capacities in the media sector so that key players can rise to new professional challenges and respond to audience needs;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To enrich and expand the informational resources available to the institutions and individuals responsible for implementing media reforms in the Southern Mediterranean Region.
One specific objective has been added by the Inception Report to give &amp;lsquo;due prominence to the project’s engagement on a governmental level and its commitment to giving new momentum to reform processes&amp;rsquo;:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To strengthen partnerships with media policy makers at ministerial and parliamentary level and with key stakeholders lobbying for media reforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Media with Experience in South European Neighbourhood Policy (Cat I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;University degree. In absence of the University degree, the relevant professional experience will be of a minimum 13 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive and relevant experience (minimum 12 years) in the field of international cooperation, preferably in geographical area of the South European Neighbourhood policy with field experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 8 years of relevant experience in the area of media development, freedom of expression. At least one of the experts should have experience in support for social dialogue, civil society or good governance and democratisation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full working knowledge of English and French and excellent report writing skills. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven Experience (min.3 years) in mid-term and final evaluation preferably of media development projects&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the Neighbourhood South region&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good understanding of EU programmes and policies in the field of media development&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full knowledge of the principles and working methods of project cycle management and EC aid delivery methods.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
