<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 09:24:49 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader and Evaluation Team, Evaluation of Budget Support in Cambodia 2011-2016</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-and-evaluation-team-</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 09:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-and-evaluation-team-</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation of Budget Support in Cambodia 2011-2016&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific rationale for undertaking this evaluation is to assess to what extent budget support in Cambodia contributed to achieve its expected results, notably through giving means to the partner government to implement the country’s Education Sector Policy, and to enhance the efficiency and effectiveness of policies, strategies and spending actions, thus contributing to sustainable results on growth and poverty reduction. 
The evaluation should also analyse how budget support has contributed to strengthening Public Financial Management (PFM), to improving transparency within government and accountability. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation will also consider other aid modalities (basket/common funds, projects), in order to assess the complementarity and synergies with budget support operations. It should look into Monitoring and Evaluation systems (M&amp;amp;E) and the availability and credibility of data. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation will take stock of what has been achieved with the main purpose to allow for lessons learnt and recommendations to inform on: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the conditions under which budget support has an effect and the possible intensity and nature (positive or negative) of such effect in Cambodia; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the design and implementation of future budget support operations in Cambodia; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;improvements to be set up by the European Union to maximize the impact of budget support in Cambodia; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;constraints in government policies, institutional structures and administrative arrangements in Cambodia which might impede the overall effectiveness and impact on spending actions and targeted public policy, and therefore of budget support. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; should have: strong experience of budget support modalities and budget support evaluation techniques, including an in-depth knowledge of the methodological approach for BS evaluations developed within the OECD/DAC framework; experience in managing complex evaluations; experience as team leader. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Evaluation Team&lt;/strong&gt; must have a thorough knowledge and experience with: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;development cooperation in general; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;different evaluation methodologies for complex evaluations; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;development cooperation in Cambodia; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;English fluent &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Within the team, thorough knowledge and experience is required with, adequacy for the assignment:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;budget support modalities; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;techniques for the evaluation of budget support; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;macroeconomics; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;public finance management; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;education sector; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;methods and techniques for rigorous impact evaluation. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following experience is an advantage: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;education sector in Cambodia; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;development cooperation in Cambodia; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ability to read and speak Khmer &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;lina_forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Development Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/social-development-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 21:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/social-development-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategic Approach for EU-Thailand Cooperation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of the assignment is to deliver a strategic approach for EU-Thailand cooperation that will contribute to Thailand&amp;rsquo;s achievement of sustainable development (SDGs), leading to reduced inequality and higher income status and at the same time demonstrating the impact and added-value of the EU contributions. Drawing lessons learned from EU relations with other upper middle income countries (such as Mexico, South Korea, Brazil), the specific objective of the study is to review and assess Thailand&amp;rsquo;s current state of development and the applicable EU instruments/initiatives and prepare a strategic approach for EU-Thailand cooperation in order to contribute to the political/policy dialogue and facilitate Thailand&amp;rsquo;s achievement of &lt;strong&gt;inclusive and sustainable development&lt;/strong&gt;, in line with the country SDGs&amp;#39; commitments. The cross-cutting issues such as gender equality, good governance, and environmental sustainability will be taken into account in the approach that will be developed. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Expert 2: Social Development expert, 30 w/d
*&lt;/em&gt;
*&lt;em&gt;Qualifications and skills *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced university degree (minimum Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree) in development studies, social development, certified by a Diploma (or equivalent professional experience of at least 9 years if candidate does not possess an advance university degree.);&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;S/he must possess facilitation and communication skills, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of oral and written English &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prepare and present well-written analytical documents &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer literacy (minimum MS Word, PowerPoint, Excel) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of experience in the domain of cooperation/development of strategies (social, environment, gender, multi-sectoral). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Up-to-date and comprehensive knowledge and demonstrated experience of EU development co-operation policies, instruments, and facilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Of the 6 years of general experience, at least 4 years are experiences in cooperation with upper middle income countries. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 experiences in development projects in ASEAN countries.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in development context in Thailand is an asset &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team leader/Development Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-development-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 21:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-development-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategic Approach for EU-Thailand Cooperation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of the assignment is to deliver a strategic approach for EU-Thailand cooperation that will contribute to Thailand&amp;rsquo;s achievement of sustainable development (SDGs), leading to reduced inequality and higher income status and at the same time demonstrating the impact and added-value of the EU contributions. Drawing lessons learned from EU relations with other upper middle income countries (such as Mexico, South Korea, Brazil), the specific objective of the study is to review and assess Thailand&amp;rsquo;s current state of development and the applicable EU instruments/initiatives and prepare a strategic approach for EU-Thailand cooperation in order to contribute to the political/policy dialogue and facilitate Thailand&amp;rsquo;s achievement of &lt;strong&gt;inclusive and sustainable development&lt;/strong&gt;, in line with the country SDGs&amp;#39; commitments. The cross-cutting issues such as gender equality, good governance, and environmental sustainability will be taken into account in the approach that will be developed. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 1: Team leader/Development Expert, 32 w/d&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced university degree (minimum Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree) in the field of development economics, political economy, certified by a Diploma (or equivalent professional experience of at least 15   years if candidate does not possess an advance university degree.);&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;S/he must possess facilitation and communication skills, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of oral and written English &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prepare and present well-written analytical documents &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer literacy (minimum MS Word, PowerPoint, Excel) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in the domain of cooperation/development of strategies (economic, investment, multi-sectoral). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Up-to-date and comprehensive knowledge and demonstrated experience of EU external policies , instruments, and facilities (including innovative financial instruments such as blending). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of international agreements &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Of the 12 years of general experience, at least 8 years are experiences in cooperation with upper middle income countries. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 1 relevant experience in designing/formulating strategic framework for cooperation for the EU &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 experiences as a team leader in the past 10 years;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key expert C II: Monitoring and Evaluation – Results</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-expert-c-ii-monitoring-and-evaluation-results</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 16:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-expert-c-ii-monitoring-and-evaluation-results</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term evaluation MDTF Khyber Pakhtunkhwa, FATA and Balochistan 2016 and 2017&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This assignment has as objective to contribute to the Annual Review of the MDTF 2016 and 2017. The overall objective of MDTF is to support the implementation of a programme reconstruction and development aimed at facilitating the recovery of the affected regions in the Khyber Pakhtunkhwa Province (&amp;ldquo;KP&amp;rdquo;), the Federally Administered Tribal Areas (&amp;ldquo;FATA&amp;rdquo;) and the Province of Baluchistan (&amp;ldquo;Baluchistan&amp;rdquo;) from the impact of: (i) the armed conflict and reducing the potential for escalation or resumption, and (ii) the floods of 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Under the overall coordination of the Team Leader and in close cooperation with the other members of the AR evaluation team, the expert is expected to contribute to the overall review conducted by a team of experts specialised in complementary fields and provide quality inputs related to his expertise in the part &amp;ldquo;Monitoring and evaluation – results&amp;rdquo; and other areas as assigned. Key work stream will include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How effective are the mechanisms in place for monitoring and evaluation and is the data required adequate, available in the format required and sufficiently robust.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quality assure the output data available for the review and provide recommendations, as appropriate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyse if the programme data sufficiently reflect its focus on poor and underserved areas, women, girls and children, and the requirements of the Gender Equality Act?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Duration&lt;/strong&gt;: January 2017 - January 2018&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key expert C II: Monitoring and Evaluation – Results, 20 w/d&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Masters Degree in in business management or administration, development studies, economics, social science or any other relevant field or its absence, equivalent professional experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong skills in writing clear, well structured and concise reports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 6 years of experience in program management of programs in the governance sector &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years proven professional experience in monitoring and evaluation of development programs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years professional experience in project cycle management and well versed in the use of the logical framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of recent developments in programme/project M&amp;E;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in evaluating complex development project/programmes, including in the fields of local or rural development and/or early recovery and rehabilitation desired&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in evaluation of Multi-donor programs, preferably Multi Donor Trust Funds and/or World Bank administered programs desired&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in evaluating projects using the DFID methodology and templates highly desired&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and interpersonal skills and be able to work in a team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Excellent knowledge of English, spoken and written is a must, Urdu is an advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The expert must be independent and free from conflicts of interest in the responsibilities he/she takes on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Assessors with Sector Experience and knowledge of EU External Aid Programmes</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-assessors-with-sector-experience-and-knowledge-of-eu-external-aid-programmes</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 08:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-assessors-with-sector-experience-and-knowledge-of-eu-external-aid-programmes</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to the evaluation of IPA II CSF &amp;lsquo;Regional Thematic Networks of CSOs&amp;rsquo; Call for Proposals&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;
To ensure adequate conditions to assess the call for proposals by providing the necessary technical assistance to the European Commission in the evaluation process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;
To assist the Evaluation Committee in assessing the proposals received under this call for proposals for 84 man - days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Assessors with Sector Experience and knowledge of EU External Aid Programmes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;senior experts&lt;/strong&gt; should have:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10 years of experience and a Master’s Degree Academic level or, in the absence of the Master’s Degree Academic level, in total at least 15 years professional experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of the issues covered by the grant programme concerned in the specific domain (e.g. Education, Culture, Good Governance, Human Rights, Minorities and Vulnerable groups, Gender issues, Reconciliation, Philanthropy, Media Freedom, Environment and climate action, Social inclusion, etc.), notably as concerns support to Civil Society Organisations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;team as a whole&lt;/strong&gt; should have the following expertise:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the rules and procedures of EU external aid programmes and ideally supporting evidence of a recent practical experience in the evaluation of proposals submitted under EU external aid programmes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of EU and enlargement-related matters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent oral and writing skills in English (level 1 in a scale from 1 to 5, where 1 is &amp;ldquo;excellent&amp;rdquo; and 5 is &amp;ldquo;basic&amp;rdquo; (Senior Experts)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced understanding of democratization and civil society related issues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one amongst the senior experts should have at least 5 years of experience in evaluation and/ or management of programmes and/or projects financed by the Instrument for Pre-accession Assistance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one amongst the senior experts should have at least 5 years of experience in evaluation and/or management of programmes and/or projects to support civil society&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience with PROSPECT and PADOR is an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The working language is English. Knowledge of Albanian, Serbian, Bosnian, Montenegrin, Macedonian and/or Turkish would be an advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the &lt;strong&gt;Assessors (Senior Experts)&lt;/strong&gt; will assume also the role of Team Leader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;Aurelie_Durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWP 2 Projects Review</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Beyond WTO Program (B-WTO) was developed in response to a request from the Government of Vietnam (GoV) for donor support to help with managing economic integration and the transition to a market economy following WTO accession. The B-WTO goal is “to strengthen government’s capacity to manage the integration of Vietnam into the global economy and the transition of Vietnam to a socialist market economy”. The immediate objective is “implementation of priority policy actions from the GoV’s Action Plan to enhance Vietnam’s capacity to sustain pro-poor growth (GAP)”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The remit of this project was a review of the 2nd annual work plan’s implementation (AWP2) of Phase 2 of the B-WTO in May 2013. The objectives of the review were to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the project implementation performance and project results relative to the logical framework targets and evaluation criteria. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the results achieved at the Component and Program’s level according to the Monitoring and Evaluation (M&amp;amp;E) framework of the Program.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify lessons learned from implementation, make recommendations for the remaining duration of the program and the Independent Completion Report process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program 2013 Performance and Quality Mapping Exercise</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID’s PNG Program is looking to improve its performance and quality (P&amp;amp;Q) standards and systems. The purpose of this project was to map the PNG Program’s current P&amp;amp;Q capacity and systems, to address the risk of AusAID being unable to demonstrate results for its increased investments in PNG over the next four years. Over the last several years, the PNG Program has undertaken a number of M&amp;amp;E assessments and reviews which have identified key strengths and challenges within the program. This project was intended to pick up where these assessments left off. Through a desk review and consultations with sector teams, the Review Team were to distil key P&amp;amp;Q risks and issues for the PNG Program. The Review Team’s brief included the provision of recommendations on priority activities to support sector approaches to M&amp;amp;E, strengthen the Program’s ability to collect evidence, provide critical analysis and report on results.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID required a consultant to assist with the development and finalisation of its Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework. Development of a humanitarian monitoring and evaluation framework is a key commitment outlined in AusAID’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy (HAP) and its associated Implementation Plan. In line with the agency focus on results reporting, the HAP and HAP Implementation Plan commit AusAID to develop a monitoring and evaluation framework to support the initial performance assessment framework contained within the HAP and AusAID annual reporting under the Comprehensive Aid Policy Framework.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key objective of this assignment was to build the Humanitarian program’s capacity for monitoring and reporting results by:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In consultation with AusAID’s Humanitarian team, redraft and finalise the Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework, to ensure it provides a platform to:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track implementation of key commitments in Australia’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy; and,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish a set of measurable humanitarian performance indicators (in addition to the two CAPF indicators) to enable AusAID to track achievements, lessons learned and to report on the results achieved from AusAID’s humanitarian work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of Pacific Forum Compact Reporting</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The purpose of the assignment was to examine country views of aid effectiveness and regional organisations expressed through Forum Compact reporting, particularly peer review of Forum Island Countries’ national development plan processes. The services provided included the preparation of a think piece which outlines key aid effectiveness issues arising from country reporting under the Compact reporting and discusses options for addressing these issues.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study on Community-based Social Protection</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/study-on-community-based-social-protection</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/study-on-community-based-social-protection</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Poverty and Social Analysis is the process of using and generating evidence on poverty throughout the aid management cycle. Most poverty and social analysis focuses on economic and human capital, but there are two oft neglected elements: voice and influence, and social capital. Yet more and more development practitioners are recognizing the importance of social capital, particularly informal social capital, in preventing and addressing poverty and vulnerability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This project supported AusAID to explore:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the role of informal social capital in the Fijian context and whether it lends itself to fair redistribution of resources and, if so, the ways in which AusAID can engage with local communities to strengthen existing social capital structures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;how such structures can enable the disempowered and poor to claim their entitlements in the three domains discussed in the PSA framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the potential challenges that can arise from such efforts. For instance, the poorest are often included on less favorable terms within social networks, and have access to fewer and lower-quality networks. Further, we need to better understand how poverty and disempowerment intersect with an absence of informal social capital, the repercussions this has, and the options available for tackling this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Provision of a Child Protection Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/provision-of-a-child-protection-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/provision-of-a-child-protection-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For this project HTSPE was contracted to provide a child protection specialist and handle all the associated management and administrative work. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The child protection specialist provided by HTSPE was required to work on an assignment designed to assist the Pacific Division (PACD) to improve its approach to child protection and managing risks to children. AusAID has a number of partners in the Pacific who work with children or come into contact with children through their activities. The AusAID-wide child protection stocktake, conducted in May 2013 found that there are a number of organisations funded by AusAID in the Pacific with a high or very high inherent child protection risk. Consistent with the stocktake report PACD proposes to escalate efforts to ensure partner organisations policies, procedures and practices are in accordance with AusAID’s Child Protection Policy 2013 and to make child protection a more explicit focus of PACD’s risk management system.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Environment and Biology Expert (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/opportunities/senior-environment-and-biology-expert-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 20:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/opportunities/senior-environment-and-biology-expert-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Expert 2 is expected to contribute the implementation of all of the related modules and the preparation of both training materials and Training Evaluation Report in the context of related chapter/s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in Biology, Ecology, Chemistry or other Natural Sciences related to assignment. In the absence of the degree required, at least 17 years of professional experience in the related areas is requested.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good command of both written and spoken English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General professional experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in the sector(s) related to the Lot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience in technical and/or scientific fields required for the implementation of the Water Framework Directive and/or Habitat Directive and/or other related Directives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 river basin management plans experience in terms of setting of environmental objectives and/or setting, design and upgrade of biological monitoring programme and/or execution and assessment of biological monitoring.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in development of measures for water pollution reduction and/or improving ecological status, and/or river basin characterisation/analysis will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in projects related to Integrated Water Resources Management will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
