<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 09:42:33 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader – Senior Justice Sector Reform Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-justice-sector-reform-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 09:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-justice-sector-reform-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The objective of the mission is to identify and formulate a programme to support, building on previous and ongoing actions and a demand-driven approach, relevant improvements of the justice system in Lebanon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader – Senior Justice Sector Reform Expert (Category I, 42 w/d)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least University Degree in law or relevant experience of 3 years in addition to the required general professional experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 15 years of experience in providing strategic and technical advice in the area of justice sector reform, including focus on areas such as juvenile justice and protection of children and other vulnerable groups; access to justice; international criminal law; international human rights law; penitentiary administration;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience as Team Leader in at least 2 identification/formulation missions in the justice sector of a minimum duration of 15 days/per mission&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in preparing the required Action Document/Fiche according to the EC template in at least 1 previous assignment related to the justice sector;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven working experience in Lebanon or other MENA countries would be a strong asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in written and spoken English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in written and spoken Arabic strongly preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;**WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/em&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Un Expert Senior en Evaluation dans le Domaine du Renforcement et de la Structuration de la Société Civile (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/un-expert-senior-en-evaluation-dans-le-domaine-du-renforcement-et-de-la-structuration-de-la-societe-civile</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2015 19:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/un-expert-senior-en-evaluation-dans-le-domaine-du-renforcement-et-de-la-structuration-de-la-societe-civile</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Cette mission d’évaluation finale doit permettre aux parties prenantes i) d’avoir une vision précise des activités réalisées au cours des 45 mois d’opérationnalité du Projet OSCAR et si non de leur impact, du moins de leurs effets sur les processus démocratiques en cours au Burundi ; ii) mais aussi, dans le cas où les conditions de démarrage du futur projet 11ème FED seraient remplies dans les prochains mois, de conforter la prise en compte de certaines des réalisations du Projet OSCAR dans le cadre de ce futur projet et iii) finalement de proposer des pistes de reformulation du futur projet 11ème FED au cas où la situation politique du pays continuerait à se dégrader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Un expert en évaluation dans le domaine du renforcement et de la structuration de la société civile (y compris les médias), ayant de l&amp;#39;expérience dans les thématiques suivantes: renforcement des capacités, ingénierie de la formation, réforme du cadre juridique régulant la société civile, structuration et mise en réseau des acteurs de la société civile, relations société civile – autorités gouvernementales, participation de la société civile aux processus de formulation et suivi-évaluation des politiques publiques. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chef de mission - Expert senior&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Niveau maîtrise en sciences sociales (formation complémentaires en droit et/ou économie souhaitable);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience de 12 ans minimum dans la mise en œuvre et/ou le suivi/évaluation de projets/programmes de développement (FED et autres bailleurs); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience de 5 ans minimum dans le domaine spécifique de la société civile;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience de 3 ans minimum dans le suivi/évaluation de projets FED;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins une expérience avec la société civile en Afrique sub-saharienne (au total 1 an de travail dans ce domaine dans cette aire géographique);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonnes compétences de communication dans différents milieux culturels;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise parfaite du français écrit et parlé.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Carbon Markets and Emissions Trading Systems</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-carbon-markets-and-emissions-trading-systems</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2015 12:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-carbon-markets-and-emissions-trading-systems</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The *&lt;em&gt;**main objective&lt;/em&gt;* of the present mid-term evaluation is to provide the relevant decision makers both in China and the European Union, with an overall independent assessment to make an informed judgment about the past performance of the project. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Particular attention must be paid to the project results in relation to supporting the national and regional institutional framework (policy and decision makers on the national and local DRC levels, as well as supporting institutions and think-tanks) and also to advance the EU-China ETS joint policy agenda, in order to document lessons learned and to provide practical recommendations for follow-up action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;**Project location&lt;/em&gt;*: China (Beijing, Shanghai, Guangdong and Hubei) and Belgium (Brussels)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Carbon Markets and Emissions Trading Systems&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;***&lt;em&gt;Qualifications and skills *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Academic qualification in a sector relevant to the assignment (at least Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree or, in its absence, equivalent professional experience of 5 years) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellent communication, drafting and reporting-writing skills; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven professional experience of at least 12 years in the sector (s) related to the Lot &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven professional experience of at least 7 years in the field of carbon markets and emissions trading systems, MRVA, registry, allocation, cap setting and market oversight. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The expert must have field experience in project management and project evaluation. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Language skills *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proficiency in written and spoken English. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience in the development of operational manuals, guides and training tools related to the ETS sector would be an asset, as well as knowledge of China and the local language (Mandarin) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert with Evaluation and Sector Experience , Cat I - Team Leader</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-with-evaluation-and-sector-experience-cat-i-team-leader</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2015 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-with-evaluation-and-sector-experience-cat-i-team-leader</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The *&lt;em&gt;**main objecti&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;ve&lt;/em&gt;* of the present mid-term evaluation is to provide the relevant decision makers both in China and the European Union, with an overall independent assessment to make an informed judgment about the past performance of the project. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Particular attention must be paid to the project results in relation to supporting the national and regional institutional framework (policy and decision makers on the national and local DRC levels, as well as supporting institutions and think-tanks) and also to advance the EU-China ETS joint policy agenda, in order to document lessons learned and to provide practical recommendations for follow-up action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project location&lt;/strong&gt;: China (Beijing, Shanghai, Guangdong and Hubei) and Belgium (Brussels)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert with Evaluation and Sector Experience , Cat I - Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Academic qualification in a sector relevant to the assignment (at least Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree or, in its absence, equivalent professional experience of 5 years) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication, drafting and reporting-writing skills; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proven professional experience of at least 12 years in the sector(s) related to the Lot at the international level in evaluation procedures and methodologies applied to the various modalities of implementation, instruments and channels of cooperation / aid delivery. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of technical and/or financial programme management as well as of Project Cycle Management (PCM) and Logical Framework Approaches. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of cost-benefit and impact analysis. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience with Governmental officials at senior level and within a team of international and national consultants &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience with EU-funded programmes and with ETS or carbon market-related programmes would be an asset. Working experience in or with China (short or long-term missions) would be also an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proficiency in written and spoken English. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rural Development Expert with specific experience in Needs Assessment in the Livestock Sector and Project Formulation</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/rural-development-expert-with-specific-experience-in-needs-assessment-in-the-livestock-sector-and-project-formulation</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/rural-development-expert-with-specific-experience-in-needs-assessment-in-the-livestock-sector-and-project-formulation</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this assignment is to provide technical support to the on-going process of defining and implementing support measures to fast-track the restructuring of the agricultural sector and establish a competitive and sustainable dairy sector that is able to produce Hellim/Halloumi in compliance with PDO requirements and in conformity with other relevant EU provisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rural Development Expert with specific experience in Needs Assessment in the Livestock Sector and Project Formulation (Category II, 30 w/d)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master’s Degree in Rural development or equivalent disciplines;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years professional experience in rural development, with main focus on livestock development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in livestock development and formulation of supportive measures;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with EU Guidelines on project cycle management and formulation procedures is an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent reporting, presentation and communication skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of participatory techniques and approaches is an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English, both spoken and written;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Turkish is an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Livestock Expert with specific experience in Elaboration of Plans to improve Milk Yields of Sheep and Goat Breeds</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/livestock-expert-with-specific-experience-in-elaboration-of-plans-to-improve-milk-yields-of-sheep-and-goat-breeds</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 07:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/livestock-expert-with-specific-experience-in-elaboration-of-plans-to-improve-milk-yields-of-sheep-and-goat-breeds</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this assignment is to provide technical support to the on-going process of defining and implementing support measures to fast-track the restructuring of the agricultural sector and establish a competitive and sustainable dairy sector that is able to produce Hellim/Halloumi in compliance with PDO requirements and in conformity with other relevant EU provisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Livestock Expert with specific experience in Elaboration of Plans to improve Milk Yields of Sheep and Goat Breeds (Category I, 50 w/d)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master’s Degree in Animal Husbandry, Biology, Animal Genetics or equivalent disciplines;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years professional experience in livestock development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in livestock breeding program;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with developing breeding plans for sheep or goats;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the Southern Mediterranean region is an advantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent reporting, presentation and communication skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English, both spoken and written;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Turkish is an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agro-economist with specific experience in Policy Formulation and Analysis for the Dairy Sector (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/agro-economist-with-specific-experience-in-policy-formulation-and-analysis-for-the-dairy-sector-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 07:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/agro-economist-with-specific-experience-in-policy-formulation-and-analysis-for-the-dairy-sector-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The *&lt;em&gt;**global objecti&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;ve&lt;/em&gt;* of this assignment is to provide technical support to the on-going process of defining and implementing support measures to fast-track the restructuring of the agricultural sector and establish a competitive and sustainable dairy sector that is able to produce Hellim/Halloumi in compliance with PDO requirements and in conformity with other relevant EU provisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agro-economist with specific experience in Policy Formulation and Analysis for the Dairy Sector (Category I, 120 w/d)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master’s Degree in Economics, Agricultural Economics or equivalent;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of professional experience in agricultural economics;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in livestock development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in policy analysis and formulation for the dairy sector;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in designing &amp;amp; supervising of value chain analysis will be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in data collection and analysis to support evidence based policy development for the dairy sector will be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent reporting, presentation and communication skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English, both spoken and written;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Turkish is an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWP 2 Projects Review</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Beyond WTO Program (B-WTO) was developed in response to a request from the Government of Vietnam (GoV) for donor support to help with managing economic integration and the transition to a market economy following WTO accession. The B-WTO goal is “to strengthen government’s capacity to manage the integration of Vietnam into the global economy and the transition of Vietnam to a socialist market economy”. The immediate objective is “implementation of priority policy actions from the GoV’s Action Plan to enhance Vietnam’s capacity to sustain pro-poor growth (GAP)”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The remit of this project was a review of the 2nd annual work plan’s implementation (AWP2) of Phase 2 of the B-WTO in May 2013. The objectives of the review were to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the project implementation performance and project results relative to the logical framework targets and evaluation criteria. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the results achieved at the Component and Program’s level according to the Monitoring and Evaluation (M&amp;amp;E) framework of the Program.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify lessons learned from implementation, make recommendations for the remaining duration of the program and the Independent Completion Report process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program 2013 Performance and Quality Mapping Exercise</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID’s PNG Program is looking to improve its performance and quality (P&amp;amp;Q) standards and systems. The purpose of this project was to map the PNG Program’s current P&amp;amp;Q capacity and systems, to address the risk of AusAID being unable to demonstrate results for its increased investments in PNG over the next four years. Over the last several years, the PNG Program has undertaken a number of M&amp;amp;E assessments and reviews which have identified key strengths and challenges within the program. This project was intended to pick up where these assessments left off. Through a desk review and consultations with sector teams, the Review Team were to distil key P&amp;amp;Q risks and issues for the PNG Program. The Review Team’s brief included the provision of recommendations on priority activities to support sector approaches to M&amp;amp;E, strengthen the Program’s ability to collect evidence, provide critical analysis and report on results.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID required a consultant to assist with the development and finalisation of its Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework. Development of a humanitarian monitoring and evaluation framework is a key commitment outlined in AusAID’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy (HAP) and its associated Implementation Plan. In line with the agency focus on results reporting, the HAP and HAP Implementation Plan commit AusAID to develop a monitoring and evaluation framework to support the initial performance assessment framework contained within the HAP and AusAID annual reporting under the Comprehensive Aid Policy Framework.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key objective of this assignment was to build the Humanitarian program’s capacity for monitoring and reporting results by:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In consultation with AusAID’s Humanitarian team, redraft and finalise the Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework, to ensure it provides a platform to:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track implementation of key commitments in Australia’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy; and,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish a set of measurable humanitarian performance indicators (in addition to the two CAPF indicators) to enable AusAID to track achievements, lessons learned and to report on the results achieved from AusAID’s humanitarian work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of Pacific Forum Compact Reporting</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The purpose of the assignment was to examine country views of aid effectiveness and regional organisations expressed through Forum Compact reporting, particularly peer review of Forum Island Countries’ national development plan processes. The services provided included the preparation of a think piece which outlines key aid effectiveness issues arising from country reporting under the Compact reporting and discusses options for addressing these issues.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study on Community-based Social Protection</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/study-on-community-based-social-protection</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/study-on-community-based-social-protection</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Poverty and Social Analysis is the process of using and generating evidence on poverty throughout the aid management cycle. Most poverty and social analysis focuses on economic and human capital, but there are two oft neglected elements: voice and influence, and social capital. Yet more and more development practitioners are recognizing the importance of social capital, particularly informal social capital, in preventing and addressing poverty and vulnerability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This project supported AusAID to explore:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the role of informal social capital in the Fijian context and whether it lends itself to fair redistribution of resources and, if so, the ways in which AusAID can engage with local communities to strengthen existing social capital structures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;how such structures can enable the disempowered and poor to claim their entitlements in the three domains discussed in the PSA framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the potential challenges that can arise from such efforts. For instance, the poorest are often included on less favorable terms within social networks, and have access to fewer and lower-quality networks. Further, we need to better understand how poverty and disempowerment intersect with an absence of informal social capital, the repercussions this has, and the options available for tackling this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Provision of a Child Protection Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/provision-of-a-child-protection-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/provision-of-a-child-protection-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For this project HTSPE was contracted to provide a child protection specialist and handle all the associated management and administrative work. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The child protection specialist provided by HTSPE was required to work on an assignment designed to assist the Pacific Division (PACD) to improve its approach to child protection and managing risks to children. AusAID has a number of partners in the Pacific who work with children or come into contact with children through their activities. The AusAID-wide child protection stocktake, conducted in May 2013 found that there are a number of organisations funded by AusAID in the Pacific with a high or very high inherent child protection risk. Consistent with the stocktake report PACD proposes to escalate efforts to ensure partner organisations policies, procedures and practices are in accordance with AusAID’s Child Protection Policy 2013 and to make child protection a more explicit focus of PACD’s risk management system.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Environment and Biology Expert (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/opportunities/senior-environment-and-biology-expert-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 20:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/opportunities/senior-environment-and-biology-expert-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Expert 2 is expected to contribute the implementation of all of the related modules and the preparation of both training materials and Training Evaluation Report in the context of related chapter/s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in Biology, Ecology, Chemistry or other Natural Sciences related to assignment. In the absence of the degree required, at least 17 years of professional experience in the related areas is requested.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good command of both written and spoken English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General professional experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in the sector(s) related to the Lot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience in technical and/or scientific fields required for the implementation of the Water Framework Directive and/or Habitat Directive and/or other related Directives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 river basin management plans experience in terms of setting of environmental objectives and/or setting, design and upgrade of biological monitoring programme and/or execution and assessment of biological monitoring.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in development of measures for water pollution reduction and/or improving ecological status, and/or river basin characterisation/analysis will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in projects related to Integrated Water Resources Management will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
