<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 08:38:52 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legal Expert (Category II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/legal-expert-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 08:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/legal-expert-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Technical Assistance to the Contracting Authority in decentralised management for the management of infrastructural projects under IPA TAIB and IPA NAP&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Global Objective&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this contract will be as follows:
To further strengthen the administrative and managerial capacity of the Decentralized Management structure for the management of the EU financial aid to the Republic of Serbia to effectively and efficiently manage EU funded infrastructural projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specific Objective (s) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective of this contract will be as follows:
Improved capacity of the Department for Contracting and Financing of the EU Funded Programmes, of the Serbian Ministry of Finance (CFCU), to award contracts, manage and monitor implementation and duly address outstanding legal and procedural issues arising in the course of preparation and implementation of infrastructural IPA 2013, 2014, 2015 and possibly 2017 projects managed under indirect management mode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Legal Expert (Category II) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Key Expert 2 will assist the Team Leader in project report drafting, organization and execution of project related trainings, OTSCs and site visits, and provide advisory services to the CFCU staff in line with the section 2.3. Requested services. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qualifications and skills 
• At least Master Degree in law, or alternatively, Bachelor Degree in the same field plus additional 3 years of general professional experience above the general professional experience duration fixed below;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;General professional experience 
• At least 6, preferably 8 years of post-graduate professional experience in law and/or procurement; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specific professional experience 
• At least 3, preferably 5 years of experience in providing legal assistance related to the issues arising from the implementation of infrastructural contracts concluded under PRAG and FIDIC;
• At least 3, preferably 5 years of experience in managing legal/procurement issues related to tenders&amp;#39; complaint and/or disputes;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Assets
• Experience in providing trainings on PRAG and/or FIDIC conditions of contract;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3976&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3976&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader / FIDIC Expert (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-fidic-expert-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 07:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-fidic-expert-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance to the Contracting Authority in decentralised management for the management of infrastructural projects under IPA TAIB and IPA NAP&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this contract will be as follows:
To further strengthen the administrative and managerial capacity of the Decentralized Management structure for the management of the EU financial aid to the Republic of Serbia to effectively and efficiently manage EU funded infrastructural projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Objective (s)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective of this contract will be as follows:
Improved capacity of the Department for Contracting and Financing of the EU Funded Programmes, of the Serbian Ministry of Finance (CFCU), to award contracts, manage and monitor implementation and duly address outstanding legal and procedural issues arising in the course of preparation and implementation of infrastructural IPA 2013, 2014, 2015 and possibly 2017 projects managed under indirect management mode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader / FIDIC Expert (Category I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Team Leader will execute, coordinate and manage the project activities. Se/he will ensure the timely and effective implementation of the services and achievement of results, through the proposed tasks. She/he is responsible for liaison between the CA, Project Beneficiary/CFCU and project team and must ensure that the experts inputs and the working days are distributed in the most efficient and effective manner. She/he will be responsible for ensuring management of the project and timely delivery of outputs. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master’s Degree in civil engineering, or alternatively Bachelor Degree in the same field plus additional 3 years of general professional experience above the general professional experience duration fixed below; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12, preferably 15 years of postgraduate professional experience in the field of civil engineering;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience in at least 3, preferably 5 completed projects either as the &amp;ldquo;Engineer&amp;rdquo; in projects implemented under FIDIC conditions of contract or as head of unit/senior project manager of EU funded works contracts &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Postgraduate professional experience as a team leader/senior project manager, or similar leading position, in at least 2, preferably 3 infrastructural projects worth at least 300.000 EUR each;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least 1, preferably 2 works contracts implemented under PRAG conditions of contract&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in providing training on FIDIC conditions of contract&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3975&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3975&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 3 - en planification stratégique et analyse des programme (catégorie III)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-3-en-planification-strategique-et-analyse-des-programme-categorie-iii</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-3-en-planification-strategique-et-analyse-des-programme-categorie-iii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectifs généraux&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif global de ce contrat est de contribuer à l&amp;#39;’amélioration de la performance et l’efficacité de l’administration publique pour accompagner le développement économique et social du pays. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectifs particuliers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elaborer un diagnostic et proposer un projet de réforme de l&amp;#39;administration et la fonction publique en République de Djibouti. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Renforcement des capacités du SECRA pour mettre en œuvre la réforme de l&amp;#39;administration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Diplômé de l’enseignement supérieur d&amp;#39;un niveau d&amp;#39;au moins Masters I (4 ans d’études supérieures) dans les domaines de planification stratégique, des sciences de gestion, management public ou autres disciplines équivalentes, il devra avoir &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;un excellent niveau de français. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cet expert devra avoir au moins 3 ans d’expérience, notamment dans des projets d&amp;#39;appui institutionnel. La connaissance  de l’administration publique djiboutienne serait un atout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;External CWS using Project-Proposal UK Application Form 
Link to job posting: &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3971&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3971&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 2 - spécialiste dans la réforme de la fonction publique (Catégorie II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-specialiste-dans-la-reforme-de-la-fonction-publique-categorie-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 14:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-specialiste-dans-la-reforme-de-la-fonction-publique-categorie-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectifs généraux&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif global de ce contrat est de contribuer à l&amp;#39;’amélioration de la performance et l’efficacité de l’administration publique pour accompagner le développement économique et social du pays. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectifs particuliers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elaborer un diagnostic et proposer un projet de réforme de l&amp;#39;administration et la fonction publique en République de Djibouti. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Renforcement des capacités du SECRA pour mettre en œuvre la réforme de l&amp;#39;administration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Diplômé de l’enseignement supérieur d&amp;#39;un niveau d&amp;#39;au moins Masters I (4 ans d’études supérieures) dans les domaines des sciences de gestion, management public, planification
stratégique ou autres disciplines équivalentes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Avec un minimum de 10 années d’expérience professionnelle dans le domaine de la réforme de la fonction publique et les appuis institutionnels. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Un excellent niveau de français oral et écrit est indispensable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;expert spécialisé dans la réforme de la fonction publique disposera d’une expertise d&amp;#39;au moins 5 ans sur l&amp;#39;élaboration et mise en œuvre des réformes de l&amp;#39;Administration et établissements publiques, notamment dans des pays en développement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;External CWS using Project-Proposal UK Application Form 
Link to job posting: &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3970&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3970&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef de mission - spécialiste dans la réforme de la fonction publique (Catégorie I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-specialiste-dans-la-reforme-de-la-fonction-publique-categorie-i</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 14:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-specialiste-dans-la-reforme-de-la-fonction-publique-categorie-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectifs généraux&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif global de ce contrat est de contribuer à l&amp;#39;’amélioration de la performance et l’efficacité de l’administration publique pour accompagner le développement économique et social du pays. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectifs particuliers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elaborer un diagnostic et proposer un projet de réforme de l&amp;#39;administration et la fonction publique en République de Djibouti. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Renforcement des capacités du SECRA pour mettre en œuvre la réforme de l&amp;#39;administration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Le chef de mission sera un expert en administration publique, organisation administrative et gestion des ressources humaines ayant bonne connaissance de l’Afrique francophone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Diplômé de l’enseignement supérieur d&amp;#39;un niveau d&amp;#39;au moins Masters I (4 ans d’études supérieures) dans les domaines des sciences de gestion, management public, planification stratégique ou autres disciplines équivalentes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Avec un minimum de12 années d’expérience professionnelle relative au secteur. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Il aura déjà dirigé des missions pour la réforme des administrations publiques, le rendant apte à organiser et manager celle-ci. Il devra avoir.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Un excellent niveau de français.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Comme chef de l’équipe, il sera le responsable du projet auprès des autorités locales, nationales et des observateurs internationaux.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format 
External CWS using Project-Proposal UK Application Form 
Link to job posting: &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3969&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3969&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Experts (x2) - (Cat III)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/technical-experts-x2-cat-iii</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 10:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/technical-experts-x2-cat-iii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the programme, of which this contract is a part, is to prepare the Turkish Cypriot community for the implementation of the acquis communautaire in the sector of energy in general and in regard to energy efficiency, beginning with schools, in particular.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To provide the Contracting Authority and the Beneficiary with a comprehensive assessment regarding the energy efficiency situation in 10 pilot schools (the list of the schools will be provided by the Beneficiary at the start of the assignment).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To provide the Contracting Authority and the Beneficiary with a clear and sustainable action plan for energy efficiency in the 10 pilot schools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To assist the Contracting Authority and the Beneficiary in implementing the energy efficiency measures foreseen in the feasibility studies of the 10 schools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To make specific recommendations for future support in the area of energy efficiency in schools in the Turkish Cypriot community based on the assessment of the situation in the pilot schools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To increase awareness on energy efficiency in the schools and of relevant stakeholders such as professional chambers and local communities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To increase skills in energy auditing of practitioners and consumers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requested Services&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To conduct a comprehensive assessment of the situation in the 10 pilot schools including (but not limited to):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carry out energy performance audits of the 10 schools and draft Energy Audit Reports. Data on energy consumption of the schools will be provided by the Beneficiary; however, their quality and format may not be fully reliable. Equipment to carry out the audits (infrared cameras, leak detectors, light meter, CO detector, etc.) will be provided by the contractor. It is expected that these tools will not be easily available for rent in Cyprus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Assessment of current local procedures and tools for measuring energy consumption in buildings and provision of recommendations to improve it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Review of implementation and effectiveness of applicable local requirements in the sector of energy efficiency in schools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prepare a Feasibility Study for measures to increase energy efficiency for each of the 10 schools (renovation/retrofitting strategies, smart metering, changes in behaviour, needs of awareness and training, etc.). The study will provide cost/benefit scenarios for different levels of increases in energy efficiency including analysis on equipment and human resources required to carry out the measures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Identify training and capacity building needs within the 10 schools with a view to implementing energy efficiency practices (in accordance with best practices and the EU acquis communautaire).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Review other EU funded projects on energy efficiency in schools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education (Minimum requirement):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A degree, preferably in a related field or, in its absence, 2 years of equivalent professional experience above the general professional experience duration fixed below (i.e. 3 + 2 = 5 years of general professional experience).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience (Minimum requirement):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 3 years of professional experience in the field of energy efficiency in buildings or energy audits in buildings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 2 years of project management experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recommended:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowledge of EU Directives and Regulations in the field of energy efficiency, including energy performance of buildings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience in conducting energy audits of buildings is a strong advantage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellent command of written and spoken English.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Command of written and spoken Turkish is a strong advantage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format 
External CWS using Project-Proposal UK Application Form 
Link to job posting: &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3967&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3967&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader - Cat I</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-cat-i-2</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 10:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-cat-i-2</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the programme, of which this contract is a part, is to prepare the Turkish Cypriot community for the implementation of the acquis communautaire in the sector of energy in general and in regard to energy efficiency, beginning with schools, in particular.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To provide the Contracting Authority and the Beneficiary with a comprehensive assessment regarding the energy efficiency situation in 10 pilot schools (the list of the schools will be provided by the Beneficiary at the start of the assignment).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To provide the Contracting Authority and the Beneficiary with a clear and sustainable action plan for energy efficiency in the 10 pilot schools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To assist the Contracting Authority and the Beneficiary in implementing the energy efficiency measures foreseen in the feasibility studies of the 10 schools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To make specific recommendations for future support in the area of energy efficiency in schools in the Turkish Cypriot community based on the assessment of the situation in the pilot schools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To increase awareness on energy efficiency in the schools and of relevant stakeholders such as professional chambers and local communities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To increase skills in energy auditing of practitioners and consumers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requested Services&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To conduct a comprehensive assessment of the situation in the 10 pilot schools including (but not limited to):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carry out energy performance audits of the 10 schools and draft Energy Audit Reports. Data on energy consumption of the schools will be provided by the Beneficiary; however, their quality and format may not be fully reliable. Equipment to carry out the audits (infrared cameras, leak detectors, light meter, CO detector, etc.) will be provided by the contractor. It is expected that these tools will not be easily available for rent in Cyprus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Assessment of current local procedures and tools for measuring energy consumption in buildings and provision of recommendations to improve it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Review of implementation and effectiveness of applicable local requirements in the sector of energy efficiency in schools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prepare a Feasibility Study for measures to increase energy efficiency for each of the 10 schools (renovation/retrofitting strategies, smart metering, changes in behaviour, needs of awareness and training, etc.). The study will provide cost/benefit scenarios for different levels of increases in energy efficiency including analysis on equipment and human resources required to carry out the measures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Identify training and capacity building needs within the 10 schools with a view to implementing energy efficiency practices (in accordance with best practices and the EU acquis communautaire).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Review other EU funded projects on energy efficiency in schools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education (Minimum requirement):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in energy, energy efficiency, renewable energy or a relevant related field or, in its absence, 5 years of equivalent professional experience above the general professional experience duration fixed below (i.e. 12 + 5 = 17 years of general professional experience in the energy sector).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience (Minimum requirement):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 12 years of professional experience in the fields of energy and energy efficiency in buildings (cumulative).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 3 years of experience in conducting energy audits of buildings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 5 years of experience in identifying measures for retrofitting existing public buildings to increase energy performance and drafting related technical specifications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recommended:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good knowledge of EU Directives and Regulations in the field of energy efficiency, including energy performance of buildings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5 years of professional experience as a Manager or Team Leader in implementing and/or managing energy efficiency in buildings programmes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience with EU funded projects and applicable procurement rules (following the PRAG).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellent command of written and spoken English.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Command of written and spoken Turkish is a strong advantage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format 
External CWS using Project-Proposal UK Application Form 
Link to job posting: &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3966&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3966&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 4 - Expert in audit of EU funded projects </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-4-expert-in-audit-of-eu-funded-projects</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 08:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-4-expert-in-audit-of-eu-funded-projects</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To further develop effective and efficient management and control system for the implementation of the IPA II programmes and to support effective implementation of the recommendations/conditions stated in the audit reports by the European Commission.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enabling NAO to effectively perform the monitoring role over the Management and Operating structure as well as for fulfilment of the conditions in the Financing Agreements and the related audit reports;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Establishing common comprehensive information security (IS) policies and procedures based on the ISO/IEC 27002: 2013 code of best practice for information security management, for the structures for indirect management of IPA II (NAO Support Office , National Fund, CFCD, Audit Authority, National IPA Coordinator and the IPA Structures within the following line ministries: Ministry of Environment and Physical Planning, Ministry of Transport and Communication, Ministry of Justice, Ministry of Interior, Ministry of Labour and Social Policy and Ministry of Education and Science);&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enabling internal auditors to execute internal audits on EU - IPA II funds for specific projects in accordance with internationally accepted standards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requested services&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The assignment consists of providing support to the beneficiaries in the specific areas where weaknesses are identified in the audit reports, such as:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Activity 1 - Support to NAO/ Managing Structure in effective supervision of the management and control system for the IPA II Programmes and certification of expenditures;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Activity 2 - Support in implementation of the recommendations stated in the Final Report from the ISO 27002 Audit and the activities in the Action plan for Information Security of the IPA II structure;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Activity 3 - Support to internal audit units in performance of the internal audit function related to IPA II specific requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree Academic level in the field of public finance, audit, business administration or in its absence, professional experience of 5 (five) years above the minimum general professional experience requested below; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Certified internal auditor by the Institute of Internal Auditors (IIA) shall be considered as an asset;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Working level of English language;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Computer-literate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of professional experience in EU programmes funds management. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 3 years of experience in area of internal audit of implementation of EU funded programmes;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience in conducting trainings in area of internal audit of EU funds is an asset.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format 
External CWS using Project-Proposal UK Application Form 
Link to job posting: &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3965&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3965&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 3 - Expert in Information Security </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-3-expert-in-information-security</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 08:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-3-expert-in-information-security</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To further develop effective and efficient management and control system for the implementation of the IPA II programmes and to support effective implementation of the recommendations/conditions stated in the audit reports by the European Commission.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enabling NAO to effectively perform the monitoring role over the Management and Operating structure as well as for fulfilment of the conditions in the Financing Agreements and the related audit reports;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Establishing common comprehensive information security (IS) policies and procedures based on the ISO/IEC 27002: 2013 code of best practice for information security management, for the structures for indirect management of IPA II (NAO Support Office , National Fund, CFCD, Audit Authority, National IPA Coordinator and the IPA Structures within the following line ministries: Ministry of Environment and Physical Planning, Ministry of Transport and Communication, Ministry of Justice, Ministry of Interior, Ministry of Labour and Social Policy and Ministry of Education and Science);&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enabling internal auditors to execute internal audits on EU - IPA II funds for specific projects in accordance with internationally accepted standards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requested services&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The assignment consists of providing support to the beneficiaries in the specific areas where weaknesses are identified in the audit reports, such as:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Activity 1 - Support to NAO/ Managing Structure in effective supervision of the management and control system for the IPA II Programmes and certification of expenditures;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Activity 2 - Support in implementation of the recommendations stated in the Final Report from the ISO 27002 Audit and the activities in the Action plan for Information Security of the IPA II structure;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Activity 3 - Support to internal audit units in performance of the internal audit function related to IPA II specific requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree Academic Level in the field of IT or in its absence, professional experience of 5 (five) years above the minimum general professional experience requested below;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;ISO/IEC 27000 certification.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of general professional experience in the field of IT.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 2 (two) completed assignments/projects linked with design, implementation and management of Information Security Management Systems (ISMS) and ISO 27000; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience in at least 1 (one) completed assignment/project in development of an ISMS using ISO/IEC 27002:2013; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience in ISMS auditing will be considered an asset.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format 
External CWS using Project-Proposal UK Application Form 
Link to job posting: &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3964&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3964&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 2 - Expert in monitoring of infrastructural projects </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-expert-in-monitoring-of-infrastructural-projects</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-expert-in-monitoring-of-infrastructural-projects</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To further develop effective and efficient management and control system for the implementation of the IPA II programmes and to support effective implementation of the recommendations/conditions stated in the audit reports by the European Commission.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enabling NAO to effectively perform the monitoring role over the Management and Operating structure as well as for fulfilment of the conditions in the Financing Agreements and the related audit reports;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Establishing common comprehensive information security (IS) policies and procedures based on the ISO/IEC 27002: 2013 code of best practice for information security management, for the structures for indirect management of IPA II (NAO Support Office , National Fund, CFCD, Audit Authority, National IPA Coordinator and the IPA Structures within the following line ministries: Ministry of Environment and Physical Planning, Ministry of Transport and Communication, Ministry of Justice, Ministry of Interior, Ministry of Labour and Social Policy and Ministry of Education and Science);&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enabling internal auditors to execute internal audits on EU - IPA II funds for specific projects in accordance with internationally accepted standards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requested services&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The assignment consists of providing support to the beneficiaries in the specific areas where weaknesses are identified in the audit reports, such as:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Activity 1 - Support to NAO/ Managing Structure in effective supervision of the management and control system for the IPA II Programmes and certification of expenditures;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Activity 2 - Support in implementation of the recommendations stated in the Final Report from the ISO 27002 Audit and the activities in the Action plan for Information Security of the IPA II structure;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Activity 3 - Support to internal audit units in performance of the internal audit function related to IPA II specific requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree Academic level in the field of engineering, public finance, audit, or in its absence, professional experience of 5 (five) years above the minimum general professional experience requested below;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Working command of English language;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Computer-literate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of professional experience in monitoring or supervision of infrastructural projects. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experience in supervision or monitoring of at least 3 EU funded infrastructure projects under red and/or yellow FIDIC rules.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format 
External CWS using Project-Proposal UK Application Form 
Link to job posting: &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3963&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3963&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 1 - Team leader</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-1-team-leader</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 08:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-1-team-leader</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To further develop effective and efficient management and control system for the implementation of the IPA II programmes and to support effective implementation of the recommendations/conditions stated in the audit reports by the European Commission.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enabling NAO to effectively perform the monitoring role over the Management and Operating structure as well as for fulfilment of the conditions in the Financing Agreements and the related audit reports;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Establishing common comprehensive information security (IS) policies and procedures based on the ISO/IEC 27002: 2013 code of best practice for information security management, for the structures for indirect management of IPA II (NAO Support Office , National Fund, CFCD, Audit Authority, National IPA Coordinator and the IPA Structures within the following line ministries: Ministry of Environment and Physical Planning, Ministry of Transport and Communication, Ministry of Justice, Ministry of Interior, Ministry of Labour and Social Policy and Ministry of Education and Science);&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enabling internal auditors to execute internal audits on EU - IPA II funds for specific projects in accordance with internationally accepted standards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requested services&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The assignment consists of providing support to the beneficiaries in the specific areas where weaknesses are identified in the audit reports, such as:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Activity 1 - Support to NAO/ Managing Structure in effective supervision of the management and control system for the IPA II Programmes and certification of expenditures;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Activity 2 - Support in implementation of the recommendations stated in the Final Report from the ISO 27002 Audit and the activities in the Action plan for Information Security of the IPA II structure;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Activity 3 - Support to internal audit units in performance of the internal audit function related to IPA II specific requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expert in Financial management/ internal control of EU funded projects &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree Academic level in the field of public finance, audit, law or, in its absence, professional experience of 5 (five) years above the minimum general professional experience requested below;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellent command of English language;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Computer-literate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of professional experience in EU programmes funds management. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 2 years of experience in financial management and control of EU programmes;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience as Team Leader and/or Chief consultant in minimum 1 (one) project financed by international donors and/or EU funds;  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience in conducting trainings in area of implementation and financial management of EU funds is an asset.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format 
External CWS using Project-Proposal UK Application Form 
Link to job posting: &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3962&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3962&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation Team: Expert II – Evaluation Expert (Cat II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-ii-evaluation-expert-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-ii-evaluation-expert-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Systematic and timely evaluation of its programmes and activities is an established priority of the European Commission. The focus of evaluations is on the assessment of achievements, the quality and the results of Actions in the context of an evolving cooperation policy with an increasing emphasis on result-oriented approaches. From this perspective, evaluations should look for evidence of why, whether or how these results are linked to the EU intervention and seek to identify the factors driving or hindering progress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evaluations should provide an understanding of the cause and effects links between inputs and activities, and outputs, outcomes and impacts. Evaluations should serve accountability, decision making, learning and management purposes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main objectives of this evaluation are to provide the relevant services of the European Union, the interested stakeholders and the wider public with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;an overall independent assessment of the past performance of the Agriculture for Development programme, paying particular attention to its results measured against its objectives;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;key lessons and recommendations in order to improve current (BAFS) and future Actions. It should not only describe what has been achieved or what the Action contributed to achieve but particularly why and upon what conditions results have been achieved or not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requested Services&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation will assess the Action using the five standard DAC evaluation criteria, namely: relevance, effectiveness, efficiency, sustainability and impact. In addition, the evaluation will assess two EU specific evaluation criteria:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;the EU added value (the extent to which the Action adds benefits to what would have resulted from Member States&amp;#39; interventions only);&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;the coherence of the Action itself, with the EU strategy in Sierra Leone and with other EU policies and Member State Actions, and the agricultural programmes of the World Bank in Sierra Leone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation team shall furthermore consider whether the following cross-cutting issues: gender equality, environmental sustainability and fostering of the private sector, were taken into account in the identification/formulation documents and the extent to which they have been reflected in the implementation of the Action and its monitoring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation process will be carried out in three phases: 
An Inception Phase, a Field Phase, and a Synthesis Phase. Deliverables in the form of reports should be submitted at the end of the corresponding phases. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum requirements of the team:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least one member of the team has sizeable experience in evaluation of agricultural policies and programmes/projects;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least one member of the team: 7 years of experience in agricultural policies and governance, strategic planning, project design and institutional capacity building; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least one member of the team: 3 years field experience in agricultural projects in West Africa, familiarity with Sierra Leone will be an asset; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least one member of the team: knowledge and experience of the project cycle management of EU funded development aid modalities;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least one team member: excellent oral and verbal communication skills in English;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills of the team:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;English &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least one team member: familiarity with one or more local languages is considered an asset.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format 
External CWS using Project-Proposal UK Application Form 
Link to job posting: &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3957&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3957&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation Team: Expert I -Team Leader – Senior Evaluator (Cat I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-i-team-leader-senior-evaluator-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-i-team-leader-senior-evaluator-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Systematic and timely evaluation of its programmes and activities is an established priority of the European Commission. The focus of evaluations is on the assessment of achievements, the quality and the results of Actions in the context of an evolving cooperation policy with an increasing emphasis on result-oriented approaches. From this perspective, evaluations should look for evidence of why, whether or how these results are linked to the EU intervention and seek to identify the factors driving or hindering progress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evaluations should provide an understanding of the cause and effects links between inputs and activities, and outputs, outcomes and impacts. Evaluations should serve accountability, decision making, learning and management purposes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main objectives of this evaluation are to provide the relevant services of the European Union, the interested stakeholders and the wider public with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;an overall independent assessment of the past performance of the Agriculture for Development programme, paying particular attention to its results measured against its objectives;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;key lessons and recommendations in order to improve current (BAFS) and future Actions. It should not only describe what has been achieved or what the Action contributed to achieve but particularly why and upon what conditions results have been achieved or not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requested Services&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation will assess the Action using the five standard DAC evaluation criteria, namely: relevance, effectiveness, efficiency, sustainability and impact. In addition, the evaluation will assess two EU specific evaluation criteria:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;the EU added value (the extent to which the Action adds benefits to what would have resulted from Member States&amp;#39; interventions only);&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;the coherence of the Action itself, with the EU strategy in Sierra Leone and with other EU policies and Member State Actions, and the agricultural programmes of the World Bank in Sierra Leone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation team shall furthermore consider whether the following cross-cutting issues: gender equality, environmental sustainability and fostering of the private sector, were taken into account in the identification/formulation documents and the extent to which they have been reflected in the implementation of the Action and its monitoring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation process will be carried out in three phases: 
An Inception Phase, a Field Phase, and a Synthesis Phase. Deliverables in the form of reports should be submitted at the end of the corresponding phases. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum requirements of the team:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least one member of the team has sizeable experience in evaluation of agricultural policies and programmes/projects;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least one member of the team: 7 years of experience in agricultural policies and governance, strategic planning, project design and institutional capacity building; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least one member of the team: 3 years field experience in agricultural projects in West Africa, familiarity with Sierra Leone will be an asset; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least one member of the team: knowledge and experience of the project cycle management of EU funded development aid modalities;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least one team member: excellent oral and verbal communication skills in English;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills of the team:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;English &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least one team member: familiarity with one or more local languages is considered an asset.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format 
External CWS using Project-Proposal UK Application Form 
Link to job posting: &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3957&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3957&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 3 – Cat III </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-3-cat-iii</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 10:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-3-cat-iii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of the programme, of which this contract is a part, is to enhance scientific literacy of the students at all levels of education in the Turkish Cypriot community via providing opportunity for laboratory experiences and to prepare them as the next generation of scientists, engineers and innovators with skills for enhanced employability and capacity for innovation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives are: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To provide a comprehensive assessment of the science and/or specialised laboratory infrastructure of around 200 pre-primary, primary, secondary education and vocational education and training schools; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To identify the types of labs required for different levels of education and to categorise the schools under different lab types in order to be able to identify the necessary equipment, materials, software needs for the establishment of science and/or specialised labs and/or mobile mini-labs in the TCc; and &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To make specific recommendations, in the form of a preparation of Technical Specifications or future EU support in the area of supplying science and/or specialised labs and/or mobile mini-labs, based on the findings from the assessment.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To provide recommendations on necessary structures for ensuring sustainability and effective utilisation and maintenance of the laboratories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technical Expert with at least 3 years of professional experience in the education sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education (Minimum requirement)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A degree in relevant fields such as science, education, pedagogy, social sciences, etc. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;or, in its absence, 2 years of equivalent professional experience beyond the general professional experience duration fixed below (i.e. 3+2 = 5 years of professional experience in the education sector).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional Experience (Minimum requirement)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 3 years of professional experience in the education sector specifically in science teaching and learning (cumulative).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 2 years of professional experience in science laboratories and experiments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 2 years of local experience in the education sector. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recommended&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of education systems and policies of EU countries and ET2020.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellent command of written and spoken English. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Command of written and spoken Turkish is a strong advantage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format 
External CWS using Project-Proposal UK Application Form 
Link to job posting: &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3953&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3953&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 2 – Cat II</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 10:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of the programme, of which this contract is a part, is to enhance scientific literacy of the students at all levels of education in the Turkish Cypriot community via providing opportunity for laboratory experiences and to prepare them as the next generation of scientists, engineers and innovators with skills for enhanced employability and capacity for innovation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To provide a comprehensive assessment of the science and/or specialised laboratory infrastructure of around 200 pre-primary, primary, secondary education and vocational education and training schools; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To identify the types of labs required for different levels of education and to categorise the schools under different lab types in order to be able to identify the necessary equipment, materials, software needs for the establishment of science and/or specialised labs and/or mobile mini-labs in the TCc; and &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To make specific recommendations, in the form of a preparation of Technical Specifications or future EU support in the area of supplying science and/or specialised labs and/or mobile mini-labs, based on the findings from the assessment.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To provide recommendations on necessary structures for ensuring sustainability and effective utilisation and maintenance of the laboratories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technical Expert with at least 6 years of professional experience in the education sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education (Minimum requirement)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in relevant fields such as science, education, pedagogy, social sciences, etc. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;or, in its absence, 2 years of equivalent professional experience beyond the general professional experience duration fixed below (i.e. 6+2 = 8 years of professional experience in the education sector).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional Experience (Minimum requirement)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 6 years of professional experience in the education sector specifically in science teaching and learning (cumulative). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 2 years of professional experience in science laboratories and experiments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In-depth knowledge of education systems and policies of EU countries and ET2020&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recommended:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with EU funded projects and applicable procurement rules (following the PRAG).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of written and spoken English. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Command of written and spoken Turkish is a strong advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format 
External CWS using Project-Proposal UK Application Form 
Link to job posting: &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3953&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3953&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader – Cat I</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-cat-i-1</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-cat-i-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of the programme, of which this contract is a part, is to enhance scientific literacy of the students at all levels of education in the Turkish Cypriot community via providing opportunity for laboratory experiences and to prepare them as the next generation of scientists, engineers and innovators with skills for enhanced employability and capacity for innovation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives are: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To provide a comprehensive assessment of the science and/or specialised laboratory infrastructure of around 200 pre-primary, primary, secondary education and vocational education and training schools; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To identify the types of labs required for different levels of education and to categorise the schools under different lab types in order to be able to identify the necessary equipment, materials, software needs for the establishment of science and/or specialised labs and/or mobile mini-labs in the TCc; and &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To make specific recommendations, in the form of a preparation of Technical Specifications or future EU support in the area of supplying science and/or specialised labs and/or mobile mini-labs, based on the findings from the assessment.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To provide recommendations on necessary structures for ensuring sustainability and effective utilisation and maintenance of the laboratories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technical Expert with at least 12 years of professional experience in the education sector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education (Minimum requirement)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in relevant fields such as science, education, pedagogy, social sciences, etc. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;or, in its absence, 4 years of equivalent professional experience beyond the general professional experience duration fixed below (i.e. 12+4 = 16 years of professional experience in the education sector).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional Experience (Minimum requirement)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 12 years of professional experience in the education sector specifically in science teaching and learning (cumulative). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 3 years of professional experience in science laboratories and experiments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In-depth knowledge of education systems and policies of EU countries and ET2020&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recommended&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 5 years of professional experience in designing technical assistance projects for the improvement of the education sector and the human-resource development sector. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience with EU funded projects and applicable procurement rules (following the PRAG).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of written and spoken English. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format 
External CWS using Project-Proposal UK Application Form 
Link to job posting: &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3953&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3953&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Senior Experts in Field of Law Enforcement </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/two-experts-in</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/two-experts-in</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term evaluation Euromed Police IV&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectives of the evaluation&lt;/strong&gt; 
Systematic and timely evaluation of its programmes and activities is an established priority of the European Commission.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The focus of evaluations is on the assessment of achievements, the quality and the results of Actions in the context of an evolving cooperation policy with an increasing emphasis on result-oriented approaches and the contribution towards the implementation of the SDGs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From this perspective, evaluations should look for evidence of why, whether or how these results are linked to the EU intervention and seek to identify the factors driving or hindering progress. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evaluations should provide an understanding of the cause and effect links between: inputs and activities, and outputs, outcomes and impacts. Evaluations should serve accountability, decision making, learning, and management purposes.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main objectives of this evaluation are to provide the relevant services of the European Union, the interested stakeholders with:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an overall independent assessment of the past performance of the Euromed Police IV, paying particular attention to its intermediate results measured against its objectives;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;key lessons and recommendations in order to improve current and future Actions. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In particular, this evaluation will serve to steer the ongoing programme and to prepare the next phase of 
this programme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main users of this evaluation will be DG NEAR B2 and indirectly DG HOME A3 and D1, DG DEVCO B5, EEAS MENA, Europol, Cepol and Interpol. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requested services 
Scope of the evaluation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation will assess the Action using the five standard DAC evaluation criteria, namely: relevance, effectiveness, efficiency, sustainability and early signs of impact. In addition, the evaluation will assess two EU specific evaluation criteria:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the EU added value (the extent to which the Action adds benefits to what would have resulted from Member States&amp;#39; interventions only);&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the coherence of the Action itself, with the EU strategy in the security sector and with other EU policies and Member State Actions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation team shall furthermore consider whether gender, the relevant SDGs and their interlinkages were identified and the rights-based approach methodology was followed in the identification/formulation documents and the extent to which they have been reflected in the implementation of the Action, its governance and monitoring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KE1 and KE2 (Cat.I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expertise required&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum requirements of the team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 5 years professional experience in the field of law enforcement, including fields such as organised crime, terrorism, cybercrime, trafficking of human beings, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Extensive experience in the field of international cooperation, of which preferably 3 years with North Africa or Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowledge of the EU Policy cycle and the work of Europol, Cepol but also Interpol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 3 years professional experience in project cycle management, in particular the logical framework approach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Significant experience in evaluation of projects in the field of law enforcement in the last five years (three references to be given with the name of the relevant evaluation manager, directorate and unit). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;None of the experts may have intervened as short-term expert in Euromed Police III or IV.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills of the team&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;English: at least 1 member shall possess a level B2 expertise;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;French: at least 1 member shall possess a level B2 expertise;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experto de Producción de informes de percepción público</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-de-produccion-de-informes-de-percepcion-publico</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 08:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-de-produccion-de-informes-de-percepcion-publico</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Programa de apoyo presupuestario al sector forestal de Honduras (PAPSFOR)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objetivos de la Evaluación&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La evaluación sistemática y oportuna, de sus programas y actividades es una clara prioridad  de la Comisión Europea . El objetivo de las evaluaciones es hacer un balance de los logros, de la calidad y de los resultados  de las Acciones, en el contexto de una estrategia de cooperación en constante evolución que se basa cada vez más en enfoques orientados a los resultados . Desde esta perspectiva, las evaluaciones deben buscar pruebas de porqué, cuáles y cómo estos resultados están vinculados a la intervención de la UE e identificar los factores claves que motivan o dificultan los avances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La evaluación deberá permitir la comprensión de la relación de causa-efecto entre las actividades, los efectos directos y los impactos. Las evaluaciones deberán tener como objetivos principales el contribuir a la rendición de cuentas, la toma de decisiones, el aprendizaje y la mejora de la gestión. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Los principales objetivos de esta evaluación son suministrar a los servicios competentes de la Unión Europea, las partes interesadas y el público en general:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Una valoración independiente de la ejecución Programa de apoyo presupuestario al sector forestal de Honduras (PAPSFOR), centrándose en especial en sus resultados ‘intermedios’ en relación a sus objetivos;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;las principales enseñanzas y recomendaciones con vistas a mejorar la Acción actuales (si aplicable) y futuras.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;En particular, esta evaluación servirá para evaluar el impacto que el Programa ha tenido hasta la fecha y comprender mejor la percepción pública de dicho impacto.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Los principales usuarios de esta evaluación serán el gobierno, la sociedad civil, los pueblos indígenas, la industria maderera, los donantes y el público en general.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experto de Producción de informes de percepción público&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Educación del equipo&lt;/strong&gt;:
Al menos una licenciatura en nivel académico o experiencia equivalente profesional, en Economía o Administración o Sociología o Psicología o Estadística o Ingeniería o Aplicaciones Informáticas, o Ciencias Políticas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experiencia del equipo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Al menos 3 años de experiencia en producción de Informes de Percepción Pública.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3932&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3932&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experto de Producción de video</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-de-produccion-de-video</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 08:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-de-produccion-de-video</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Programa de apoyo presupuestario al sector forestal de Honduras (PAPSFOR)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objetivos de la Evaluación&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La evaluación sistemática y oportuna, de sus programas y actividades es una clara prioridad  de la Comisión Europea . El objetivo de las evaluaciones es hacer un balance de los logros, de la calidad y de los resultados  de las Acciones, en el contexto de una estrategia de cooperación en constante evolución que se basa cada vez más en enfoques orientados a los resultados . Desde esta perspectiva, las evaluaciones deben buscar pruebas de porqué, cuáles y cómo estos resultados están vinculados a la intervención de la UE e identificar los factores claves que motivan o dificultan los avances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La evaluación deberá permitir la comprensión de la relación de causa-efecto entre las actividades, los efectos directos y los impactos. Las evaluaciones deberán tener como objetivos principales el contribuir a la rendición de cuentas, la toma de decisiones, el aprendizaje y la mejora de la gestión. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Los principales objetivos de esta evaluación son suministrar a los servicios competentes de la Unión Europea, las partes interesadas y el público en general:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Una valoración independiente de la ejecución Programa de apoyo presupuestario al sector forestal de Honduras (PAPSFOR), centrándose en especial en sus resultados ‘intermedios’ en relación a sus objetivos;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;las principales enseñanzas y recomendaciones con vistas a mejorar la Acción actuales (si aplicable) y futuras.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;En particular, esta evaluación servirá para evaluar el impacto que el Programa ha tenido hasta la fecha y comprender mejor la percepción pública de dicho impacto.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Los principales usuarios de esta evaluación serán el gobierno, la sociedad civil, los pueblos indígenas, la industria maderera, los donantes y el público en general.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experto de Producción de video&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Educación del equipo&lt;/strong&gt;:
Al menos una licenciatura en nivel académico o experiencia equivalente profesional, en Comunicación o Periodismo o relevante en producción del video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experiencia del equipo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Al menos 3 años de experiencia en producción de videos.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;El experto 5 necesita conocimiento en ambos idiomas de español e inglés.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3931&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3931&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experto con experiencia local</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-con-experiencia-local</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-con-experiencia-local</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Programa de apoyo presupuestario al sector forestal de Honduras (PAPSFOR)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objetivos de la Evaluación&lt;/strong&gt;
La evaluación sistemática y oportuna, de sus programas y actividades es una clara prioridad  de la Comisión Europea . El objetivo de las evaluaciones es hacer un balance de los logros, de la calidad y de los resultados  de las Acciones, en el contexto de una estrategia de cooperación en constante evolución que se basa cada vez más en enfoques orientados a los resultados . Desde esta perspectiva, las evaluaciones deben buscar pruebas de porqué, cuáles y cómo estos resultados están vinculados a la intervención de la UE e identificar los factores claves que motivan o dificultan los avances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La evaluación deberá permitir la comprensión de la relación de causa-efecto entre las actividades, los efectos directos y los impactos. Las evaluaciones deberán tener como objetivos principales el contribuir a la rendición de cuentas, la toma de decisiones, el aprendizaje y la mejora de la gestión. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Los principales objetivos de esta evaluación son suministrar a los servicios competentes de la Unión Europea, las partes interesadas y el público en general:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Una valoración independiente de la ejecución Programa de apoyo presupuestario al sector forestal de Honduras (PAPSFOR), centrándose en especial en sus resultados ‘intermedios’ en relación a sus objetivos;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;las principales enseñanzas y recomendaciones con vistas a mejorar la Acción actuales (si aplicable) y futuras.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;En particular, esta evaluación servirá para evaluar el impacto que el Programa ha tenido hasta la fecha y comprender mejor la percepción pública de dicho impacto.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Los principales usuarios de esta evaluación serán el gobierno, la sociedad civil, los pueblos indígenas, la industria maderera, los donantes y el público en general.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experto con experiencia local&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Educación del equipo&lt;/strong&gt;:
Al menos una licenciatura en nivel académico o experiencia equivalente profesional, en disciplinas relativas en Administración Publica, Economía, Medio Ambiente o Forestal o Desarrollo o Agronomía o Biología o Ecología o Cambio Climático.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experiencia del equip&lt;/strong&gt;o&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Al menos 3 años de experiencia en relación del tema de Lot 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Al menos 3 años de experiencia en países en vías de desarrollo en América Latina.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferiblemente, un mínimo de 1 año de experiencia en gestión de proyectos de apoyo presupuestario.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in this role please apply via the following link to the DAI website, including your CV in EC format &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3929&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3929&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
