<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2016 21:32:18 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Public Sector Reform (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-public-sector-reform-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2016 21:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-public-sector-reform-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Governance and Public finances Management Sector Review to Mongolia
*&lt;/em&gt;
The global objective of the assignment is to undertake a review of the Governance sector (for this assignment the scope of the term governance will focus on public sector reform, management of public finances and civil service reform) in Mongolia that will provide information for an
implementation strategy for the EU in the Governance sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of the assignment are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To assess previous Governance sector strategies and reforms in Mongolia, identifying the main obstacles that hindered the achievement of development outcomes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To assess the Governance sector performance and policies, identifying the main challenges and opportunities for the new Government to carry out successful reforms and policies in this sector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To carry out a risk analysis for budget support operations in the country&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To identify areas of intervention and aid delivery methods with its pros and cons, for the EU development cooperation in the Governance sector for the period 2017-2020.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Public Sector Reform (Category I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expert 2 will focus on governance aspects of the assignment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in Law, Political science, Economy, sociology and/or equivalent proven professional experience of at least 12 years related fields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education at advanced degree would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum required &lt;strong&gt;professional and technical skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Profound knowledge and experience of at least 10 years in public sector reform projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in governance sector reviews (in at least 3 international projects).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in programme preparation and drafting programming documents according to EU Budget procedures (at least 3 EU funded projects)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following &lt;strong&gt;professional and technical skills&lt;/strong&gt; would be an advantage:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work experience in at least one long-term international assignment related to public sector reform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in anti-corruption and/or civil service reform projects in middle income countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Middle income countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in the countries listed below3; experience in working in Mongolia is considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Communication skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical skills are required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very good communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very good drafting skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert must be proficient in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to  &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader Senior Expert in Public Finance Management (Cat. I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-expert-in-public-finance-management-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2016 21:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-expert-in-public-finance-management-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Governance and Public Finances Management Sector Review to Mongolia
*&lt;/em&gt;
The global objective of the assignment is to undertake a review of the Governance sector (for this assignment the scope of the term governance will focus on public sector reform, management of public finances and civil service reform) in Mongolia that will provide information for an
implementation strategy for the EU in the Governance sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of the assignment are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To assess previous Governance sector strategies and reforms in Mongolia, identifying the main obstacles that hindered the achievement of development outcomes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To assess the Governance sector performance and policies, identifying the main challenges and opportunities for the new Government to carry out successful reforms and policies in this sector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To carry out a risk analysis for budget support operations in the country&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To identify areas of intervention and aid delivery methods with its pros and cons, for the EU development cooperation in the Governance sector for the period 2017-2020.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader Senior Expert in Public Finance Management (Cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in economics / public finances or equivalent proven professional experience of at least 12 years related fields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education at advanced degree would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum required professional and technical skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Profound knowledge and experience of at least 10 years in the field of public finances management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in sector reviews of the public finances management sector (in at least 3 international projects).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in programme preparation and drafting programming documents according to EU Budget procedures (at least 3 EU funded projects)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following &lt;strong&gt;professional and technical skills&lt;/strong&gt; would be an advantage:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work experience in at least one long-term international assignment, related to public finances management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Public Expenditure and Financial Accountability (PEFA) methodology.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience elaborating risk analysis for budget support operations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Middle income countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in the countries listed below2; experience in working in Mongolia is considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Communication skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical skills are required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very good communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very good drafting skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert must be proficient in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;Nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M&amp;E Expert (Cat.II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/me-expert-catii</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 19:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/me-expert-catii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Local Economic Development Programme (ProDEL): M&amp;amp;E Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project of which this contract will be a part is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ProDEL´s&lt;/strong&gt; overall objective is to contribute to poverty reduction through income generation and employment opportunities in the rural areas of Mozambique. The purpose is to promote the economic development in the rural areas of Gaza, Inhambane and Sofala Provinces, by strengthening the productive base and the competitiveness of local micro, small and medium enterprises.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;M&amp;amp;E Expert (Cat.II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University  degree  in  development  studies,  project  planning  and  management, geography, sociology, or other related discipline relevant to the assignment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate with programme stakeholders in Portuguese and English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 6 years work experience, including M&amp;amp;E related to rural development. Specific professional experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the design and implementation of M&amp;amp;E systems, preferably for rural development programmes involving the public sector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience  with  data  collection  and  analysis  (quantitative  and  qualitative  data), statistics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in conducting training sessions, including facilitation skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very strong planning, system development and organizational skills, including results- orientation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent analytical skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good understanding of change management concepts and approaches.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent oral and written communications skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work with minimal supervision.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to undertake field visits.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully proficient in the following software applications: Word, Excel, and Power point.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strong advantage / highly desirable&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous work experience in advisory positions and/or capacity development related including the public sector in developing countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with modern technologies/IT solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Relevant in country experience in Mozambique, preferably including:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;design and implementation of M&amp;amp;E systems for preferably rural, economic, or agriculture development programmes;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;knowledge and familiarity with national statistics and alternative data sources;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;experience with primary data collection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Legal Expert </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-legal-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 09:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-legal-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EEM Haiti 2016&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objectives of the mission are the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess and evaluate all aspects of the electoral process in Haiti, and make recommendations in the area of electoral reform;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the implementation of previous EU (and non-EU) election related mission’s recommendations and propose targeted recommendations the authorities of Haiti should take in order to improve the election framework;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify needs and potential for additional bilateral or EU electoral assistance programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Legal Expert (Cat. I, approx. 90 WD)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education at least Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree Academic level in Political Science, International Relations, Law or any other discipline relevant to the assignment. In its absence, equivalent professional experience (more than 12 years). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in the area related to Lot 7. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years work experience in the field of electoral assistance and electoral observation and analysis, preferably as part of an EU Election Observation Mission or an Election Technical Assistance project of the EU or of other international organisations, possibly including managing an electoral observation mission, drafting statements and reports; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;S/he must have previously been directly involved in the organisation of election observation by the EU or other organisations with the participation in at least 3 election observation missions  with international or domestic organisations. Those can include: Election Observation Missions (Core Team positions), Election Assessment Team (expert position), Election Expert Mission (expert position), Exploratory Mission (expert position), Needs Assessment Missions (expert position). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with the legal and regulatory framework for the elections as well as international and regional standards for elections. In this context the “Compendium of International Standards for Elections” is an important background document; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven work experience on electoral legislation and good understanding of election dispute resolution systems; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent understanding of the functioning of election management bodies; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in assessing the media landscape and media framework, according to international and regional standards, particularly as regards to elections, will be an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in the country and/or the region and good networks within the different sectors of society in order to be immediately operational will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt; 
Excellent written and spoken French. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to  &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;Veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Political Expert (Cat. I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-political-expert-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-political-expert-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EEM Haiti 2016&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objectives of the mission are the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess and evaluate all aspects of the electoral process in Haiti, and make recommendations in the area of electoral reform;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the implementation of previous EU (and non-EU) election related mission’s recommendations and propose targeted recommendations the authorities of Haiti should take in order to improve the election framework;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify needs and potential for additional bilateral or EU electoral assistance programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Political Expert (Cat. I, approx. 60 WD)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced University degree in Law, Political Science, International Relations or any other discipline relevant to the assignment, or equivalent professional experience of approximately 12 years in the area related to Lot 7. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in the area related to Lot 7. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years work experience in the field of electoral assistance and electoral observation and analysis, preferably as part of an EU Election Observation Mission or an EU Election Technical Assistance project, possibly including managing an electoral observation mission, drafting statements and reports; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;S/he must have previously been directly involved in the organisation of election observation by the EU or other organisations with the participation in at least 3 election observation missions with international or domestic organisations. Those can include: Election Observation Missions (Core Team positions), Election Assessment Team (expert position), Election Expert Mission (expert position), Exploratory Mission (expert position), Needs Assessment Missions (expert position). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with the legal and regulatory framework for the election as well as international and regional standards for elections. In this context the “Compendium of International Standards for Elections ” is an important background document; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven work experience on electoral legislation and good understanding of election dispute resolution systems; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;S/he must be familiar with election -related legislation and international standards in the election field. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;S/he must have previously been directly involved in the organisation of election observation by the EU or other organizations. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in the country and/or the region, of working in a post -conflict environment and good networks within the different sectors of society in order to be immediately operational is an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt; 
Excellent written and spoken skills in French.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to  &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;Veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader/Electoral Expert (Cat.I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-electoral-expert-cati</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-electoral-expert-cati</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EEM Haiti 2016&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objectives of the mission are the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess and evaluate all aspects of the electoral process in Haiti, and make recommendations in the area of electoral reform;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess the implementation of previous EU (and non-EU) election related mission’s recommendations and propose targeted recommendations the authorities of Haiti should take in order to improve the election framework;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify needs and potential for additional bilateral or EU electoral assistance programmes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader/Electoral Expert (Cat. I, approx. 61 WD)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced University degree in Law, Political Science, International Relations or any other discipline relevant to the assignment, or equivalent professional experience of approximately 12 years in the area related to Lot 7. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in the area related to Lot 7. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years work experience in the field of electoral assistance and electoral observation and analysis, preferably as part of an EU Election Observation Mission or an Election Technical Assistance project of the EU or of other international organisations, possibly including managing an electoral observation mission, drafting statements and reports; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;S/he must have previously been directly involved in the organisation of election observation by the EU or other organisations with the participation in at least 4 election observation missions with international or domestic organisations. Those can include: Election Observation Missions  (Core Team positions), Election Assessment Team (expert position), Election Expert Mission (expert position), Exploratory Mission (expert position), Needs Assessment Missions (expert position); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with the legal and regulatory framework for the elections as well as international and regional standards for elections. In this context the “Compendium of International Standards for Elections” is an important background document; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent understanding of the functioning of election management bodies; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in assessing the media landscape and media framework, according to international and regional standards, particularly as regards to elections, will be an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in the country and/or the region and good networks within the different sectors of society in order to be immediately operational will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Language skills *&lt;/em&gt;
Excellent written and spoken French. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, the &lt;strong&gt;Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; will present the following profile: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and inter-personal skills; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent report drafting skills; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordination and management skills and past experience of management in a similar assignment, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven knowledge and field experience of EU policies and programmes in the area of human rights, democratization and good governance; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to  &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;Veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organisational Development Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/organisational-development-expert-1</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 11:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/organisational-development-expert-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance to consolidate the scope for the NSG Enterprise Architecture&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective is to further develop the ICT capability of the NSG in delivering training and development programmes efficiently and effectively. This objective will contribute to a professional public service that delivers quality services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Specific objective(s) *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective of this assignment, of which these Terms of Reference (ToR) will be part of, is to consolidate into one comprehensive project scope all the elements of the Enterprise Architecture into one solid Terms of Reference for the Public Service Training and Capacity Building Programme in accordance with the EU Restricted Procedures for service contracts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organisational Development Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 6 years&amp;#39; experience and knowledge of Organisational Development preferably in South Africa.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience in business process mapping and design in the context of public service learning/training&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience in ICT strategy design, development and implementation for the higher education sector evidenced by experience at least in 2 projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least one of the experts must have demonstrable knowledge of EU contractual/procurement procedures either through programme/project design/preparation, management or implementation most notably of Restricted Procedures for service contracts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The experts must sign a declaration of objectivity and confidentiality, annex A3 of the PRAG.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Enterprise Architecture Expert in Education, Training and Development Sector (Cat.I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-enterprise-architecture-expert-in-education-training-and-development-sector-cati</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 11:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-enterprise-architecture-expert-in-education-training-and-development-sector-cati</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance to consolidate the scope for the NSG Enterprise Architecture&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective is to further develop the ICT capability of the NSG in delivering training and development programmes efficiently and effectively. This objective will contribute to a professional public service that delivers quality services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective of this assignment, of which these Terms of Reference (ToR) will be part of, is to consolidate into one comprehensive project scope all the elements of the Enterprise Architecture into one solid Terms of Reference for the Public Service Training and Capacity Building Programme in accordance with the EU Restricted Procedures for service contracts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Senior Enterprise Architecture Expert in Education, Training and Development Sector (Cat.I) *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification &amp;amp; Skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Masters’ Degree or an equivalent qualification in Information &amp;amp; Communication Technology (ICT) or equivalent,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; In the absence of a Master’s Degree, a Bachelor’s Degree or an equivalent qualification in Information &amp;amp; Communication Technology or equivalent, will be considered with at least 15 years&amp;#39; experience in the fields listed above&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enterprise Architecture certification and/or Governance of Enterprise IT certification or IT certification or equivalent would be an added advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 12 years&amp;#39; experience and extensive knowledge of Enterprise Architecture design, development and implementation in the Education, Training and Development sector&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with the Government Wide Enterprise Architecture (GWEA), and related frameworks would be an added advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience in designing ICT tools and systems in the context of higher education sector&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience in ICT strategy design, development and implementation for the higher education sector evidenced by experience at least in 2 projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert/e en Évaluation de Programmes de Développement et de Cooperation</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-e-en-evaluation-de-programmes-de-developpement-et-de-cooperation-1</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 08:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-e-en-evaluation-de-programmes-de-developpement-et-de-cooperation-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Evaluer l&amp;#39;impact des projets de jumelages réalisés au Maroc en termes de renforcement de la capacité administrative et technique des administrations concernées et de  odernisation de leur organisation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert/e en Évaluation de Programmes de Développement et de Cooperation</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-e-en-evaluation-de-programmes-de-developpement-et-de-cooperation</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 06:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-e-en-evaluation-de-programmes-de-developpement-et-de-cooperation</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation de l&amp;#39;impact des Projets de Jumelages Instituionnels Rerealises au Maroc&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evaluer l&amp;#39;impact des projets de jumelages réalisés au Maroc en termes de renforcement de la capacité administrative et technique des administrations concernées et de  odernisation de leur organisation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Expert/e en Évaluation de Programmes de Développement et de Cooperation
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale : Diplôme d&amp;#39;enseignement supérieur de niveau Master (bac +5) en sciences politiques, sciences économiques, sciencesjuridiques/ droit ou domaine équivalent, ou en cas d&amp;#39;absence de diplôme une expérience professionnelle de minimum 17 années.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale : Très bonne maîtrise de la langue française parlée et écrite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale: 12 année en matière d&amp;#39;évaluation de programmes de développement et de coopération,dont au moins 2 ans à l&amp;#39;international dans des pays d&amp;#39;un niveau de développement similaire au Maroc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exigence minimale: * Expérience de l&amp;#39;évaluation d&amp;#39;au moins 3 programmes de renforcement de capacités institutionnelles d&amp;#39;administrations publiques comme exigence minimale;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en matière d&amp;#39;instruments de coopération pour le renforcement de capacités institutionnelles;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience fortement souhaitable des instruments: jumelage institutionnel, TAIEX et SIGMA;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans un pays ou ex-pays candidat à l&amp;#39;adhésion à l&amp;#39;UE souhaitable;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en matière de coordination de mission pour assurer la fonction de chef de mission souhaitable.
• Atout: Connaissance des procédures UE pour les instruments de jumelage institutionnel et assistance technique.
• Exigence minimale : Très bonne maîtrise de la langue française parlée et écrite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWP 2 Projects Review</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Beyond WTO Program (B-WTO) was developed in response to a request from the Government of Vietnam (GoV) for donor support to help with managing economic integration and the transition to a market economy following WTO accession. The B-WTO goal is “to strengthen government’s capacity to manage the integration of Vietnam into the global economy and the transition of Vietnam to a socialist market economy”. The immediate objective is “implementation of priority policy actions from the GoV’s Action Plan to enhance Vietnam’s capacity to sustain pro-poor growth (GAP)”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The remit of this project was a review of the 2nd annual work plan’s implementation (AWP2) of Phase 2 of the B-WTO in May 2013. The objectives of the review were to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the project implementation performance and project results relative to the logical framework targets and evaluation criteria. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the results achieved at the Component and Program’s level according to the Monitoring and Evaluation (M&amp;amp;E) framework of the Program.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify lessons learned from implementation, make recommendations for the remaining duration of the program and the Independent Completion Report process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program 2013 Performance and Quality Mapping Exercise</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID’s PNG Program is looking to improve its performance and quality (P&amp;amp;Q) standards and systems. The purpose of this project was to map the PNG Program’s current P&amp;amp;Q capacity and systems, to address the risk of AusAID being unable to demonstrate results for its increased investments in PNG over the next four years. Over the last several years, the PNG Program has undertaken a number of M&amp;amp;E assessments and reviews which have identified key strengths and challenges within the program. This project was intended to pick up where these assessments left off. Through a desk review and consultations with sector teams, the Review Team were to distil key P&amp;amp;Q risks and issues for the PNG Program. The Review Team’s brief included the provision of recommendations on priority activities to support sector approaches to M&amp;amp;E, strengthen the Program’s ability to collect evidence, provide critical analysis and report on results.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID required a consultant to assist with the development and finalisation of its Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework. Development of a humanitarian monitoring and evaluation framework is a key commitment outlined in AusAID’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy (HAP) and its associated Implementation Plan. In line with the agency focus on results reporting, the HAP and HAP Implementation Plan commit AusAID to develop a monitoring and evaluation framework to support the initial performance assessment framework contained within the HAP and AusAID annual reporting under the Comprehensive Aid Policy Framework.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key objective of this assignment was to build the Humanitarian program’s capacity for monitoring and reporting results by:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In consultation with AusAID’s Humanitarian team, redraft and finalise the Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework, to ensure it provides a platform to:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track implementation of key commitments in Australia’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy; and,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish a set of measurable humanitarian performance indicators (in addition to the two CAPF indicators) to enable AusAID to track achievements, lessons learned and to report on the results achieved from AusAID’s humanitarian work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of Pacific Forum Compact Reporting</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The purpose of the assignment was to examine country views of aid effectiveness and regional organisations expressed through Forum Compact reporting, particularly peer review of Forum Island Countries’ national development plan processes. The services provided included the preparation of a think piece which outlines key aid effectiveness issues arising from country reporting under the Compact reporting and discusses options for addressing these issues.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study on Community-based Social Protection</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/study-on-community-based-social-protection</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/study-on-community-based-social-protection</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Poverty and Social Analysis is the process of using and generating evidence on poverty throughout the aid management cycle. Most poverty and social analysis focuses on economic and human capital, but there are two oft neglected elements: voice and influence, and social capital. Yet more and more development practitioners are recognizing the importance of social capital, particularly informal social capital, in preventing and addressing poverty and vulnerability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This project supported AusAID to explore:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the role of informal social capital in the Fijian context and whether it lends itself to fair redistribution of resources and, if so, the ways in which AusAID can engage with local communities to strengthen existing social capital structures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;how such structures can enable the disempowered and poor to claim their entitlements in the three domains discussed in the PSA framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the potential challenges that can arise from such efforts. For instance, the poorest are often included on less favorable terms within social networks, and have access to fewer and lower-quality networks. Further, we need to better understand how poverty and disempowerment intersect with an absence of informal social capital, the repercussions this has, and the options available for tackling this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Provision of a Child Protection Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/provision-of-a-child-protection-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/provision-of-a-child-protection-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For this project HTSPE was contracted to provide a child protection specialist and handle all the associated management and administrative work. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The child protection specialist provided by HTSPE was required to work on an assignment designed to assist the Pacific Division (PACD) to improve its approach to child protection and managing risks to children. AusAID has a number of partners in the Pacific who work with children or come into contact with children through their activities. The AusAID-wide child protection stocktake, conducted in May 2013 found that there are a number of organisations funded by AusAID in the Pacific with a high or very high inherent child protection risk. Consistent with the stocktake report PACD proposes to escalate efforts to ensure partner organisations policies, procedures and practices are in accordance with AusAID’s Child Protection Policy 2013 and to make child protection a more explicit focus of PACD’s risk management system.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Environment and Biology Expert (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/opportunities/senior-environment-and-biology-expert-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 20:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/opportunities/senior-environment-and-biology-expert-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Expert 2 is expected to contribute the implementation of all of the related modules and the preparation of both training materials and Training Evaluation Report in the context of related chapter/s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in Biology, Ecology, Chemistry or other Natural Sciences related to assignment. In the absence of the degree required, at least 17 years of professional experience in the related areas is requested.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good command of both written and spoken English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General professional experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in the sector(s) related to the Lot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience in technical and/or scientific fields required for the implementation of the Water Framework Directive and/or Habitat Directive and/or other related Directives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 river basin management plans experience in terms of setting of environmental objectives and/or setting, design and upgrade of biological monitoring programme and/or execution and assessment of biological monitoring.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in development of measures for water pollution reduction and/or improving ecological status, and/or river basin characterisation/analysis will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in projects related to Integrated Water Resources Management will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
