<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2016 09:33:15 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experto Categoría II - Coordinador </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-categoria-ii-coordinador</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2016 09:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experto-categoria-ii-coordinador</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ATI MMAyA 2016-17&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;El contrato tiene como objetivo general apoyar al MMAYA en la implementación de los programas actuales así como en la fase de preparación de un Nuevo Convenio de Financiación (CF) Sectorial y el Programas de Asistencia Técnica al MMAyA. El asesoramiento se producirá a través de la provisión de estudios, metodologías, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location visits&lt;/strong&gt;: La Paz, misiones a las potenciales zonas de intervención: Santa Cruz, Tarija, Cochabamba, Beni, Pando y Oruro&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experto Categoría II - Coordinador  (110 días de trabajo)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preparación y calificaciones&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formación académica en los rubros de economía, ciencias sociales o biología. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formación complementaria (maestría) particularmente en temáticas de desarrollo y/o relacionadas al sector de agua y medioambiente.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debe hablar y escribir fluidamente en español. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Debe tener facilidad de comunicación y negociación para relacionarse con autoridades nacionales, subnacionales y organizaciones sociales, competencia intercultural y la predisposición de adaptarse a cambios del entorno institucional con creatividad. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experiencia profesional general&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mínimo de 6 años de experiencia en el sector de agua y medioambiente. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mínimo de 6 años de experiencia laboral en países en vías de desarrollo.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mínimo de 3 años de experiencia laboral con organismos de cooperación (donantes, agencias técnicas, ONGs) en Bolivia.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia demostrada en el desarrollo y/o implementaciones de programas sectoriales, en coordinación con instancias gubernamentales y/o sociales.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experiencia profesional específica deseable&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia específica relacionada con políticas de agua, manejo de cuencas, biodiversidad y/o sector forestal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia en el diseño y/o implementación de programas de fortalecimiento de capacidades. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiencia en trabajo dentro de o en apoyo a instituciones gubernamentales a nivel central o sub-nacional. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assistant(e) Social(e) (cat. II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/assistante-sociale-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2016 14:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/assistante-sociale-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Etude sur la nature et le volume du contentieux du placement des enfants au CARSEC de Nouakchott&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectifs généraux&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Améliorer l’efficacité du fonctionnement de la justice envers les mineurs en Mauritanie&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif particulier&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifier des pistes de travail judiciaires et sociologiques pour que l’ordonnance de protection pénale de l’enfance soit appliquée de façon plus efficace.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assistant(e) Social(e) (cat. II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BAC+4 dans sciences de l&amp;#39;éducation, sociales ou équivalentes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6 ans d’expérience dans l’accompagnement des mineurs en conflit avec la loi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 2 expériences d&amp;#39;études et/ou recherches de terrain dans le domaine du suivi des mineurs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance du français et d&amp;#39;au moins une autre langue officielle mauritanienne (hassanya, peulh, soninké ou wolof)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance des outils informatiques (notamment Word et Excel)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;Aurelie_Durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Un(e) Magistrat(e) Senior Spécialisé(e) dans la Justice des Mineurs </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/une-magistrate-senior-specialisee-dans-la-justice-des-mineurs</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2016 14:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/une-magistrate-senior-specialisee-dans-la-justice-des-mineurs</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Etude sur la nature et le volume du contentieux du placement des enfants au CARSEC de Nouakchott&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectifs généraux&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Améliorer l’efficacité du fonctionnement de la justice envers les mineurs en Mauritanie&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif particulier&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifier des pistes de travail judiciaires et sociologiques pour que l’ordonnance de protection pénale de l’enfance soit appliquée de façon plus efficace.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Un(e) Magistrat(e) Spécialisé(e) dans la Justice des Mineurs (cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formation permettant d&amp;#39;accéder au titre de magistrat dans le pays d&amp;#39;origine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10 ans d’expérience en juridiction des mineurs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 2 expériences d&amp;#39;études et/ou recherches de terrain dans le domaine de la juridiction des mineurs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance du français et de l&amp;#39;arabe&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance des outils informatiques (notamment Word et Excel)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;Aurelie_Durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junior Civil Society Expert familiar with Enlargement Agenda in Western Balkans and Turkey</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-civil-society-expert-familiar-with-enlargement-agenda-in-western-balkans-and-turkey</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2016 14:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-civil-society-expert-familiar-with-enlargement-agenda-in-western-balkans-and-turkey</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation of the Civil Society Facility for the Western Balkans and Turkey&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a mid-term evaluation of EU&amp;rsquo;s support to civil society organisations in the Western Balkans (namely in Albania, Bosnia and Herzegovina; Croatia; former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia; Kosovo, Montenegro and Serbia) and Turkey over the period 2011-2016 in the context of the EU enlargement policy. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The primary objective of the evaluation is to assess the performance of financial assistance in achieving its objectives, and namely, its relevance, efficiency, effectiveness, EU added value, coherence, complementarity and consistency as well as impact and sustainability. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation will also provide findings and recommendations to assist the Directorate General for Neighbourhood and Enlargement Negotiations of the European Commission (DG NEAR) in the programming and implementation of EU pre-accession assistance to support civil society in candidate and potential candidate countries with a view of improving the instruments available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Junior Civil Society Expert familiar with Enlargement Agenda in Western Balkans and Turkey&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;: Education at least Master&amp;rsquo;s degree Academic Level (where a university degree has been awarded on completion of four years study in a university or equivalent institution) in social sciences, public affairs, political sciences, international relations or related field or, in its absence, at least 5 years of professional experience in the same fields. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;: At least 3 years of professional experience in evaluation, project cycle management, sound financial management audit, monitoring or academic research &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years professional experience in the field of Civil Society. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with the European institutional environment and the Enlargement agenda in the Western Balkans and Turkey. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with the role of civil society in the Western Balkans and Turkey, including opportunities and challenges faced. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated interpersonal and diplomatic skills, as well as the ability to communicate effectively with all stakeholders and to present ideas clearly and effectively. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of any local languages in the region (WBT) will be an advantage. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;minimum requirement for the team&lt;/strong&gt; as a whole are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience covering at least 80% of the sectors of implementation of CSO grants and contracts under the CSF as per background &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent oral and writing skills in English (level 1 in a scale from 1 to 5, where 1 is &amp;ldquo;excellent&amp;rdquo; and 5 is &amp;ldquo;basic&amp;rdquo; (all the experts) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very good knowledge of the history, culture, social and political situation of the Western Balkans and Turkey &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very good knowledge of the European institutional environment and the Enlargement agenda in the Western Balkans and Turkey &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced understanding of democratization and civil society related issues &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one of the experts should possess IT and database management capacities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Command of the following languages would be considered an advantage: Albanian, Serbo-Croat-Bosnian, Macedonian and Turkish (team as a whole)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Civil Society Experts familiar with Enlargement Agenda in Western Balkans and Turkey</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-civil-society-experts-familiar-with-enlargement-agenda-in-western-balkans-and-turkey</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2016 13:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-civil-society-experts-familiar-with-enlargement-agenda-in-western-balkans-and-turkey</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation of the Civil Society Facility for the Western Balkans and Turkey&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a mid-term evaluation of EU&amp;rsquo;s support to civil society organisations in the Western Balkans (namely in Albania, Bosnia and Herzegovina; Croatia; former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia; Kosovo, Montenegro and Serbia) and Turkey over the period 2011-2016 in the context of the EU enlargement policy. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The primary objective of the evaluation is to assess the performance of financial assistance in achieving its objectives, and namely, its relevance, efficiency, effectiveness, EU added value, coherence, complementarity and consistency as well as impact and sustainability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation will also provide findings and recommendations to assist the Directorate General for Neighbourhood and Enlargement Negotiations of the European Commission (DG NEAR) in the programming and implementation of EU pre-accession assistance to support civil society in candidate and potential candidate countries with a view of improving the instruments available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3 Senior Civil Society Experts familiar with Enlargement Agenda in Western Balkans and Turkey&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;: Education at least Master&amp;rsquo;s degree Academic Level (where a university degree has been awarded on completion of four years study in a university or equivalent institution) in social sciences, public affairs, political sciences, international relations or related field or, in its absence, at least 15 years of professional experience in the same fields. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;: At least 12 years of professional experience in evaluation, project management, sound financial management audit, monitoring or academic research. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years professional experience in the field of Civil Society. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with the European institutional environment and the Enlargement agenda in the Western Balkans and Turkey. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with the role of civil society in the Western Balkans and Turkey, including opportunities and challenges faced. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated interpersonal and diplomatic skills, as well as the ability to communicate effectively with all stakeholders and to present ideas clearly and effectively. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of any local languages in the region (WBT) will be an advantage. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one amongst the senior experts should have at least 5 years of experience in team leadership and drafting evaluation reports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one amongst the senior experts should have at least 5 years of experience in evaluation of EU pre-accession assistance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least one amongst the senior experts should have at least 5 years of experience in evaluation and/or management of programmes and/or project to support civil society&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 2 and 3: Data Collection Analyst on Gender Equality in Public Administration </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-and-3-data-collection-analyst-on-gender-equality-in-public-administration</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 18:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-and-3-data-collection-analyst-on-gender-equality-in-public-administration</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Study on Gender Equality in Public Administration in the Western Balkans
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;
The overall objective of this assignment is to contribute to strengthening girl&amp;rsquo;s and women&amp;rsquo;s voice and participation in the Western Balkans, in particular, women’s empowerment and expanded participation in policy-making and leadership in the executive branch of the state.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The study will cover the Western Balkans (Albania, Bosnia &amp;amp; Herzegovina, Kosovo, the former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, Montenegro and Serbia) and should achieve the following specific objectives:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide an overview of the current state-of-play, gaps, barriers and challenges to women&amp;rsquo;s participation in decision-making, both participation in public policy/strategy development and participation in leadership positions. The analysis will focus on the thematic area &amp;lsquo;strengthening voice and participation&amp;rsquo; identified in the Gender Action Plan. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyse country-specific legal frameworks, policies and initiatives indicating major constraints and enabling factors of promoting gender equality and women’s empowerment in public administration. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify policy and programming recommendations for further action, including specific entry points for the EC to advance women’s equal participation in public administration in the Western Balkans.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2 and 3: Data Collection Analyst on Gender Equality in Public Administration (maximum 70 working days)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These Category III analysts shall:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Carry out data collection on Gender Equality in Public Administration in all the Western Balkan countries;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support the Team Leader on desk review of findings and data; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the drafting of all deliverables of the study; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Draft initial correspondence requesting data, including a brief questionnaire;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proactively contact institution/agency/department that house civil servant data in all countries in the region; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continue correspondence, with the support of the team leader, until any available data is collected. Organize collected data;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Synthesize findings into a first-level analysis on the availability of data. Summarize experience and lessons-learned from data collection efforts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performing supporting and administrative activities related to the project implementation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competencies&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong command of data collection and analysis;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication, organization, and time management skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to perform tasks in timely manner and under pressure, to tight deadlines;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate in English verbally and in writing with a wide range of stakeholders (e.g. government officials, civil society organizations, etc.) and ability to work collaboratively online and via email;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to work independently and as part of a team seamlessly using a range of modern means of communication.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University Degree in relevant area such as Public Administration, Public Policy, Social and Political Sciences, Gender Studies, International Law, Development Studies, or equivalent. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of relevant professional experience in gender and/or one or more of the areas of, governance (with particular emphasis on public administration reforms)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with extensive online research;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with quantitative research and data collection;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of decision-making processes in public policy, public service delivery, institutional capacity building, human resource management policies, professional ethics and/or civil service reform would be desirable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of the international framework on gender equality and women&amp;rsquo;s empowerment, particularly in the area of women&amp;rsquo;s participation in policy and decision-making and leadership; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the EU Gender Equality Policy and Gender Action Plan would be considered an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in the Western Balkans in issues related to public administration reform and/or gender equality will be a strong asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent spoken and written English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of any of the languages spoken in the Western Balkans would be a distinctive advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert on Gender Equality in Public Administration (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-on-gender-equality-in-public-administration-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 18:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-on-gender-equality-in-public-administration-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Study on Gender Equality in Public Administration in the Western Balkans&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of this assignment is to contribute to strengthening girl&amp;rsquo;s and women&amp;rsquo;s voice and participation in the Western Balkans, in particular, women’s empowerment and expanded participation in policy-making and leadership in the executive branch of the state.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The study will cover the Western Balkans (Albania, Bosnia &amp;amp; Herzegovina, Kosovo*, the former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, Montenegro and Serbia) and should achieve the following specific objectives:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide an overview of the current state-of-play, gaps, barriers and challenges to women&amp;rsquo;s participation in decision-making, both participation in public policy/strategy development and participation in leadership positions. The analysis will focus on the thematic area &amp;lsquo;strengthening voice and participation&amp;rsquo; identified in the Gender Action Plan. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyse country-specific legal frameworks, policies and initiatives indicating major constraints and enabling factors of promoting gender equality and women’s empowerment in public administration. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify policy and programming recommendations for further action, including specific entry points for the EC to advance women’s equal participation in public administration in the Western Balkans.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 1: Team leader, Senior Expert on Gender Equality in Public Administration (maximum 70 working days)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The team leader (&lt;strong&gt;Senior expert – Category I&lt;/strong&gt;) shall: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plan, supervise, coordinate and monitor the overall implementation of the study; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plan and supervise all the tasks according to the proposed methodology, including research and data collection, performing gender equality analysis and drafting of the study;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supervise the work of the junior experts (experts 2 and 3) to perform all the activities concerning research and collection of relevant data; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure backstopping and financial management of the project; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain regular communication with the contracting authority.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competencies&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong command of data collection and analysis;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication, organization, and time management skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to perform tasks in timely manner and under pressure, to tight deadlines;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong interpersonal skills, ability to coordinate and synchronize work with diverse cultural backgrounds, and ability to   work in different environments;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to communicate in English verbally and in writing with a wide range of stakeholders (e.g. government officials, civil society organizations, etc.) and ability to work collaboratively online and via email;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to work independently and as part of a team seamlessly using a range of modern means of communication;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent report writing skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Masters&amp;#39; Degree in relevant area such as Public Administration, Public Policy, Social and Political Sciences, Gender Studies, International Law, or equivalent. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 10 years of relevant professional experience in gender and/or one or more of the areas of governance (with particular emphasis on public administration reforms);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in data collection;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project management;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience coordinating/supervising studies/research projects;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience  in quantitative research and statistical analysis &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in analysis and research on public administration reform and/or gender mainstreaming in the public sector;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of the international framework on gender equality and women&amp;rsquo;s empowerment, particularly in the area of women&amp;rsquo;s participation in policy and decision-making and leadership; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent knowledge of decision-making processes in public policy, public service delivery, institutional capacity building, human resource management policies, professional ethics and/or civil service reform would be desirable;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the EU Gender Equality Policy and Gender Action Plan would be considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in the Western Balkans in issues related to public administration reform and/or gender equality will be a strong asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent spoken and written English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of any of the languages spoken in the Western Balkans would be a distinctive advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Management of Not-for-Profit Organisations</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-management-of-not-for-profit-organisations</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 11:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-management-of-not-for-profit-organisations</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance to OCTA for its Institutional Strengthening&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of this activity is to assist the Executive Committee of OCTA in the implementation of its mandate from the 14th OCTA Ministerial Conference to &amp;ldquo;examine options for further strengthening the OCTA Secretariat&amp;rdquo;, to seek to address the &amp;ldquo;need for technical assistance and support&amp;rdquo; in addition to members&amp;#39; contribution to the operation cost for OCTA&amp;rsquo;s secretariat, and to &amp;ldquo;review the Articles of Association in view of presenting recommendations to the 15th Ministerial Conference&amp;rdquo; in February 2017.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPECIFIC OBJECTIVE(S)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of the assignment include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Objective 1: Assist in ensuring that it fulfills its legal, contractual, fiscal, accounting and HR obligations;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Objective  2: Assist  OCTA  in reviewing the Articles  of Association  in the  context of  its institutional strengthening and presenting recommendations to the Ministerial Conference;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Objective 3: Assist OCTA in the process of applying for financial support by the European Union in the frame of the 11th EDF.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The requirement is for one &lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert&lt;/strong&gt; for up to 60 days, with proven experience in the daily management of non-for-profit organisations with a public mission active in the field of EU affairs, and excellent knowledge of the Belgian legal environment. Experience with OCTs or similar will be an advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior expert in Management of Not-for-Profit Organisations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in law, social sciences, human resources management or other relevant field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A high level of written  and spoken  English, and a working  knowledge of French and/or Flemish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Essential&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Management expert with at least 12 years experience as Director, Secretary General, Executive Secretary, Administrative Director or Financial Director of not-for-profit organisation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with different stakeholders, including governments, and finding compromises suitable for all.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant work experience in a Belgium-based organisation active in the field of EU affairs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of relevant Belgian Law applicable to NGOs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable experience in application for and management of funds from the European Union.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Desirable&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in organisation with public mission and/or composed of public members.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with territories similar to Overseas Countries and Territories.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to  &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programme Development Expert for Judicial Accountability and Professionalism</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/programme-development-expert-for-judicial-accountability-and-professionalism</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 09:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/programme-development-expert-for-judicial-accountability-and-professionalism</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Design of an EU Support Programme to BiH to fight Organised Crime and Corruption and to enhance the impact of the work of the Office of the Disciplinary Council&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;overall objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the assignment is to design a support programme to be financed under IPA 2015 as a grant for the rule of law in BiH, and specifically to improve the fight against organised crime and corruption, and improve professionalism and accountability of the judiciary and prosecutorial services throughout BIH. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Programme Development Expert for Judicial Accountability and Professionalism&lt;/strong&gt; (45 working days)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;S/he combines both technical competence and practical experience in the development of assistance programmes and projects in the field of judicial reform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University education of at least a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree academic level in the area of law/political science/ security studies/economics/development/human resources or any other appropriate discipline or equivalent working experience with 10 years of relevant professional experience in an area associated to this contract above the 12 years required below&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not less than 12 years general professional experience related to the lot, including not less than 10 years’ experience in Judicial Reform, Rule of Law, Public Administration Reform or Development Assistance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have direct experience in the planning and /or delivery of EU assistance in the areas of Rule of Law. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have previous experience in the design and/or implementation of EU assistance under Practical Guide regulations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct experience from EU actions in the Western Balkans region would be considered advantageous.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct experience from EU post-conflict stabilisation assistance would be advantageous.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of written and verbal English language, including familiarity with vocabulary and nomenclature relating to the area of judicial accountability, professionalism, efficiency and management. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the official languages of BiH considered an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programme Development Expert for Criminal Justice</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/programme-development-expert-for-criminal-justice</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/programme-development-expert-for-criminal-justice</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Design of an EU Support Programme to BiH to fight Organised Crime and Corruption and to enhance the impact of the work of the Office of the Disciplinary Council&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the assignment is to design a support programme to be financed under IPA 2015 as a grant for the rule of law in BiH, and specifically to improve the fight against organised crime and corruption, and improve professionalism and accountability of the judiciary and prosecutorial services throughout BIH. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Programme Development Expert for Criminal Justice&lt;/strong&gt; (45 working days)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;S/he combines both technical competence and practical experience in the development of assistance programmes and projects in the field of Criminal Justice Reform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;University education of at least a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in the area of law/political science/ security studies/economics/development or any other appropriate discipline or equivalent working experience with 10 years of relevant professional experience in an area associated to this contract above the 12 years required below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not less than 12 years of general professional experience related to the Lot, including not less than 10 years’ experience in Criminal Justice, Law Enforcement, Rule of Law or Development Assistance in the area of Criminal Justice Reform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have direct experience in the planning and/or delivery of EU assistance in the areas of Criminal Justice, Security Sector Reform and/or Rule of Law. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have previous experience in the design and/or implementation of EU assistance under Practical Guide regulations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct experience from EU actions in the Western Balkans region would be considered advantageous.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct experience from EU post-conflict stabilisation assistance would be advantageous.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of written and verbal English, including familiarity with the vocabulary and nomenclature relating to criminal justice. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the official languages of BiH considered an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:lina_forgeaux@dai.com&quot;&gt;Lina_Forgeaux@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Procurement Expert – Category II </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/procurement-expert-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 12:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/procurement-expert-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JASPERS - Support to preparation of Model Concession Agreement for InterModal Terminals&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project will be to develop a Draft Concession Agreement for the granting of rights to develop an Intermodal Terminal through a combination of grants and private finance, and to operate the facility on a commercial basis, with specified rights and procedures for future expansion of capacity or services provided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key expert 4: Procurement Expert – Category II&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Postgraduate degree in finance, law or related field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency  in  English  is  required.  Knowledge  of  Romanian  is  a  distinct advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At  least  ten  (10)  years’  international  experience  in  procurement  activities  for infrastructure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The candidate must be familiar with current Romanian and EU Laws relating to Procurement, and have international experience in procurement for PPP projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contracts Expert Category II </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/contracts-expert-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 12:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/contracts-expert-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JASPERS - Support to preparation of Model Concession Agreement for InterModal Terminals&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;overall objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the project will be to develop a Draft Concession Agreement for the granting of rights to develop an Intermodal Terminal through a combination of grants and private finance, and to operate the facility on a commercial basis, with specified rights and procedures for future expansion of capacity or services provided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key expert 3: Contracts Expert Category II&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications, skills and languages&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Postgraduate degree in finance, law or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency  in  English  is  required.  Knowledge  of  Romanian  is  a  distinct advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least ten (10) years’ experience in drafting commercial contracts, with exposure to PPP transportation project relevant experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with Romanian Laws relating to Financial Accounting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound knowledge in the field of project economic analysis, risk allocation, tariffs, and financial tools of infrastructure development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dail.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Expert – Category II </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/financial-expert-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 12:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/financial-expert-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JASPERS - Support to preparation of Model Concession Agreement for InterModal Terminals&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project will be to develop a Draft Concession Agreement for the granting of rights to develop an Intermodal Terminal through a combination of grants and private finance, and to operate the facility on a commercial basis, with specified rights and procedures for future expansion of capacity or services provided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key expert 2: Financial Expert – Category II&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications, skills and languages&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Postgraduate degree in engineering, finance, law, business administration or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency  in  English  is  required.  Knowledge  of  Romanian  is  a  distinct advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least ten (10) years of experience in a lead advisory capacity for the preparation of PPP infrastructure projects, including having acted in a lead advisory capacity to a sponsor or lender of at least one project financed on a limited recourse basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar  with  the  technical  aspects  of  infrastructure  development  and investment,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound  knowledge  in  the  field  of  project  financing,  banking  and  risk allocation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability  to  demonstrate  experience  in  the  preparation  and  structuring  of PPP/Concession contracts in the private sector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior PPP Expert/Team Leader</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-ppp-expert-team-leader</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-ppp-expert-team-leader</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JASPERS - Support to preparation of Model Concession Agreement for InterModal Terminals&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project will be to develop a Draft Concession Agreement for the granting of rights to develop an Intermodal Terminal through a combination of grants and private finance, and to operate the facility on a commercial basis, with specified rights and procedures for future expansion of capacity or services provided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key expert 1: PPP Expert/Team Leader – Category  II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications, skills and languages&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master degree  in  engineering,  finance,  law,  business  administration  or related field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least ten (10) years of PPP transportation project relevant experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the management of market sounding in a PPP project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with the technical aspects of transportation needs and development in the ‘New Member States’ of the EU.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound knowledge in the field of project economic analysis, risk allocation, tariffs, and financial tools of infrastructure development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity  with  the  formulation  of  policies  and  strategies  as  well  as community participation would be further advantageous.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert for SSE in Asia </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-for-sse-in-asia</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-for-sse-in-asia</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Feasibility study on identification of PI action on Social and Solidarity Economy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this assignment is to assist the European Commission preparation and formulation of an action on Social and Solidarity Economy for the following Countries: USA, Brazil, Mexico, India and South Korea. A preliminary study will be produced to assess the feasibility of a structured cooperation project on SSE. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Introducing SSE as a mean of doing business differently will help/allow the more socially and inclusive innovative stakeholders of the private sector and civil society to play a decisive role for growth and development, in the Single Market and worldwide. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objective of this action is to contribute fostering the supportive ecosystems for social enterprises, in order to create space for them to continue contributing in shaping and implementing markets and business conduct models aimed at sustainable, inclusive, fairer and equitable economic growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;SSE Expert for Asia (Category I) *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master Degree or equivalent diploma in an area relevant to SSE (Law, Business, Economy, etc.) or equivalent experience of 3 years which must be additional to the general professional experience duration fixed below; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorough knowledge of SSE policies and strategies, in particular the EU SBI; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent writing and communication skills in English. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in the sectors related to the Trade, Standards and Private sector. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of professional experience in the field of SSE, the analysis of SSE policies, including legal and institutional aspects; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years of professional experience related to SSE in Asia; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 relevant professional experiences as expert for identification or formulation for relevant EU funded programmes; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience related to SSE and carried out in India and/or in Republic of South Korea is an advantage. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert for SSE in the Americas </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-for-sse-in-the-americas</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-for-sse-in-the-americas</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Feasibility study on identification of PI action on Social and Solidarity Economy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this assignment is to assist the European Commission preparation and formulation of an action on Social and Solidarity Economy for the following Countries: USA, Brazil, Mexico, India and South Korea. A preliminary study will be produced to assess the feasibility of a structured cooperation project on SSE. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Introducing SSE as a mean of doing business differently will help/allow the more socially and inclusive innovative stakeholders of the private sector and civil society to play a decisive role for growth and development, in the Single Market and worldwide. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objective of this action is to contribute fostering the supportive ecosystems for social enterprises, in order to create space for them to continue contributing in shaping and implementing markets and business conduct models aimed at sustainable, inclusive, fairer and equitable economic growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert for SSE in the Americas (Category I&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master Degree or equivalent diploma in an area relevant to SSE (Law, Business, Economy, etc.) or equivalent experience of 3 years which must be additional to the general professional experience duration fixed below; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven knowledge of SSE policies and strategies, in particular the EU SBI; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven excellent writing and oral communication skills in English; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good communication skills in French, Spanish and/or Portuguese are an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in the sectors related to Trade, Standards and Private sector. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of professional experience in the field of SSE, the analysis of SSE policies, including legal and institutional aspects; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years of professional experience related to SSE in the Americas; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 relevant professional experiences as expert for identification or formulation for relevant EU funded programmes; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience related to SSE and carried out in USA, Mexico and/or in Brazil is an advantage. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Safety Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/food-safety-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 09:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/food-safety-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preparation of twinning fiche for Strengthening the Veterinary Services and Food Safety Capacities of the Lebanese Ministry of Agriculture&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt; of the project could be summarized as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enhance capacities of the Veterinary Services of the Lebanese Ministry of Agriculture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strengthen food safety and quality systems for products of animal origin. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following results are expected:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Veterinary regulations harmonized with EU regulation and enforced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Upgrading of Institutional and operational capacities of the Veterinary Services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capacity building of the MoA Veterinary Services and other concerned staff&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The final output foreseen is a Twinning Fiche which includes notably the description of the action,  the necessary time frame/work plan for proper implementation, the logical framework matrix, budget.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: December 2016-March 2017 (87 working days)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert n°2: Food Safety Expert, 15 w/d&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This expert should have a background in food safety as related to animal products. S/he should be knowledgeable with the EU Rules and Procedures. S/he should have the following profile:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Doctor of Veterinary Medicine (DVM) or  at least a Masters Degree in a relevant, directly related discipline&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound communications skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to work in close cooperation with all international and local stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least six (6) years of experience in designing and managing development projects in the field of food safety related to animal products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Three (3) years of EU experience in food safety legislation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Six (6) years of specific experience in designing/managing EU projects in the field of food safety&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in institutional strengthening projects in food safety related fields &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in designing and managing one or more of the following EU project modalities of implementation (grant, services) is compulsory&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in designing and managing EU-funded twinning projects is a strong asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language Skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent writing and editing skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English (spoken and written) is compulsory&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Arabic and French would be an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader, Expert in Veterinary Services</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-expert-in-veterinary-services</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 08:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-expert-in-veterinary-services</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preparation of twinning fiche for Strengthening the Veterinary Services and Food Safety Capacities of the Lebanese Ministry of Agriculture&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt; of the project could be summarized as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enhance capacities of the Veterinary Services of the Lebanese Ministry of Agriculture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strengthen food safety and quality systems for products of animal origin. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following results are expected:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Veterinary regulations harmonized with EU regulation and enforced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Upgrading of Institutional and operational capacities of the Veterinary Services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Capacity building of the MoA Veterinary Services and other concerned staff&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The final output foreseen is a Twinning Fiche which includes notably the description of the action,  the necessary time frame/work plan for proper implementation, the logical framework matrix, budget.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: December 2016-March 2017 (87 working days)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert n°1: Team Leader, Expert in Veterinary Services&lt;/strong&gt;, 31 w/d&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This expert should have a background in veterinary services and should be knowledgeable with the EU Rules and Procedures. S/he will bear the ultimate responsibility for supplying the final version of the Twinning Fiche and its budget estimate, as well as the final report. S/he should have the following profile:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Doctor of Veterinary Medicine (DVM) or at least a PhD in a relevant, directly related discipline&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound communications skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to work in close cooperation with all international and local stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least twelve (12) years of experience in designing and managing development projects in the field of veterinary services and food safety;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least five (5) years of EU experience in veterinary and food safety legislation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ten (10) years of specific experience in designing/managing EU projects in the field of veterinary services and food safety. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in institutional strengthening projects in veterinary and food safety related fields &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated knowledge of EU project cycle management, EU external aid procedures is compulsory&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in designing and managing one or more of the following EU project modalities of implementation (grant, services) is compulsory&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in designing and managing EU-funded twinning projects is a strong asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language Skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent writing and editing skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English (spoken and written) is compulsory&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Arabic and French would be an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EU Procedures, Monitoring &amp; Evaluation (M&amp;E) and Formulation Expert (Cat. I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/eu-procedures-monitoring-evaluation-me-and-formulation-expert-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 12:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/eu-procedures-monitoring-evaluation-me-and-formulation-expert-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation, Re-formulation and Monitoring of a Decentralisation Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the assignment is to compile and analyse the necessary information for the EU Delegation in Jordan to make an informed decision on the way forward regarding the project “Decentralisation and Local Development Support Programme (DLDSP)”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt; of the assignment include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To conduct an evaluation of the above-mentioned project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To reformulate the project, if deemed relevant and feasible, under a new approach.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To monitor the remaining period of implementation of the project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EU Procedures, Monitoring &amp;amp; Evaluation (M&amp;amp;E) and Formulation Expert (Cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Postgraduate degree in law, political sciences, public administration, economics, international relations; or undergraduate degree in these specialities with additional 2-year experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience working for European Union institutions, governmental institutions, development cooperation agencies, regional or local authorities, international organisations, development cooperation agencies, regional or local authorities, international organisations, consultancy firms, civil society and/or non-governmental organisations in the management, implementation, identification, formulation, monitoring or evaluation of development or technical cooperation projects/programmes funded by the European Union.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of experience and demonstrated knowledge of the EU’s external action and of EU procedures for the delivery of aid and cooperation to third countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in working on decentralisation, electoral assistance, in particular local and regional elections, civic education, voter information and public awareness in the framework of development/technical cooperation projects/programmes will be considered a strong asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in UN policies and procedures will be considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent of both spoken and written English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communications, drafting, reporting and project-budgeting skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;Aurelie_Durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader/Decentralisation Expert (Cat. I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-decentralisation-expert-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 11:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-decentralisation-expert-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation, Re-formulation and Monitoring of a Decentralisation Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the assignment is to compile and analyse the necessary information for the EU Delegation in Jordan to make an informed decision on the way forward regarding the project “Decentralisation and Local Development Support Programme (DLDSP)”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt; of the assignment include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To conduct an evaluation of the above-mentioned project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To reformulate the project, if deemed relevant and feasible, under a new approach.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To monitor the remaining period of implementation of the project.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader/Decentralisation Expert (Cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Postgraduate degree in law, political sciences, public administration, economics, international relations; or undergraduate degree in these specialities with additional 2-year experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience working for governmental institutions, regional or local authorities, international organisations, consultancy firms or civil society organisations in the field of decentralisation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience in the implementation, identification, formulation, monitoring or evaluation of development/technical cooperation projects/programmes funded by international donors in the field of decentralisation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working as a civil servant/consultant for a regional or local authority or a ministry/authority dealing with decentralisation of an EU member state will be considered a strong asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in working on electoral assistance, in particular local and regional elections, civic education, voter information and public awareness will be considered a strong asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in EU policies and procedures for internal or external actions will be considered a strong asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in UN policies and procedures will be considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of both spoken and written English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication, drafting, reporting and managerial skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;Aurelie_Durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
