<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 13:55:48 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader /Agro-Economist (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-agro-economist-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 13:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-agro-economist-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identification of a Programme on Job Creation in the Autonomous Region of Muslim Mindanao&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Job Creation Programme should contribute to the peace building process in the ARMM area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objective of the EU programme is to increase income earning opportunities for the local populations affected by decades of conflict and neglect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader /Agro-Economist (Category I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in Agro-economy or any other related discipline, or equivalent professional experience of at least 20 years in agro-economics and rural development fields;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in conducting agricultural feasibility studies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated Experience in conducting workshops (participatory project appraisal, objective oriented planning, logframe); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in marketing and post-harvest technologies og agricultural crops; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the EU procedures would be an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong expertise in local economic planning and a minimum of 7 years of work experience with the Private sector and SME development at local level; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong experience with communities involvement; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with the design of vocational training programme and micro-projects; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perfect command of English. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Management/Evaluation Experience in Low Carbon/Sustainable Urbanisation Projects (Cat. I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/management-evaluation-experience-in-low-carbon-sustainable-urbanisation-projects-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 11:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/management-evaluation-experience-in-low-carbon-sustainable-urbanisation-projects-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation of the Project “Europe-China Eco Cities link” (EC Link-Project)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of this project is to contribute to assess the extent to which the project has achieved its purpose to date, what the level of attainment of concrete outputs is and make recommendations on its potential for a successful completion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aim of the project to be evaluated is to assist Chinese cities in adopting energy and resource efficient ecological solutions by sharing experiences on sustainable urbanisation between Europe and China.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert with Management/Evaluation Experience in Low Carbon/Sustainable Urbanisation Projects (Cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Academic qualification in a sector relevant to the assignment (at least Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree or, in its absence, equivalent professional experience of 5 years) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication, drafting and reporting-writing skills; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in written and spoken English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;General professional experience *&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven professional experience of at least 12 years in the sector (s) related to the Lot. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven professional experience of at least 7 years specifically in the field of low-carbon/sustainable urbanization. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The expert must have field experience in project management and project evaluation. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert with M&amp;E, Technical/Financial Programme Management Experience in Relevant Sector (TL) (Cat. I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-with-me-technical-financial-programme-management-experience-in-relevant-sector-tl-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-with-me-technical-financial-programme-management-experience-in-relevant-sector-tl-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation of the Project “Europe-China Eco Cities link” (EC Link-Project)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of this project is to contribute to assess the extent to which the project has achieved its purpose to date, what the level of attainment of concrete outputs is and make recommendations on its potential for a successful completion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aim of the project to be evaluated is to assist Chinese cities in adopting energy and resource efficient ecological solutions by sharing experiences on sustainable urbanisation between Europe and China.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert with M&amp;amp;E, Technical/Financial Programme Management Experience in Relevant Sector (TL) (Cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Academic qualification in a sector relevant to the assignment (at least Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree or, in its absence, equivalent professional experience of 5 years)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication, drafting and reporting-writing skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in written and spoken English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven professional experience of at least 12 years at international level in monitoring and evaluation procedures and methodologies applied to the various modalities of implementation, instruments and channels of cooperation / aid delivery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of technical and/or financial programme management as well as of Project Cycle Management (PCM) and Logical Framework Approaches.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of cost-benefit and impact analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience with Governmental officials at senior level and within a team of international and national consultants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience with EU-funded programmes and with urbanisation-related programmes would be an asset. Working experience in or with China (short or long-term missions) would be also an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Public Finance Management and Reform Costing </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-public-finance-management-and-reform</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-public-finance-management-and-reform</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rule of Law in Ukraine &amp;lsquo;Policy and Budgetary Analysis in the area of Police/Law-Enforcement Reform&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;overall objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this contract is to contribute to the development and consolidation of the Rule of Law in Ukraine (RoL) in line with international standards and best European practices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt; of the Mission are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To analyse the GoU policies and the allocated budget for MoIA and law-enforcement reforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist the GoU with finalising strategic reform documents and implementation plans.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify needs and propose potential donor support in order to bring the Ukrainian MoIA and law-enforcement agencies up to the relevant international standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Public Finance Management and Reform Costing Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;University Degree or equivalent relevant to the assignment
General professional experience: At least 10 years of experience of work in or with the public service with a proven &amp;ldquo;track record&amp;rdquo; in &amp;ldquo;costing&amp;rdquo; of strategies/policies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least 7 years involvement in Public Financial Management (PFM) and/or institutional reforms or equivalent experience of work in a public entity with exposure to budgeting for the justice/police and/or security sector reforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in analysing, commenting and providing recommendations on Governmental budget related to security sector/justice/law enforcement (at least 5 years).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;excellent command of both written and spoken English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader/Policy Expert in field of Police/Law-Enforcement Reform</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-policy-expert-in-field-of-police-law-enforcement-reform</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 10:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-policy-expert-in-field-of-police-law-enforcement-reform</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rule of Law in Ukraine &amp;lsquo;Policy and Budgetary Analysis in the area of Police/Law-Enforcement Reform&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;overall objective&lt;/strong&gt; of this contract is to contribute to the development and consolidation of the Rule of Law in Ukraine (RoL) in line with international standards and best European practices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;specific objectives&lt;/strong&gt; of the Mission are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To analyse the GoU policies and the allocated budget for MoIA and law-enforcement reforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist the GoU with finalising strategic reform documents and implementation plans.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify needs and propose potential donor support in order to bring the Ukrainian MoIA and law-enforcement agencies up to the relevant international standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader/Policy Expert in field of Police/Law-Enforcement Reform&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;University Degree or equivalent relevant to the assignment
General professional experience: At least 10 years of experience of work in the Rule of Law area, preferably in or with law-enforcement bodies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least 7 years of professional working experience in formulation and implementation of strategic documents in the RoL/law-enforcement area acquired in other countries than Ukraine.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least 3 years of experience in design and implementation of donor funded projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience in writing quality assessment of projects/designing developmental strategies in the area and/or donor funded projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;excellent command of both written and spoken English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category I Information Management Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-information-management-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2015 13:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-information-management-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To contribute to the socio-economic development and poverty reduction in Zimbabwe through supporting agricultural related information collection, data quality control and analysis as well as outreach, capacity development, management and information dissemination. These should be attended in a way that can effectively and efficiently contribute to creating a sustainable, diversified, competitive and efficient agricultural sector that supports inclusive economic growth and revenue generation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category I Information Management Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in the fields of agriculture, Information management, international cooperation or equivalent. OR 12 years&amp;#39; professional experience in consultancy and management of programs/projects in the field of data systems analysis and management, policy and programming.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience in information management systems, policy formulation and programming;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong background in agriculture and food security issues. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Southern Africa region and Zimbabwe in the above sectors wold be an added value. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the European Union instruments for ACP countries and of EDF procedures is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category I Agricultural Statistics and Monitoring Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in the fields of agriculture, Statistics, Information management, Geographic information systems, Agricultural monitoring, Agro meteorology or equivalent. OR 12 years&amp;#39; professional experience in consultancy and management of programs/projects in the field of data systems analysis and management, policy and programming.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience in agricultural statistics, information management systems, Geographic Information systems and mapping;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong background in agriculture and food security issues. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Southern Africa region and Zimbabwe in the above sectors would be an added value.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWP 2 Projects Review</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Beyond WTO Program (B-WTO) was developed in response to a request from the Government of Vietnam (GoV) for donor support to help with managing economic integration and the transition to a market economy following WTO accession. The B-WTO goal is “to strengthen government’s capacity to manage the integration of Vietnam into the global economy and the transition of Vietnam to a socialist market economy”. The immediate objective is “implementation of priority policy actions from the GoV’s Action Plan to enhance Vietnam’s capacity to sustain pro-poor growth (GAP)”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The remit of this project was a review of the 2nd annual work plan’s implementation (AWP2) of Phase 2 of the B-WTO in May 2013. The objectives of the review were to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the project implementation performance and project results relative to the logical framework targets and evaluation criteria. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the results achieved at the Component and Program’s level according to the Monitoring and Evaluation (M&amp;amp;E) framework of the Program.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify lessons learned from implementation, make recommendations for the remaining duration of the program and the Independent Completion Report process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program 2013 Performance and Quality Mapping Exercise</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID’s PNG Program is looking to improve its performance and quality (P&amp;amp;Q) standards and systems. The purpose of this project was to map the PNG Program’s current P&amp;amp;Q capacity and systems, to address the risk of AusAID being unable to demonstrate results for its increased investments in PNG over the next four years. Over the last several years, the PNG Program has undertaken a number of M&amp;amp;E assessments and reviews which have identified key strengths and challenges within the program. This project was intended to pick up where these assessments left off. Through a desk review and consultations with sector teams, the Review Team were to distil key P&amp;amp;Q risks and issues for the PNG Program. The Review Team’s brief included the provision of recommendations on priority activities to support sector approaches to M&amp;amp;E, strengthen the Program’s ability to collect evidence, provide critical analysis and report on results.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID required a consultant to assist with the development and finalisation of its Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework. Development of a humanitarian monitoring and evaluation framework is a key commitment outlined in AusAID’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy (HAP) and its associated Implementation Plan. In line with the agency focus on results reporting, the HAP and HAP Implementation Plan commit AusAID to develop a monitoring and evaluation framework to support the initial performance assessment framework contained within the HAP and AusAID annual reporting under the Comprehensive Aid Policy Framework.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key objective of this assignment was to build the Humanitarian program’s capacity for monitoring and reporting results by:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In consultation with AusAID’s Humanitarian team, redraft and finalise the Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework, to ensure it provides a platform to:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track implementation of key commitments in Australia’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy; and,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish a set of measurable humanitarian performance indicators (in addition to the two CAPF indicators) to enable AusAID to track achievements, lessons learned and to report on the results achieved from AusAID’s humanitarian work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of Pacific Forum Compact Reporting</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The purpose of the assignment was to examine country views of aid effectiveness and regional organisations expressed through Forum Compact reporting, particularly peer review of Forum Island Countries’ national development plan processes. The services provided included the preparation of a think piece which outlines key aid effectiveness issues arising from country reporting under the Compact reporting and discusses options for addressing these issues.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study on Community-based Social Protection</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/study-on-community-based-social-protection</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/study-on-community-based-social-protection</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Poverty and Social Analysis is the process of using and generating evidence on poverty throughout the aid management cycle. Most poverty and social analysis focuses on economic and human capital, but there are two oft neglected elements: voice and influence, and social capital. Yet more and more development practitioners are recognizing the importance of social capital, particularly informal social capital, in preventing and addressing poverty and vulnerability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This project supported AusAID to explore:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the role of informal social capital in the Fijian context and whether it lends itself to fair redistribution of resources and, if so, the ways in which AusAID can engage with local communities to strengthen existing social capital structures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;how such structures can enable the disempowered and poor to claim their entitlements in the three domains discussed in the PSA framework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the potential challenges that can arise from such efforts. For instance, the poorest are often included on less favorable terms within social networks, and have access to fewer and lower-quality networks. Further, we need to better understand how poverty and disempowerment intersect with an absence of informal social capital, the repercussions this has, and the options available for tackling this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Provision of a Child Protection Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/provision-of-a-child-protection-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/provision-of-a-child-protection-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For this project HTSPE was contracted to provide a child protection specialist and handle all the associated management and administrative work. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The child protection specialist provided by HTSPE was required to work on an assignment designed to assist the Pacific Division (PACD) to improve its approach to child protection and managing risks to children. AusAID has a number of partners in the Pacific who work with children or come into contact with children through their activities. The AusAID-wide child protection stocktake, conducted in May 2013 found that there are a number of organisations funded by AusAID in the Pacific with a high or very high inherent child protection risk. Consistent with the stocktake report PACD proposes to escalate efforts to ensure partner organisations policies, procedures and practices are in accordance with AusAID’s Child Protection Policy 2013 and to make child protection a more explicit focus of PACD’s risk management system.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Environment and Biology Expert (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/opportunities/senior-environment-and-biology-expert-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 20:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/opportunities/senior-environment-and-biology-expert-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Expert 2 is expected to contribute the implementation of all of the related modules and the preparation of both training materials and Training Evaluation Report in the context of related chapter/s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in Biology, Ecology, Chemistry or other Natural Sciences related to assignment. In the absence of the degree required, at least 17 years of professional experience in the related areas is requested.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good command of both written and spoken English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General professional experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of experience in the sector(s) related to the Lot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience in technical and/or scientific fields required for the implementation of the Water Framework Directive and/or Habitat Directive and/or other related Directives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 river basin management plans experience in terms of setting of environmental objectives and/or setting, design and upgrade of biological monitoring programme and/or execution and assessment of biological monitoring.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in development of measures for water pollution reduction and/or improving ecological status, and/or river basin characterisation/analysis will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in projects related to Integrated Water Resources Management will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
