<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 13:45:40 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key Expert in EDF Financial and Procurement Procedures / PCM and Performance Assessment/Logical Framework (Category 2) </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-expert-in-edf-financial-and-procurement-procedures-pcm-and-performance-assessment-logical-framework-category-2</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-expert-in-edf-financial-and-procurement-procedures-pcm-and-performance-assessment-logical-framework-category-2</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to West Africa Gulf of Guinea Organisation in Maritime Security (SWAGOGOMS)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This assignment will provide a coherent proposal to  ECOWAS and EU for the fight against illicit maritime activities in the Gulf of Guinea. It will give sufficient background information and justifications to enable the ECOWAS and EU to make an informed decision on specific objectives and implementation modalities of  the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Expert in EDF Financial and Procurement Procedures / PCM and Performance Assessment/Logical Framework (Category 2)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a University Degree in Project Management, Business, Finance, Engineering, Development Cooperation,or relevant, directly related discipline, or equivalent; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with development of coherent concepts for EDF projects (including design of objectives, OVIs, results, contractual procedures, activities, planning, budgets Minimum of 8 years of professional experience as programme manager/expert &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 4 years&amp;#39; experience with EDF programming procedures will be an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in contributing to the design, identification, formulation of EU development Projects (at least 5 identifications of formulations) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred skills&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project management EU Funded projects in developing countries (at least 3 years); would be an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of maritime security issues an asset &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent in English both in spoken and written language; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of spoken and written French; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Portuguese is considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key Expert in Information Systems and Data-gathering, Management and Exchange (Category 2)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-expert-in-information-systems-and-data-gathering-management-and-exchange-category-2</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-expert-in-information-systems-and-data-gathering-management-and-exchange-category-2</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to West Africa Gulf of Guinea Organisation in Maritime Security (SWAGOGOMS)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This assignment will provide a coherent proposal to  ECOWAS and EU for the fight against illicit maritime activities in the Gulf of Guinea. It will give sufficient background information and justifications to enable the ECOWAS and EU to make an informed decision on specific objectives and implementation modalities of  the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Expert in Information Systems and Data-gathering, Management and Exchange (Category 2)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Minimum required skills: *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Candidate should have&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a University Degree in Information technology, engineering, or relevant, directly related discipline, or equivalent; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 5 years of professional experience as IT/network programme manager/expert in inter-systems information exchange. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project management in developing countries; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred skills:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with EDF programming procedures will be an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience (min 2 years of the the maritime) sector an asset &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in contributing to the design, the identification, the formulation of EU development Projects an asset &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work experience in GoG countries an asset &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent in English both in spoken and written language; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of spoken and written French; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Portuguese is considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key Expert in Rule of Law and Maritime Law Enforcement (Traffics, other Illicit Activities) (category 1)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-expert-in-rule-of-law-and-maritime-law-enforcement-traffics-other-illicit-activities-category-1</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 13:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/key-expert-in-rule-of-law-and-maritime-law-enforcement-traffics-other-illicit-activities-category-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to West Africa Gulf of Guinea Organisation in Maritime Security (SWAGOGOMS)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This assignment will provide a coherent proposal to  ECOWAS and EU for the fight against illicit maritime activities in the Gulf of Guinea. It will give sufficient background information and justifications to enable the ECOWAS and EU to make an informed decision on specific objectives and implementation modalities of  the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Expert in Rule of Law and Maritime Law Enforcement (Traffics, other Illicit Activities) (category 1)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master Degree (University Level) in Law, Political Science, Development Cooperation, Humanitarian Aid or relevant, directly related discipline, or equivalent; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in international standards and methods regarding maritime law reforms; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 8 years of professional experience as programme manager/expert in maritime legislation (ZEE and territorial waters), law enforcement and operational implementation of activities at international level encompassing trafficking (humans, arms, drugs etc) and IUU fishing &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in contributing to the design, the identification, the formulation of EU development Projects (at least 2 identifications of formulations) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Experience in communication, negotiation and dialogue at high level; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred skills&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of West Africa Peace and security dynamics &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 3 years&amp;#39; experience with EDF programming procedures will be an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience of the workings of the maritime law sector in GoG an asset &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in design of capacity building projects on maritime law reform and law enforcement will be an asset &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent in English both in spoken and written language;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Knowledge of spoken and written French required; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Portuguese is considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader and Key Expert in Maritime Security and Identification/Formulation</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-and-key-expert-in-maritime-security-and-identification-formulation</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-and-key-expert-in-maritime-security-and-identification-formulation</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to West Africa Gulf of Guinea Organisation in Maritime Security (SWAGOGOMS)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This assignment will provide a coherent proposal to ECOWAS and EU for the fight against illicit maritime activities in the Gulf of Guinea. It will give sufficient background information and justifications to enable the ECOWAS and EU to make an informed decision on specific objectives and implementation modalities of  the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader and Key Expert in Maritime Security and Identification/Formulation responsible of the mission and final AD&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master Degree (Academic level) in Defence or Security Affairs, Project and Programme Management, , Public Administration, Political Science, Law or relevant, directly related discipline, or equivalent; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 8 years professional experience in maritime security sector &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in monitoring the identification/formulation of large development projects in complex political environments (at least3 significant identifications/formulations) with particular reference to EU-funded projects/programmes, and familiarity with the methodological approach set by the European Commission; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of EDF programming procedures &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound and proven experience in identification and formulation methods and techniques, preferably in developing countries, including at the programme and policy level plus relevant field experience. Ability to assess and communicate best practices; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in problem analysis, stakeholders&amp;#39; analysis and construction of logical framework; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full working knowledge of English and French, as well as excellent report writing and communication skills in both languages; additional knowledge of Portuguese will be an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative ability to identify practical solutions to overcome challenges to time-critical projects; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Experience in communication, negotiation and dialogue at high level; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred skills&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 12 years of professional experience &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 5 years&amp;#39; experience with EDF programming procedures will be an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in EC programmes design and identification in developing countries &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; In-depth knowledge of maritime security related issues and systems &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of West Africa peace and security architecture and dynamics. Work experience at least in two Gulf of Guinea Countries &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in contributing to ECOWAS programmes &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific expertise in maritime security systems and infrastructure issues (technical assistance, capacity development, training, awareness campaigns) especially in countries with common law legal system 
• Experience in Nigeria&amp;rsquo;s governance issues an asset &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category II Information Management and Agriculture/FNS Policy Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-information-management-and-agriculture-fns-policy-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2015 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-information-management-and-agriculture-fns-policy-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To contribute to the socio-economic development and poverty reduction in Zimbabwe through supporting agricultural related information collection, data quality control and analysis as well as outreach, capacity development , management and information dissemination. These should be attended in a way that can effectively and efficiently contribute to creating a sustainable, diversified, competitive and efficient agricultural sector that supports inclusive economic growth and revenue generation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category I Agricultural Statistics and Monitoring Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in the fields of agriculture, Statistics, Information management, Geographic information systems, Agricultural monitoring, Agro meteorology or equivalent. OR 12 years&amp;#39; professional experience in consultancy and management of programs/projects in the field of data systems analysis and management, policy and programming.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience in agricultural statistics, information management systems, Geographic Information systems and mapping;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong background in agriculture and food security issues. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Southern Africa region and Zimbabwe in the above sectors would be an added value.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:%20chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category I Information Management Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-information-management-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2015 13:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-information-management-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To contribute to the socio-economic development and poverty reduction in Zimbabwe through supporting agricultural related information collection, data quality control and analysis as well as outreach, capacity development, management and information dissemination. These should be attended in a way that can effectively and efficiently contribute to creating a sustainable, diversified, competitive and efficient agricultural sector that supports inclusive economic growth and revenue generation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category I Information Management Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in the fields of agriculture, Information management, international cooperation or equivalent. OR 12 years&amp;#39; professional experience in consultancy and management of programs/projects in the field of data systems analysis and management, policy and programming.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience in information management systems, policy formulation and programming;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong background in agriculture and food security issues. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Southern Africa region and Zimbabwe in the above sectors wold be an added value. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the European Union instruments for ACP countries and of EDF procedures is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category I Agricultural Statistics and Monitoring Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in the fields of agriculture, Statistics, Information management, Geographic information systems, Agricultural monitoring, Agro meteorology or equivalent. OR 12 years&amp;#39; professional experience in consultancy and management of programs/projects in the field of data systems analysis and management, policy and programming.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience in agricultural statistics, information management systems, Geographic Information systems and mapping;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong background in agriculture and food security issues. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Southern Africa region and Zimbabwe in the above sectors would be an added value.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experts d’analyse Stratégique et Evaluation de Politiques publiques (secteur agricole)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-danalyse-strategique-et-evaluation-de-politiques-publiques-secteur-agricole</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 12:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-danalyse-strategique-et-evaluation-de-politiques-publiques-secteur-agricole</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Analyse d&amp;#39;économie politique (PEA) des filières de l&amp;#39;arachide et du riz au Sénégal&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;L’objectif général&lt;/strong&gt; est améliorer la compréhension du pays afin d&amp;#39;appuyer le dialogue sectoriel et les interventions actuelles
et futures de l&amp;#39;UE et des partenaires techniques et financiers (PTF) dans les filières de l&amp;#39;arachide et du
riz.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les &lt;strong&gt;objectifs particuliers&lt;/strong&gt; sont:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apporter une compréhension actualisée des enjeux politico-économiques des filières de l&amp;#39;arachide et du riz et des opportunités de changement au niveau national et local;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alimenter le dialogue de l&amp;#39;UE et des PTFs avec les acteurs sénégalais autour des politiques publiques afin d&amp;#39;accroitre l&amp;#39;efficacité de l&amp;#39;aide extérieure;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifier des actions futures de coopération au développement, y compris dans le cadre de la programmation conjointe européenne qui est en cours de préparation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifier les risques pouvant affecter les actions de la coopération au développement et servir de base à un cadre de gestion des risques;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Servir d&amp;#39;outil de référence pour le dialogue des PTF.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deux Experts d’analyse Stratégique et Evaluation de Politiques Publiques (Secteur Agricole)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme en agronomie, économie, études de développement, sciences politiques, sciences juridiques ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une parfaite maîtrise de la langue française ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;12 ans d&amp;#39;expérience professionnelle minimale;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;10 ans d’analyse stratégique et évaluation de politiques publiques (secteur agricole) ;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Une expérience dans la conduite de PEA en Afrique ;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Connaissance approfondie du contexte politique, économique et social sénégalais et idéalement du secteur de l&amp;#39;agriculture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert Non Principal en phytopathologie et /ou amélioration variétale</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-non-principal-en-phytopathologie-et-ou-amelioration-varietale</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 22:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-non-principal-en-phytopathologie-et-ou-amelioration-varietale</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appuis institutionnels pour le suivi de secteur sucrier de Madagascar&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général du projet dont ce marché fait partie est de contribuer au renforcement des capacités de suivi du secteur sucrier à Madagascar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Le lieu d’intervention&lt;/strong&gt; est à Antananarivo, avec des déplacements à prévoir dans les régions: Ambilobe, Namakia ou autres zones sucrières.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert Non Principal en phytopathologie et /ou amélioration variétale
**
**Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Docteur en phytopathologie ou équivalent ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parfaite maitrise des logiciels d’informatique courants (Microsoft office, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale *&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 3 ans d’expérience dans le domaine de phytopathologie et/ ou amélioration variétale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en transfert de compétence ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en canne à sucre.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise du français; une bonne connaissance du malgache serait un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert non-Principal en juridique du foncier</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-non-principal-en-juridique-du-foncier</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 21:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-non-principal-en-juridique-du-foncier</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appuis institutionnels pour le suivi de secteur sucrier de Madagascar&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général du projet dont ce marché fait partie est de contribuer au renforcement des capacités de suivi du secteur sucrier à Madagascar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Le lieu d’intervention&lt;/strong&gt; est à Antananarivo, avec des déplacements à prévoir dans les régions: Ambilobe, Namakia ou autres zones sucrières.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert non-Principal en juridique du foncier&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formation de niveau Bac+5 en droit foncier ;
Parfaite maitrise du logiciels d’informatique courant (Microsoft office, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 3 ans d’expérience dans le domaine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en transfert de compétence ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en domaine d’acquisition de propriété foncière.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise du français ; une bonne connaissance du malgache serait un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert non-Principal de Développement social, anthropologie et genre</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-non-principal-de-developpement-social-anthropologie-et-genre</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 21:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-non-principal-de-developpement-social-anthropologie-et-genre</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appuis institutionnels pour le suivi de secteur sucrier de Madagascar&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général du projet dont ce marché fait partie est de contribuer au renforcement des capacités de suivi du secteur sucrier à Madagascar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Le lieu d’intervention&lt;/strong&gt; est à Antananarivo, avec des déplacements à prévoir dans les régions: Ambilobe, Namakia ou autres zones sucrières.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert non-Principal de Développement social, anthropologie et genre&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formation de niveau Bac+5 en sciences sociales ou en sociologie/anthropologie ou équivalent ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parfaite maitrise des logiciels d’informatique courants (Microsoft office, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 3 ans d’expérience dans le domaine social, anthropologie et genre;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gestion des organisations paysannes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Expérience en transfert de compétences ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en accompagnement de groupements de producteurs, en appuis conseils aux structures paysannes ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise du français ; une bonne connaissance du malgache serait un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert non-Principal en Systèmes d&#39;information géographiques</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-non-principal-en-systemes-dinformation-geographiques</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 21:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-non-principal-en-systemes-dinformation-geographiques</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appuis institutionnels pour le suivi de secteur sucrier de Madagascar&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général du projet dont ce marché fait partie est de contribuer au renforcement des capacités de suivi du secteur sucrier à Madagascar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Le lieu d’intervention&lt;/strong&gt; est à Antananarivo, avec des déplacements à prévoir dans les régions: Ambilobe, Namakia ou autres zones sucrières.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert non-Principal en Systèmes d&amp;#39;information géographiques
**
**Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formation de niveau Bac+5 en géomètre topographe ou équivalent ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parfaite maitrise des logiciels d’informatique (SIG, CAO, DAO&amp;hellip;) ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parfaite maîtrise de matériel de forte technicité (GPS…).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale :&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 3 ans d’expérience dans le domaine des informations géographiques;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expériences professionnelles à Madagascar et/ ou dans les régions d’intervention.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en relevé sur terrain ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en conception des plans et des cartes comprenant des projets d’aménagement (route, ouvrages d’art…). ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en intervention dans la réalisation du cadastre qui délimite les domaines fonciers ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise du français ; une bonne connaissance du malgache serait un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert Ingénieur Informaticien </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-ingenieur-informaticien</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 21:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-ingenieur-informaticien</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Appuis institutionnels pour le suivi de secteur sucrier de Madagascar
*&lt;/em&gt;
L&amp;#39;objectif général du projet dont ce marché fait partie est de contribuer au renforcement des capacités de suivi du secteur sucrier à Madagascar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Le lieu d’intervention&lt;/strong&gt; est à Antananarivo, avec des déplacements à prévoir dans les régions: Ambilobe, Namakia ou autres zones sucrières.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert Ingénieur Informaticien – Catégorie II (66 jours ouvrables)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formation de niveau Bac + 5 en informatique et gestion des bases de données ou équivalent ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parfaite maitrise des logiciels d’informatique courants (Microsoft office, linux, …).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale *&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 6 ans d’expériences dans le domaine des infrastructures réseaux, web et les framework (CodeIgniter, Simfony 2, JQuery…)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle à Madagascar et/ ou dans des pays en développement,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience en traitement de données statistiques et des logiciels correspondant (SPSS, XLSTAT, STATA…) ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience en traitement de données géographiques et foncières.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise du français ; une bonne connaissance du malgache serait un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert Spécialiste en Communication</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-specialiste-en-communication</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 20:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-specialiste-en-communication</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Appuis institutionnels pour le suivi de secteur sucrier de Madagascar
*&lt;/em&gt;
L&amp;#39;objectif général du projet dont ce marché fait partie est de contribuer au renforcement des capacités de suivi du secteur sucrier à Madagascar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Le lieu d’intervention&lt;/strong&gt; est à Antananarivo, avec des déplacements à prévoir dans les régions: Ambilobe, Namakia ou autres zones sucrières.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert Spécialiste en communication- catégorie II (68 jours ouvrables)&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formation de niveau Baccalauréat + 5 en communication ou équivalent ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parfaite maitrise des logiciels d’informatique courants (Microsoft office, Suite Adobe, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle à Madagascar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique *&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en design et art graphique surtout dans le cadre de communication  (conception de spot TV – Design brochure - web…) ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience sur le transfert de savoir sur l’exploitation des Nouvelles Technologiques de Communication existante à Madagascar ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en organisation des manifestations économiques.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise du français ; une bonne connaissance du malgache serait un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert Socio-économiste</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-socio-economiste</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 20:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-socio-economiste</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appuis institutionnels pour le suivi de secteur sucrier de Madagascar&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général du projet dont ce marché fait partie est de contribuer au renforcement des capacités de suivi du secteur sucrier à Madagascar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Le lieu d’intervention&lt;/strong&gt; est à Antananarivo, avec des déplacements à prévoir dans les régions: Ambilobe, Namakia ou autres zones sucrières.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert Socio-économiste- Catégorie II (132 jours ouvrables)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formation de niveau Baccalauréat + 5 en socio-économie ou M2 ou équivalent;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale :&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 6 ans d’expérience dans les études filières, ou dans le domaine du développement rural, ou agronomie, ou agroalimentaire;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expériences professionnelles à Madagascar et/ ou dans les régions d’intervention ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expériences générales dans le domaine de suivi et évaluation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique :&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans la réalisation d’études filière ou dans la gestion des projets de développement agricole ou développement rural ou de projet de transformation agricole ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expériences liées à des projets sucriers ou des projets de transformation alimentaire seraient un atout ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expériences dans le domaine de renforcement de capacités organisationnelles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parfaite maitrise des logiciels d’informatique courants (Microsoft office, Suite Adobe, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise du français, une bonne connaissance de la langue Malgache serait un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert in Participatory Planning and Elections </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-participatory-planning-and-elections</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 12:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-participatory-planning-and-elections</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final evaluation of the &amp;lsquo;Support to Nigerian Electoral Cycle 2012-2015&amp;rsquo; and EU additional support to Nigeria Electoral Cycle 2011-2015&amp;#39; projects&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation will provide the EU and other partners with an assessment of the project’s performance in terms of relevance, efficiency, effectiveness, sustainability and impact (actual or expected) of the support provided to INEC and key stakeholders and its impact on elections as well as policy issues arising from the implementation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in Participatory Planning and Elections (cat. II, 20w/d)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in Politics, Law, Development Studies or related social science fields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 4 missions monitoring and evaluating election related projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;S/He must have at least 6 years of professional experience at international level some of which should have been acquired in a developing country.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of international electoral standards and principles; good knowledge of electoral law preferred; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in participatory planning and management of large development projects in complex political environments, including specific working experience in dealing with elections, electoral management bodies and civil society groups;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in donors-government coordination and strategic understanding to ensure overall coordination of the project;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative ability to identify practical solutions to overcome challenges to time-critical projects;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly developed interpersonal skills to constructively interact with stakeholders at all levels;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge / Experience in Nigeria and/or West Africa or similar countries is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader - Senior Democratic Governance Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-democratic-governance-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-democratic-governance-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final evaluation of the &amp;lsquo;Support to Nigerian Electoral Cycle 2012-2015&amp;rsquo; and EU additional support to Nigeria Electoral Cycle 2011-2015&amp;#39; Projects&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation will provide the EU and other partners with an assessment of the project’s performance in terms of relevance, efficiency, effectiveness, sustainability and impact (actual or expected) of the support provided to INEC and key stakeholders and its impact on elections as well as policy issues arising from the implementation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader - Senior Democratic Governance Expert&lt;/strong&gt;
(Cat. I, 23w/d)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Masters’ degree in Political Science, Law, Development Studies or related social science fields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team leader on at least 6 missions monitoring and evaluating election related projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;S/He must have at least 12 years of professional experience at international level (worked in at least two countries) some of which should have been acquired in a developing country.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge in key areas related to democratic governance including political parties, the media, civil society, and advocacy/education.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of capacity development in electoral support activities, such as civic/voter education, voter registration, and mobilization for inclusive participation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in the planning and management of the voter registration or IT component of an electronic voter registration exercise or equivalent operation in complex political environments is an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with international standards and methods regarding elections planning and administration;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven field research and report writing skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perfect English language skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge / Experience in Nigeria and/or West Africa or similar countries is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronic_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Promotion of Human Rghts and Related Governance Fields </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-promotion-of-human-rghts-and-related-governance-fields</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 12:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-promotion-of-human-rghts-and-related-governance-fields</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identification and formulation mission for the Programme &amp;lsquo;Support to the implementation of Human Rights International Conventions&amp;rsquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective is to assist the EU Delegation in the preparation of detailed design of a programme 2017-2020 dedicated to supporting implementation of international human rights conventions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Promotion of Human Rghts and Related Governance Fields&lt;/strong&gt; (specifically in Pakistan)  (Cat. I, 62 w/d approx.):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The expert must hold a minimum Master Degree in one or more of the following fields: social or political sciences, law, public administration or any other relevant discipline. If an expert does not hold a master degree, then 3 years in addition to the general professional experience is required;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• A minimum of 12 years of professional experience in the sector directly related to the lot and specifically in promotion of human rights and related governance fields&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific experience and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development work in relation to human rights in South Asia and in Pakistan;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the situation of the Human Rights in Pakistan;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing human rights programmes or projects related to capacity building and the promotion and protection of human rights, including projects/programmes focused on women, children and minorities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development of the EU programming documents such as identification fiches, action documents and all related annexes, policy analysis will be an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cooperation with donors, international organisations, public administration and civil society in the sector;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Human rights and gender sensitive approach to development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multi-stakeholder consultations;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design of a comprehensive institutional development programme;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong inter-personal and presentation skills, awareness of cultural sensitivities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong report writing skills, using a clear and concise language, structuring written presentations;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent knowledge of English and Urdu is compulsory.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Promotion of Human Rghts and Related Governance Fields (TL) </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-promotion-of-human-rghts-and-related-governance-fields-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 12:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-promotion-of-human-rghts-and-related-governance-fields-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identification and formulation mission for the Programme &amp;lsquo;Support to the implementation of Human Rights International Conventions&amp;rsquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective is to assist the EU Delegation in the preparation of detailed design of a programme 2017-2020 dedicated to supporting implementation of international human rights conventions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Promotion of Human Rghts and Related Governance Fields (TL)&lt;/strong&gt; (cat. I, 62 w/d approx.):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The expert must hold a minimum Master Degree in one or more of the following fields: social or political sciences, law, public administration or any other relevant discipline. If an expert does not hold a master degree, then 3 years in addition to the general professional experience is required;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General experience:&lt;/strong&gt;
A minimum of 12 years of professional experience in the sector directly related to the lot and specifically in promotion of human rights and related governance fields;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific experience and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development work in relation to human rights;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing human rights programmes or projects related to capacity building and the promotion and protection of human rights, including projects/programmes focused on women, children and minorities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Development of the EU programming documents such as identification fiches, action documents and all related annexes, policy analysis;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cooperation with donors, international organisations, public administration and civil society in the sector;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Human rights and gender sensitive approach to development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multi-stakeholder consultations;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design of a comprehensive institutional development programme;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong inter-personal and presentation skills, awareness of cultural sensitivities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong report writing skills, using a clear and concise language, structuring written presentations;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team leadership or project manager experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent knowledge of English is compulsory.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Engineer  (Category II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/engineer-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 10:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/engineer-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Evaluation of Community Development Programme Phase 4 (CDP-4)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of CDP-4 is to reduce poverty in Kenya through empowering communities to initiate and implement community-based socio-economic infrastructure and environmental projects subsequently leading to better governance at the local, district, county and national levels. The CDP-4 purpose is to support and mainstream community-led approaches to poverty reduction and sustainable management of natural resources by communities in rural and peri-urban areas across Kenya.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Engineer  (Category II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of first degree in Civil/Agricultural/Structural/ Environmental Engineering. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project design and development &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recognized and/or registered by relevant a professional bodies e.g. Engineers Registration Board (ERB), or the Institution of Engineers or an equivalent body.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project proposal design, budgeting, and Logical  Framework development &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 5 years&amp;#39; experience in engineering design and implementation of community-based Projects; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in environmental impact assessments and audit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Expert (Category II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/social-expert-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 10:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/social-expert-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Evaluation of Community Development Programme Phase 4 (CDP-4)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of CDP-4 is to reduce poverty in Kenya through empowering communities to initiate and implement community-based socio-economic infrastructure and environmental projects subsequently leading to better governance at the local, district, county and national levels. The CDP-4 purpose is to support and mainstream community-led approaches to poverty reduction and sustainable management of natural resources by communities in rural and peri-urban areas across Kenya.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Social Expert (Category II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of first degree in Agriculture, Sociology or any other relevant social science &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project cycle management, participatory planning, capacity building and monitoring and evaluation; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in inclusion of cross cutting issues such as gender, good governance, environmental conservation, HIV/AIDS, vulnerable groups in project design and implementation; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with community mobilization, participation and involvement. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project design, budgeting, and Logical Framework development &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 5 years of experience in implementation of community-based programmes in Kenya or East African countries. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
