<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 08:17:39 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert No. 2 (Category I expert) - Expert in the field of PPP and delivery of trainings</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-no-2-category-i-expert-expert-in-the-field-of-ppp-and-delivery-of-trainings</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 08:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-no-2-category-i-expert-expert-in-the-field-of-ppp-and-delivery-of-trainings</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the contract is to improve the general conditions in the Beneficiary country for more successful implementation of the Law on Public-Private Partnership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The specific objective of this assignment is Harmonization of the Law on Public-Private Partnership with the latest available EU Directive;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strengthen the administrative capacities of the Ministry of Economy as the final beneficiary of the project, as well as the other National and Local Authorities and the private sector for implementation of the legal framework for Public-Private Partnership.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Expert No. 2 will be in charge of preparing the materials, organizing and delivering trainings in the field of PPP, mainly for the tasks envisaged in Activity 1.2 and Activity 2, as he/she will also assist the Expert No.1 (Team Leader) in preparation of the Guide for implementation of the PPP. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least Master Degree  Academic level in Business Administration, law, economic or engineering, or in its absence, 3 years of general professional experience above the minimum general professional experience requested below. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Minimum 12 years of general professional experience in the area of PPP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience in at least 3 years of delivering trainings in the fields of PPP;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience in at least one (1) International/EU funded project in the area of PPP.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert No. 1 (Category I expert /Team Leader) Legal approximation Expert in the field of PPP</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-no-1-category-i-expert-team-leader-legal-approximation-expert-in-the-field-of-ppp</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 08:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-no-1-category-i-expert-team-leader-legal-approximation-expert-in-the-field-of-ppp</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the contract is to improve the general conditions in the Beneficiary country for more successful implementation of the Law on Public-Private Partnership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The specific objective of this assignment is Harmonization of the Law on Public-Private Partnership with the latest available EU Directive;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strengthen the administrative capacities of the Ministry of Economy as the final beneficiary of the project, as well as the other National and Local Authorities and the private sector for implementation of the legal framework for Public-Private Partnership.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Legal approximation expert in the field of public private partnership will act as a Team leader, thus he/she will be responsible for day to day exercises, making sure that the objectives and outputs of the Project are being met and Project activities delivered. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Team Leader also has to play a key role with respect to outreach, information sharing, public visibility, and liaising with other technical assistance initiatives. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an expert in the field of public - private partnership he/she has to be working on the activities 1 – Assessment and harmonization of the legislation on concessions and public private partnership compatible with EU legislation and activity - Sub-activity 1.1: Analysis of the current situation regarding PPP and Activity - 2- Preparation of Guide for implementation of the public private partnership compatible with EU legislation and to coordinate the other activity regarding the development of the Institutional capacity of the Legal Department - Unit for normative and legal affairs in area of Public-Private partnership and Concession and ensure that the functions and the legal provisions are commensurate with the requirements detailed in the public - private partnership system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least Master Degree  Academic level in law, or in its absence, 3 years of general professional experience above the minimum general professional experience requested below. 
General professional experience &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Minimum 12 years of experience in commercial Law;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 5 years of experience in the area of PPP legislation; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience in at least two (2) EU funded projects in the area of PPP;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience in at least one (1) project aimed on drafting or preparation of legislative documents (Law/Bylaw/Guidelines/Manuals etc.) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language and computer literacy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Fluent in oral and written English;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Computer literacy&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Profil de l&#39;expert 2,  – catégorie 1 (12 ans d&#39;expérience au moins)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/profil-de-lexpert-2-categorie-1-12-ans-dexperience-au-moins</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 08:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/profil-de-lexpert-2-categorie-1-12-ans-dexperience-au-moins</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif global est de contribuer à la conservation de la biodiversité et des services écosystémiques pour un développement durable en Afrique de l’Ouest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif spécifique est de renforcer durablement la conservation des écosystèmes du complexe WAP (W, Pendjari, Arly) dans une perspective régionale et avec optimisation des bénéfices pour la population riveraine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deux experts de catégorie 1 pour 47 jours prestés chacun dont 10 jours prestés chacun dans leur pays. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;expert 2 aura un diplôme d&amp;#39;enseignement supérieur dans un des domaines suivants : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sciences agronomiques, forestières, biologiques ou socio-économiques (ou équivalent), 
L&amp;#39;expert devra posséder au moins 12 ans  d&amp;#39;expérience en coopération au développement. 
Il devra posséder une excellente connaissance et pratique en gestion du cycle de projet / approche cadre logique. 
Il devra posséder une bonne connaissance des cadres institutionnels des pays africains en matière de gestion de l&amp;#39;environnement. 
L&amp;#39;expert devra maîtriser le français à l&amp;#39;écrit et à l&amp;#39;oral. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;expert devra avoir les expériences spécifiques minimales suivantes : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir travaillé au moins cinq ans sur un ou des projets liés à la conservation de la nature / biodiversité ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir réalisé au moins 2 études de formulation ou identification dans le domaine de la protection de l&amp;#39;environnement. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir réalisé au moins 3 évaluations externes (ex-ante, à mi-parcours ou finale)

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir travaillé au moins deux ans le contexte Ouest Africain ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Une expérience spécifique dans les domaines suivants est un plus : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;au moins trois ans sur un ou des projets de développement de capacités institutionnelles, en lien avec le développement local ou le développement rural (environnement, agriculture, élevage, agroforesterie), et &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir travaillé avec les organismes régionaux du type de l&amp;#39;UEMOA ou de la CEDEAO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail:%20CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Profil de l&#39;expert 1, Chef de mission  – catégorie 1 (12 ans d&#39;expérience au moins)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/profil-de-lexpert-1-chef-de-mission-categorie-1-12-ans-dexperience-au-moins</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 08:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/profil-de-lexpert-1-chef-de-mission-categorie-1-12-ans-dexperience-au-moins</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif global est de contribuer à la conservation de la biodiversité et des services écosystémiques pour un développement durable en Afrique de l’Ouest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif spécifique est de renforcer durablement la conservation des écosystèmes du complexe WAP (W, Pendjari, Arly) dans une perspective régionale et avec optimisation des bénéfices pour la population riveraine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deux experts de catégorie 1 pour 47 jours prestés chacun dont 10 jours prestés chacun dans leur pays. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Profil de l&amp;#39;expert 1, Chef de mission  – catégorie 1 (12 ans d&amp;#39;expérience au moins)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;expert doit posséder au moins un diplôme d&amp;#39;enseignement supérieur dans un des domaines suivants : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agronomie, foresterie, environnement / ressources naturelles (ou équivalent)
L&amp;#39;expert devra posséder au moins 12 ans d&amp;#39;expérience dans l&amp;#39;appui aux politiques, programmes ou de projets de développement. 
Il devra posséder une excellente connaissance et pratique en gestion du cycle de projet / approche cadre logique. 
Il devra posséder une très bonne connaissance théorique et pratique des procédures du FED. 
L&amp;#39;expert devra maîtriser le français à l&amp;#39;écrit et à l&amp;#39;oral, &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;expert devra avoir les expériences spécifiques minimales suivantes : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir travaillé au moins cinq ans sur un ou des projets liés à la conservation de la nature / biodiversité;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir réalisé au moins 2 études de formulation ou identification dans le domaine de la protection de l&amp;#39;environnement. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir réalisé au moins 5 évaluations externes (ex-ante, à mi-parcours ou finale), dont au moins 3 financées par la Commission Européenne (FED ou BUDGET), dont au moins une évaluation sur un projet régional. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir travaillé au moins deux ans dans le contexte Ouest Africain ou d&amp;#39;une autre région africaine;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Une expérience spécifique dans les domaines suivants est un plus : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;au moins trois ans sur un ou des projets de développement, en lien avec le développement local ou le développement rural (environnement, agriculture, élevage, agroforesterie), et &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir une expérience plus large en &amp;ldquo;approche cadre logique / gestion du cycle de projet / intégration de l&amp;#39;environnement&amp;rdquo;. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir travaillé avec une ou des Communautés Economiques Régionales africaine du type de l&amp;#39;UEMOA ou de la CEDEAO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir une expérience avec le Programme des Nations Unies pour le Développement (PNUD/UNDP)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail:%20CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMarina_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert III (Communication Expert, Cat.II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-iii-communication-expert-catii</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 08:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-iii-communication-expert-catii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to strengthen the role and coordination of the Ministry for EU Affairs (MEU) in capacity building of local grassroots NGOs and strengthening public-Civil Society Organizations (CSO) cooperation at local level in accordance with EU accession process. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specifically the objective are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To increase awareness in local actors such as civil society organizations (particularly grassroots) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To implement pilot schemes for the strategies developed by the Ministry for EU Affairs at local level,&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To develop the capacity of local actors especially the civil society organizations in Antalya and İzmir concerning the EU process and the access to EU funds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responsible for the implementation of all communication activities as well as the preparation of all visibility materials. He/she will support the Team Leader as necessary in the promotional and networking aspects of the activities. Each activity will include a communication aspect thus the communication expert shall be available for all contracting period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Qualifications and Skills:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least Master’s degree or equivalent in Communication or Public Relations or Social Sciences or equivalent. In the absence of the required degree, minimum 11 years of working experience in the field of communication is requested.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Good command of spoken and written English.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 6 years of experience in the field of communication.
Specific Professional Experience &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 2 work experiences in EU projects as a Communication or Public Relations (PR) expert.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 5 experiences in designing or preparation of PR publications (such as poster, brochure, flyer, newsletter, compendium etc.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Work experience involving local administrations and other local actors in Turkey will be an asset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail:%20veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert II (Civil Society Expert, Cat.II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-ii-civil-society-expert-catii</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 08:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-ii-civil-society-expert-catii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to strengthen the role and coordination of the Ministry for EU Affairs (MEU) in capacity building of local grassroots NGOs and strengthening public-Civil Society Organizations (CSO) cooperation at local level in accordance with EU accession process. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specifically the objective are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To increase awareness in local actors such as civil society organizations (particularly grassroots) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To implement pilot schemes for the strategies developed by the Ministry for EU Affairs at local level,&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To develop the capacity of local actors especially the civil society organizations in Antalya and İzmir concerning the EU process and the access to EU funds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responsible for the implementation of “Activity B.1.2. Capacity Building Training for Civil Society Organizations”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Qualifications and Skills:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least Master’s degree. In the absence of the required degree at least 11 years of professional experience the area relevant to the assignment is requested,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Good command of spoken and written English,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 6 years of experience in the sector(s) related to the lot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*Specific Professional Experience *&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 3 work experiences in the fields of civil society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 5 experiences as a trainer in the field of civil society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience in preparation of a training module in the field of civil society will be an asset. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Consulting experience working with Civil Society Organizations will be an asset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail:%20veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert I (Team Leader, Cat. II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-i-team-leader-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 08:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-i-team-leader-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of this assignment is to strengthen the role and coordination of the Ministry for EU Affairs (MEU) in capacity building of local grassroots NGOs and strengthening public-Civil Society Organizations (CSO) cooperation at local level in accordance with EU accession process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specifically the objective are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To increase awareness in local actors such as civil society organizations (particularly grassroots) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To implement pilot schemes for the strategies developed by the Ministry for EU Affairs at local level,&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To develop the capacity of local actors especially the civil society organizations in Antalya and İzmir concerning the EU process and the access to EU funds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responsible for general coordination of project activities, project management and implementation, thus he/she will ensure coordination among other experts and backstopping team. Team Leader will mainly be responsible for each activity and preparation of the reports (inception and final reports). Team Leader will specifically deal with Training for Project Cycle Management. Team Leader will also responsible for checking the outputs and indicators are in accordance with the ToR and the work schedule. He/she shall act as the main counterpart to the MEU in relation to the performance of project activities. He/she will be responsible for the efficient and effective financing management monitoring and the project implementation in line with EU procedures and this ToR.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Qualifications and Skills:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least Master’s degree. In the absence of the required degree, at least 11 years of work experience in the area relevant to assignment is requested.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Good command of spoken and written English.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Turkish language will be an asset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 6 years of experience in the sector(s) related to the lot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*Specific Professional Experience *&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• At least 3 experiences as team leader or project manager or other managerial positions in   EU projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Work experience as a trainer on PCM in at least 3 trainings for EU-funded programmes or projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mail:%20veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ASiST Programme</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/asist-programme-1</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 14:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/asist-programme-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Purpose of role&lt;/strong&gt;
DAI’s ASiST programme is an advisory service for the European Commission rural development, food security and nutrition directorate (unit C1) within the Directorate General for Development and Cooperation (DEVCO). ASiST aims at providing support to identify and fine-tune tools to achieve the strategic objectives of food and nutrition security and sustainable agriculture in developing countries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ASiST Coordinator will provide direct hands-on support to the Team Leader and C1 Programme Manager to coordinate efficient delivery across the repertoire of ASiST technical and operational tasks. The role will add further value to ASiST by supporting a number of new or expanded functions, including: (i) coordinating a new technical help desk service; (ii) servicing ASiST’s knowledge management systems; and (iii) strengthening coordination and communications with internal and external stakeholders. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key tasks and responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;General operational support&lt;/em&gt;
• Routine support to the full complement of programme activities under the supervision of the Team Leader and DEVCO C1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Regular liaison with the DEVCO C1 Programme Manager and core team to ensure efficient and effective activity coordination, including through attending in-person meetings at DEVCO headquarters on a flexible basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Service and participate in ASiST’s frequent meetings and events, including organising venues, attendance lists, agendas, minute taking, circulating and monitoring agreed follow-up actions. These events include regular strategy meetings with DEVCO and the ASiST team as well as a range of conferences, presentations, roundtables, etc involving other DEVCO units, services and partners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Direct support to delivery of ASiST technical services. These include quality assurance of reports, research, studies, etc relating to ASiST’s core technical themes as well as an often significant volume of demand-driven requests from DEVCO and EU Delegations. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Play an active role in programme process planning and improvement initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Communication and collaboration&lt;/strong&gt;
• Serve as the coordination point to facilitate ongoing technical and thematic collaboration with other relevant DEVCO units and services (such as NAS and FANSSA) around key topics and activities of mutual relevance;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Support the team to continually promote ASiST, EU and thematic visibility, including through developing and disseminating communications materials, maintaining newsletters, etc;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Manage ASiST’s knowledge management systems, including: coordinating and disseminating regular knowledge products; helping DEVCO C1 in organising EU InfoPoint debriefings; taking the lead role in managing ASiST content on the Capacity4Dev portal. With the latter, the junior expert will be in charge of collecting contributions from ASiST experts after each mission and updating Capacity4Dev by writing blog posts on specific insights and writing briefs to illustrate social transfer instruments and issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Responsible for helping the Team Leader to explore and develop innovative ways of exchanging information and learning with C1 and EUDs around key themes and services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ASiST Helpdesk coordination&lt;/strong&gt;
• Work with the team to set up and manage the ASiST helpdesk, including receiving, fielding and coordinating enquiries and responses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications, knowledge, skills and experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/em&gt;
• Minimum Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in a relevant field or equivalent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience in coordinating projects and activities operating across multiple locations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience with project communications and knowledge management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience in providing quality assurance to reports and proofing reports or written products for development agencies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Excellent written and verbal communication skills in both English and French.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Strong organisational skills with excellent attention to detail.
• Proactive, resourceful, team player and able to independently manage complex tasks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Excellent interpersonal skills – able to establish and maintain positive working relationships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• A strong client-service delivery approach to delivering tasks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Ability to work under pressure and to tight deadlines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• MS Office expertise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;
• Minimum 5 years of professional experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Previous experience working with European Union Delegations and DEVCO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;
• Minimum 5 years of professional experience in one of the following thematic areas: food security, nutrition, resilience, sustainable agriculture, rural development, social transfers. Field experience would be an advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Demonstrable understanding of DEVCO, EUD processes and PRAG rules.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience working with EU-funded projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Experience working in international development cooperation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV to &lt;a href=&quot;mail:%20penny_buckle@dai.com&quot;&gt;penny_buckle@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Area B Enhancing Cybersecurity in ECOWAS region (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/area-b-enhancing-cybersecurity-in-ecowas-region-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 19:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/area-b-enhancing-cybersecurity-in-ecowas-region-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identification/Formulation Support to West Africa Peace, Security and Stability: Complementary action combatting other main threats&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This assignment will provide a coherent proposal to ECOWAS and EU for the strengthening of coordination and cooperation in security in West Africa and the implementation of programmes dealing with specific threats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Area B Enhancing Cybersecurity in ECOWAS region (Category I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master Degree (University Level) in Information technology, project management, engineering, law, finance, or relevant, directly related discipline, or equivalent professional qualification.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 12 years of professional experience which must include 5 years  of professional experience as programme manager/expert in relation to cybersecurity;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in international standards and methods regarding cybersecurity; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in contributing to the design, the identification, the formulation of development projects, particularly EU financed. Having been a team member of at least 2 identifications or formulations will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in communication, negotiation and dialogue at high level demonstrated by having been a team member of at least 2 relevant assignments, with preference in developing countries. Knowledge of West Africa Peace and security dynamics will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work experience in at least two sub-saharan countries. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full working knowledge of English and at least very good command of French (or vice versa), as well as excellent report writing and communication skills in both languages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Area A Libre Circulation, Gestion Sécurisée des Frontières et Développement des Zones Frontalières (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/area-a-libre-circulation-gestion-securisee-des-frontieres-et-developpement-des-zones-frontalieres-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 19:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/area-a-libre-circulation-gestion-securisee-des-frontieres-et-developpement-des-zones-frontalieres-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identification/Formulation Support to West Africa Peace, Security and Stability: Complementary action combatting other main threats&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This assignment will provide a coherent proposal to ECOWAS and EU for the strengthening of coordination and cooperation in security in West Africa and the implementation of programmes dealing with specific threats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Area A Libre Circulation, Gestion Sécurisée des Frontières et Développement des Zones Frontalières (Category I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master Degree (University Level) in Defence, Customs, Law, Political Science, Development Cooperation, Humanitarian Aid or relevant, directly related discipline, or equivalent;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 12 years of professional experience which must include 5 years  of professional experience as programme manager/expert in relation to border security management, freedom of movement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in international standards and methods regarding border security management, freedom of movement; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in contributing to the design, the identification, the formulation of development projects, particularly EU financed. Having been a team member of at least 2 identifications or formulations will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in communication, negotiation and dialogue at high level demonstrated by having been a team member of at least 2 relevant assignments, with preference in developing countries. Knowledge of West Africa Peace and security dynamics will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work experience in at least two sub-saharan countries. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full working knowledge of English and at least very good command of French (or vice versa), as well as excellent report writing and communication skills in both languages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader, Security specialist + Identification/ Formulation Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-security-specialist-identification-formulation-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 19:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-security-specialist-identification-formulation-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identification/Formulation Support to West Africa Peace, Security and Stability: Complementary action combatting other main threats&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This assignment will provide a coherent proposal to ECOWAS and EU for the strengthening of coordination and cooperation in security in West Africa and the implementation of programmes dealing with specific threats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader, Security specialist + Identification/ Formulation Specialist&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master Degree (Academic level) in Defence or Security Affairs, Project and Programme Management, Public Administration, Political Science, Engineering, Law or relevant, directly related discipline, or equivalent professional qualification.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 12 years of professional experience which must include 5 years professional experience in security sector in developing countries. In-depth knowledge of security related issues, systems and infrastructures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in monitoring the identification/formulation of large development projects in complex political environments (at least 2 significant identifications/formulations) with particular reference to EU-funded projects/programmes, and familiarity with the methodological approach set by the European Commission, preferably in developing countries. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in EDF financial and procurement procedures. Minimum of 2 references as programme manager/expert in delivering EU project logical frameworks, Identification/formulation Action Documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in problem analysis, stakeholders&amp;#39; analysis, assessment and communication of best practices demonstrated by having been team leader in two relevant assignments, particularly in the security field.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full working knowledge of English and at least very good command of French (or vice versa), as well as excellent report writing and communication skills in both languages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work experience at least in two West African Countries demonstrated by having been team member of at least 2 assignments in the region. Knowledge of West Africa peace and security architecture will be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in technical assistance, capacity development, training, awareness campaigns especially in countries with common law legal system, will be an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 2 and 3: Data Collection Analyst on Gender Equality in Public Administration </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-and-3-data-collection-analyst-on-gender-equality-in-public-administration</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-and-3-data-collection-analyst-on-gender-equality-in-public-administration</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Study on Gender Equality in Public Administration in the Western Balkans&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of this assignment is to contribute to strengthening girl&amp;rsquo;s and women&amp;rsquo;s voice and participation in the Western Balkans, in particular, women’s empowerment and expanded participation in policy-making and leadership in the executive branch of the state. The study will cover the Western Balkans (Albania, Bosnia &amp;amp; Herzegovina, Kosovo*, the former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, Montenegro and Serbia) and should achieve the following specific objectives:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Provide an overview of the current state-of-play, barriers and challenges to women&amp;rsquo;s participation in decision-making, both participation in public policy/strategy development and participation in leadership positions. The analysis will focus on the thematic area &amp;lsquo;strengthening voice and participation&amp;rsquo; identified in the Gender Action Plan. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Analyse country-specific legal frameworks, policies and initiatives indicating major constraints and enabling factors of promoting gender equality and women’s empowerment in public administration. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Identify policy and programming recommendations for further action, including specific entry points for the EC to advance women’s equal participation in public administration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2 and 3: Data Collection Analyst on Gender Equality in Public Administration&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;(maximum 70 working days)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;University Degree in relevant area such as Public Administration, Public Policy, Social and Political Sciences, Gender Studies, International Law, Development Studies, or equivalent. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of relevant professional experience one or more of the areas of gender, governance (with particular emphasis on public administration reforms), and/or data collection;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with extensive online research;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with quantitative research and data collection;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of decision-making processes in public policy, public service delivery, institutional capacity building, human resource management policies, professional ethics and/or civil service reform would be desirable;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of the international framework on gender equality and women&amp;rsquo;s empowerment, particularly in the area of women&amp;rsquo;s participation in policy and decision-making and leadership; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the EU Gender Equality Policy and Gender Action Plan would be considered an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in the Western Balkans in issues related to public administration reform and/or gender equality will be a strong asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent spoken and written English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of any of the languages spoken in the Western Balkans would be a distinctive advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team leader, Senior Expert in Public Administration Reform</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-expert-in-public-administration-reform</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 16:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-expert-in-public-administration-reform</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Study on Gender Equality in Public Administration in the Western Balkans&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of this assignment is to contribute to strengthening girl&amp;rsquo;s and women&amp;rsquo;s voice and participation in the Western Balkans, in particular, women’s empowerment and expanded participation in policy-making and leadership in the executive branch of the state. The study will cover the Western Balkans (Albania, Bosnia &amp;amp; Herzegovina, Kosovo*, the former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia, Montenegro and Serbia) and should achieve the following specific objectives:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Provide an overview of the current state-of-play, barriers and challenges to women&amp;rsquo;s participation in decision-making, both participation in public policy/strategy development and participation in leadership positions. The analysis will focus on the thematic area &amp;lsquo;strengthening voice and participation&amp;rsquo; identified in the Gender Action Plan. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Analyse country-specific legal frameworks, policies and initiatives indicating major constraints and enabling factors of promoting gender equality and women’s empowerment in public administration. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Identify policy and programming recommendations for further action, including specific entry points for the EC to advance women’s equal participation in public administration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team leader, Senior Expert in Public Administration Reform 
(maximum 70 working days)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Masters&amp;#39; Degree in relevant area such as Public Administration, Public Policy, Social and Political Sciences, Gender Studies, International Law, or equivalent. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;minimum 10 years of relevant professional experience in one or more of the areas of gender, governance (with particular emphasis on public administration reforms), and/or data collection;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project management;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience coordinating/supervising studies/research projects;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with quantitative research and data collection;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experience in analysis and research on public administration reform and/or gender mainstreaming in the public sector:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of the international framework on gender equality and women&amp;rsquo;s empowerment, particularly in the area of women&amp;rsquo;s participation in policy and decision-making and leadership; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent knowledge of decision-making processes in public policy, public service delivery, institutional capacity building, human resource management policies, professional ethics and/or civil service reform would be desirable;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the EU Gender Equality Policy and Gender Action Plan would be considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in the Western Balkans in issues related to public administration reform and/or gender equality will be a strong asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent spoken and written English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of any of the languages spoken in the Western Balkans would be a distinctive advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert on EU Directives and Harmonized Standards for Doors and Windows (Category II) </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-eu-directives-and-harmonized-standards-for-doors-and-windows-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 08:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-eu-directives-and-harmonized-standards-for-doors-and-windows-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance for the capacity building of ISRM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of the project is to contribute to free movement of goods with the EU and enhance the free trade, through reinforcing the capacity of quality infrastructure in the area of standardisation in the Beneficiary Country. The specific objective this contract is to strengthen the ISRM managerial, technical, financial and administrative capacities and to further improve the standardization and certification process in the ISRM.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert on EU Directives and Harmonized Standards for Doors and Windows (Category II)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master degree academic level  in doors and windows technology or equivalent general professional experience of 3 (three) above the minimum general professional experience requested below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 (six) years professional experience in doors and windows industry.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least in 3 years EU legislation and standards for doors and windows industry and CE marking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert on  EU Directives and Harmonized Standards for Food Industry (Category II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-eu-directives-and-harmonized-standards-for-food-industry-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 08:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-on-eu-directives-and-harmonized-standards-for-food-industry-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance for the capacity building of ISRM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of the project is to contribute to free movement of goods with the EU and enhance the free trade, through reinforcing the capacity of quality infrastructure in the area of standardisation in the Beneficiary Country. The specific objective this contract is to strengthen the ISRM managerial, technical, financial and administrative capacities and to further improve the standardization and certification process in the ISRM.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert on  EU Directives and Harmonized Standards for Food Industry (Category II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;•At least Master degree academic level  in food technology or equivalent general professional experience of 3 (three) above the minimum general professional experience requested below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;General professional experience&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;•At least 6 (six) years professional experience in the food industry &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;•Experience of at least 3 years related to EU legislation and standards for food industry and CE marking. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IT Expert (Category II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/it-expert-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 08:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/it-expert-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance for the capacity building of ISRM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of the project is to contribute to free movement of goods with the EU and enhance the free trade, through reinforcing the capacity of quality infrastructure in the area of standardisation in the Beneficiary Country. The specific objective this contract is to strengthen the ISRM managerial, technical, financial and administrative capacities and to further improve the standardization and certification process in the ISRM.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IT Expert (Category II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This expert shall be IT advisor for the development DMS for certification activities &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master degree academic level  in IT engineering, or in its absence, equivalent general professional experience of 3 (three) years above the minimum general professional experience requested below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least six (6) years in development and/or adaptation/upgrade of information management systems &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least 2 (two) projects in the development/upgrade of DMS for general standardisation or certification activities. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Certification (Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-certification-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 08:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-certification-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance for the capacity building of ISRM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of the project is to contribute to free movement of goods with the EU and enhance the free trade, through reinforcing the capacity of quality infrastructure in the area of standardisation in the Beneficiary Country. The specific objective this contract is to strengthen the ISRM managerial, technical, financial and administrative capacities and to further improve the standardization and certification process in the ISRM.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in Certification (Category I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This expert shall develop certification activities within ISRM set forth under Activity 1. In particular, expert will provide consultancy related to setting up of a national conformity assessment body for the selected Quality Management Systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master degree academic level  social/technical/natural sciences or equivalent general professional experience of 3 (three) years above the minimum general professional experience requested below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Certified IRCA trainer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has certificate  for EN ISO 17021-1:2015 and EN ISO 9001:2015 &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 (twelve) years professional experience in the area of certification activities. In this line, the expert must have experience in certification as well as in the general standardisation activities (such as working experience in certification bodies; accreditation bodies, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 (three) years of experience in the field of organization and administration of certification activities or capacity building of certification bodies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert for Standardization and Training (Category I)(TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-for-standardization-and-training-category-itl</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 07:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-for-standardization-and-training-category-itl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Technical Assistance for the capacity building of ISRM
*&lt;/em&gt;
The global objective of the project is to contribute to free movement of goods with the EU and enhance the free trade, through reinforcing the capacity of quality infrastructure in the area of standardisation in the Beneficiary Country. The specific objective this contract is to strengthen the ISRM managerial, technical, financial and administrative capacities and to further improve the standardization and certification process in the ISRM.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert for Standardization and Training (Category I)(TL)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master degree academic level  in social/technical/natural sciences or equivalent general professional experience of 3 (three) years above the minimum general professional experience requested below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least 12 years of experience in the field of Quality Infrastructure&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least 2 (two) projects for capacity building and/or providing of trainings in the field of standardization and certification;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least one project as trainer, advisor and/or consultant providing capacity building and institutional-strengthening support to Quality Infrastructure institutions, in particular developing their managerial skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 2 (Senior Category):- Trade Finance Analyst/Value Chains </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-senior-category-trade-finance-analyst-value-chains</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-senior-category-trade-finance-analyst-value-chains</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance for the Formulation of Private Sector Development Support to Botswana under the 11th EDF&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of the assignment is to provide assistance to the Government of Botswana and the EU Delegation in the formulation of support to private sector development to be funded under the 11th EDF NIP. The purpose of this assignment is to improve the design of the support to private sector development by reviewing the selected option as per the identification mission report and action document.  The specific objectives are as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review the relevance, scope and focus of the project proposed and of each of its components&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess institutional capacity of the organisations involved, in particular the Ministry of Investment Trade and Industry (MITI)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discuss and define a programme governance structure with stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the mobilisation and participation of the intermediary organisations and other institutions involved&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce the Action Document, Financing Agreement, Technical and Administrative Provisions, Logical Framework, a detailed budget and ToRs to launch a tender to implement the respective work package, as applicable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2 (Senior Category):- Trade Finance Analyst/Value Chains – 30 working days&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum requirements&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education at least Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree Academic Level in economics, trade, finance or industrial development.  In the absence of a University Degree stated above, 12 years of equivalent professional experience which must be above the general professional experience duration fixed below, are required in the area of trade and/or Private Sector Development. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience of up to 12 years in sectors related to Trade, Micro-Finance and capacity building for private sector including SMMEs, IOs and civil society organisations involved in economic development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10 years&amp;#39; professional experience with the Access to Finance aspect of private sector development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable experience in conducting market analyses, investigating constraints to competitiveness and innovation for SMMEs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in trade related data base development and management information system development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good understanding of investment environment involving SMEs, banks and intermediary organisation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with value chain analysis and development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in monitoring private sector development programmes is considered a distinctive advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in working with public institutions and private sector organisations is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader/Trade Policy and Private Sector Development/Value Chains (Category I) (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-trade-policy-and-private-sector-development-value-chains-category-i-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 21:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-trade-policy-and-private-sector-development-value-chains-category-i-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance for the Formulation of Private Sector Development Support to Botswana under the 11th EDF&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of the assignment is to provide assistance to the Government of Botswana and the EU Delegation in the formulation of support to private sector development to be funded under the 11th EDF NIP. The purpose of this assignment is to improve the design of the support to private sector development by reviewing the selected option as per the identification mission report and action document.  The specific objectives are as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review the relevance, scope and focus of the project proposed and of each of its components&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assess institutional capacity of the organisations involved, in particular the Ministry of Investment Trade and Industry (MITI)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discuss and define a programme governance structure with stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the mobilisation and participation of the intermediary organisations and other institutions involved&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce the Action Document, Financing Agreement, Technical and Administrative Provisions, Logical Framework, a detailed budget and ToRs to launch a tender to implement the respective work package, as applicable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 1: Team Leader/Trade Policy and Private Sector Development/Value Chains (Category I) – 40 working days&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum requirements&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master degree / Academic level in Economics, Business, Finance, Trade or related field.  In the absence of a University Degree stated above, 12 years of equivalent professional experience which must be above the general professional experience duration fixed below, are required in the area of trade and/or Private Sector Development. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years&amp;#39; experience, preferably in Africa, in the analysis, design and/or delivery of economic and trade co-operation programmes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience in project formulations, with at least one mission in the field of private sector development and trade policy regimes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 10  years of experience in value chain development&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrable experience of leading a team of experts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least five (5) successful formulation mission in an upper middle income country;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sound understanding of international and EU regulatory aspects affecting export/import activities &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of international and regional trade policies, international trade related assistance programmes, preferably in landlocked countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with export development activities at sector level, particularly with regards to exports (market analysis, export promotion, export management skills, etc.) and making market works for the poor. Business enabling environment reforms and support to SMMEs (access to finance, etc.);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of EC implementation rules/constraints and particularly the Project Cycle Management concept and logical framework approach.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience in Southern Africa, in particular Botswana would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:elena_bellitto@dai.com&quot;&gt;elena_bellitto@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
