<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2015 07:33:51 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader/Agronomist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-agronomist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2015 07:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-agronomist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectives of the role&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall goal of this activity is to reduce the burden of childhood malnutrition through the production, promotion and uptake of nutritious, locally-produced complementary foods for children of 6-23 months, and nutritional supplements for pregnant and lactating women (PLW).  The activity is implemented by Clinton Health Access Initiative (CHAI) who work closely with local governments, international investors and donors.  The activity is initially being implemented in Rwanda and Ethiopia and will potentially be expanded to two further African countries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MFAT are contributing to component three of the activity which aims to ensure a reliable supply of local crop inputs for the factory that will produce the complementary foods.  To achieve this, CHAI are working with smallholder farmers, cooperatives and unions to increase the quantity and quality of maize and soya produced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These services will supply technical assistance to CHAI, local trainers and government extension providers to strengthen farmer training programmes and provide technical information to farmers unions and cooperatives to inform investments in harvest and post-harvest technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The outcomes of these services will be:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Extension service providers can sustainably deliver practical and effective farmer-oriented training to increase the quantity and quality of soya and maize yields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Farmers cooperatives and unions are able to make informed decisions about the costs and benefits of investing in agricultural technology to assist with planting, harvest and post-harvest.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; will:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Ensure all team members are briefed on their roles and responsibilities in the project, and ensure all team inputs are well coordinated and delivered to a high quality standard;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Liaise with CHAI and key stakeholders in Rwanda; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support the New Zealand Aid Programme to actively engage in the agriculture components of the initiative, including through attendance at the annual steering committee meetings; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare work plans and budget; coordinate  inputs; and consolidate reports;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define monitoring and evaluation system in conjunction with CHAI and the government;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist with preparation of extension manual and farmer training packages for maize and soy production;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support delivery of training to extension officers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Length of the project: It is anticipated that approximately 120 days of technical assistance per year will be provided by a team of advisors over a three year period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to apply&lt;/strong&gt;: Please send a recent version of your CV to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarah_owen@dai.com&quot;&gt;Sarah_Owen@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Please note that all profiles are indicative only and therefore subject to change once the ToR is made available.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader for the Investment Design Process for Peace though Education</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-for-the-investment-design-process-for-peace-though-education</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 14:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-for-the-investment-design-process-for-peace-though-education</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectives of the role&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objective of the assignment is to assist DFAT in drafting an investment concept for an Australian Government investment in peace though education and lead the drafting of an investment design for six-year Australian Government aid investment program   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Length of the project&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Team Leader will be engaged for an initial nine month period with an option to extend up to a total of 12 months. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 10-year experience working in education programs, preferably conflict-sensitive education programs &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of the nature and history of conflicts in Muslim Mindanao &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of key players in Muslim Mindanao, along with a demonstrated network of contacts in ARMM, will be viewed positively &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have been substantially involved in an education or peace program design process; or service delivery in conflict zones &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have led or managed a team responsible for the design and/or implementation of a conflict-sensitive education program &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with and understanding of designs of donor supported conflict sensitive education programs in the Philippines or overseas &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience in conducting analytical work and high quality technical writing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Professional Experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced degree in Education, Development, Economics, Political Science, Asian Studies, Peace and Conflict Studies or a field related to conflict sensitive development/education; University degree in above fields, combined with substantial relevant experience, may be considered in lieu of an advanced degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preferably Filipino national and based in the Philippines, an international advisor may be considered&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deadline for Application: Please apply to: &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:katarzyna_rybak@dai.com&quot;&gt;katarzyna_rybak@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;strong&gt;4 August 2015&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Please note that all profiles are indicative only and therefore subject to change once the ToR is made available.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Especialista em Análise de Género (categoria II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/especialista-em-analise-de-genero-categoria-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2015 11:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/especialista-em-analise-de-genero-categoria-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Rever e analisar a situação actual, constrangimentos e oportunidades para o avanço na promoção da igualdade de mulheres e raparigas moçambicanas e seu empoderamento, face aos resultados, identificar recomendações práticas e operacionais para a avaliação da Estratégia de Género e para dar seguimento a esta agenda. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;O principal resultado desta análise será a produção de um Documento de Análise, identificação de desafios e de oportunidades e Recomendações para superar os desafios. O relatório deverá incluir a descrição da metodologia, as sugestões de áreas prioritárias e acções para serem desenvolvidas através de um plano de acção do Ministério do Género, Criança e Acção Social com que poderá contar com o suporte da União Europeia e outros parceiros.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectivos Expecíficos&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.1. Analisar, utilizando um quadro de análise integrado (macro-meso-micro), a situação da igualdade de género em Moçambique, e fazer um sumário (até 10 paginas) incluindo as seguintes áreas: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Situação socioeconómica de mulheres e raparigas (incluindo um análise sobre a relação género e pobreza); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acesso a Justiça e direitos humanos; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Situação politica (participação, liderança, processos de tomada de decisão, etc.);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acesso a serviços e recursos produtivos (incluindo Acesso à saúde e uma análise sobre género e HIV/Sida, terra, mercados, crédito, etc.);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Legislação (quadro legal, normativo e costumeiro); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dados estatísticos sobre mulher e rapariga (com uma componente de diversidade rural/urbana, minorias linguísticas, etc.). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.2. Tendo em conta este contexto, analisar e aferir o quadro legal e político para a igualdade de género e identificar oportunidades e constrangimentos para o avanço da mulher e rapariga. Este ponto deverá incluir: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Uma revisão descritiva das principais políticas nacionais, estratégias e iniciativas que determinam o quadro legal para a igualdade de género, incluindo mecanismos nacionais para a transversalização do género e instrumentos de planificação e orçamentação com base no género, e o contexto geral de financiamento;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mapeamento das actividades financiadas pelos parceiros de desenvolvimento na área de igualdade de género, idealmente com alguma indicação sobre as tendências de financiamento e escala (incluindo uma indicação sobre onde o suporte é direccionado ao Ministério do Género, Criança e Acção Social, e a outros ministérios e interessados, por exemplo organizações da sociedade civil) e áreas prioritárias de intervenção. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Uma análise dos principais constrangimentos, principais lacunas, desafios e oportunidades dentro do quadro legal e político (incluindo constrangimentos institucionais, culturais e de recursos), e uma análise de risco e de oportunidades (SWOT/FODA análises). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.3. Apresentar uma metodologia operacional e de análise, recomendações (a curto prazo e a médio prazo) para os diferentes actores chave, incluindo Sociedade Civil, o Governo de Moçambique (incluindo Ministério de Economia e Finanças, INE, etc.), parceiros bilaterais e multilaterais. Este processo poderá culminar na definição das bases para o futuro plano de acção a ser desenvolvido numa fase posterior. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Especialista em Análise de Género (categoria II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Especialista sénior com pelo menos 5 anos de experiência profissional relevante;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Curso universitário ou equivalente;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mínimo 5 anos de experiência progressiva na área de igualdade de género e empoderamento da mulher e rapariga; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Habilidades de comunicação e experiência em elaboração de relatórios; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Habilidade em gestão de equipas; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiência de trabalho em países africanos similares, sendo Moçambique uma vantagem;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiência em Português (escrito e falado) é um requisito; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluente em inglês (escrito e falado) é também um requisito.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Especialista em Orcamentacao Baseada no Género (categoria I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/especialista-em-orcamentacao-baseada-no-genero-categoria-i</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2015 11:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/especialista-em-orcamentacao-baseada-no-genero-categoria-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Rever e analisar a situação actual, constrangimentos e oportunidades para o avanço na promoção da igualdade de mulheres e raparigas moçambicanas e seu empoderamento, face aos resultados, identificar recomendações práticas e operacionais para a avaliação da Estratégia de Género e para dar seguimento a esta agenda. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;O principal resultado desta análise será a produção de um Documento de Análise, identificação de desafios e de oportunidades e Recomendações para superar os desafios. O relatório deverá incluir a descrição da metodologia, as sugestões de áreas prioritárias e acções para serem desenvolvidas através de um plano de acção do Ministério do Género, Criança e Acção Social com que poderá contar com o suporte da União Europeia e outros parceiros.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectivos Expecíficos&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.1. Analisar, utilizando um quadro de análise integrado (macro-meso-micro), a situação da igualdade de género em Moçambique, e fazer um sumário (até 10 paginas) incluindo as seguintes áreas: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Situação socioeconómica de mulheres e raparigas (incluindo um análise sobre a relação género e pobreza); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acesso a Justiça e direitos humanos; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Situação politica (participação, liderança, processos de tomada de decisão, etc.);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acesso a serviços e recursos produtivos (incluindo Acesso à saúde e uma análise sobre género e HIV/Sida, terra, mercados, crédito, etc.);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Legislação (quadro legal, normativo e costumeiro); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dados estatísticos sobre mulher e rapariga (com uma componente de diversidade rural/urbana, minorias linguísticas, etc.). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.2. Tendo em conta este contexto, analisar e aferir o quadro legal e político para a igualdade de género e identificar oportunidades e constrangimentos para o avanço da mulher e rapariga. Este ponto deverá incluir: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Uma revisão descritiva das principais políticas nacionais, estratégias e iniciativas que determinam o quadro legal para a igualdade de género, incluindo mecanismos nacionais para a transversalização do género e instrumentos de planificação e orçamentação com base no género, e o contexto geral de financiamento;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mapeamento das actividades financiadas pelos parceiros de desenvolvimento na área de igualdade de género, idealmente com alguma indicação sobre as tendências de financiamento e escala (incluindo uma indicação sobre onde o suporte é direccionado ao Ministério do Género, Criança e Acção Social, e a outros ministérios e interessados, por exemplo organizações da sociedade civil) e áreas prioritárias de intervenção. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Uma análise dos principais constrangimentos, principais lacunas, desafios e oportunidades dentro do quadro legal e político (incluindo constrangimentos institucionais, culturais e de recursos), e uma análise de risco e de oportunidades (SWOT/FODA análises). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.3. Apresentar uma metodologia operacional e de análise, recomendações (a curto prazo e a médio prazo) para os diferentes actores chave, incluindo Sociedade Civil, o Governo de Moçambique (incluindo Ministério de Economia e Finanças, INE, etc.), parceiros bilaterais e multilaterais. Este processo poderá culminar na definição das bases para o futuro plano de acção a ser desenvolvido numa fase posterior. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Especialista em orcamentacao baseada no género (categoria I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Especialista com pelo menos 10 anos de experiência profissional relevante;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Curso universitário/ pós graduação (mestrado) ou equivalente;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mínimo de 7 anos de experiência progressiva em análise orçamentação baseada no género; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Habilidades de comunicação e experiência em elaboração de relatórios; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conhecimento profundo em orçamentação e finanças públicas; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Domínio de análises de países/ ou avaliação de programas; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conhecimento de computador e internet; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiência de trabalho em países africanos similares, sendo Moçambique uma vantagem; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiência no âmbito de análise institucional e capacitação serão também consideradas pontos de vantagem; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiência em Português (escrito e falado) é um requisito; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluente em inglês (escrito e falado) é também um requisito.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Especialista em Análise de Género (categoria I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/especialista-em-analise-de-genero-categoria-i</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2015 10:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/especialista-em-analise-de-genero-categoria-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Rever e analisar a situação actual, constrangimentos e oportunidades para o avanço na promoção da igualdade de mulheres e raparigas moçambicanas e seu empoderamento, face aos resultados, identificar recomendações práticas e operacionais para a avaliação da Estratégia de Género e para dar seguimento a esta agenda. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;O principal resultado desta análise será a produção de um Documento de Análise, identificação de desafios e de oportunidades e Recomendações para superar os desafios. O relatório deverá incluir a descrição da metodologia, as sugestões de áreas prioritárias e acções para serem desenvolvidas através de um plano de acção do Ministério do Género, Criança e Acção Social com que poderá contar com o suporte da União Europeia e outros parceiros.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectivos Expecíficos&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.1. Analisar, utilizando um quadro de análise integrado (macro-meso-micro), a situação da igualdade de género em Moçambique, e fazer um sumário (até 10 paginas) incluindo as seguintes áreas: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Situação socioeconómica de mulheres e raparigas (incluindo um análise sobre a relação género e pobreza); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acesso a Justiça e direitos humanos; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Situação politica (participação, liderança, processos de tomada de decisão, etc.);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acesso a serviços e recursos produtivos (incluindo Acesso à saúde e uma análise sobre género e HIV/Sida, terra, mercados, crédito, etc.);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Legislação (quadro legal, normativo e costumeiro); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dados estatísticos sobre mulher e rapariga (com uma componente de diversidade rural/urbana, minorias linguísticas, etc.). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.2. Tendo em conta este contexto, analisar e aferir o quadro legal e político para a igualdade de género e identificar oportunidades e constrangimentos para o avanço da mulher e rapariga. Este ponto deverá incluir: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Uma revisão descritiva das principais políticas nacionais, estratégias e iniciativas que determinam o quadro legal para a igualdade de género, incluindo mecanismos nacionais para a transversalização do género e instrumentos de planificação e orçamentação com base no género, e o contexto geral de financiamento;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mapeamento das actividades financiadas pelos parceiros de desenvolvimento na área de igualdade de género, idealmente com alguma indicação sobre as tendências de financiamento e escala (incluindo uma indicação sobre onde o suporte é direccionado ao Ministério do Género, Criança e Acção Social, e a outros ministérios e interessados, por exemplo organizações da sociedade civil) e áreas prioritárias de intervenção. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Uma análise dos principais constrangimentos, principais lacunas, desafios e oportunidades dentro do quadro legal e político (incluindo constrangimentos institucionais, culturais e de recursos), e uma análise de risco e de oportunidades (SWOT/FODA análises). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.3. Apresentar uma metodologia operacional e de análise, recomendações (a curto prazo e a médio prazo) para os diferentes actores chave, incluindo Sociedade Civil, o Governo de Moçambique (incluindo Ministério de Economia e Finanças, INE, etc.), parceiros bilaterais e multilaterais. Este processo poderá culminar na definição das bases para o futuro plano de acção a ser desenvolvido numa fase posterior. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Especialista em análise de género (categoria I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Especialista com pelo menos 10 anos de experiência profissional relevante;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Curso universitário/ pós graduação (mestrado) ou equivalente;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mínimo 7 anos de experiência progressiva na área de igualdade de género e empoderamento da mulher e rapariga; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiência em avaliação e / ou concepção do programa; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Habilidades de comunicação e experiência em elaboração de relatórios; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Habilidade em gestão de equipas;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiência de trabalho em países africanos similares, sendo Moçambique uma vantagem; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiência no âmbito de análise institucional e capacitação serão também consideradas pontos de vantagem;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiência em Português (escrito e falado) é um requisito; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluente em inglês (escrito e falado) é também um requisito.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert(e) Sénior de Catégorie I en Développement Institutionnel dans le Secteur Postal (Cat. I, 33 hommes/jours)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-senior-de-categorie-i-en-developpement-institutionnel-dans-le-secteur-postal-cat-i-33-hommes-jours</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-senior-de-categorie-i-en-developpement-institutionnel-dans-le-secteur-postal-cat-i-33-hommes-jours</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Appui à l’adoption d’une stratégie d’ouverture progressive à la concurrence et à la préparation de la création d’une autorité de régulation indépendante du secteur postal, par le rapprochement aux exigences de l’Acquis de l&amp;#39;UE et des bonnes pratiques européennes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Project duration: maximum 12 months&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert(e) Sénior de Catégorie I en Développement Institutionnel dans le Secteur Postal (Cat. I, 33 hommes/jours)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire supérieur (niveau Master) en administration publique ou diplôme équivalent et pertinent par rapport aux objectifs du contrat ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience professionnelle de 5 ans an faveur d’une administration ou organisation postale en plus de celle indiquée comme expérience professionnelle générale, pourra compenser l’absence de Master ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise parfaite de la langue française parlée et écrite &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Douze ans d’expérience générale en renforcement institutionnel et/ou réglementaire ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience spécifique de 2 ans en développement institutionnel d’organismes de régulation ou institutions publiques dans les secteurs poste et télécommunications ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience de 3 ans dans le secteur postal, de l’énergie ou des télécommunications ayant fait l’objet d’ouverture à la concurrence ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert(e) Sénior de Catégorie I en Droit Postal (Cat. I, 72 hommes/jours)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-senior-de-categorie-i-en-droit-postal-cat-i-72-hommes-jours</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 15:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-senior-de-categorie-i-en-droit-postal-cat-i-72-hommes-jours</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Appui à l’adoption d’une stratégie d’ouverture progressive à la concurrence et à la préparation de la création d’une autorité de régulation indépendante du secteur postal, par le rapprochement aux exigences de l’Acquis de l&amp;#39;UE et des bonnes pratiques européennes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert(e) Sénior de Catégorie I en Droit Postal (Cat. I, 72 hommes/jours)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire supérieur (niveau Master), en droit ou diplôme équivalent et pertinent par rapport aux objectifs du contrat ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience professionnelle de 5 ans en droit postal en plus de celle indiquée comme expérience professionnelle générale, pourra compenser l’absence de Master ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maîtrise parfaite de la langue française parlée et écrite 
Expérience professionnelle: &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Douze ans d’expérience générale en réglementation et/ou renforcement institutionnel ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience spécifique règlementation des services postaux à l’échelle nationale en UE ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience spécifique de deux ans dans l’élaboration de textes juridiques, notamment relatifs au SUP en UE ou dans un pays en voie d’adhésion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert(e) Sénior de Catégorie I en Stratégie Postale et Chef de Mission (Cat. I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-senior-de-categorie-i-en-strategie-postale-et-chef-de-mission-cat-i</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-senior-de-categorie-i-en-strategie-postale-et-chef-de-mission-cat-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Appui à l’adoption d’une stratégie d’ouverture progressive à la concurrence et à la préparation de la création d’une autorité de régulation indépendante du secteur postal, par le rapprochement aux exigences de l’Acquis de l&amp;#39;UE et des bonnes pratiques européennes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert(e) Sénior de Catégorie I en Stratégie Postale et Chef de Mission (Cat. I, 88 hommes/jours)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire supérieur (niveau Master) en économie ou diplôme équivalent et pertinent par rapport aux objectifs du contrat ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Une expérience professionnelle de 5 ans en économie dans le secteur postal en plus de celle indiquée comme expérience professionnelle générale, pourra compenser l’absence de Master ; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maîtrise parfaite de la langue française parlée et écrite &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;12 ans d’expérience professionnelle en renforcement institutionnel ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience spécifique de 2 ans dans l’élaboration et/ou la mise en œuvre de stratégies de développement du secteur postal; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Management Information Systems Expert (Team Leader) - Category I</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-management-information-systems-expert-team-leader-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 14:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-management-information-systems-expert-team-leader-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To integrate the cane farmer registry and the cane parcel database with the  mill scale database;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To design, build and operationalize a Harvesting Management and Delivery System (HMDS);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To provide capacity building of industry&amp;rsquo;s stakeholders on the HMDS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Management Information Systems Expert (Team Leader) - Category I&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MSc level in Rural Systems Management, computer science or in related field of information technology or computer science, programming or computer engineering, database systems and management, professional and technical studies in GIS or other appropriate training in GIS with specific skills in database, GIS and Management Information Systems (MIS).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;: Minimum of post qualification 8 years of experience in the design, development and implementation of a Management Information System (MIS) preferable using ESRI ArcGIS (including designing user friendly databases and structured data analysis) or related analytic discipline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in monitoring and evaluation, assessments, data collection and coordination, information analysis and database management related to programmes would be considered an advantage; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Training and certifications in the field of GIS; iii) ESRI’s GIS software packages (ArcGIS for Desktop and extensions, ArcGIS for Server), SQL Server, and global positioning systems; iv) SQL database programming (MS, SQL Server, Sybase); and v) Developing software applications with .NET framework (C#, ASP.NET, etc).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full working knowledge of English, with at least five years working experience in English-speaking countries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gouvernance (Ressources Naturelles) Expert (cat. II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/gouvernance-ressources-naturelles-expert-cat-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/gouvernance-ressources-naturelles-expert-cat-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général&lt;/strong&gt; de cette évaluation est de fournir au Gouvernement de la RD Congo et à l&amp;#39;Union européenne une analyse du programme PAG qui se focalise en particulier sur la pertinence, la performance et les impacts. Cette analyse est nécessaire afin de vérifier si les objectifs du programme PAG ont été atteints et de dégager les enseignements à retenir pour les programmes de bonne gouvernance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Il s&amp;#39;agira plus spécifiquement d&amp;#39;une évaluation du montage du programme et de sa mise en œuvre - en utilisant les critères clés de l&amp;#39;évaluation:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluer l&amp;#39;atteinte des objectifs du Programme ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluer la pertinence, l&amp;#39;efficacité et l&amp;#39;efficience de la méthodologie et de l&amp;#39;approche d&amp;#39;exécution;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluer l&amp;#39;organisation et le fonctionnement du programme, notamment le fonctionnement de l&amp;#39;UGP; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluer l&amp;#39;impact du programme sur les bénéficiaires;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluer l&amp;#39;appréciation, l&amp;#39;appropriation et la pérennisation du programme ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;En ce qui concerne le volet ressources naturelles tenant compte de l’évaluation des interventions du PAG, et des besoins actuels du secteur en RDC, dégager des axes d&amp;#39;appui pertinents que pourraient soutenir la DUE, le cas échéant (dans un cadre régional ou bilatéral) ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;En ce qui concerne le volet justice, évaluer la coordination avec le PARJ qui a commencé deux ans avant la fin du PAG ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pour les trois volets évaluer la coordination avec les programmes des autres partenaires en fonction des secteurs concernés ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Examiner les objectifs du programme à la lumière des considérations de genre.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gouvernance (Ressources Naturelles) Expert (cat. II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir un diplôme en en sciences politiques, en sciences sociales, droit, économie ou autre diplôme pertinent (bac +5);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maitrise de la langue française&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle d’au moins 6 ans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle de minimum 6 ans dans l’analyse, la conception ou la gestion de projets de développement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solide connaissance de la problématique de la gouvernance, y-compris une expérience avérée dans le domaine des ressources naturelles
*Bonne connaissance des procédures de l&amp;#39;Union européenne et de la coopération ACP-UE&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience pratique d&amp;#39;évaluation d&amp;#39;au moins deux projets financés par l&amp;#39;Union européenne&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience avérée dans le domaine des mines en RDC (atout)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;Nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gouvernance (volet Justice) Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/gouvernance-volet-justice-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 09:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/gouvernance-volet-justice-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général&lt;/strong&gt; de cette évaluation est de fournir au Gouvernement de la RD Congo et à l&amp;#39;Union européenne une analyse du programme PAG qui se focalise en particulier sur la pertinence, la performance et les impacts. Cette analyse est nécessaire afin de vérifier si les objectifs du programme PAG ont été atteints et de dégager les enseignements à retenir pour les programmes de bonne gouvernance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Il s&amp;#39;agira plus spécifiquement d&amp;#39;une évaluation du montage du programme et de sa mise en œuvre - en utilisant les critères clés de l&amp;#39;évaluation:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluer l&amp;#39;atteinte des objectifs du Programme ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluer la pertinence, l&amp;#39;efficacité et l&amp;#39;efficience de la méthodologie et de l&amp;#39;approche d&amp;#39;exécution;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluer l&amp;#39;organisation et le fonctionnement du programme, notamment le fonctionnement de l&amp;#39;UGP; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluer l&amp;#39;impact du programme sur les bénéficiaires;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluer l&amp;#39;appréciation, l&amp;#39;appropriation et la pérennisation du programme ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;En ce qui concerne le volet ressources naturelles tenant compte de l’évaluation des interventions du PAG, et des besoins actuels du secteur en RDC, dégager des axes d&amp;#39;appui pertinents que pourraient soutenir la DUE, le cas échéant (dans un cadre régional ou bilatéral) ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;En ce qui concerne le volet justice, évaluer la coordination avec le PARJ qui a commencé deux ans avant la fin du PAG ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pour les trois volets évaluer la coordination avec les programmes des autres partenaires en fonction des secteurs concernés ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Examiner les objectifs du programme à la lumière des considérations de genre.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gouvernance (volet Justice) Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoir un diplôme en sciences politiques, en sciences sociales, économie, droit ou autre diplôme pertinent (bac +5)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maitrise de la langue française&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle d’au moins 12 ans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle de minimum 12 ans dans l’analyse, la conception ou la gestion de projets de développement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solide connaissance de la problématique de la gouvernance, y-compris une expérience avérée dans le volet justice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne connaissance des procédures de l&amp;#39;Union européenne et de la coopération ACP-UE&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience pratique d&amp;#39;évaluation d&amp;#39;au moins deux projets financés par l&amp;#39;Union européenne&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;Nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finances Publiques Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/finances-publiques-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 09:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/finances-publiques-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;objectif général de cette évaluation est de fournir au Gouvernement de la RD Congo et à l&amp;#39;Union européenne une analyse du programme PAG qui se focalise en particulier sur la pertinence, la performance et les impacts. Cette analyse est nécessaire afin de vérifier si les objectifs du programme PAG ont été atteints et de dégager les enseignements à retenir pour les programmes de bonne gouvernance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Il s&amp;#39;agira plus spécifiquement d&amp;#39;une évaluation du montage du programme et de sa mise en œuvre - en utilisant les critères clés de l&amp;#39;évaluation:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluer l&amp;#39;atteinte des objectifs du Programme ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluer la pertinence, l&amp;#39;efficacité et l&amp;#39;efficience de la méthodologie et de l&amp;#39;approche d&amp;#39;exécution;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluer l&amp;#39;organisation et le fonctionnement du programme, notamment le fonctionnement de l&amp;#39;UGP; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluer l&amp;#39;impact du programme sur les bénéficiaires;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluer l&amp;#39;appréciation, l&amp;#39;appropriation et la pérennisation du programme ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;En ce qui concerne le volet ressources naturelles tenant compte de l’évaluation des interventions du PAG, et des besoins actuels du secteur en RDC, dégager des axes d&amp;#39;appui pertinents que pourraient soutenir la DUE, le cas échéant (dans un cadre régional ou bilatéral) ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;En ce qui concerne le volet justice, évaluer la coordination avec le PARJ qui a commencé deux ans avant la fin du PAG ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pour les trois volets évaluer la coordination avec les programmes des autres partenaires en fonction des secteurs concernés ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Examiner les objectifs du programme à la lumière des considérations de genre.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Finances Publiques Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Avoir un diplôme en sciences politiques, en sciences sociales, droit, économie ou autre diplôme pertinent (bac +5)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maitrise de la langue française&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expérience professionnelle d’au moins 12 ans&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expérience professionnelle de minimum 12 ans dans l’analyse, la conception ou la gestion de projets de développement&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Solide connaissance de la problématique de la gouvernance, y-compris une expérience avérée dans minimum le domaine des finances publiques&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expérience professionnelle probante en gestion de programmes et projets financés par l&amp;#39;Union européenne&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expérience pratique d&amp;#39;évaluation d&amp;#39;au moins trois projets financés par l&amp;#39;Union européenne, dont de préférence  au minimum un projet en Afrique subsaharienne&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;Nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experts in SME Access to Finance, PSD, Public Private Partnerships, Macro Economic Analysis &amp; Financial Sector Policies</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-in-sme-access-to-finance-psd-public-private-partnerships-macro-economic-analysis-financial-sector-policies</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2015 14:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-in-sme-access-to-finance-psd-public-private-partnerships-macro-economic-analysis-financial-sector-policies</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;DAI Europe is a leading international developing consulting firm working throughout the developing world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due to our expanding portfolio we are looking to supplement our database of independent consultants for project work (not permanent posts).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We seek experienced independent consultants who specialise in the following areas: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SME access to finance &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Private sector development &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Public private partnerships (PPP)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Macroeconomic analysis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Financial sector policies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An excellent command of English is required and a good working knowledge of French, Spanish and/or Arabic would be an advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Work experience with the &lt;strong&gt;European Commission (EC)&lt;/strong&gt;, the &lt;strong&gt;European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD)&lt;/strong&gt; and the &lt;strong&gt;European Investment Bank (EIB)&lt;/strong&gt; is an advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like to be considered for inclusion in our Consultants’ Database please email your CV (preferably in EC format) to Nicolas Fichers (&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicolas_fichers@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicolas_fichers@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;) quoting reference: CV – Finance, PSD, PPP and Macroeconomy&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further information on &lt;strong&gt;DAI can be found at &lt;a href=&quot;http://dai.com/&quot;&gt;http://dai.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junior Architect</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-architect</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2015 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-architect</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; is to ensure proper and timely implementation of the operations covered under the RCOP (Regional Competitiveness Operational Programme) and also CISOP (Competitiveness and Innovation Sectorial Operational Programme).  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Junior Architect&lt;/strong&gt; 
(78 working days):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of general professional working experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS degree in architecture.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in a relevant discipline. In the absence of a master&amp;rsquo;s degree, the expert should have 4 years of equivalent professional experience. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In-depth knowledge and experience in reviewing of procurement files (e.g. tender dossiers, design, cost estimate, etc.) of construction works.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Construction tender evaluation experience would be an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of PRAG procurement procedures would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of FIDIC conditions of contract and experience of implementing construction contracts under FIDIC would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be fluent in English and Turkish&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have excellent analytical and communication (oral and written) skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have full computer literacy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWP 2 Projects Review</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/awp-2-projects-review</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Beyond WTO Program (B-WTO) was developed in response to a request from the Government of Vietnam (GoV) for donor support to help with managing economic integration and the transition to a market economy following WTO accession. The B-WTO goal is “to strengthen government’s capacity to manage the integration of Vietnam into the global economy and the transition of Vietnam to a socialist market economy”. The immediate objective is “implementation of priority policy actions from the GoV’s Action Plan to enhance Vietnam’s capacity to sustain pro-poor growth (GAP)”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The remit of this project was a review of the 2nd annual work plan’s implementation (AWP2) of Phase 2 of the B-WTO in May 2013. The objectives of the review were to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the project implementation performance and project results relative to the logical framework targets and evaluation criteria. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate the results achieved at the Component and Program’s level according to the Monitoring and Evaluation (M&amp;amp;E) framework of the Program.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify lessons learned from implementation, make recommendations for the remaining duration of the program and the Independent Completion Report process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-me</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program 2013 Performance and Quality Mapping Exercise</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/program-2013-performance-and-quality-mapping-exercise</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID’s PNG Program is looking to improve its performance and quality (P&amp;amp;Q) standards and systems. The purpose of this project was to map the PNG Program’s current P&amp;amp;Q capacity and systems, to address the risk of AusAID being unable to demonstrate results for its increased investments in PNG over the next four years. Over the last several years, the PNG Program has undertaken a number of M&amp;amp;E assessments and reviews which have identified key strengths and challenges within the program. This project was intended to pick up where these assessments left off. Through a desk review and consultations with sector teams, the Review Team were to distil key P&amp;amp;Q risks and issues for the PNG Program. The Review Team’s brief included the provision of recommendations on priority activities to support sector approaches to M&amp;amp;E, strengthen the Program’s ability to collect evidence, provide critical analysis and report on results.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/humanitarian-performance-assessment-framework</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusAID required a consultant to assist with the development and finalisation of its Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework. Development of a humanitarian monitoring and evaluation framework is a key commitment outlined in AusAID’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy (HAP) and its associated Implementation Plan. In line with the agency focus on results reporting, the HAP and HAP Implementation Plan commit AusAID to develop a monitoring and evaluation framework to support the initial performance assessment framework contained within the HAP and AusAID annual reporting under the Comprehensive Aid Policy Framework.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key objective of this assignment was to build the Humanitarian program’s capacity for monitoring and reporting results by:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In consultation with AusAID’s Humanitarian team, redraft and finalise the Humanitarian Performance Assessment Framework, to ensure it provides a platform to:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track implementation of key commitments in Australia’s 2011 Humanitarian Action Policy; and,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish a set of measurable humanitarian performance indicators (in addition to the two CAPF indicators) to enable AusAID to track achievements, lessons learned and to report on the results achieved from AusAID’s humanitarian work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of Pacific Forum Compact Reporting</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/review-of-pacific-forum-compact-reporting</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The purpose of the assignment was to examine country views of aid effectiveness and regional organisations expressed through Forum Compact reporting, particularly peer review of Forum Island Countries’ national development plan processes. The services provided included the preparation of a think piece which outlines key aid effectiveness issues arising from country reporting under the Compact reporting and discusses options for addressing these issues.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Program M&amp;E Specialist</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 16:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Bryan Schuetz</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/lots/dfat/health-program-m-and-e-specialist</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In partnership with the Ministry of Health (MoH), the Australian Government is scoping and piloting a new approach to engagement in the health sector in Timor-Leste. The program approach is innovative in several respects. Key program features are: a systems perspective; joint program oversight by MoH and Australian Government; an emphasis on capacity facilitation through coaching rather than an over-reliance on more traditional technical assistance approaches; ongoing processes of joint intervention design throughout implementation; and rapid cycles of evidence-informed adaptation. These will require significant investments in interactive, exploratory, and rigorous monitoring and evaluation, requiring support from an M&amp;amp;E Specialist that is comfortable with non-traditional M&amp;amp;E approaches. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Health Program M&amp;amp;E Specialist worked with the Australian Government Timor-Leste Health Team to design an M&amp;amp;E system for Australia’s support to the health sector, that is aligned with the Ministry of Health’s draft Sector M&amp;amp;E Framework and consistent with Australian Aid Program M&amp;amp;E Standards. The primary purpose of the M&amp;amp;E System will be to support strategic management and ongoing improvement of the Australian Government - MoH partnership in the health sector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
