<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2016 21:25:23 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Category I Experts in Public Administration Reform, HR Management in Civil Service and Civil Service Reform</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/public-administration-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2016 21:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/public-administration-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advisory Support to Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s Public Administration Reform Implementation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To improve accountability,  quality, effectiveness  and efficiency of the Ukrainian  public administration on the basis of Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s Strategy of Public Administration  Reform and its Implementation Plan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific  objectives&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To assist the Government of Ukraine in the process of launching the PAR Strategy, including establishment  of relevant strategic framework, coordination structures and monitoring  mechanism; To assist the Government in initial implementation  of specific actions of the PAR Strategy through coaching  and  provision  of  conceptual,  methodological  and  operational  guidance  based  on  the principles  of public administration  and best European  practices. This shall cover reorganization  of public administration,  policy making reform and civil service reform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Three Category I Experts in Public Administration Reform, HR Management in Civil Service and Civil Service Reform&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications  and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master degree in a field related to the assignment (law, public administration, management, economy) or equivalent professional experience (7 years of experience in public sector); Excellent English communication skills, both spoken and written;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Ukrainian (or Russian) will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a minimum of 12 years experience in civil service or public sector following the award of the above required Master degree;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:
At  least 8  years of specific and  practical experience (following the award of  the above required Master degree) in the fields related to the assignment:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert I&lt;/strong&gt;: design and implementation of large scale public administration reforms, including overall coordination of PAR process,   reorganisation of public administration, policy making reform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert II&lt;/strong&gt;: HR management in civil service, civil service reform, including reform of salary system and design of relevant information management systems;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert III&lt;/strong&gt;: design and implementation of large scale public administration reforms, including reorganisation of public administration, cost analysis of PAR&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of 8 years of experience required above, at least 3 years of experience at senior level in the EU Member State&amp;rsquo;s administration or in the administration of an accession country in the fields related to the assignment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While analysing specific professional experience, a particular attention will be paid to the following issues:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;practical experience in the area of PAR at strategic level;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience in drafting I implementing large scale reforms of public sector or I and public administration;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience of preparing policy and legal assessments, comparative analysis in the area of PAR;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience in facilitating high level policy dialogue in the area of PAR.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;practical experience in the area of civil service reform at strategic level;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience in drafting I implementing civil service reform, including drafting legal,policy (conceptual) and methodological documents;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience in designing I implementing large scale IT projects related to HRM in civil service;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;knowledge of European principles of public administration with a particular focus on civil service.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 3&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;practical experience in the area of PAR at strategic level;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience in drafting I implementing large scale reforms of public sector or /and public administration;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience in carrying out cost analysis of PAR and its main components&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience in facilitating high level policy dialogue in the area of reorganisation of public administration;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;experience in carrying out functional review of public bodies;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation Experts with experience of Implementation Procedures of the ENI or IPA II AND CIR</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/evaluation-experts-with-experience-of-implementation-procedures-of-the-eni-or-ipa-ii-and-cir</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2016 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/evaluation-experts-with-experience-of-implementation-procedures-of-the-eni-or-ipa-ii-and-cir</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Review Evaluations of ENI and IPA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Instrument for Pre-accession assistance (IPA II) and European Neighbourhood Policy (ENI) evaluations, together with the other independent evaluations of each External Financing Instrument (EFI) and the Coherence Report, will be some of the sources of information to feed into the Mid Term Review Report (MTR) of the EFIs. The MTR is required by the Common Implementing Regulation (CIR) Article 17, by end December 2017. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation Experts with experience of Implementation Procedures of the ENI or IPA II AND CIR&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are seeking &lt;strong&gt;separate teams for the two evaluations&lt;/strong&gt;, but the profiles are both as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of EU external action policies, and the implementation modalities &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of the international aid and development effectiveness agenda and principles and of the EU enlargement policy, and also have good knowledge of cross cutting issues, especially gender mainstreaming &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;EU external co-operation policy and development policy of Member States, and their aid modalities &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implementation procedures of the ENI or IPA II AND CIR &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compliance checking in the area of policy implementation &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluation methods and techniques in general and, preferably, of evaluation in the field of external relations and development cooperation; in particular the team needs to demonstrate experience in analytical methods which can evaluate change, and which can evaluate contribution &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quantitative and qualitative data collection and analysis &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For &lt;strong&gt;IPA and ENI&lt;/strong&gt; The evaluation team should have an excellent command of English – both spoken and written – and the ability to function at a high level in French &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For &lt;strong&gt;ENI&lt;/strong&gt;- team members should also have good understanding of &lt;strong&gt;Arabic or Russian&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category III Expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-iii-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 15:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-iii-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Assistance for the Development of New State Aid Legislation&amp;#39;, financed under IPA 2014 National Programme&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Global objective: To improve and strengthen the institutional capacity of the Albanian State Aid Control Sector to manage and enforce the new State Aid rules. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Specific objective(s): To ensure the approximation of legislation in State Aid area in compliance with the EU acquis and enforce a State Aid control system in Albania according to European Commission recommendations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One Cat. III Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification and skills&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree in law, economics, finance, public administration, or any other relevant field related to the project; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in both written and spoken English (min 2 point in the scale from 1 to 5 where 1 is excellent and 5 is basic) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least 3 years of experience in the development and operation of a country state aid control system. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific experience&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least one project related to approximation of the state aid legislation with the EU acquis &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in capacity development/building related to state aid discipline of public and/or private institutions &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Involvement in key position(s) for similar assignment will be considered an asset &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experts for bid: Ukraine Financial Sector Transformation Activity</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-for-bid-ukraine-financial-sector-transformation-activity</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 08:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-for-bid-ukraine-financial-sector-transformation-activity</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Ukraine Financial Sector Transformation (FST) Activity&lt;/strong&gt; is a four-year effort, estimated to start in summer 2016, that aims to transform and stabilize Ukraine’s financial sector, with an emphasis on: increasing public confidence in and understanding of the banking system, improving the non-bank financial sector regulatory environment, increasing access to finance for SMEs, bolstering financial inclusion, expanding digital finance solutions, and supporting the growth of a balanced and sustainable pension system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DAI seeks experts available for &lt;strong&gt;short-term assignments&lt;/strong&gt; to support a donor-funded financial sector strengthening project in Ukraine in the following areas:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Financial literacy/consumer protection &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Financial reporting standards/IFRS/XBRL &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pension reform (around Pillars II and III in particular) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Energy market trading &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reform experience with securities/stock market regulators &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Payment systems /digital financial services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Commodity market reform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compliance with EU Directives related to the EU Association Agreement and the Deep and Comprehensive Free Trade Agreement (DCFTA)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compliance/legal and regulatory experience with IOSCO standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a &lt;strong&gt;USAID-funded project&lt;/strong&gt; but the expertise and skills required are closely aligned to those required for EC BENEF Lot 10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:ukraine@dai.com&quot;&gt;ukraine@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experts in Governance and Home Affairs (Cat.II) (one Team leader)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-in-governance-and-home-affairs-catii-one-team-leader</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-in-governance-and-home-affairs-catii-one-team-leader</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final evaluation GENRE I T03.12 - Improving the economic and social situation of women and their families in the Central African Republic&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;overall objective&lt;/strong&gt; of the assignment is to evaluate the Programme &amp;ldquo;Improving the economic and social situation of women and their families in the Central African Republic&amp;rdquo; of the Bêkou EU Trust Fund.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experts in Governance and Home Affairs (Cat.II) (one Team leader)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The experts should have at least a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Social sciences, Development, International relations or other relevant fields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They should have at least 3 years (&lt;strong&gt;6 years for TL&lt;/strong&gt;) professional experience in Governance and Home Affairs, with a focus in Gender, local development and/or income-generating activities. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He/she should have excellent communication and writing skills, be familiar with evaluation techniques and project management. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;team leader&lt;/strong&gt; must also demonstrate strong organisational and coordination skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All team experts must have a proven experience in evaluation techniques and crisis environments. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous work experience in the Central African Republic is an advantage and familiarity with international and EU approaches to resilience, LRRD, development, conflict prevention and peace- building would be a considerable asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experts must be capable of working in a fragile environment and travel under difficult conditions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The evaluation experts must be fluent in French, with excellent writing skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chloe_messenger@dai.com&quot;&gt;chloe_messenger@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Civil society and rule of law/governance/and democracy expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/civil-society-and-rule-of-law-governance-and-democracy-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 20:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/civil-society-and-rule-of-law-governance-and-democracy-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formulation Study: Agents for Citizen-driven Transformation (EU-ACT) Programme&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Objective&lt;/strong&gt;
To assist the National Authorising Officer/EU Delegation in the formulation of a civil support programme under the 11th EDF National Indicative Programme for Nigeria 2014-2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Objective&lt;/strong&gt;
To assist the National Authorising Officer/EU Delegation in the formulation of a civil society support programme, by defining an appropriate basis for the formulation/design of the programme, in accordance with the 11th EDF National Indicative Programme for Nigeria 2014-2020, and relevant EU templates and guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Civil society and rule of law/governance/and democracy expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a University Degree in Political Science, Law, Sociology, Anthropology, Development Studies, International Relations, Public Administration, Medicine, Public Health, Economics, Business, Engineering or directly related discipline, or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in management of projects relating to civil society, democratic governance, and/or related areas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project design and development of logical framework.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific expertise in civil society AND areas directly relating to focal sector 1, 2 or 3 of the 11th EDF NIP, in Sub-Saharan Africa.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Full working knowledge of English, as well as excellent report writing and communication skills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minimum 6 years of professional experience in project management/design/implementation of civil
society, governance, democracy, and/or related, programmes in a developing country context.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minimum 3 years of recent and continuous professional experience in civil society AND areas directly relating to focal sector 1, 2 or 3 of the 11th EDF NIP gained in-country, in Sub-Saharan Africa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minimum 5 years recent and continuous in-country professional experience on civil society in Sub- Saharan Africa, with preference in Nigeria, gained through direct work experience or/and advisory functions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience in human rights based approach to development programming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proven field research and report writing skills;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Civil society sustainable energy and access to electricity expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/civil-society-sustainable-energy-and-access-to-electricity-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 20:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/civil-society-sustainable-energy-and-access-to-electricity-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formulation Study: Agents for Citizen-driven Transformation (EU-ACT) Programme&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Objective&lt;/strong&gt;
To assist the National Authorising Officer/EU Delegation in the formulation of a civil support programme under the 11th EDF National Indicative Programme for Nigeria 2014-2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Objective&lt;/strong&gt;
To assist the National Authorising Officer/EU Delegation in the formulation of a civil society support programme, by defining an appropriate basis for the formulation/design of the programme, in accordance with the 11th EDF National Indicative Programme for Nigeria 2014-2020, and relevant EU templates and guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Civil society sustainable energy and access to electricity expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a University Degree in Political Science, Law, Sociology, Anthropology, Development Studies, International Relations, Public Administration, Medicine, Public Health, Economics, Business, Engineering or directly related discipline, or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in management of projects relating to civil society, democratic governance, and/or related areas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project design and development of logical framework.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific expertise in civil society AND areas directly relating to focal sector 1, 2 or 3 of the 11th EDF NIP, in Sub-Saharan Africa.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Full working knowledge of English, as well as excellent report writing and communication skills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minimum 6 years of professional experience in project management/ design/ implementation of civil society, governance, democracy, and/or related, programmes in a developing country context.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minimum 3 years of recent and continuous professional experience in civil society AND areas directly relating to focal sector 1, 2 or 3 of the 11th EDF NIP gained in-country, in Sub-Saharan Africa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minimum 5 years recent and continuous in-country professional experience on civil society in Sub- Saharan Africa, with preference in Nigeria, gained through direct work experience or/and advisory functions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience in human rights based approach to development programming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proven field research and report writing skills;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Civil society and health/nutrition/resilience expert</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/civil-society-and-health-nutrition-resilience-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 20:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/civil-society-and-health-nutrition-resilience-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formulation Study: Agents for Citizen-driven Transformation (EU-ACT) Programme&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Objective&lt;/strong&gt;
To assist the National Authorising Officer/EU Delegation in the formulation of a civil support programme under the 11th EDF National Indicative Programme for Nigeria 2014-2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Objective&lt;/strong&gt;
To assist the National Authorising Officer/EU Delegation in the formulation of a civil society support programme, by defining an appropriate basis for the formulation/design of the programme, in accordance with the 11th EDF National Indicative Programme for Nigeria 2014-2020, and relevant EU templates and guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Civil society and health/nutrition/resilience expert
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master Degree in Political Science, Law, Sociology, Anthropology, Development Studies, International Relations, Public Administration, Medicine, Public Health, Economics, Business, Engineering, or directly related discipline, or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in leading missions for EU project identification, formulation or evaluation in civil society, democratic governance, and/or related areas in Sub-Saharan Africa.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in civil society AND areas directly related to any of the focal sectors 1, 2 or 3 of the 11th EDF NIP, in Sub-Saharan Africa.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working across different international donor-funded civil society related programmes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of EDF procedures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of gender and development related cross-cutting issues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in needs/risk/stakeholders&amp;#39; analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in project design and development of logical frameworks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full working knowledge of English, as well as excellent report writing and communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 12 years of professional experience in design, implementation and evaluation of civil society programmes in a developing country context.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 5 years of professional experience in civil society AND areas directly related to any of the focal sectors 1, 2 or 3 of the 11th EDF NIP, gained in a county in Sub-Saharan Africa.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific expertise on civil society in developing country context, including on methodologies and support modalities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 years of experience with EDF procedures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in development cooperation in Sub-Saharan Africa.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with international frameworks and standards for civil society effectiveness.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in human rights based approach to development programming.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven field research and report writing skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junior Expert in Gender and Development with experience in Maldives</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-expert-in-gender-and-development-with-experience-in-maldives</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 11:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-expert-in-gender-and-development-with-experience-in-maldives</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sri Lanka and The Maldives Gender Analysis and GAP II Planning&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The gender analysis will provide an understanding on the various types/categories of gender inequalities that persist in Sri Lanka and the Maldives and its causes, including how it intersects with other inequalities, how it impacts on human rights enjoyment and on the benefits produced by development efforts. Further, the analysis will provide an in-depth view of the Governments commitments as reflected in the current legislations and their limitations, if any, and the capacity to work on GEWE issues. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The gender analysis should provide quantitative and qualitative information, sex-age disaggregated data and analysis on the gender situation in the countries in order for the EU Delegation and EU Member States to contribute to the policy dialogue and facilitate the formulation of gender-sensitive strategies and programmes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Junior Expert in Gender and Development with experience in Maldives  – (5 working days)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree or equivalent with relevant work experience in sociology, development studies gender studies or equivalent &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good communication skills, both oral and written &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer literacy (minimum MS Word, Excel, MIS) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 6 years extensive experience in the context of gender and development and/or as a consultant from both short and long-term assignment on gender related studies &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of the development context and gender situation of the Maldives &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience related to gender analysis and/or studies in post-conflict areas and/or issues pertaining to ethnic, cultural and religious issues in the Maldives &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fluency in English and Divehi&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Junior Expert in Gender and Development with experience in Sri Lanka (Category II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-expert-in-gender-and-development-with-experience-in-sri-lanka-category-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 11:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/junior-expert-in-gender-and-development-with-experience-in-sri-lanka-category-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sri Lanka and The Maldives Gender Analysis and GAP II Planning&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The gender analysis will provide an understanding on the various types/categories of gender inequalities that persist in Sri Lanka and the Maldives and its causes, including how it intersects with other inequalities, how it impacts on human rights enjoyment and on the benefits produced by development efforts. Further, the analysis will provide an in-depth view of the Governments commitments as reflected in the current legislations and their limitations, if any, and the capacity to work on GEWE issues. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The gender analysis should provide quantitative and qualitative information, sex-age disaggregated data and analysis on the gender situation in the countries in order for the EU Delegation and EU Member States to contribute to the policy dialogue and facilitate the formulation of gender-sensitive strategies and programmes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Junior Expert in Gender and Development with experience in Sri Lanka (Category II) – (23 working days)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University degree or equivalent with relevant work experience in sociology, development studies gender studies or equivalent &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good communication skills, both oral and written &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer literacy (minimum MS Word, Excel, MIS) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum 6 years extensive experience in the context of gender and development and/or as a consultant from both short and long-term assignment on gender related studies &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive knowledge of the development context and gender situation of Sri Lanka &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Specific professional experience *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience related to gender analysis and/or studies in post-conflict areas and/or issues pertaining to ethnic, cultural and religious diversity in Sri Lanka &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fluency in English and one or preferably both official languages of Sri Lanka namely Sinhala and Tamil&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Social Development and Gender Expert (TL Category I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-social-development-and-gender-expert-tl-category-i</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 11:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-social-development-and-gender-expert-tl-category-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sri Lanka and The Maldives Gender Analysis and GAP II Planning&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The gender analysis will provide an understanding on the various types/categories of gender inequalities that persist in Sri Lanka and the Maldives and its causes, including how it intersects with other inequalities, how it impacts on human rights enjoyment and on the benefits produced by development efforts. Further, the analysis will provide an in-depth view of the Governments commitments as reflected in the current legislations and their limitations, if any, and the capacity to work on GEWE issues. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objective&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The gender analysis should provide quantitative and qualitative information, sex-age disaggregated data and analysis on the gender situation in the countries in order for the EU Delegation and EU Member States to contribute to the policy dialogue and facilitate the formulation of gender-sensitive strategies and programmes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Social Development and Gender Expert (TL Category I) – (38 working days)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification and skills&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Postgraduate university degree or equivalent with relevant work experience in development studies, social development, gender studies or equivalent; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong writing and communication skills; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer literacy (minimum MS Word, Excel, Power Point Presentations). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 12 years’ experience in social development and gender analysis &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific experience and expertise on gender analysis, gender mainstreaming and women&amp;rsquo;s participation is mandatory &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Up-to-date and comprehensive knowledge and experience of EU development, policies, instruments and facilities especially on gender, is considered mandatory &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience of working on national gender policies in developing countries &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working in South Asia and Sri Lanka being desirable &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organisational development and capacity building experience &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of international/regional agreements and initiatives on gender (UN, CEDAW, Beijing, etc.) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in managing a team of experts &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience related to post-conflict contexts and ethnic, cultural and religious diversity situations &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience of EU practices in development programmes related to the sector of reconciliation, rural development, and good governance. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fluency in English with proven oral and written skills&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 3, Spécialiste en SIG, Catégorie I </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-3-specialiste-en-sig-categorie-i</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2016 07:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-3-specialiste-en-sig-categorie-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formulation PIR/Pastoralisme&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif général&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apporter une assistance technique à l’identification et à la formulation du sous-programme Pastoralisme et transhumance du PIR 11e FED. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectifs spécifiques&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proposer et argumenter le choix dans le PRIDEC de la ou des parties correspondant le mieux aux priorités de la CEDEAO et de l’UEMOA en matière de transhumance et pastoralisme, et au concept du sous-programme Pastoralisme et transhumance du PIR 11e FED. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formuler le Document d’Action/Identification. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formuler le Document d’Action/Formulation qui sera la base de la convention de financement du programme.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt; : 240 days&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 3, Spécialiste en SIG, Catégorie I&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spécialiste des systèmes d’information géographique (SIG), possédant les diplômes supérieurs appropriés : géographie, informatique, etc. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert avec un minimum de 12 années d’expérience, disposant d’une compétence en géographie et en informatique appliquées au développement, avec un minimum de 3 missions de planification, mise en oeuvre ou suivi/évaluation des politiques agricoles durables. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Il dispose d&amp;#39;une compétence démontrée dans au moins 3 projets dans le domaine de la politique agricole durable. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exigences minimales&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Il dispose d’une bonne expérience en matière d&amp;#39;appui institutionnel et organisationnel dans le secteur agricole et rural avec un minimum de 5 années d’expérience professionnelle dans le secteur de l&amp;#39;appui institutionnel. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expertise en SIG pour le développement rural, la planification et le suivi est nécessaire. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Il maîtrise le cycle des projets de développement. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Il dispose d&amp;#39;une expérience en Afrique subsaharienne. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exigences préférentielles&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seront considérés comme des atouts une expérience en pastoralisme, en décentralisation, et en commerce transfrontalier en Afrique. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;expert prestera au maximum 70 jours selon la répartition indicative suivante : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;54 jours dans 6pays sur les 8 concernés ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;16 jours au lieu de résidence pour la documentation et la rédaction des rapports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;corinamaria_campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 2, Expert en politique de l’élevage, Catégorie I</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-expert-en-politique-de-lelevage-categorie-i</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2016 07:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-expert-en-politique-de-lelevage-categorie-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formulation PIR/Pastoralisme&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif général&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apporter une assistance technique à l’identification et à la formulation du sous-programme Pastoralisme et transhumance du PIR 11e FED. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectifs spécifiques&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Proposer et argumenter le choix dans le PRIDEC de la ou des parties correspondant le mieux aux priorités de la CEDEAO et de l’UEMOA en matière de transhumance et pastoralisme, et au concept du sous-programme Pastoralisme et transhumance du PIR 11e FED. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formuler le Document d’Action/Identification. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3Formuler le Document d’Action/Formulation qui sera la base de la convention de financement du programme.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt; : 240 days&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2, Expert en politique de l’élevage, Catégorie I&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spécialiste des politiques publiques de l’élevage et en santé animale (gouvernance vétérinaire, épizooties, zoonoses et contrôle des maladies animales transfrontalières), hautement qualifié, possédant les diplômes supérieurs appropriés dans un des domaines suivants : zootechnie, science vétérinaire, développement rural, administration publique et/ou diplôme lié à la politique publique. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert avec un minimum de 12 années d’expérience dans les politiques publiques de l’élevage, en gouvernance vétérinaire et santé animale, dont 5 ans en Afrique subsaharienne. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Il dispose d&amp;#39;une compétence avérée (au moins 3 projets) dans la gestion et les réformes du secteur public, les politiques communautaires en Afrique, et le développement institutionnel régional. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Il dispose d&amp;#39;une compétence démontrée (au moins 3 projets) de formulation et/ou d&amp;#39;évaluation de programmes d’appui à l’élevage et dans le domaine de la gouvernance vétérinaire, et a effectué au moins 3 missions de planification, mise en oeuvre ou suivi-évaluation des politiques de transhumance et de pastoralisme. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exigences minimales&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Il possède une bonne connaissance, acquise en Afrique subsaharienne, des finances publiques, de la socio-économie, du partenariat public-privé avec les organisations professionnelles et les organisations de la société civile en élevage. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Il dispose d’une expertise en surveillance épidémiologique et d’une expérience de 5 ans au moins en appui institutionnel et organisationnel dans le secteur de la prévention et de la lutte contre les maladies animales transfrontalières. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Il maîtrise le cycle des projets de développement. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Il dispose d&amp;#39;une expérience en Afrique de l’ouest. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exigences préférentielles&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seront considérés comme des atouts une expérience en pastoralisme, en décentralisation, en commerce transfrontalier en Afrique, et en procédures du FED régional. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;expert prestera au maximum 70 jours selon la répartition indicative suivante : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;54 jours dans 6pays sur les 8 concernés ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;16 jours au lieu de résidence pour la documentation et la rédaction des rapports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;corinamaria_campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef de mission. Expert 1, Pastoraliste, Catégorie</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-expert-1-pastoraliste-categorie</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2016 07:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-expert-1-pastoraliste-categorie</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formulation PIR/Pastoralisme&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif général :&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apporter une assistance technique à l’identification et à la formulation du sous-programme Pastoralisme et transhumance du PIR 11e FED. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Objectifs spécifiques :
*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proposer et argumenter le choix dans le PRIDEC de la ou des parties correspondant le mieux aux priorités de la CEDEAO et de l’UEMOA en matière de transhumance et pastoralisme, et au concept du sous-programme Pastoralisme et transhumance du PIR 11e FED. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formuler le Document d’Action/Identification. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formuler le Document d’Action/Formulation qui sera la base de la convention de financement du programme.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 240 days&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Chef de mission. Expert 1, Pastoraliste, Catégorie I *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spécialiste du pastoralisme et de la transhumance, notamment transfrontalière, hautement qualifié, possédant les diplômes supérieurs appropriés dans un des domaines suivants : zootechnie, science vétérinaire, agronomie, géographie, environnement, développement rural et/ou diplôme lié au pastoralisme. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expert avec un minimum de 12 années d’expérience dans des projets de développement, dont 5 ans en Afrique subsaharienne, et disposant d’une compétence avérée dans au moins 3 projets dans le domaine du pastoralisme et de la transhumance, et une compétence relative à l&amp;#39;aide européenne. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exigences minimales&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Il dispose d&amp;#39;une expertise avérée dans au moins 3 pays ouest-africains (sahéliens et côtiers) sur les meilleures pratiques favorisant le pastoralisme et la transhumance : alimentation et soin des ruminants, différents biotopes pastoraux en Afrique, types de pasteurs, types de mobilité des troupeaux, organisation professionnelle des éleveurs et des agriculteurs, filières bétail-viande, etc. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Il dispose également d’une bonne expérience en matière d&amp;#39;appui institutionnel et organisationnel dans le secteur rural avec au moins 5 ans d’expérience professionnelle dans le domaine de l&amp;#39;appui institutionnel. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Il possède une expérience en procédures du FED. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Il maîtrise le cycle des projets de développement. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exigences préférentielles :&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seront considérés comme des atouts une expérience en décentralisation, en commerce transfrontalier en Afrique, et en procédures du FED régional. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L&amp;#39;expert prestera au maximum 70 jours selon la répartition indicative suivante : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;54 jours dans 6 pays sur les 8 concernés ; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;16 jours au lieu de résidence pour la documentation et la rédaction des rapports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;corinamaria_campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Administrative Assistant – Expertise in IT &amp; Databases used for CfP</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/administrative-assistant-expertise-in-it-databases-used-for-cfp</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 16:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/administrative-assistant-expertise-in-it-databases-used-for-cfp</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to the assessment of proposals received under the PanAf CSO call for proposals&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GLOBAL OBJECTIVE&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To recruit assessors to assist the European Commission in the evaluation and selection of the best proposals received under EuropeAid/150550/DH/ACT/Multi and to achieve a high quality, complete and coherent selection process of projects in line with the criteria set in the guidelines for grant applicants. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPECIFIC OBJECTIVE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To provide technical support to the services of the European Commission in order to reach the global objective, as regards both the technical and the financial assessment of the proposals received.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 200 days&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Administrative Assistant – Expertise in IT &amp;amp; Databases used for CfP&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be IT proficient and master the use of the usual IT applications (word processors, spreadsheets, databases and email); &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a work experience in a multicultural environment could be considered an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have working knowledge of IT systems and databases used in the processing of calls for proposals and administrative/eligibility assessment experience will be considered an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be proficient in English and have good command of French. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com 
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Assessors – Junior Experts with Experience related to one of Thematic Lots of CfP + EU Development Policy</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/8-assessors-junior-experts-with-experience-related-to-one-of-thematic-lots-of-cfp-eu-development-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 16:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/8-assessors-junior-experts-with-experience-related-to-one-of-thematic-lots-of-cfp-eu-development-policy</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to the assessment of proposals received under the PanAf CSO call for proposals&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GLOBAL OBJECTIVE&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To recruit assessors to assist the European Commission in the evaluation and selection of the best proposals received under EuropeAid/150550/DH/ACT/Multi and to achieve a high quality, complete and coherent selection process of projects in line with the criteria set in the guidelines for grant applicants. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPECIFIC OBJECTIVE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To provide technical support to the services of the European Commission in order to reach the global objective, as regards both the technical and the financial assessment of the proposals received.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 200 days&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8 Assessors – Junior Experts with Experience related to one of Thematic Lots of CfP + EU Development Policy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each assessor must: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold a university level education in Law, Political Sciences, International Relations, Development Studies or other relevant subject; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a junior expert with at least 3 years of professional experience related to – at least- one thematic lots of the call for proposals (democracy, governance, human rights, peace and security issues and gender issues), involvement of civil society organisations and other related topics; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have knowledge of EU development policy; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have experience in project management and/or monitoring experience; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be proficient in English and have good command of French with ability to read proposals and review quality of proposals assessments; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in assessing proposals submitted under European Union calls for proposals will be considered an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work experience in developing countries and in particularly in Africa will be considered an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Co-Ordinator. Senior Expert in Civil Society or Areas covered by CfP and EU Policies/Programmes</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/co-ordinator-senior-expert-in-civil-society-or-areas-covered-by-cfp-and-eu-policies-programmes</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 16:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/co-ordinator-senior-expert-in-civil-society-or-areas-covered-by-cfp-and-eu-policies-programmes</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support to the assessment of proposals received under the PanAf CSO call for proposals&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;GLOBAL OBJECTIVE *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To recruit assessors to assist the European Commission in the evaluation and selection of the best proposals received under EuropeAid/150550/DH/ACT/Multi and to achieve a high quality, complete and coherent selection process of projects in line with the criteria set in the guidelines for grant applicants. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPECIFIC OBJECTIVE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To provide technical support to the services of the European Commission in order to reach the global objective, as regards both the technical and the financial assessment of the proposals received.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 200 days&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Co-Ordinator. Senior Expert in Civil Society or Areas covered by CfP and EU Policies/Programmes&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold a University level education in Law, Political Sciences, International Relations, Development Studies or other relevant subject; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a senior expert with at least 10 years of professional experience related to one or more of the areas covered by the call for proposals (democracy, governance, human rights, peace and security issues and gender issues), involvement of civil society organisations and other related topics; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have knowledge of EU policies and programmes, particularly in the area of democracy, human rights, peace and security and gender; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have team management, project management and/or monitoring and coordination experience; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be proficient in English and have good command of French with ability to read proposals and review quality of proposals assessments; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience as coordinator in evaluation of calls for proposals will be considered an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have working knowledge of IT systems and databases used in the processing of calls for proposals and administrative/eligibility assessment experience will be considered an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work experience in developing countries and in particularly in African countries will be considered an asset; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the work of the institutions/organs of the African Union will be considered an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;CorinaMaria_Campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Integrated Coastal Zone Management and Climate Change Policy </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-integrated-coastal-zone-management-and-climate-change-policy</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 20:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-integrated-coastal-zone-management-and-climate-change-policy</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Evaluation of the GCCA Support Project to the Gambia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall objective of this project is to contribute to the capability of the government and people of The Gambia to adapt to increased climate variability and change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Integrated Coastal Zone Management and Climate Change Policy (Cat. I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree of equivalent in the area relevant to the assignments such as environmental sciences, climate change, management of natural resources, land management and planning, geography or economy or relevant professional experience of 3 years duration (above the general professional experience below);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;General professional experience of at least 12 years in an area relevant to the assignment;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven international experience with evaluations, sector assessment, project/programme planning and execution and development exercises in the field of Integrated Coastal Zone Management and Climate Change Policy;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An experience in the EU sector policies and strategic orientations and practical knowledge of the EU cooperation in the area relevant to the assignment;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiences in least developed countries with fragile institutional context;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;Veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spécialiste Senior de l’environnement </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/specialiste-senior-de-lenvironnement</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 07:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/specialiste-senior-de-lenvironnement</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Assistance technique a l&amp;#39;ordonnateur regional pour la programmation du 11eme FED des PTOM de la region Pacifique
*&lt;/em&gt;
La mission principale sera d’assister la Nouvelle-Calédonie en tant qu’OR à l’élaboration du projet de Document de Programmation, ainsi que la signature de la convention de financement. Cette tâche sera effectuée avec la collaboration de toutes les parties impliquées dans la préparation du Document de Programmation et dans le respect des principes et procédures du 11° FED prévus dans la DAO et dans les instructions de programmation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif global&lt;/strong&gt;
L’objectif principal de la mission est de fournir une assistance technique à la Nouvelle Calédonie en tant qu’OR lors de la phase de préparation des documents prévus pour la programmation des ressources allouées aux PTOM du Pacifique au titre du 11ème FED (enveloppe régionale) ; il s’agit en particulier de la préparation, de l’élaboration et de la rédaction du document de programmation jusqu’à son approbation formelle par les services de la Commission européenne, et de la convention de financement afférente 
Le programme régional du Pacifique devra prendre en compte l’impact régional des interventions, les études et lorsque cela est pertinent les projets qui sont ou seront mis en oeuvre dans ce contexte.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectifs spécifiques&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;Objectif 1&lt;/strong&gt; : Faciliter la définition et formuler des recommandations pour la programmation, la conception, la gestion, la mise en oeuvre, le suivi et l’évaluation du programme régional, dans le cadre du 11ème FED 
&lt;strong&gt;Objectif 2&lt;/strong&gt; : Faciliter l’organisation des consultations nécessaires dans le cadre du « comité régional de pilotage de la programmation » (CRPP), et avec les pays du groupe ACP du Pacifique et les organisations régionales mandatées (« Duly Mandated Regional Organisations »), tout au long du processus de programmation et en particulier dans le cadre du montage du programme (en préparation des résultats attendus dans la section 2.4). 
&lt;strong&gt;Objectif 3&lt;/strong&gt; : Produire et garantir la qualité et la conformité de l’ensemble des composantes du document de programmation du 11ème FED régional PTOM - Océan Pacifique (partie A, Document d&amp;#39;Action lors de la phase d&amp;#39;identification, partie B – Document d&amp;#39;Action lors de la phase de formulation), y inclus ses annexes, au regard de la règlementation européenne applicable. 
&lt;strong&gt;Objectif 4&lt;/strong&gt; : Produire et garantir la qualité et la conformité du projet de la convention de financement du 11ème FED entre l’Union européenne et la Nouvelle Calédonie en tant qu’OR concernant le programme régional, y inclus ses annexes (et notamment).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Location&lt;/strong&gt;: Nouvelle-Calédonie, Wallis et Futuna et Polynésie Française, Nouvelle Zélande, Fidji &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spécialiste de l’environnement&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formation&lt;/strong&gt;:
Niveau Master en environnement, sciences de l’environnement ou droit de l’environnement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:
&lt;strong&gt;Prérequis&lt;/strong&gt; : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au minimum 12 années d’expérience dans le domaine des politiques publiques en matière d’environnement et du changement climatique &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissances et expériences dans le domaine de l’environnement et la gestion des ressources naturelles, le changement climatique et la prévention des risques de catastrophes naturelles &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Si possible connaissance du contexte naturel, culturel et politique des PTOM européens du Pacifique et de l&amp;#39;environnement socio-culturel océanien &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance des outils informatiques &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aptitude à évaluer la capacité institutionnelle des institutions impliquées dans la mise en oeuvre de programmes de développement &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Langue&lt;/strong&gt;:
*&lt;em&gt;Exigée *&lt;/em&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parfait maîtrise du français, lu, écrit et parlé. La langue de cette mission est le français &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne connaissance de la langue anglaise lu, écrite et parlée &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;corinamaria_campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spécialiste de la planification et la gestion de projet et de la coopération régionale </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/specialiste-de-la-planification-et-la-gestion-de-projet-et-de-la-cooperation-regionale</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/specialiste-de-la-planification-et-la-gestion-de-projet-et-de-la-cooperation-regionale</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assistance technique a l&amp;#39;ordonnateur regional pour la programmation du 11eme FED des PTOM de la region Pacifique (Cat.I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La mission principale sera d’assister la Nouvelle-Calédonie en tant qu’OR à l’élaboration du projet de Document de Programmation, ainsi que la signature de la convention de financement. Cette tâche sera effectuée avec la collaboration de toutes les parties impliquées dans la préparation du Document de Programmation et dans le respect des principes et procédures du 11° FED prévus dans la DAO et dans les instructions de programmation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectif global&lt;/strong&gt;
L’objectif principal de la mission est de fournir une assistance technique à la Nouvelle Calédonie en tant qu’OR lors de la phase de préparation des documents prévus pour la programmation des ressources allouées aux PTOM du Pacifique au titre du 11ème FED (enveloppe régionale) ; il s’agit en particulier de la préparation, de l’élaboration et de la rédaction du document de programmation jusqu’à son approbation formelle par les services de la Commission européenne, et de la convention de financement afférente 
Le programme régional du Pacifique devra prendre en compte l’impact régional des interventions, les études et lorsque cela est pertinent les projets qui sont ou seront mis en oeuvre dans ce contexte.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectifs spécifiques&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;strong&gt;Objectif 1&lt;/strong&gt; : Faciliter la définition et formuler des recommandations pour la programmation, la conception, la gestion, la mise en oeuvre, le suivi et l’évaluation du programme régional, dans le cadre du 11ème FED 
&lt;strong&gt;Objectif 2&lt;/strong&gt; : Faciliter l’organisation des consultations nécessaires dans le cadre du « comité régional de pilotage de la programmation » (CRPP), et avec les pays du groupe ACP du Pacifique et les organisations régionales mandatées (« Duly Mandated Regional Organisations »), tout au long du processus de programmation et en particulier dans le cadre du montage du programme (en préparation des résultats attendus dans la section 2.4). 
&lt;strong&gt;Objectif 3&lt;/strong&gt; : Produire et garantir la qualité et la conformité de l’ensemble des composantes du document de programmation du 11ème FED régional PTOM - Océan Pacifique (partie A, Document d&amp;#39;Action lors de la phase d&amp;#39;identification, partie B – Document d&amp;#39;Action lors de la phase de formulation), y inclus ses annexes, au regard de la règlementation européenne applicable. 
&lt;strong&gt;Objectif 4&lt;/strong&gt; : Produire et garantir la qualité et la conformité du projet de la convention de financement du 11ème FED entre l’Union européenne et la Nouvelle Calédonie en tant qu’OR concernant le programme régional, y inclus ses annexes (et notamment)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Location&lt;/strong&gt;: Nouvelle-Calédonie, Wallis et Futuna et Polynésie Française, Nouvelle Zélande, Fidji &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Spécialiste de la planification et la gestion de projet et de la coopération régionale *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formation&lt;/strong&gt;:
Niveau Master en gestion de projets et/ou coopération et/ou intégration régionale et/ou développement international &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience&lt;/strong&gt;:
*&lt;em&gt;Prérequis *&lt;/em&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au minimum 12 années d’expérience dans le domaine des politiques publiques et des relations internationales &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance accrue des politiques d’environnement, sciences de l’environnement, droit de l’environnement &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance et expérience dans le domaine des procédures européennes notamment du FED, et du cycle de gestion de projet &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance du contexte naturel, culturel, politique des PTOM européens du Pacifique &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance des outils informatiques &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aptitude à évaluer la capacité institutionnelle des institutions impliquées dans la mise en oeuvre de programmes de développement &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance des PTOM et de l&amp;#39;environnement socio-culturel océanien &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience réussie dans au moins 5 missions de ce type &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en communication et en interaction avec des acteurs variés : gouvernement, organisations régionales, ONG, associations, etc &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Langue&lt;/strong&gt;:
*&lt;em&gt;Exigée *&lt;/em&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parfait maîtrise du français, lu, écrit et parlé. La langue de cette mission est le français. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne connaissance de la langue anglaise lu, écrite et parlée &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:corinamaria_campian@dai.com&quot;&gt;corinamaria_campian@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
