<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 14:08:02 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of Social Services Delivery</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/analysis-of-social-services-delivery</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 13:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/analysis-of-social-services-delivery</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To contribute to the analytical work of the sector of social services delivery in Armenia, and to contribute to a new EU intervention in this field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific objectives:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To produce an analysis of the state of the social services delivery in Armenia (strategy, actors, funding, decision-making, coverage, statistical data, active donors);&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To support the Ministry of Labour and Social Affairs with the strategic policy direction in this sector, and the EU Delegation with the identification of a new EU-funded action in this area&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Social Services Delivery (TL)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant University Degree in the field of social sciences, political science, public administration, economics, or relevant field;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent English, oral and written.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least 10 years of a wide international experience in the field of social services delivery. Previous experience with EU-funded projects is not required. Previous experience in the region is also not required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experience  in  formulating  developmental  programs in  the  field  of  social  services  delivery would be an asset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;agnese_ortolani@dai.com&quot;&gt;Agnese_Ortolani@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
