<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 13:50:34 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>KE2 Expert in Sustainable Development, NRM or Environment (Cat 2)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/ke2-expert-in-sustainable-development-nrm-or-environment-cat-2</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 13:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/ke2-expert-in-sustainable-development-nrm-or-environment-cat-2</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ex-post Evaluation of the project &amp;lsquo;Support for the Implementation of Mauritius Strategy for Small Islands Developing States in the ESA-IO Region&amp;rsquo; project (also known as ISLANDS Phase I &amp;amp; II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective of the evaluation&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of the ex-post evaluation of the ISLANDS Programme is to provide the IOC and the European Union, with necessary information on the performance of the project, both under Phase I and Phase II.  These results will be used in the formulation and implementation of an 11 the EDF project under the Eastern and South African and Indian ocean region Regional Indicative Programme for island developing states.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This evaluation will serve to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Make an overall independent assessment about the past performance of the project, paying particular attention to the efficiency and effectiveness of the project actions against its objectives, as well as indications of impacts and outcomes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify key lessons learnt and propose practical recommendations for followup actions that can be included in the new 11th EDF regional project on SIDS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Validate the final findings of the ex-post evaluation with relevant stakeholders (National Focal Points of countries covered, IOC Secretariat and EU)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific aspects to be evaluated&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The consultants are requested to verify, analyse and assess the integration and impact of cross cutting issue in the project, in particular gender equality and protection of the environment.  The consultants are required to use their professional judgement and experience to review all relevant factors and to bring these to the attention of the IOC and European Union.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KE2 Expert in Sustainable Development, NRM or Environment (Cat 2)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum requirements of the team&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Educational qualifications at Masters’ level in environment, or sustainable development, or natural resource management &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience in evaluation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience in climate change and sustainable development &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least one member of the team should have working experience in Sustainable Development Goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least one member of the team should have working experience in Small Island State issues &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least one member of the team should have good knowledge of the Eastern and Southern African and Indian Ocean region&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills of the team&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in written and spoken English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in written and spoken French&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please apply via the following link, sumbitting your CV in EC format &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/requisitions/RequisitionView.jsp?act=view&amp;amp;id=3760&amp;amp;et=REQU&amp;amp;actionId=1&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/requisitions/RequisitionView.jsp?act=view&amp;amp;id=3760&amp;amp;et=REQU&amp;amp;actionId=1&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KE1 Team Leader (Cat 1)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/ke1-team-leader-cat-1</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 13:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/ke1-team-leader-cat-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ex-post Evaluation of the project &amp;lsquo;Support for the Implementation of Mauritius Strategy for Small Islands Developing States in the ESA-IO Region&amp;rsquo; project (also known as ISLANDS Phase I &amp;amp; II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global objective of the evaluation&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The global objective of the ex-post evaluation of the ISLANDS Programme is to provide the IOC and the European Union, with necessary information on the performance of the project, both under Phase I and Phase II.  These results will be used in the formulation and implementation of an 11 the EDF project under the Eastern and South African and Indian ocean region Regional Indicative Programme for island developing states.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This evaluation will serve to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make an overall independent assessment about the past performance of the project, paying particular attention to the efficiency and effectiveness of the project actions against its objectives, as well as indications of impacts and outcomes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify key lessons learnt and propose practical recommendations for followup actions that can be included in the new 11th EDF regional project on SIDS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Validate the final findings of the ex-post evaluation with relevant stakeholders (National Focal Points of countries covered, IOC Secretariat and EU)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific aspects to be evaluated&lt;/strong&gt; 
The consultants are requested to verify, analyse and assess the integration and impact of cross cutting issue in the project, in particular gender equality and protection of the environment.  The consultants are required to use their professional judgement and experience to review all relevant factors and to bring these to the attention of the IOC and European Union&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KE1 Team Leader (Cat 1)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum requirements of the team  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Educational qualifications at masters level in environment, or sustainable development,or natural resource management &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience in evaluation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working experience in climate change and sustainable development &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least one member of the team should have working experience in Sustainable Development Goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least one member of the team should have working experience in Small Island State issues &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;at least one member of the team should have good knowledge of the Eastern and Southern African and Indian Ocean region&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills of the team&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in written and spoken English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in written and spoken French&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please apply via the following link, submitting your CV in EC format &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/requisitions/RequisitionView.jsp?act=view&amp;amp;id=3760&amp;amp;et=REQU&amp;amp;actionId=1&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/requisitions/RequisitionView.jsp?act=view&amp;amp;id=3760&amp;amp;et=REQU&amp;amp;actionId=1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert 2 – Catégorie II, Evaluation Finale de la Decision AO/FED/2009/21 - 626</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-categorie-ii-evaluation-finale-de-la-decision-ao-fed-2009-21-626</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 13:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-2-categorie-ii-evaluation-finale-de-la-decision-ao-fed-2009-21-626</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation Finale de la Decision AO/FED/2009/21 - 626&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cette évaluation est principalement vouée à fournir aux services compétents de l’Union Européenne et aux parties prenantes intéressées:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une analyse globale et indépendante de la performance de la décision AO/FED/2009/21-626 “Développement des capacités institutionnelles dans le cadre de la modernisation de la fonction publique en matière de planification en Angola”, en prêtant une attention particulière a ses résultats en comparaison avec les objectifs fixes ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Des leçons et des recommandations de manière à améliorer, le cas échéant, les actions futures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;En particulier, cette évaluation servira à comprendre la performance de l’action, ses facteurs déterminants et ceux qui ont freiné l’obtention des résultats aussi bien que les perspectives de durabilité de ses résultats, de manière ont server de base à la planification des actions et des interventions futures de l’UE dans le même secteur.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les principaux utilisateurs de cette évaluation seront la délégation de l’UE en Angola, les services compétents de l’UE a Bruxelles, le Ministère de l’Economie et du Plan de la République d’Angola &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2 – Catégorie II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formation académique de niveau universitaire, de préférence en sciences sociales, économie, science politique, ou autre discipline pertinente ou équivalente. Une spécialisation dans le domaine de l’évaluation et gestion de projets sera considérée un avantage ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle en gestion et/ou évaluation de projets de développement de minimum 5 ans. Une expérience dans les pays ACP sera considérée un avantage;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle en tant qu’évaluateur de projets de développement (minimum 5 évaluations) ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience et connaissances des politiques, règles et procédures de gestion des financements du FED ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience préalable en Angola en tant qu’expert en évaluations sera considérée un avantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellente maitrise du portugais, lu, parlé, écrit (le rapport final devra être rédigé en portugais)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne connaissance de l’anglais et/ou du français lus, écrits, parlés.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef de mission, Evaluation Finale de la Decision AO/FED/2009/21 - 626</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 13:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation Finale de la Decision AO/FED/2009/21 - 626&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cette évaluation est principalement vouée à fournir aux services compétents de l’Union Européenne et aux parties prenantes intéressées:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une analyse globale et indépendante de la performance de la décision AO/FED/2009/21-626 “Développement des capacités institutionnelles dans le cadre de la modernisation de la fonction publique en matière de planification en Angola”, en prêtant une attention particulière a ses résultats en comparaison avec les objectifs fixes ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Des leçons et des recommandations de manière à améliorer, le cas échéant, les actions futures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;En particulier, cette évaluation servira à comprendre la performance de l’action, ses facteurs déterminants et ceux qui ont freiné l’obtention des résultats aussi bien que les perspectives de durabilité de ses résultats, de manière ont server de base à la planification des actions et des interventions futures de l’UE dans le même secteur.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les principaux utilisateurs de cette évaluation seront la délégation de l’UE en Angola, les services compétents de l’UE a Bruxelles, le Ministère de l’Economie et du Plan de la République d’Angola &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chef de mission – Catégorie I&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formation académique de niveau universitaire, de préférence en sciences sociales, économie, science politique, ou autre discipline pertinente ou équivalente ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle en gestion et/ou évaluation de projets de développement de minimum 10 ans, dont 3 ans dans des pays ACP ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle en tant qu’évaluateur et coordinateur de minimum 10 évaluations de projets. L’évaluation de projets dans le domaine de la réforme institutionnelle et d’appui aux services de l’ON du FED sera considérée un avantage ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance approfondie des politiques, règles et procédures de gestion des financements du FED ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Forte capacité analytique et de synthèse ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience préalable en Angola en tant qu’expert en évaluations sera considérée un avantage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellente maitrise du portugais, lu, parlé, écrit (le rapport final devra être rédigé en portugais)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne connaissance de l’anglais et/ou du français lus, écrits, parlés.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert in Public Health, Monitoring and Evaluation</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-public-health-monitoring-and-evaluation</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 12:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-in-public-health-monitoring-and-evaluation</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation of the Programme in support for the Health Sector II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The consultants will provide clear advice on the Program´s outcomes and the sustainability of the actions and tools developed as part of PASS II. He will conduct a sound analysis of the Program within the health sector in Angola in order to assess key factors influencing sustainability issues and produce recommendations to reinforce the sustainability and the ownership by MINSA.  They will assess the effectiveness of the Program´s interventions in achieving the goal and objectives set in the original Financing Agreement, which are: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Overall objective: to contribute to improved health conditions of the population, especially women and children, with a focus in the provinces of Huambo, Bié, Benguela, Huíla e Luanda. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific objectives: 1: To strengthen MOH capacity, at central level, in strategic and operational planning, budgeting, organization of the health system, training and management of Human Resources for Health, coordination, advocacy and monitoring and evaluation; 2: To strengthen Provincial Health Directorates capacity and leadership in planning, budgeting, development of the health system (including training and management of HRH) and management of activities, in accordance with the ongoing administrative decentralization and the Revitalization of the Municipal Health System processes; 3: To improve the accessibility and quality of the basic package of health services provided to the population at municipal level, by reinforcing the availability of good quality essential maternal, newborn and children health services, with a specific focus in the provinces of Huambo, Bie, Benguela, Huíla and Luanda.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert in Public Health, Monitoring and Evaluation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6-year experience in Public Health, Monitoring and Evaluation. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MSc in Public Health, Public Administration, or equivalent from a recognized University.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience of at least 6 years as Monitoring and Evaluation consultant in the public health sector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with at least 2 different organizations in conducting evaluations and assessments of public health interventions. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Background working in post conflict environments and fragile states in the health sector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with EU funded programs: EDF, Global Budget, etc. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity and experience with EU programs of support to the health sector. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong interpersonal communications and writing skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical and synthesis skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Negotiation skills to develop consensus around policy strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in Portuguese &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent Portuguese written skills / English written skills desirable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:almudena_salmeron@dai.com&quot;&gt;Almudena_Salmeron@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:fwcsieaLot4@dai.com&quot;&gt;FWCSIEALot4@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; in cc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Public Health, Health Policy and Planning</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-public-health-health-policy-and-planning</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 11:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-public-health-health-policy-and-planning</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation of the Programme in support for the Health Sector II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The consultants will provide clear advice on the Program´s outcomes and the sustainability of the actions and tools developed as part of PASS II. He will conduct a sound analysis of the Program within the health sector in Angola in order to assess key factors influencing sustainability issues and produce recommendations to reinforce the sustainability and the ownership by MINSA.  They will assess the effectiveness of the Program´s interventions in achieving the goal and objectives set in the original Financing Agreement, which are: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Overall objective: to contribute to improved health conditions of the population, especially women and children, with a focus in the provinces of Huambo, Bié, Benguela, Huíla e Luanda. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific objectives: 1: To strengthen MOH capacity, at central level, in strategic and operational planning, budgeting, organization of the health system, training and management of Human Resources for Health, coordination, advocacy and monitoring and evaluation; 2: To strengthen Provincial Health Directorates capacity and leadership in planning, budgeting, development of the health system (including training and management of HRH) and management of activities, in accordance with the ongoing administrative decentralization and the Revitalization of the Municipal Health System processes; 3: To improve the accessibility and quality of the basic package of health services provided to the population at municipal level, by reinforcing the availability of good quality essential maternal, newborn and children health services, with a specific focus in the provinces of Huambo, Bie, Benguela, Huíla and Luanda.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Public Health, Health Policy and Planning&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12-year experience in Public Health.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MSc in Public Health, Health Policy and Planning, Health Services Management, or equivalent from a recognized University.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience of at least 12 years as public health expert / consultant in developing countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with at least 3 different organizations in conducting health systems reviews, health sector reforms, strategic planning and health services evaluations. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Background working in post conflict environments and fragile states in the health sector.Experience working with EU funded programs: EDF, Global Budget, etc. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience in Angola. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity and experience with EU programs of support to the health sector in Angola and other countries. Strong analytical and synthesis skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Negotiation skills to develop consensus around policy strategies. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent leadership skills, ability to exercise a significant degree of initiative and to work effectively with stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work with individuals and teams in completing tasks that are urgent, high priority and sensitive, and ability to deliver high quality work on tight timelines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong interpersonal communications and writing skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in Portuguese.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent Portuguese written skills / English written skills desirable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:almudena_salmeron@dai.com&quot;&gt;Almudena_Salmeron@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:fwciealot4@dai.com&quot;&gt;FWCSIEALot4@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; in cc.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert technique en services d&#39;appui à l&#39;industrie</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-technique-en-services-dappui-a-lindustrie</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 08:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/expert-technique-en-services-dappui-a-lindustrie</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assistance technique pour la mise en oeuvre de la reforme des centres techniques sectoriels en Tunisie&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contribuer au développement des performances des centres techniques sectoriels en les rendant à même d’assumer convenablement leur rôle de soutien et de développement du secteur industriel et d’être des contributeurs efficaces et reconnus au renforcement de l’industrie tunisienne.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert technique en services d&amp;#39;appui à l&amp;#39;industrie&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire dans un domaine pertinent (ingénieur, gestion ou équivalent), ou expérience équivalente (minimum 2 ans en plus des 12 ans demandés ci-dessous).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle d&amp;#39;au moins 12 ans au sein de structures publiques ou privées d&amp;#39;appui technologique à l’industrie avec un degré croissant de responsabilité technique (Management, organisation, planification et contrôle des activités d&amp;#39;une équipe d&amp;#39;expert).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;incluant une expérience pratique dans l’élaboration et la production des documents de planification et de budget d&amp;#39;investissements;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avoir des aptitudes à communiquer et à animer des réunions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ayant une expérience d&amp;#39;au moins 3 ans dans des postes de chef de département technique au sein de centres techniques ou des institutions similaires.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ayant animé au moins un séminaire/atelier pour un auditoire non spécialisé.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience de travail en Tunisie ou dans un pays du voisinage sud.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonne connaissance de la langue française parlée et écrite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:almudena_salmeron@dai.com&quot;&gt;Almudena_Salmeron@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef de mission, expert en management d&#39;institutions d&#39;appui technologique à l&#39;industrie</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-expert-en-management-dinstitutions-dappui-technologique-a-lindustrie</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 07:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/chef-de-mission-expert-en-management-dinstitutions-dappui-technologique-a-lindustrie</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assistance technique pour la mise en oeuvre de la reforme des centres techniques sectoriels en Tunisie&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contribuer au développement des performances des centres techniques sectoriels en les rendant à même d’assumer convenablement leur rôle de soutien et de développement du secteur industriel et d’être des contributeurs efficaces et reconnus au renforcement de l’industrie tunisienne.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chef de mission, expert en management d&amp;#39;institutions d&amp;#39;appui technologique à l&amp;#39;industrie&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire de niveau Master dans un domaine pertinent (ingénieur, gestion ou équivalent), ou expérience équivalente (minimum 2 ans en plus des 12 ans demandés ci-dessous).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience professionnelle d&amp;#39;au moins 12 ans au sein de structures publiques ou privées d&amp;#39;appui technologique à l’industrie avec un degré croissant de responsabilité, démontrant des connaissances en planification stratégique, management financier et de ressources humaines;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ayant une expérience pratique avérée dans l’élaboration et la production des documents de planification.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ayant une expérience d&amp;#39;au moins 3 ans dans des postes de management senior au sein de centres techniques ou des institutions similaires1;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ayant mené au moins une mission d’expertise en tant que chef de mission;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ayant participé à un projet d’appui à une structure type centre technique;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ayant une expérience de travail en Tunisie ou dans un pays du voisinage sud;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonne connaissance de la langue anglaise parlée et écrite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonne connaissance de la langue française parlée et écrite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to [Almudena Salmeron (mailto:&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:almudena_salmeron@dai.com&quot;&gt;almudena_salmeron@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;)]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PFM Expert (Category III)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/pfm-expert-category-iii</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 07:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/pfm-expert-category-iii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of the project are to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve framework for corruption prevention, in particular through increasing transparency and detection of corruption, improving handling and follow up of corruption reports, and strengthening the controlling regime for political parties&amp;#39; financing.
Improve framework for corruption repression, in particular through improving efficiency and effectiveness of criminal investigations against corruption; and supporting a good track record of investigated cases submitted to the prosecution services.
Improve framework for awareness of corruption, in particular through encouraging civil society and the general public to report corruption cases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master’s degree at University Level in economics or related, or, in its absence, at least 5 years&amp;#39; equivalent professional experience in the sectors related to PFM;
At least 3 years&amp;#39; general experience in public finance management;
Major contribution under at least one EU budget support programmes reviews, preferably in relation to financial management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3644&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3644&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rule of Law Expert (Category III)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/rule-of-law-expert-category-iii</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 07:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/rule-of-law-expert-category-iii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of the project are to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve framework for corruption prevention, in particular through increasing transparency and detection of corruption, improving handling and follow up of corruption reports, and strengthening the controlling regime for political parties&amp;#39; financing.
Improve framework for corruption repression, in particular through improving efficiency and effectiveness of criminal investigations against corruption; and supporting a good track record of investigated cases submitted to the prosecution services.
Improve framework for awareness of corruption, in particular through encouraging civil society and the general public to report corruption cases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications required:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master’s degree at University Level in political or social sciences/law/another relevant discipline, or, in its absence, at least 5 years&amp;#39; equivalent professional experience in the sectors related to the reinforcement of the rule of law and administration of justice;
At least 3 years&amp;#39; general experience in the rule of law, administration of justice or the public sector;
Major contribution under at least one EU budget support programmes reviews, preferably in relation to rule of law.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3644&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3644&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader (Category II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-category-ii-1</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 07:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-category-ii-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description of Project:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of the project are to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve framework for corruption prevention, in particular through increasing transparency and detection of corruption, improving handling and follow up of corruption reports, and strengthening the controlling regime for political parties&amp;#39; financing.
Improve framework for corruption repression, in particular through improving efficiency and effectiveness of criminal investigations against corruption; and supporting a good track record of investigated cases submitted to the prosecution services.
Improve framework for awareness of corruption, in particular through encouraging civil society and the general public to report corruption cases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience and Qualifications Required:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least a Master’s degree at University Level in political or social sciences/law/another relevant discipline, or, in its absence, at least 8 years&amp;#39; equivalent professional experience in the sectors related to the reinforcement of the rule of law and administration of justice;
At least 6 years&amp;#39; general experience in the rule of law sector;
Major contribution under at least three EU budget support programmes reviews, preferably in relation to rule of law;
Knowledge of prevention, repression, awareness of corruption will be considered as an asset;
Very good knowledge of English language, including effective spoken presentation and written reporting abilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3644&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3644&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experts in Human Rights, Migration, Justice, Decentralization and Civil Society</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-in-human-rights-migration-justice-decentralization-and-civil-society</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2018 16:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-in-human-rights-migration-justice-decentralization-and-civil-society</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In readiness for projects announced under FWC SIEA 1018 Lot 3 &lt;strong&gt;DAI Europe&lt;/strong&gt; would like to invite potential candidates to apply for future short and long-term assignments in the following technical areas:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Human rights, Democracy &amp;amp; Rule of Law (minorities inclusion, elections, democratisation, media, justice/penitentiary/police reform, public administration etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Civil Society (trainings, needs diagnostic of CSOs etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Decentralization (community-based development, local authority etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Migration (legal migration, mobility, human trafficking, asylum etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conflict Resolution, Peace &amp;amp; Security (DDR, SALW, SSR, land mines, rehabilitation and demobilisation etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kindly note that this is a general call for experts with expertise relevant to &lt;strong&gt;FWC SIEA 2018 Lot 3&lt;/strong&gt; and not a call for a specific mission or project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Requirements for Category I (Senior) Experts&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in areas related to the above, including Human Rights, Politics, Economics, Law, Rule of Law, Conflict Studies or similar. In its absence, must have at least 18 years of professional work experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years&amp;#39; experience related to policy development, public administration and institutional reform, capacity building of civil society and government or similar;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience with at least 1 assignment funded by the European Union (EC, EIB, EBRD etc);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Requirements for Category II (Mid-level) Experts&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in in areas related to the above, including Human Rights, Politics, Economics, Law, Rule of Law, Conflict Studies or similar. In its absence, must have at least 12 years of professional work experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years&amp;#39; experience related to policy development, public administration and institutional reform, capacity building of civil society and government or similar;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Requirements for Category III (Junior) Experts&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in in areas related to the above, including Human Rights, Politics, Economics, Law, Rule of Law, Conflict Studies or similar. In its absence, must have at least 6 years of professional work experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years&amp;#39; experience related to policy development, public administration and institutional reform, capacity building of civil society and government or similar;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in being considered for these opportunities please apply via &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3642&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3642&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experts in Infrastructure, Energy, Private Sector Development and Sustainable Growth</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-in-infrastructure-energy-private-sector-development-and-sustainable-growth</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2018 15:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experts-in-infrastructure-energy-private-sector-development-and-sustainable-growth</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In readiness for projects announced under FWC SIEA 1018 Lot 2 &lt;strong&gt;DAI Europe&lt;/strong&gt; would like to invite potential candidates to apply for future short and long-term assignments in the following technical areas:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transport &amp;amp; Infrastructure (roads, railways, harbours, airports, buildings, inter-modal infrastructure etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Digital Technologies (cybersecurity, data protection, broadband, surveillance etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Earth Observation (satellite data, policy and analysis)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Urban Development &amp;amp; Cities (smart cities, social housing, mobility, urban resilience etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sustainable Energy (renewable energies, power grids, energy efficiency etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nuclear Safety (Safety, decommissioning, waste disposal etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sustainable Waste Management &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Private Sector (SMEs, commercial banking, PPPs etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trade (customs, integration, SPS, Barriers to trade, metrology, intellectual property, competition etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employment Creation (labour market analysis, wage policy, trade unions, job creation etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kindly note that this is a general call for experts with expertise relevant to &lt;strong&gt;FWC SIEA 2018 Lot 2&lt;/strong&gt; and not a call for a specific mission or project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Requirements for Category I (Senior) Experts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in areas related to the above, including Engineering, Banking and Finance, Business Administration, Data management or similar. In its absence, must have at least 18 years of professional work experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years&amp;#39; experience related to infrastructure, energy, private sector development or sustainable growth;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience with at least 1 assignment funded by the European Union (EC, EIB, EBRD etc).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Requirements for Category II (Mid-level) Experts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in in areas related to the above, including Engineering, Banking and Finance, Business Administration, Data management or similar. In its absence, must have at least 12 years of professional work experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years&amp;#39; experience related to infrastructure, energy, private sector development or sustainable growth.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Requirements for Category III (Junior) Experts&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in in areas related to the above, including Engineering, Banking and Finance, Business Administration, Data management or similar. In its absence, must have at least 6 years of professional work experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years&amp;#39; experience related to infrastructure, energy, private sector development or sustainable growth.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in being considered for these opportunities please apply via &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3641&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3641&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rural Development and/or Natural Resource Management Experts</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/rural-development-and-or-natural-resource-management-experts</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/rural-development-and-or-natural-resource-management-experts</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DAI Europe&lt;/strong&gt; would like to invite potential candidates to apply for future short and long-term assignments in the following technical areas:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agriculture (crop production practices, marketing, value-chains etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Livestock (animal products production, veterinary, animal health etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Forestry (management, conservation, value-chains etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fishery &amp;amp; Aquaculture &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Land management (land use planning, land reforms etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Food Security &amp;amp; Nutrition (early warning systems, food production, food safety, cash transfers etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rural Infrastructure (irrigation, drainage etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Natural Resource Management (waste, pollution, green economy etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Disaster Risk Reduction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kindly note that this is a general call and not a call for a specific mission or project&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Requirements for Category I (Senior) Experts&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in Agronomy and Agricultural Studies, Climate Change, Environment Studies, Food Security and Nutrition, Natural Resource Management, Forestry, Disaster Risk Reduction, Veterinary/Husbandry or similar. In its absence, must have at least 18 years of professional work experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years&amp;#39; experience related to rural development and natural resource management;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience with at least 1 assignment funded by the European Union (EC, EIB, EBRD).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Requirements for Category II (Mid-level) Experts&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in Agronomy and Agricultural Studies, Climate Change, Environment Studies, Food Security and Nutrition, Natural Resource Management, Forestry, Disaster Risk Reduction, Veterinary/Husbandry or similar. In its absence, must have at least 12 years of professional work experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years&amp;#39; experience related to rural development and natural resource management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Requirements for Category III (Junior) Experts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree in Agronomy and Agricultural Studies, Climate Change, Environment Studies, Food Security and Nutrition, Natural Resource Management, Forestry, Disaster Risk Reduction, Veterinary/Husbandry or similar. In its absence, must have at least 6 years of professional work experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years&amp;#39; experience related to rural development and natural resource management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in being considered for these opportunities please apply via &lt;a href=&quot;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3628&quot;&gt;https://chm.tbe.taleo.net/chm04/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=DAINC&amp;amp;cws=1&amp;amp;rid=3628&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Une expertise genre/approche droit – Expert(e) 2 – catégorie II</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/une-expertise-genre-approche-droit-experte-2-categorie-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 22:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/une-expertise-genre-approche-droit-experte-2-categorie-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation finale du &amp;lsquo;Programme de Renforcement Institutionnel de la Chambre des Représentants&amp;rsquo; et Identification/Formulation d&amp;#39;un programme d&amp;#39;appui au Parlement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Une évaluation systématique et opportune de ses programmes et de ses activités est une priorité établie de la Commission Européenne. L’évaluation se concentre sur l’analyse des réalisations, l’atteinte et la qualité des résultats de l’action, dans le contexte d’une politique de coopération en constante évolution, avec un accent de plus en plus marqué sur les approches orientées sur les résultats. De ce point de vue, les évaluateurs devraient trouver les preuves expliquant les raisons, les cas de figure et la manière dont ces résultats sont liés à l’intervention de l’UE et essayer d’identifier les facteurs générant ou entravant le progrès.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Une expertise genre/approche droit – Expert(e) 2 – catégorie II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire supérieur (minimum BAC + 5) en sciences politiques et/ou économiques et/ou sciences sociales et/ou sciences juridiques ou discipline similaire ou équivalent comme exigence minimale – comme exigence minimale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Un diplôme ou certificat universitaire spécifique de formation en genre (master, diplôme d&amp;#39;expertise, etc.) constitue un atout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience d&amp;#39;au moins 6 années en matière d&amp;#39;identification et/ou formulation et /ou mise en œuvre et/ou évaluation de programmes – comme exigence minimale.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience d&amp;#39;au moins 2 années dans la promotion de l&amp;#39;égalité et des droits de l&amp;#39;homme et/ou dans une approche droit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 expériences dans le domaine de la formulation et/ou mise en œuvre, et/ou du suivi et/ou de l&amp;#39;évaluation de projets / programmes dans les domaines la gouvernance – comme exigence minimale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 expériences d&amp;#39;identification et formulation de programme de promotion de l&amp;#39;égalité et/ou de promotion de la gouvernance et des droits de l&amp;#39;homme (approche droit) pour l&amp;#39;Union Européenne&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une partie significative de l&amp;#39;expérience acquise à l&amp;#39;international (&amp;gt;2 ans), comme exigence minimale.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissances linguistiques&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne maîtrise de la langue française parlée et écrite comme exigence minimale ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Une expertise en évaluation et identification formulation de projet de Gouvernance/Etat de droit/Démocratie/Droits de l&#39;homme</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/une-expertise-en-evaluation-et-identification-formulation-de-projet-de-gouvernance-etat-de-droit-democratie-droits-de-lhomme</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 22:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/une-expertise-en-evaluation-et-identification-formulation-de-projet-de-gouvernance-etat-de-droit-democratie-droits-de-lhomme</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation finale du &amp;lsquo;Programme de Renforcement Institutionnel de la Chambre des Représentants&amp;rsquo; et Identification/Formulation d&amp;#39;un programme d&amp;#39;appui au Parlement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Une évaluation systématique et opportune de ses programmes et de ses activités est une priorité établie de la Commission Européenne. L’évaluation se concentre sur l’analyse des réalisations, l’atteinte et la qualité des résultats de l’action, dans le contexte d’une politique de coopération en constante évolution, avec un accent de plus en plus marqué sur les approches orientées sur les résultats. De ce point de vue, les évaluateurs devraient trouver les preuves expliquant les raisons, les cas de figure et la manière dont ces résultats sont liés à l’intervention de l’UE et essayer d’identifier les facteurs générant ou entravant le progrès.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Une expertise en évaluation et identification formulation de projet de Gouvernance/Etat de droit/Démocratie/Droits de l&amp;#39;homme – Expert(e) 2 – catégorie II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire supérieur (minimum BAC + 5) en sciences politiques et/ou économiques et/ou sciences sociales et/ou sciences juridiques ou discipline similaire ou équivalent comme exigence minimale ou à défaut 10 ans d&amp;#39;expériences en matière de gouvernance et/ou des droits humains – comme exigence minimale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience d&amp;#39;au moins 6 années en matière d&amp;#39;identification et/ou formulation et /ou mise en œuvre et/ou évaluation de programmes – comme exigence minimale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience d&amp;#39;au moins 3 années en matière de gouvernance publique&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 expériences dans le domaine de la formulation et/ou la mise en œuvre et/ou du suivi et/ou de l&amp;#39;évaluation de projets / programmes dans les domaines la gouvernance– comme exigence minimale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 expériences de formulation et/ou d&amp;#39;identification et/ou formulation de programmes pour l&amp;#39;Union Européenne&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une partie significative de l&amp;#39;expérience acquise à l&amp;#39;international (&amp;gt;2ans), comme exigence minimale.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissances linguistiques&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne maîtrise de la langue française parlée et écrite comme exigence minimale ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne maîtrise de la langue arabe parlée et écrite est un atout&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Une expertise en Etat de Droit et/ou Démocratisation et/ou Appui au Parlement (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/une-expertise-en-etat-de-droit-et-ou-democratisation-et-ou-appui-au-parlement-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 20:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/une-expertise-en-etat-de-droit-et-ou-democratisation-et-ou-appui-au-parlement-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation finale du &amp;lsquo;Programme de Renforcement Institutionnel de la Chambre des Représentants&amp;rsquo; et Identification/Formulation d&amp;#39;un programme d&amp;#39;appui au Parlement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Une évaluation systématique et opportune de ses programmes et de ses activités est une priorité établie de la Commission Européenne. L’évaluation se concentre sur l’analyse des réalisations, l’atteinte et la qualité des résultats de l’action, dans le contexte d’une politique de coopération en constante évolution, avec un accent de plus en plus marqué sur les approches orientées sur les résultats. De ce point de vue, les évaluateurs devraient trouver les preuves expliquant les raisons, les cas de figure et la manière dont ces résultats sont liés à l’intervention de l’UE et essayer d’identifier les facteurs générant ou entravant le progrès.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Une expertise en Etat de Droit et/ou Démocratisation et/ou Appui au Parlement (chef de mission) – Expert(e) 1 – catégorie I&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Formation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire supérieur (minimum BAC + 5) en sciences politiques et/ou économiques et/ou sciences sociales et/ou sciences juridiques ou discipline similaire ou équivalent comme exigence minimale ou à défaut 12 ans d&amp;#39;expériences en matière de gouvernance et/ou des droits humains – comme exigence minimale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience d&amp;#39;au moins 12 années en matière de gouvernance publique – comme exigence minimale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 expériences dans le domaine de la formulation et/ou de la mise en œuvre, du suivi et/ou de l&amp;#39;évaluation de projets / programmes dans les domaines de l&amp;#39;Etat de Droit et/ou Démocratisation et/ou Appui au Parlement – comme exigence minimale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 Expériences en tant que chef d&amp;#39;équipe comme exigence minimale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 Expérience dans le cadre de programme d&amp;#39;appui à l&amp;#39;Etat de Droit et/ou Démocratisation et/ou Appui au Parlement financés par l&amp;#39;Union Européenne souhaitable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une partie de l&amp;#39;expérience acquise à l&amp;#39;international (&amp;gt; 2 ans), comme exigence minimale.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La bonne connaissance du contexte institutionnel et parlementaire au Maroc est un atout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissances linguistiques&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne maîtrise de la langue française parlée et écrite comme exigence minimale ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne maîtrise de la langue arabe parlée et écrite est un atout&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concepteur-Rédacteur </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/concepteur-redacteur</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 16:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/concepteur-redacteur</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appui au développement d&amp;#39;un système de probation - mesures alternatives à la prison en Tunisie&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif général du présent marché est d’apporter un appui au développement des mesures alternatives a la prison a travers la mise en place d’un plan national de probation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les objectifs particuliers pour cette demande de prestation sont les suivants :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accompagner le MJ et les principaux acteurs dans la mise en place des structures de coordination et mis en œuvre du plan ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appuyer le MJ pour la finalisation d’une stratégie et d’un plan de diffusion de la probation et des mesures alternatives à la prison ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appuyer le MJ pour l’élaboration d’une stratégie de communication sur le développement d’un système de probation en Tunisie et accompagnement dans sa mise en œuvre ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consolider les bureaux de probation existants (renforcer les services de la DGPR, les outils informatiques et statistiques des bureaux de probation, développer des partenariats avec les institutions, acteurs non étatiques, entreprises susceptibles d’accueillir les condamnés bénéficiant de mesures de probation (en lien avec l’appel à proposition PARJ 2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formuler des recommandations concrètes et des projets visant à consolider le système national de probation/mesures alternatives à la prison.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 4 : Concepteur-Rédacteur (Catégorie II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme de l’enseignement supérieur de niveau Master ou équivalent dans un des domaines suivants : marketing, communication, relations publiques ou autre discipline pertinente ; en l’absence de ce diplôme, une expérience professionnelle équivalente (minimum 2 ans en plus des 6 demandés ci-dessous) ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellente maitrise de la langue française écrite et orale ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellente maitrise des outils informatiques (Word, Excel, PowerPoint).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expérience considérée comme indispensable :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Un minimum de 6 ans d’expérience générale dans le domaine de la communication et de la visibilité ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Un minimum de 4 ans d’expérience (pouvant être comprise dans l’expérience générale) en tant que concepteur-rédacteur de messages-clés ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience significative (au moins 2 supports) en matière de conception et rédaction de supports de communication ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience significative (au moins 2 projets) dans des missions de sensibilisation sur des réformes problématiques.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expériences considérées comme des atouts supplémentaires :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins une expérience de travail en Tunisie et/ou dans les pays ENI ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connaissance de la langue arabe.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Formation/Coaching des Agents de Probation – (Catégorie II)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/formation-coaching-des-agents-de-probation-categorie-ii</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 16:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/formation-coaching-des-agents-de-probation-categorie-ii</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appui au développement d&amp;#39;un système de probation - mesures alternatives à la prison en Tunisie&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif général du présent marché est d’apporter un appui au développement des mesures alternatives a la prison a travers la mise en place d’un plan national de probation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les objectifs particuliers pour cette demande de prestation sont les suivants :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accompagner le MJ et les principaux acteurs dans la mise en place des structures de coordination et mis en œuvre du plan ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appuyer le MJ pour la finalisation d’une stratégie et d’un plan de diffusion de la probation et des mesures alternatives à la prison ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appuyer le MJ pour l’élaboration d’une stratégie de communication sur le développement d’un système de probation en Tunisie et accompagnement dans sa mise en œuvre ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consolider les bureaux de probation existants (renforcer les services de la DGPR, les outils informatiques et statistiques des bureaux de probation, développer des partenariats avec les institutions, acteurs non étatiques, entreprises susceptibles d’accueillir les condamnés bénéficiant de mesures de probation (en lien avec l’appel à proposition PARJ 2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formuler des recommandations concrètes et des projets visant à consolider le système national de probation/mesures alternatives à la prison.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 3 : Formation/Coaching des Agents de Probation – (Catégorie II)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme de l’enseignement supérieur de niveau Master ou équivalent dans un des domaines suivants : droit, sciences politiques, sciences humaines ou sociales ; en l’absence de ce diplôme, une expérience professionnelle équivalente (minimum 2 ans en plus des 6 demandés ci-dessous) ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellente maitrise de la langue française écrite et orale ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellente maitrise des outils informatiques (Word, Excel, PowerPoint).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expérience considérée comme indispensable :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Un minimum de 6 ans d’expérience générale dans le domaine de la probation ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Un minimum de 4 ans d’expérience (pouvant être comprise dans l’expérience générale) dans l’accompagnement (formation/coaching/encadrement) d’agents de probation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expériences considérées comme des atouts supplémentaires :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans une structure administrative en charge du suivi des probationnaires ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en Tunisie et/ou les pays du voisinage (ENI).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appui Institutionnel/Planification – (Catégorie I)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/appui-institutionnel-planification-categorie-i</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/appui-institutionnel-planification-categorie-i</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appui au développement d&amp;#39;un système de probation - mesures alternatives à la prison en Tunisie&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;L’objectif général du présent marché est d’apporter un appui au développement des mesures alternatives a la prison a travers la mise en place d’un plan national de probation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Les objectifs particuliers pour cette demande de prestation sont les suivants :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accompagner le MJ et les principaux acteurs dans la mise en place des structures de coordination et mis en œuvre du plan ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appuyer le MJ pour la finalisation d’une stratégie et d’un plan de diffusion de la probation et des mesures alternatives à la prison ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Appuyer le MJ pour l’élaboration d’une stratégie de communication sur le développement d’un système de probation en Tunisie et accompagnement dans sa mise en œuvre ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consolider les bureaux de probation existants (renforcer les services de la DGPR, les outils informatiques et statistiques des bureaux de probation, développer des partenariats avec les institutions, acteurs non étatiques, entreprises susceptibles d’accueillir les condamnés bénéficiant de mesures de probation (en lien avec l’appel à proposition PARJ 2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formuler des recommandations concrètes et des projets visant à consolider le système national de probation/mesures alternatives à la prison.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2 : Appui Institutionnel/Planification – (Catégorie I)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme de l’enseignement supérieur de niveau Master ou équivalent dans un des domaines suivants : droit, sciences politiques, sciences humaines ou sociales ; en l’absence de ce diplôme, une expérience professionnelle équivalente (minimum 4 ans en plus des 12 demandés ci-dessous) ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellente maitrise de la langue française écrite et orale ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellente maitrise des outils informatiques (Word, Excel, PowerPoint).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expérience considérée comme indispensable :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Un minimum de 12 ans d’expérience générale dans des projets d’appui institutionnel ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Un minimum de 5 ans d’expérience (pouvant être comprise dans l’expérience générale) dans l’élaboration de stratégies, de plans d’action, et de leur structure de mise en œuvre (au moins 2 projets documentés) ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expériences considérées comme des atouts supplémentaires :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maitrise d’un ou plusieurs domaines traités dans le cadre du projet (réforme de la justice/systèmes pénitentiaires, services de probation, système d’information, communication etc…) ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience dans des projets similaires ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en matière de gestion de projets de coopération ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en Tunisie et/ou les pays du voisinage (ENI).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
