<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DAI Framework Contract Opportunities</title>
    <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 14:13:01 -0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Expert in Economic Integration and/or Trade with experience in EC Project Design &amp; Development</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-economic-integration-and-or-trade-with-experience-in-ec-project-design-developmen</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 14:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-expert-in-economic-integration-and-or-trade-with-experience-in-ec-project-design-developmen</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Evaluation EPA and CDB Standby Facilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Systematic and timely evaluation of its programmes and activities is an established priority of the European Commission. The focus of evaluations is on the assessment of achievements, the quality and the results of Actions in the context of an evolving cooperation policy with an increasing emphasis on result-oriented approaches. From this perspective, evaluations should look for evidence of why, whether or how these results are linked to the EU intervention and seek to identify the factors driving or hindering progress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evaluations should provide an understanding of the cause and effects links between inputs and activities, and outputs, outcomes and impacts. Evaluations should serve accountability, decision making, learning, and management purposes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main objectives of this evaluation are to provide the relevant services of the European Union, the interested stakeholders with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an overall independent assessment of the performance of the Action 2012/FED/299-293/EPA Stand by Facility for Capacity Building and the Action 2012/FED/299-636/ CSME Standby Facility for Capacity Building paying particular attention to its results measured against its objectives;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;key lessons and recommendations in order to inform future Actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In particular, this evaluation will serve to determine to which extent the Facilities have achieved their objectives, and contributed to strengthen CSME and EPA implementation at the national level. It will also look at how the Actions have contributed to increasing ownership of the CSME and EPA processes through the delivery of tangible results.  The performance of the management and approval process should also be assessed. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation should make recommendations for future Actions, in particular: are such facilities the best vehicle to assist Member States with implementation at the national level and if not, what would be the alternative; if renewed, what would be the best governance and monitoring mechanism. It should be assessed whether a demand driven facility (as opposed to allocations pre-identified per Member States) would be a better to way to ensure efficiency of the use of resources, with recommendations as to how accompany those Member States with fewer capacities. The evaluation should recommend a strategy which would assist with prioritising the areas with most urgent need at the national level. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main users of this evaluation will be the European Commission, the CARIFORUM Directorate and the CDB, the CSME Unit and CARIFORUM Member States.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Expert in Economic Integration and/or Trade with experience in EC Project Design &amp;amp; Development&lt;/strong&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Economics, Business Administration, International relations or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OR in its absence not less than three (3) years&amp;#39; relevant experience in addition to the 12 years professional experience required below&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;12 Years in international development, in particular, areas related to economic integration/ and or Trade&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8 Years project/program monitoring and evaluation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience in Project Cycle Management (PCM), in particular EC project design and development. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must possess a high level of fluency in English (spoken and written).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Knowledge of the EU/CARIFORUM EPA and/or the CSME will be an advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experience with EU funded programmes for the Caribbean will be an advantage. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:anju_english@dai.com&quot;&gt;anju_english@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Category III (Junior) Evaluation Experts</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/two-category-iii-junior-evaluation-experts</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/two-category-iii-junior-evaluation-experts</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation of EU Cooperation with Armenia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall engagement with Armenia should be taken into consideration in the analysis, including agreements, the co-operation framework and any other official commitments. To the extent possible, the evaluation should distinguish the results obtained through the various EU instruments used in Armenia. Interventions funded by other donors (including i.e. IFIs, UN organisations, bil-lateral agencies and international organisations) at the sector level cannot be part of the evaluation scope – unless they are co-financed, including blending, by the EU. However, the coherence and complementarity between these interventions and the EU cooperation strategy evaluated must be examined.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More specifically, the evaluation will assess:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The relevance and coherence of European Union’s co-operation strategy and programmes in the period 2010- mid-2017; This assessment should be done based on a dynamic approach looking for example at issues such as the extent to which the EU support has been responsive to the changes in the socio-economic context of Armenia.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The implementation of the European Union’s co-operation, focusing on impact, sustainability, effectiveness and efficiency for the period 2010- mid-2017. The evaluation should keep its focus broad and take also into account implementation of activities approved prior to 2010 but implemented during the evaluation period, as appropriate, as well as the new programming for the period 2017– 2020&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The consistency between programming and implementation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The value added of the European Union’s interventions (at both strategic and implementation levels).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The coordination and complementarity of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s interventions with other donors&amp;#39; interventions and coherence between the European Union&amp;rsquo;s interventions and policies that are likely to affect the partner country/region. The latter should include an assessment of the extent the programmes, financed by the EU, are coherent with the objectives set in agreement with Armenia.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The coordination and coherence of the various types of cooperation (Bilateral, Regional and Thematic instruments). This should include an assessment of the &amp;ldquo;fitness for purpose&amp;rdquo; of the tools/instruments relative to the context of Armenia and efficiency of the procedures used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Two Category III (Junior) Evaluation Experts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation team should have the following demonstrated experience and expertise:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of EU external action policies, and specifically of the EU Neighbourhood policy, and their implementation modalities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s co-operation with Armenia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of the international aid and development effectiveness agenda and principles, as well as have good knowledge of cross cutting issues, especially gender mainstreaming, and e.g. of Global Partnership for effective development co-operation (Busan)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluation methods and techniques in general and, preferably, of evaluation in the field of external relations and development cooperation; in particular the team needs to demonstrate experience in analytical methods which can evaluate change, and which can evaluate contribution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be able to cover the following fields:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;rule of law and democratisation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;public administration reform;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;public finance management;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;economic infrastructure development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;human capital development, socio-economic reform and sustainable development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integrated border management and migration;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;communication/visibility/PR;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;civil society development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;private sector development, trade and investment, market and regulatory reform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Working knowledge of the EU budget support modality&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quantitative and qualitative data collection and analysis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team leader should have excellent communication, team co-ordination, presentation and proven report writing and editing skills in English. (S)he should have the experience of carrying out at least two complex evaluations as the team leader.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The evaluation team should have an excellent command of English – both spoken and written – and the ability to function at a high level in Armenian. Working knowledge of Russian would be an advantage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Evaluation Experts (including a Team Leader)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-evaluation-experts-including-a-team-leader</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 12:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/senior-evaluation-experts-including-a-team-leader</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation of EU Cooperation with Armenia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall engagement with Armenia should be taken into consideration in the analysis, including agreements, the co-operation framework and any other official commitments. To the extent possible, the evaluation should distinguish the results obtained through the various EU instruments used in Armenia. Interventions funded by other donors (including i.e. IFIs, UN organisations, bil-lateral agencies and international organisations) at the sector level cannot be part of the evaluation scope – unless they are co-financed, including blending, by the EU. However, the coherence and complementarity between these interventions and the EU cooperation strategy evaluated must be examined.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More specifically, the evaluation will assess:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The relevance and coherence of European Union’s co-operation strategy and programmes in the period 2010- mid-2017; This assessment should be done based on a dynamic approach looking for example at issues such as the extent to which the EU support has been responsive to the changes in the socio-economic context of Armenia.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The implementation of the European Union’s co-operation, focusing on impact, sustainability, effectiveness and efficiency for the period 2010- mid-2017. The evaluation should keep its focus broad and take also into account implementation of activities approved prior to 2010 but implemented during the evaluation period, as appropriate, as well as the new programming for the period 2017– 2020&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The consistency between programming and implementation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The value added of the European Union’s interventions (at both strategic and implementation levels).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The coordination and complementarity of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s interventions with other donors&amp;#39; interventions and coherence between the European Union&amp;rsquo;s interventions and policies that are likely to affect the partner country/region. The latter should include an assessment of the extent the programmes, financed by the EU, are coherent with the objectives set in agreement with Armenia.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The coordination and coherence of the various types of cooperation (Bilateral, Regional and Thematic instruments). This should include an assessment of the &amp;ldquo;fitness for purpose&amp;rdquo; of the tools/instruments relative to the context of Armenia and efficiency of the procedures used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category I (Senior) Evaluation Experts (including a Team Leader)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The evaluation team should have the following demonstrated experience and expertise:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of EU external action policies, and specifically of the EU Neighbourhood policy, and their implementation modalities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s co-operation with Armenia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of the international aid and development effectiveness agenda and principles, as well as have good knowledge of cross cutting issues, especially gender mainstreaming, and e.g. of Global Partnership for effective development co-operation (Busan)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluation methods and techniques in general and, preferably, of evaluation in the field of external relations and development cooperation; in particular the team needs to demonstrate experience in analytical methods which can evaluate change, and which can evaluate contribution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be able to cover the following fields:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;rule of law and democratisation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;public administration reform;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;public finance management;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;economic infrastructure development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;human capital development, socio-economic reform and sustainable development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integrated border management and migration;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;communication/visibility/PR;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;civil society development;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;private sector development, trade and investment, market and regulatory reform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of the EU budget support modality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quantitative and qualitative data collection and analysis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team leader should have excellent communication, team co-ordination, presentation and proven report writing and editing skills in English. (S)he should have the experience of carrying out at least two complex evaluations as the team leader.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The evaluation team should have an excellent command of English – both spoken and written – and the ability to function at a high level in Armenian. Working knowledge of Russian would be an advantage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert(e) Senior, de catégorie II, en Communication et Media</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-senior-de-categorie-ii-en-communication-et-media</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-senior-de-categorie-ii-en-communication-et-media</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Renforcement de la culture de la protection des données a caractère personnel au Maroc&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Renforcer le niveau de la protection des données à caractère personnel au sens des exigences de l&amp;#39;Acquis et des bonnes pratiques européennes. En particulier : Evaluer la portée de la nouvelle règlementation européenne sur la protection des données à caractère personnel, préparer un plan d’action indicatif pour sa mise en œuvre et développer des actions d’information et d’éducation numérique.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Projet duree&lt;/strong&gt;: 18 mois&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert(e) Senior, de catégorie II, en Communication et Media&lt;/strong&gt; (71 h/j) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire supérieur, niveau Master, en communication/information ou diplôme équivalent et pertinent par rapport aux objectifs du contrat ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience professionnelle de 3 ans dans le domaine de l’information ou la communication institutionnelle au sein d’une entreprise ou d’une institution publique en plus de celle indiquée comme expérience professionnelle générale, pourra compenser l’absence de Master ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins six ans d’expérience en conseil, conception et/ou mise en œuvre de programmes et supports  d’information/communication au sein d’administrations publiques, services publics ou institutions d’appui aux entreprises, organisations professionnelles ou associations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 2 ans d’expérience en économie numérique, Internet et/ou traitement des données, acquise au sein d’entreprises privées ou publiques.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissance linguistique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonne maîtrise du français&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonne maîtrise de l&amp;#39;arabe constitue un atout&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to  &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;Veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert(e) Senior, de Catégorie I, en Etudes d’impact </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-senior-de-categorie-i-en-etudes-dimpact</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 11:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-senior-de-categorie-i-en-etudes-dimpact</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Renforcement de la culture de la protection des données a caractère personnel au Maroc&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Renforcer le niveau de la protection des données à caractère personnel au sens des exigences de l&amp;#39;Acquis et des bonnes pratiques européennes. En particulier : Evaluer la portée de la nouvelle règlementation européenne sur la protection des données à caractère personnel, préparer un plan d’action indicatif pour sa mise en œuvre et développer des actions d’information et d’éducation numérique.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Projet duree&lt;/strong&gt;: 18 mois&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert(e) Senior, de Catégorie I, en Etudes d’impact&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire supérieur, niveau Master, en sociologie et/ou économie et/ou statistiques ou diplôme équivalent et pertinent par rapport aux objectifs du contrat ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience professionnelle de 4 ans dans l’élaboration d’étude d’impact socio-économiques en plus de celle indiquée comme expérience professionnelle générale, pourra compenser l’absence de Master ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins douze ans d’expérience en conseil économique et statistique ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 5 ans d’expérience en élaboration d’étude d’impact socio-économiques lié à l’adoption de mesures de nature normative/règlementaires.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissance linguistique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonne maîtrise du français&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to  &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;Veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert(e) Senior, de Catégorie I, Juriste, Chef de Mission </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-senior-de-categorie-i-juriste-chef-de-mission</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 11:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/experte-senior-de-categorie-i-juriste-chef-de-mission</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Renforcement de la culture de la protection des données a caractère personnel au Maroc&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Renforcer le niveau de la protection des données à caractère personnel au sens des exigences de l&amp;#39;Acquis et des bonnes pratiques européennes. En particulier : Evaluer la portée de la nouvelle règlementation européenne sur la protection des données à caractère personnel, préparer un plan d’action indicatif pour sa mise en œuvre et développer des actions d’information et d’éducation numérique.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Projet duree&lt;/strong&gt;: 18 mois&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert(e) Senior, de Catégorie I, Juriste, Chef de Mission&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications et compétences&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diplôme universitaire supérieur, niveau Master, en droit privé et/ou droit européen et/ou droit du commerce électronique et/ou de l&amp;#39;économie numérique ou diplôme équivalent et pertinent par rapport aux objectifs du contrat ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience professionnelle de 5 ans en qualité de juriste dans un cabinet de conseil ou d’avocat, la direction juridique d’une entreprise ou d’un établissement public en plus de celle indiquée comme expérience professionnelle générale, pourra compenser l’absence de Master ;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle générale&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Une expérience professionnelle d’au moins 12 ans dans le domaine de l’économie numérique et/ou du droit de la protection des données personnelles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expérience professionnelle spécifique&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au moins 4 ans dans la rédaction et/ou l&amp;#39;application des règles nationales et/ou européennes et/ou internationales de protection des données personnelles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expérience en matière de coopération technique comme un atout&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaissance linguistique&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Très bonne maîtrise du français&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to  &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&quot;&gt;Veronica_hernandez-castilla@dai.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category II: Legal Expert </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-legal-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-legal-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Canvas for Innovation: A Way Forward to Strengthening the National Innovation Ecosystem - Feasibility Studie&lt;/strong&gt;s&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project is to support further development of the innovation ecosystem in the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of this assignment are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To assess the current national innovation ecosystem; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To develop new instruments/measures for support of innovations in companies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 12 months&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert category II: Legal Expert&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master Degree5 Academic level in legal studies or, in its absence, professional experience of 5 (five) years above the minimum general professional experience requested below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 (six) years of general professional experience in practicing commercial law in the beneficiary country.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in drafting laws or implementing legislation in the beneficiary country.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category I: Business Support Expert </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-business-support-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 11:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-business-support-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Canvas for Innovation: A Way Forward to Strengthening the National Innovation Ecosystem - Feasibility Studies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project is to support further development of the innovation ecosystem in the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of this assignment are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To assess the current national innovation ecosystem; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To develop new instruments/measures for support of innovations in companies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 12 months&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert Category I: Business Support Expert&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master Degree Academic level4, or in its absence professional experience of 5 (five) years above the general professional experience required bellow.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of professional experience in the field of development or implementation of the private sector policy (such as: working in public administration in the area of PSD policy or providing advisory services for PSD policy development implementation)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years working experience in a public body for innovation support in EU member states or accession countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category I: Innovation Policy Expert /Team Leader</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-innovation-policy-expert-team-leader</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 10:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-innovation-policy-expert-team-leader</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Canvas for Innovation: A Way Forward to Strengthening the National Innovation Ecosystem - Feasibility Studies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project is to support further development of the innovation ecosystem in the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The specific objectives of this assignment are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To assess the current national innovation ecosystem; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To develop new instruments/measures for support of innovations in companies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 12 months&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert Category I: Innovation Policy Expert /Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least Master Degree Academic level3, or in its absence professional experience of 5 (five) years above the general professional experience required bellow.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of professional experience in the field of development or implementation of the private sector policy (such as: working in public administration in the area of PSD policy or providing advisory services for PSD policy development implementation)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 (five) years of professional experience in development or implementation of public innovation policy;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participation in development of at least 1 (one) assessment/evaluation on public policies/programs, preferably policies/programs for PSD;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience as a Team Leader in EU funded project will be an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cat.II Assessors - Experts in Gender Equality and Women&#39;s Empowerment or Sexual and Reproductive Health/Rights</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/catii-assessors-experts-in-gender-equality-and-womens-empowerment-or-sexual-and-reproductive-health-rights</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 21:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/catii-assessors-experts-in-gender-equality-and-womens-empowerment-or-sexual-and-reproductive-health-rights</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preventing Sexual and Gender Based Violence against Women and Girls in Developing Countries&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To provide technical support to the European Commission services in order to reach the global objective, as regards both the technical and the financial assessment of the received proposals. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assessors [7 openings] – Cat. II&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The expert assessors must have university degree and at least 6 years of professional experience in Gender equality and women&amp;rsquo;s empowerment and/or sexual and reproductive health and rights. The team will cover at least collectively the required professional experience from the two fields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A profound experience of project and programme cycle management and /or evaluation is required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of professional experience from developing countries, 5 years of working with civil society organisations or other non-state actors as well as have demonstrated knowledge on EC policies and programmes is required. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have good command of English or French. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The team of assessors should have language competences covering the two languages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TL/Senior Expert in Gender Equality and Women&#39;s Empowerment or Sexual and Reproductive Health/Rights (or similar field) </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/tl-senior-expert-in-gender-equality-and-womens-empowerment-or-sexual-and-reproductive-health-rights-or-similar-field</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 21:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/tl-senior-expert-in-gender-equality-and-womens-empowerment-or-sexual-and-reproductive-health-rights-or-similar-field</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preventing Sexual and Gender Based Violence against Women and Girls in Developing Countries&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To provide technical support to the European Commission services in order to reach the global objective, as regards both the technical and the financial assessment of the received proposals. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TL/Senior Expert in Gender Equality and Women&amp;rsquo;s Empowerment or Sexual and Reproductive Health/Rights (or similar field)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The team leader must have university degree of relevant discipline and at least 12 years of professional experience in Gender Equality and women&amp;rsquo;s&amp;#39; empowerment and sexual and reproductive health and rights or in human rights or any other related relevant sector. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of professional experience from developing countries, 5 years of working with civil society organisations or other non-state actors as well as have demonstrated knowledge on EC policies and programmes is required. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience as team leader is preferable. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have good command of English or French with ability to read proposals and review the quality of proposal assessments in both languages. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category II:  Economic/Business expert </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-economic-business-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 20:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-economic-business-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drafting a Feasibility Study for Establishment of Science and Technology Park&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project is to improve the current innovation ecosystem in the country by strengthening the cooperation among academia, industry and government. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project shall develop a comprehensive Feasibility study and Action plan for the establishment and operation of a Science and Technology Park (STP) aiming to strengthen the country’s innovation capacities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert category II:  Economic/business expert (40 working days)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education of at least Master Degree Academic level, in Economic or Business Administration, or general professional experience of 3 (three) years above the minimum general professional experience requested below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of general professional experience in economics or business administration in preparation of business models/plans and/or cost-benefit analysis. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least two (2) project for preparation of cost-benefit analysis for construction of science or technology parks, or economic and industrial zones. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language Skills&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English, both written and spoken. Knowledge of the Macedonian language is an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&quot;&gt;gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category II: Architect/Civil Engineer </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-architect-civil-engineer</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-ii-architect-civil-engineer</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drafting a Feasibility Study for Establishment of Science and Technology Park&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project is to improve the current innovation ecosystem in the country by strengthening the cooperation among academia, industry and government. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project shall develop a comprehensive Feasibility study and Action plan for the establishment and operation of a Science and Technology Park (STP) aiming to strengthen the country’s innovation capacities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert Category II: Architect/Civil Engineer (40 working days)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education at least Master Degree Academic level, in Architecture or Engineering, or general professional experience of 3 (three) years above the minimum general professional experience requested below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years of general professional experience in architecture or civil engineering in preparations of architectural/construction project designs. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least two (2) projects in preparation of architectural and urban design for construction of science and technology parks or economic and industrial zones;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in English, both written and spoken. Knowledge of the Macedonian language is an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&quot;&gt;gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category I: Science Technology Park Expert (TL)</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-science-technology-park-expert-tl</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 20:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-science-technology-park-expert-tl</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drafting a Feasibility Study for Establishment of Science and Technology Park&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall objective of the project is to improve the current innovation ecosystem in the country by strengthening the cooperation among academia, industry and government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project shall develop a comprehensive Feasibility study and Action plan for the establishment and operation of a Science and Technology Park (STP) aiming to strengthen the country’s innovation capacities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert Category I: STP Expert (70 working days)/ to act also as a Team Leader&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further to his/her overall project management and coordination, project representation, as well as reporting. He/she should ensure that the project outputs and reporting requirements are timely fulfilled. He/she shall will coordinate, supervise, manage, monitor and appraise all aspects of the project experts’ output.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education of at least Master Degree Academic level , in engineering, economics or business administration, or general professional experience of 3 (three) years above the minimum general professional experience requested below. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of general professional experience in engineering, economy or business administration or similar, in business modelling, preparations of business plans/studies. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least two (2) projects related to preparation of Feasibility Study for Science and/or Technology Park, or preparation of STP model analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language skills&lt;/strong&gt; 
Fluency in English, both written and spoken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&quot;&gt;gabriela_georgieva@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legal/Judicial/Security Reform Expert with Police/Judiciary or Justice Ministry Experience</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/legal-judicial-security-reform-expert-with-police-judiciary-or-justice-ministry-experience</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/legal-judicial-security-reform-expert-with-police-judiciary-or-justice-ministry-experience</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identification and Formulation Mission - Rule of Law - Fata, KP and Balochistan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; is to assist the EU Delegation in the design of a programme under the AAP 2018 to reinforce the rule of law in KP, FATA and Balochistan. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Legal/Judicial/Security Reform Expert with Police/Judiciary or Justice Ministry Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s Degree in law, political science, international relations or any relevant disciplines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Experience *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 6 years of relevant professional experience in programs related to rule of Law, judicial or security reform, particularly direct experience working with the Police, Judiciary, Line Ministries for justice or related fields.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proven knowledge of the socio-political situation in Pakistan and particularly in KP and FATA is required&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proven working experience in rule of law and justice or security sector in Pakistan and particularly in KP and FATA would be a distinct advantage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strong communication skills and proven record of multi-stakeholder consultations and cooperation with donors, international organisations, public administrations and civil society in the sector;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strong inter-personal and presentation skills, awareness of cultural sensitivities;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ability to independently solve complex and challenging problems;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strong report writing skills, using a clear and concise language, structuring written presentations;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Urdu/Pashtun would be an asset&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Leader, Senior Expert in Rule of Law, Justice or Security Sector and/or Police Reform</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-expert-in-rule-of-law-justice-or-security-sector-and-or-police-reform</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 17:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/team-leader-senior-expert-in-rule-of-law-justice-or-security-sector-and-or-police-reform</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identification and Formulation Mission Rule of Law - Fata, KP and Balochistan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;global objective&lt;/strong&gt; is to assist the EU Delegation in the design of a programme under the AAP 2018 to reinforce the rule of law in KP, FATA and Balochistan. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Leader, Senior Expert in Rule of Law, Justice or Security Sector and/or Police Reform&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s Degree in law, political science, international relations or any relevant disciplines &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specialisation course in security sector reform, rule of law or justice reform would be an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*&lt;em&gt;Experience *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 12 years of relevant professional experience, including at least five years in a senior positions in an international development role in Rule of Law, justice or security sector and/or police reform;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Professional experience in countries with holistic approaches to security sector reform and rule of law, including experience working with the major stakeholders is required;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proven track record of developing rule of law programme in fragile situations in Europe or South Asia is desirable and knowledge of the political context of KP an FATA in Pakistan will be a distinct advantage;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowledge of the International and EU policy documents relevant to Rule of law and security sector reform programming in situations of fragility &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous experience in EU programming documents such as identification fiches, action documents and all the related annexes is required&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strong communication skills and proven record of multi-stakeholder consultations and cooperation with donors, international organisations, public administrations and civil society in the sector;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strong inter-personal and presentation skills, awareness of cultural sensitivities;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ability to independently solve complex and challenging problems;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strong report writing skills, using a clear and concise language, structuring written presentations;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation Expert specialised in Local Development and Local Governance</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/evaluation-expert-specialised-in-local-development-and-local-governance</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 16:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/evaluation-expert-specialised-in-local-development-and-local-governance</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation - Support to Public Administration Reform and Local Development&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Systematic and timely evaluation of its programmes and activities is an established priority of the European Commission. The focus of evaluations is on the assessment of achievements, the quality and the results of Actions in the context of an evolving cooperation policy with an increasing emphasis on result-oriented approaches. From this perspective, evaluations should look for evidence of why, whether or how these results are linked to the EU intervention and seek to identify the factors driving or hindering progress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evaluations should provide an understanding of the cause and effects links between inputs and activities, and outputs, outcomes and impacts. Evaluations should serve accountability, decision making, and learning and management purposes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main objectives of this evaluation are to provide the relevant services of the European Union, the interested stakeholders with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an overall independent assessment of the past performance of the &amp;lsquo;Support to Public Administration Reform and Local Development&amp;rsquo; Programme, paying particular attention to its [in case of a mid-term evaluation you may add ‘intermediate’] results measured against its objectives;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Key lessons and recommendations in order to improve current performance of the programme and to provide an insight into future cooperation with Egypt in the sectors of interventions. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In particular, this evaluation will serve in assessing key elements of relevance, effectiveness, efficiency, sustainability, and early signs of impact among other important criteria.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main users of this evaluation will be the European Union and the Government of Egypt (GoE) represented by key beneficiaries and stakeholders of the programme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 6 months&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 3 – Evaluation Expert specialised in Local Development and Local Governance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The expert should have at least a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in a domain relevant to the assignment (e.g. local governance, Public Administration, public management, or other relevant field of Social Sciences) or, in its absence, a Bachelor Degree and an additional equivalent professional experience of at least three years working on development projects in areas related to the programme to be evaluated. The equivalent experience must be above the general experience duration fixed below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional experience and competencies:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of proven professional experience in fields of Development Cooperation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record of specific professional experience in local development and decentralisation reforms. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in evaluating cooperation programmes, especially EU funded interventions, with focus on local development / local governance / decentralisation. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least one assignment in capacity building, particularly in the field of local development and training capacities in fields of local governance and decentralisation. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analytical and methodological skills, excellent interpersonal and communications skills, as well as the ability to function in sensitive contexts. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working in ENP countries, especially those of the ENP South, will be considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English (speaking and writing skills).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of the Arabic language (speaking and writing skills) will be considered an asset. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Category I: Evaluation Expert specialised in PFM Reform </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-evaluation-expert-specialised-in-pfm-reform</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 16:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/category-i-evaluation-expert-specialised-in-pfm-reform</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation - Support to Public Administration Reform and Local Development&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Systematic and timely evaluation of its programmes and activities is an established priority of the European Commission. The focus of evaluations is on the assessment of achievements, the quality and the results of Actions in the context of an evolving cooperation policy with an increasing emphasis on result-oriented approaches. From this perspective, evaluations should look for evidence of why, whether or how these results are linked to the EU intervention and seek to identify the factors driving or hindering progress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evaluations should provide an understanding of the cause and effects links between inputs and activities, and outputs, outcomes and impacts. Evaluations should serve accountability, decision making, and learning and management purposes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main objectives of this evaluation are to provide the relevant services of the European Union, the interested stakeholders with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an overall independent assessment of the past performance of the &amp;lsquo;Support to Public Administration Reform and Local Development&amp;rsquo; Programme, paying particular attention to its [in case of a mid-term evaluation you may add ‘intermediate’] results measured against its objectives;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Key lessons and recommendations in order to improve current performance of the programme and to provide an insight into future cooperation with Egypt in the sectors of interventions. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In particular, this evaluation will serve in assessing key elements of relevance, effectiveness, efficiency, sustainability, and early signs of impact among other important criteria.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main users of this evaluation will be the European Union and the Government of Egypt (GoE) represented by key beneficiaries and stakeholders of the programme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 6 months&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 2 - Category I: Evaluation Expert specialised in PFM Reform&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The expert should have at least a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in a domain relevant to the assignment (e.g. public finance management, development Economics, Public Administration, public management, or other relevant field of Social Sciences) or, in its absence, a Bachelor Degree and an additional equivalent professional experience of at least three years working on development projects in areas related to the programme to be evaluated. The equivalent experience must be above the general experience duration fixed below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional experience and competencies:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of proven professional experience in fields of Development Cooperation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record of specific professional experience in public finance management. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in evaluating cooperation programmes, especially EU funded interventions, with focus on public finance management / economic development. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least one assignment in capacity building, particularly in the field of strengthening public finance management.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analytical and methodological skills, excellent interpersonal and communications skills, as well as the ability to function in sensitive contexts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working in ENP countries, especially those of the ENP South, will be considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English (speaking and writing skills).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of the Arabic language (speaking and writing skills) will be considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation Expert (Team Leader) and Expert in Governance Reform</title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/evaluation-expert-team-leader-and-expert-in-governance-reform</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/evaluation-expert-team-leader-and-expert-in-governance-reform</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation - Support to Public Administration Reform and Local Development&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Systematic and timely evaluation of its programmes and activities is an established priority of the European Commission. The focus of evaluations is on the assessment of achievements, the quality and the results of Actions in the context of an evolving cooperation policy with an increasing emphasis on result-oriented approaches. From this perspective, evaluations should look for evidence of why, whether or how these results are linked to the EU intervention and seek to identify the factors driving or hindering progress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evaluations should provide an understanding of the cause and effects links between inputs and activities, and outputs, outcomes and impacts. Evaluations should serve accountability, decision making, and learning and management purposes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main objectives of this evaluation are to provide the relevant services of the European Union, the interested stakeholders with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;an overall independent assessment of the past performance of the &amp;lsquo;Support to Public Administration Reform and Local Development&amp;rsquo; Programme, paying particular attention to its [in case of a mid-term evaluation you may add ‘intermediate’] results measured against its objectives;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Key lessons and recommendations in order to improve current performance of the programme and to provide an insight into future cooperation with Egypt in the sectors of interventions. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In particular, this evaluation will serve in assessing key elements of relevance, effectiveness, efficiency, sustainability, and early signs of impact among other important criteria.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main users of this evaluation will be the European Union and the Government of Egypt (GoE) represented by key beneficiaries and stakeholders of the programme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 6 months&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert 1 - Category 1: Evaluation Expert (Team Leader) and Expert in Governance Reform&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Education&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The expert should have at least a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in a domain relevant to the assignment (e.g. Public Administration, public management, development Economics, or other relevant field of Social Sciences) or, in its absence, a Bachelor Degree and an additional equivalent professional experience of at least three years working on development projects in areas related to the programme to be evaluated. The equivalent experience must be above the general experience duration fixed below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professional experience and competencies&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 12 years of proven professional experience in fields of Development Cooperation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record of specific professional experience at least in governance, including in public administration / administrative reform. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in evaluating cooperation programmes, especially EU funded interventions. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record of assignments as Team Leader of development cooperation funded assignments. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in at least one assignment in capacity building, particularly in the field of strengthening public services. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analytical and methodological skills, excellent interpersonal and communications skills, as well as the ability to function in sensitive contexts. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience of working in ENP countries, especially those of the ENP South, will be considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent command of English (speaking and writing skills).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of the Arabic language (speaking and writing skills) will be considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:aurelie_durand@dai.com&quot;&gt;aurelie_durand@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Systems Analysis Expert </title>
      <link>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/systems-analysis-expert</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Penny  Buckle</author>
      <guid>http://frameworkcontracts.com/current-opportunities/systems-analysis-expert</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mid-term Evaluation for Assistance to Agriculture in the West Bank (AAWB) and Private Sector Reconstruction Gaza Agriculture (PSRG-A) Programmes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The AAWB programme entered into full scale implementation aiming to serve about 400 final beneficiaries as well as the PSRG-A programme may serve about 400 final beneficiaries too. In total the estimated number of final beneficiaries is estimated at 800.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DESCRIPTION OF THE EVALUATION ASSIGNMENT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Type of evaluation&lt;/strong&gt; Mid-term Evaluation
&lt;strong&gt;Coverage *&lt;em&gt;AAWB and PSRG-A Programmes under three decisions
*&lt;/em&gt;Geographic scope&lt;/strong&gt; West Bank and Gaza Strip
&lt;strong&gt;Period to be evaluated&lt;/strong&gt; The entire period&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project duration&lt;/strong&gt;: 120 days&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Systems Analysis Expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualification and skills&lt;/strong&gt;:
*&lt;em&gt;Education *&lt;/em&gt;: at least a Master&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Management Information Systems (MIS), Business Administration, Economics or other cognate discipline; OR equivalent professional experience of 6 years (above the general professional experience duration fixed below) in an area of systems analysis and assessment related to public sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6 years professional experience in the management and/or evaluation of projects in the fields of development aid.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific professional experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years&amp;#39; experience in MIS systems analysis of the public sector.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience of working in a development policy environment in fragile or conflict affected regions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you meet the requirements and would be interested in applying for this role please email your CV in EC format to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&quot;&gt;nicte_garcia-soria@dai.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WE ARE ONLY ABLE TO RESPOND TO CANDIDATES WHO MEET THE SPECIFICATIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
